Chapter 1

Rigel had once read that a strong physical foundation was the key to any truly impressive work of magical architecture. Whoever wrote that, she reflected, had never been to the Weasleys' house.

"Don't worry, it's more structurally sound than it looks," Ron assured her as they walked up the front walk.

"It'd have to be," Rigel said vaguely, still staring. The Burrow looked as if someone had taken a charming country home, stacked another charming country home on top of it, attached half a semi-charming shed to the left side of that, and then added windows the way a child adds sprinkles to a cupcake.

"It's not much," Ron said, rubbing his neck uncomfortably.

"It's amazing," Rigel said honestly, "Do you know how much power went into the original keystones to make it stable?"

Ron blinked at her, then smiled wryly, "No, but I bet Percy does."

Rigel glanced amusedly at her redheaded…friend? Close acquaintance? Something like that. She wasn't sure why Ron was the one to collect her from Sirius' house, actually, since it was the Twins who extended the invitation, but she wouldn't complain. She liked Ron well enough, when he and Draco weren't scowling at one another.

"Well, here it is," Ron said grandly, opening the front door wide, "Home sweet—"

"Puppy!"

"You came!"

Two tornados swept Rigel around in a series of dizzying circles before she could get a proper look at the inside of the Burrow, and she took a moment to uncross her eyes before she greeted their exuberant grins with studied consideration.

"Let me guess," she said, tilting her head slightly to one side, "Dread and Scourge?"

Fred puffed up importantly and said, "That's Mr. Scourge to you."

George aimed a mock punch at Fred's arm, and Fred ducked dramatically.

"Dread?" George chuckled, "More like Fled."

"You're one to talk, Porridge," Fred sniffed.

Ron snorted, "Not sure that one quite works."

"Oh? How about this one, Prawn?"

"More like Yawn."

"Or maybe Bon-bon?"

"And that's my cue to leave," Ron rolled his eyes, "Thank Fate every day you don't have any siblings, Rigel. I'll go tell Mum you're here."

"Don't listen to him, Pup," George said good-naturedly, "Younger siblings are a blast."

"Are you quite done accosting our guest?" Percy came striding into the room, straightening his horn-rimmed glasses as he looked Rigel up and down, "You look well, Rigel."

"Older ones on the other hand…" Fred muttered.

"What was that?" Percy turned his sharp gaze on his brother.

Fred straightened and pasted on a smile that fooled no one, "Just giving Rigel a hand, I said."

"We were about to conduct a tour, in fact," George said, "We thought we'd start with your closet, Percy, specifically the collection of pen nibs you keep in a box up there, so if you don't mind—"

"This must be young Rigel Black, then."

A middle-aged woman with fiery hair and a welcoming expression bustled into the room. She spoke briskly, eyed the acid burns on Rigel's boots sharply, and smiled warmly. Rigel didn't think she'd ever been looked at so affectionately by someone she'd just met.

"Pleased to meet you, Mrs. Weasley," Rigel said, bowing to the same degree she would to Mrs. Malfoy, "My father has only wonderful things to say about you and your family. He sends his regards, and please, call me Rigel."

Mrs. Weasley chuckled, "So polite!" She turned to narrow her eyes at her three middle children, "Why can't you ever be that polite?"

"I am that polite, Mother," Percy said stiffly.

"Being polite is not the same as having a stick up your—"

"George!"

"I'm Fred, Mum," George rolled his eyes.

Mrs. Weasley sighed, "Sure you are, Dear."

Rigel was taken aback by their family dynamic. It was almost prickly, and yet…no one seemed to really mean any of the things they were saying, as if their dialogue was all part of an inside, family joke. It was…endearing, in an overwhelming kind of a way.

"Well, it is very lovely to meet you, Rigel," Mrs. Weasley said, "Come into the kitchen, won't you? I'll put a kettle on. I must say, I didn't imagine you'd be so thin…"

The Weasley matriarch bustled away into the next room, leaving Rigel to smother a wince and follow behind her.

"Don't take it personal," Fred whispered.

"She thinks Hagrid is too skinny," George added.

"Though you do seem to have grown in the last few weeks," Percy said, eyeing her critically.

"My Aunt Lily's cooking," Rigel said, affecting a shrug. Of course they would notice—even though the latest dose of Modified Polyjuice hadn't changed her appearance too much, it was still an abrupt transformation. Most noticeably, the potion had increased her height by an inch and a half, giving her a slightly gangly look that she had learned to ignore.

They trooped into the kitchen, which held the biggest kitchen table she'd ever seen, discounting Grimmauld Place's formal dining table. The Weasley kitchen could probably seat twelve, at least. At the moment, the only one sitting at it was Ginny. Even though it had only been two and a half weeks since the end of school, Ginny already looked much better than she had the last time Rigel saw her. Not softer, exactly, but…calmer. More at peace, perhaps. Rigel hoped the Occlumency lessons would ground her even more, when they began.

"Hello, Ginny," Rigel said politely, "Good to see you."

"Hello, Rigel," Ginny said, "Couldn't get out of coming after all?"

"Ginny!" Mrs. Weasley scowled, "Don't be rude."

"It's quite all right, Mrs. Weasley," Rigel said, smiling slightly, "I like Ginny rude."

Ron made a choking noise that he quickly turned into a cough, and the Twins (whose title she always capitalized in her head for some reason) both guffawed.

"Well," Mrs. Weasley didn't seem to know what to say to that, so she set about making tea.

They all took seats around the table, and Rigel slipped into one next to Percy, still curious about the magic holding up the Burrow.

"Percy, do you know anything about the structural wards for this house?"

Percy raised an eyebrow before saying slowly, "A bit, why?"

"In potions, magic acts as the ultimate stabilizer, sometimes even compensating for otherwise unstable combinations, so I wondered if it might not be the same for magical structures," Rigel began.

Fred cut her off with an extremely loud throat clearing, and George contributed by putting a hand over Rigel's mouth. Rigel stopped talking, and raised her eyebrows at the two with calm patience.

"No shop-talk," George said helpfully, "This is a social visit."

When he moved his hand away, Rigel asked, "Is talking not considered social here?"

"Talking about academics certainly isn't," Fred said firmly.

"It's not academics, just a bit of magical theory," Rigel pointed out, "And I'm pretty sure asking about the host's family home is the very basics of social small talk."

"About the host family's wards?" George drawled.

Rigel mentally awarded the point to George. It wasn't really good form to ask about another wizard's wards, as a matter of security.

Ron smirked, "He's got you there. But there's nothing wrong if it's just theory. How many times have you two regaled us with the theory behind your latest pranking invention at the table? I want to hear about the wards, too."

"Dad would know better," Percy said, "But I believe the Weasley who built this house had the help of a Light Lady. She supposedly instilled a great deal of power into one of the key—"

Percy was interrupted by the fireplace roaring to life. The sickly green color of the flames told them someone was coming through the floo, and the way the Weasley's all frowned or cocked their heads curiously told Rigel that whoever it was, they weren't expected.

Yet another redhead ducked into the kitchen, de-ashing himself with a careless shake.

"Bill!"

The newcomer waved a hand ironically in response to the cry that went up around the kitchen, "Yes, it's me. Did I surprise you?"

"What on Merlin's green earth are you doing here?" Mrs. Weasley planted her hands on her hips, "You said you wouldn't be home again till July."

Bill raised an eyebrow, "Not happy to see me, Mum?"

Mrs. Weasley rolled her eyes, "Oh, come here, then."

Bill grinned and strode over to kiss his mother on the cheek. Rigel didn't think she'd ever seen someone look cool while hugging their mum, but somehow Bill Weasley pulled it off. His hair was long, which made his mother cluck despairingly as she bustled about getting cups for tea. He was tall, lean, and when he turned his head to hide his grin from Mrs. Weasley's disapproving eyes, the silver fang dangling from his ear flashed as it caught the light.

"Who's this then?" the older boy—man, really—asked as he sat down. His eyes flicked over Rigel's face, but no recognition lit his mildly curious expression.

"This is Rigel Black," Ron said hastily, apparently taking responsibility for Rigel's place there, "He's in my class at Hogwarts."

Bill mulled that over for a moment before answering, "Sirius Black's son, then." It didn't sound like a question, but Rigel nodded in any case. "I hear you saved my little sister's life a few weeks ago, and that of my brother's a year before that."

Rigel blinked slowly to give herself time to formulate a response, "Ginny and I saved one another, and Ron's life was never in any mortal danger from the sickness. It's a pleasure to meet you, however."

Bill gave a slow grin, "Modest, are you? That's good."

Rigel had the absurd impulse to say something inane like 'thank you,' but she resisted.

"Why are you back early, Bill?" Percy asked curiously, "Aren't you scheduled to be on a dig right now?"

"Bill's a curse breaker for Gringotts," George informed Rigel quietly, "He's been working in Egypt lately, on a series of old tombs they just uncovered."

"You'll hear about it soon enough in the Prophet," Bill said, shrugging, "But the dig was put on hold. One of the tombs we were set to excavate was broken into last night."

"What?"

"Merlin!"

"Was anyone hurt?"

"Everyone's fine," Bill assured his family, "They're not even sure it was a break-in. The air-seal over the site was broken, but no opening big enough for someone to get in or out of was created. Also, preliminary investigation seems to indicate that the treasures we expected to find are still in there. If it was broken into, they didn't want gold."

"Does that mean you're fired?" Ginny asked drolly.

Bill reached over to tug on her hair admonishingly, "Hush, you. No one fires Bill Weasley. I just get a few days off while they look for clues. Once that's done, we can get on with the actual tomb-plundering."

"When you said you wanted to be a pirate when you grew up, your father and I always laughed," Mrs. Weasley sighed, "I suppose the joke is on us."

"It could be worse," Bill shrugged casually, "Charlie wanted to be Vampire when he was little."

Mrs. Weasley tittered with an embarrassed glance at Rigel, "That was just a phase."

"He used to only come out of his room at night," Percy sighed, "And I remember him refusing to eat anything that wasn't red-colored."

"That's right," Bill chuckled, "He used to mush all of his food together until it was pulverized, then eat with his hands. It was disgusting."

"He was eight," Mrs. Weasley huffed, "And he was over it in a few months."

"What does he do now?" Rigel asked curiously.

"He's a dragon-tamer," Ron said casually.

Rigel's eyebrows rose. A curse-breaker, a dragon-tamer—the Weasleys certainly were a formidable bunch.

"We like a bit of danger," George said, as if he could guess her thoughts.

"Gryffindors," Fred shrugged, grinning.

"That's no excuse," Percy sniffed.

"Like you aren't going to be the most formidable lawyer that ever lived, Perce," Ginny scoffed, "I bet you set a record for most criminals who plead guilty and beg for mercy at the mere mention of you."

"I'm not going to be a trial lawyer," Percy protested, though his ears were pink at the praise.

"You say that now," Ginny smirked, "But we all know you can't resist the limelight for long."

Percy scowled, but Rigel could tell it was good-natured. They knew one another so well, this family. They knew each other's strengths and weaknesses, and they talked about them openly for all to hear. It was sort of amazing, to Rigel at least. Her family was warm, and open on the surface…but they all had things they didn't talk about, too. Diana, Lily's muggle relatives, their friend Pettigrew from school…the list went deep. Even Archie and she had secrets, now.

Then again, Rigel scolded herself, the Weasleys probably had secrets too—everyone did, didn't they? If they came to her house, it would probably seem like the Blacks and Potters were themselves an ideal family, at least at first.

Still, the idea of the Weasley family was nice, she thought.

She didn't stay at the Weasleys' home more than a few hours. It was good to catch up with her friends from school, but she didn't have time to spend all evening away from her work.

Her internship started next week. It would last all of July and August, ending just before she had to go back to Hogwarts. As she understood it, most of the internship was research-oriented, but she wanted to be as prepared as she could be for any practical challenges she would face.

As such, she spent as many hours a day as she could afford in her lab. When she returned from the Weasleys' house, she stopped only to change into her work robes before heading back into the basement. She was almost through with the latest batch of potions Krait had commissioned from her. She continued to conduct her business with Krait by owl mail, though she told herself she wasn't avoiding Diagon Alley. Or Leo.

If Krait noticed how much quicker she responded to his orders, not having to wait for the mail to go through Archie in America first anymore, he probably attributed it to her having more free time now that school was out. If he was offended she hadn't been in to see him personally since she got back, he didn't say so. Leo hadn't ever answered her letter, hadn't given an explanation as to why he'd deliberately set her up for exposure at AIM. If she traipsed through Diagon Alley every day, sooner or later she'd run into him. She had no interest in spending time with people she couldn't trust, however.

As she was making a supply list for the stores she'd depleted since Christmas, her father poked his head into the lab and called her name.

"Harry? You down here?"

"Just finishing up for the night, Dad," Harry said absently, deciding that it would be safer to order two bushels of winterfig twigs, just in case."

"How can you stand it down here for so long?" James ruffled up the back of his hair absently as he looked around the well-lit lab, "Don't you want a window, or something?"

"I have plenty of light, Dad," Harry said patiently, "I don't need a fake window with its accompanying, detrimental distractions."

"If you say so, kiddo," James said, obviously too tired to really care—not that Harry blamed him; his life was tiring, after all, "Though I don't know if there's anything detrimental about a little sunshine." The look on his face was affable bewilderment. It was a look Harry had always associated with her dad, as he wore it often around her. She knew she confused him, but she also knew he didn't hold it against her, so their relationship was fine, no matter what others might think.

"You know Sirius would just charm it to rain frogs all day," Harry said, deliberately lightening the mood, "And that would be distracting."

"Yeah," James chuckled, "You'd be lucky if it was just frogs…still…" his face dissolved into puzzled concern once more, "You spend an awfully long time down here every day. Archie went over to see one of his friends from school today—the Weasley boy, you know. You could go visit Hermione, or another friend, if you wanted."

Harry smiled reassuringly, "I'm just preparing for my internship, Dad. You know how important it is to me. Besides, I did go out today—I went book shopping, remember?"

At least, that's what Archie, who was pretending to be Harry that afternoon, had done.

"Oh," James said, "Books, right. Potions books, I suppose?"

"Healer's books, actually."

"You're sticking with that, then?" James sounded approving.

"As long as I can," Harry said honestly. At her father's conflicted look, she added, "For me, not just for Archie."

James smiled, "You're a good one, Harry. Your mother and I are so proud of you."

"Thanks, Dad," Harry said. She didn't know exactly what his words were supposed to mean, but she took them for what they were: unconditional support, if not understanding.

"Oh, a letter came in the mail today—from that correspondence school of yours," James added before he left, "Are you sure you have time for more classes this summer? You've got that internship as well."

"I didn't sign up for very many," Harry said quickly, "I shouldn't have trouble doing both."

"If you're sure," James said easily, having long ago learned not to argue with Harry about what she could and couldn't do. He almost always ended up eating his words. "Dinner will be at Grimmauld tonight. Wash up first, okay?"

"Of course, Dad," Harry said, already turning back to her supply list, "See you in a bit."

Dinner wasn't quite the same cheerful, noisy affair it had been the last time they were all home. It was still plenty noisy, and it wasn't that anyone was unhappy, but the meal was tempered by a kind of strained weariness that perhaps only parents of newborn babies could understand.

Addy was a joy to all of them, but Harry could see the toll that having a baby in the family again was taking on her parents.

Sirius kept up conversation with Remus and Archie, while Lily and James only participated when called upon, otherwise conserving their energy for eating. Lily's face, though full of love, was thinner, her eyelids just a little slower to blink. Harry knew, just based on how often she herself awoke to the sound of a baby's cries in the dead of night, that Lily wasn't getting much sleep. James laughed readily at Sirius' jokes, but half a beat slower than was natural.

Harry was in charge of feeding Addy that night—they all took it in turns. On the surface it seemed rather elementary: put bottle in baby's mouth, wait for baby to drink it all, then stop. Unfortunately, such a process depended entirely upon baby's cooperation, and didn't take into account the fact that Addy hated Harry.

As in, actually couldn't stand to be around Harry at all.

When Harry held her, she cried. When Harry leaned in to kiss her forehead, she cried. Whether Harry offered toys, milk, cooing noises, or diaper changes didn't matter—Addy still cried. After the first week, Harry had decided the best course of action was to stop antagonizing the obviously distressed infant. She still looked on fondly as Addy interacted with the other members of their family—from a distance—but the only times she directly interacted with her sister herself were feeding times.

Harry had quickly discovered it worked best if she laid Addy in a little nest of baby blankets, propped at half-mast, and arranged for the bottle to rest on another, smaller nest on blankets on Addy's little chest, also propped at an angle against her mouth. This way, all she had to do was watch as Addy drank, make sure she stopped for air and burps often enough, and take away the bottle when Addy was done.

All the others except Remus cradled the baby in their arms as they fed her. Harry's only consolation was that if Addy didn't like Remus much either, it at least meant she wasn't a great judge of character, and her dislike of Harry didn't mean Harry was inherently dislikable…probably.

Addy finally settled into her dinner—after Harry stopped touching her—and Harry kept an eye on her while she mechanically ate her own meal.

It went on uninterrupted for a few minutes, until Remus suddenly blurted, "Harry, that's meat!"

Harry looked down at her plate. There was indeed a piece of chicken on her plate. She must have absent-mindedly taken one from the center pile.

"I…eat meat now," she said, shrugging, "I'm going into adolescence—you've seen how much I've grown the past five months. It isn't healthy to maintain a vegetarian diet when I can't devote the time or energy to really pay attention to getting the right nutrition anymore. Sorry I didn't tell you," she added as an afterthought.

"Sweet!" Archie said, cheerfully scraping the rest of his chicken onto Harry's plate, "Cause I'm full."

Harry looked down at the half-eaten chicken on her plate, "Thanks?" She saw Addy's bottle start slipping from the corner of her eye, so she reached out straightened it, ignoring the little whimper her baby sister let out when Harry's finger brushed her cheek accidentally.

Archie got up to rummage around the kitchen, "Where's the bunt cake Dad brought home yesterday?"

"Do you actually know what the word 'full' means, or is that just something you say when you want to leave the table?" Remus asked.

"I'm pretty sure the meaning of full is 'I'm tired of eating this and ready for something else,'" Archie called back.

The conversation moved on, and Harry mentally thanked Archie for the distraction. She'd gotten used to eating meat in the kitchens with Binny, which was probably the one place, apart from her lab, where she felt relaxed while at Hogwarts. Perhaps she had associated the relaxed feeling of eating at home with 'a safe place to eat meat' in her head, but it was still an unforgivable lapse in concentration.

On the up side, their parents (and especially hers) were noticeably less attentive to Harry and Archie this summer, and it didn't take a genius to work out that Addy simply needed their attention more. The infant's needs also drained the adults of their excess energy, made them less attentive and more easily distracted. On the down side, this meant Harry was becoming less attentive in turn, because any slip-ups she made were largely overlooked, but soon she would be back dealing with people who were not strung-out from dealing with an infant all day on top of demanding careers, and those people would notice if she slipped up.

After dinner, James helped Remus clean up the kitchen, Archie went up to his room to 'finish a letter to Draco,' Lily took Addy back to Godric's Hollow to take a bath, and Harry went back to her lab. She was almost done with Flint's summer assignments, but she wanted to draft a letter to Blaise for his opinion on binary rune circles before she started outlining the Runes essay.

She wanted nothing to distract her from the internship, which loomed closer in the back of her mind each day. Sometimes Harry felt like she was being stalked by a beast she knew full well was coming, but couldn't turn around and face. But no, that was silly. She was ready for this internship. She was.

That weekend she received a letter from Krait. He'd arranged a meeting with Horace Burke, and apparently (and a bit annoyingly) assured him she would be there to discuss a proposition for expanding his order.

On Sunday morning before most of the shops along Diagon Alley had even opened, Harry slipped out the floo while Lily was busy giving Addy her morning bottle.

She was no longer that wide-eyed child who'd coming traipsing through Knockturn Alley looking for a job last summer. She kept sharp eyes on passersby, and the hand in her robe pocket rested not on a wand—for she was banned from magic over the summer—but on a small platinum knife designed for only the most meticulous of ingredient preparation.

She relaxed only when she stepped into the familiar Serpent's Storeroom. After glancing around, she swiftly un-relaxed when she realized that Krait, and Horace Burke as well, were nowhere to be seen. Instead, she shared the shop with one Lionel Hurst, King of The Lower Alleys, and current number one on Harry's list of people she didn't want to see.

He was somehow even taller than he'd been over Christmas, his skin tanned and his clothes casual. His white teeth flashed in a smile when she walked in, but it swiftly faded when she didn't smile back.

She rested her back against the shop door and lifted her chin challengingly, "After your unprovoked sabotage at AIM you've descended to merely wasting my time with fake meetings, Leo?"

"Sabotage is a little dramatic, lass," Leo protested, not moving from where he was leaned indolently against a shelf across from the door.

"What do they call it around here when one person tries to ruin the plans of another person? Do they call it friendship, Leo?"

"Not in as many words," Leo muttered, lifting one shoulder uncomfortably, "Look, Harry, will you let me explain?"

"I asked for an explanation several months ago. You never replied," Harry said flatly.

"I felt I needed to explain in person," Leo said lightly, "And I didn't want to risk a letter, since it might be construed as yet another threat to your all-important secrets."

"Yes, my important secrets," Harry said slowly, "The ones you knew about, the ones I told you were important, the ones you betrayed when you sent your man to my school armed with the power of my undoing."

"When truth is a threat, you have to admit something's wrong—"

"Says the King of the Shadow World?" Harry snapped incredulously, "The only thing wrong is—is me, obviously, for misplacing my trust in you."

Leo stalked across the room so fast that Harry didn't have time to flinch. He was right up in her face, looming over her, and glaring as he spoke in a low, harsh bite, "Now don't start playing the trust card with me, lass. Don't act like you gave me your trust and I betrayed it. You didn't tell me your secrets. I pried them out of you—"

"By sneaking around behind my back—"

"By looking after you the way you clearly can't be trusted to look after yourself—"

"What would you know of trust?" Harry scowled, "You, who sends Marek to my school to mess up everything? Did you even give it a second thought? Or did you just shrug and decide that only the things you decide are important are worth caring about?"

"Harry…"

"No!" Harry could feel blood flowing to her face, as it did on the rare occasion she ever got really upset, but she couldn't help herself. Leo had no idea how much damage he could have caused, but she had to make him understand that she wasn't playing. "You have to listen to me, Leo! Don't look at me and see a little girl who doesn't know any better, don't wait for me to finish and then ignore what I said, listen, okay?"

Leo took a breath so deep it pressed his chest up against her own for a moment, then he turned his head and blew it out, stepped back, and crossed his arms expectantly, "Okay. I'm listening."

Harry thought carefully about what she wanted to say. She took a moment to swing her point of view in Leo's direction, to think about why he might have acted the way he did, what he might think about her, and how to address the real problems between them. If she wanted him to listen, she had to let him see she understood his side.

"I think some of the things you believe about me are wrong," she began. "When we met, you thought I was a boy, and when I finally corrected you about it, I think you may have come to the conclusion that I hide things casually, without good reason, and without thinking the consequences through, is that right?"

Leo tilted his head consideringly, then nodded slowly, "In a way."

Harry firmed her gaze, "That was a very poor example of the secrets I carry and the deceptions I carry out. I'm not trying to alarm you, Leo, but you need to understand that whatever you think of my life, it hangs in a precarious place right now. I've taken as many precautions as I can think of, fortified my position a hundred times over, but I know it isn't enough. You, however, don't know how dangerous a position you put me in when you sent Marek to AIM looking for me." She held up a hand to forestall Leo's objections, "I know it isn't your fault you don't know, because I can't tell you, but you did know that I was keeping secrets, you did know that they were complicated, and you still sent people to interfere. Do you understand why I'm angry?"

Leo shot her an unimpressed glance, "If you're done patronizing me, yes, I know why you're mad. I respect that you don't appreciate my interference, but I'm not the one who doesn't understand how dangerous your way of life is—I'm not talking about whatever perceived danger you feel will befall you if people know you're a girl, though I can guess it has something to do with the discrimination you feel exists against women in the potions community. I'm talking about the damage it will do to your psyche to put yourself under constant pressure like that. Secrets aren't good for the soul, Harry. They're going to consume your entire life, because that's what lies do—I'm not telling you this as some kind of White Wizard, Harry. I know this because I've been you. I understand living a complete lie, segmenting your life into different compartments with different identities that you never let overlap. I don't want that life for you, Harry. I'm not trying to ruin your life. I'm trying to save it, before you get in too deep. You're twelve. If people find out what you're hiding now, it won't be that big of a deal. You can move past it, your friends at school will forgive you, and things will be okay. If you keep this up until you're seventeen, though…Harry, it's not a good idea. Surely you can see that?"

Harry felt her anger soften slightly. "Leo…thank you for looking out for me."

"But?" he said wryly.

"But you don't have all the facts," Harry said sadly, "I do see the sense in your advice, but I'm telling you…it's not that simple. It's already too late to go back and simply confess everything. What I've done…can't be undone. Please say you won't ever try and meddle in my life like that again."

Leo's face was mulishly unwilling.

Harry tried a different tract, "Not just for me, Leo, but for your own sake. You really don't want to get mixed up in—"

"Don't."

Leo took another long breath, and Harry waited for him to find his words.

"Don't tell me what I do or don't want to do for you, Harry," Leo said softly, "I've said it before—I'm your friend. I'm not gonna keep away to save my own skin. If you're really sure you can't get out of whatever mess you're in…then I won't try to pull you out myself ever again. But please…please be careful. I know I said that before, but I didn't really believe that you could be in that much trouble. You're a Potter, practically royalty, and still a kid, how could you be in any real danger? That was stupid of me, I guess. I only have to remember myself at your age…" he grimaced, "Actually, I can't believe I didn't think of it like that before now. Do you need papers to flee the country?"

Harry let a laugh escape her, and stepped forward to hug Leo briefly, "You're pretty foolish for a king, Leo."

"Well, you're pretty shady for an Auror's daughter, lass," Leo muttered into her hair.

Harry stepped back and shrugged, "I guess if anyone knows about not following in our parents' footsteps, it's us."

Harry turned to go, but Leo laughed, saying, "Oh, no you don't. I have something for you—an apology."

Harry raised her eyebrows, "Okay, I'm listening."

Leo laughed again, "Like I'm going to say it? No, you don't deserve the satisfaction."

"How do you figure that?" Harry asked dryly.

"Well if you hadn't been such an untrusting little—"

"Not seeing the apology part yet."

"Ahem," Leo coughed dramatically, "Follow me."

He took her out into the alleys, past the Dancing Phoenix…and up Dogwood Lane.

"This feels familiar," she commented as they stopped before number eight.

"Do you have the key?" Leo asked, smirking.

Rigel opened her mouth to retort, then realized that no, actually, she didn't. "I usually floo in," she mumbled.

"Sure you do," Leo said, "Come on, then."

He led her around to the backstreet, and took out his wand. Harry tensed automatically, but Leo held up his hands calmly, "I'm going to levitate you up to your window—which you don't keep locked—"

"I know that," Harry snapped.

Leo just gave her this look, and continued, "Don't wiggle too much or it'll compromise the spell."

Harry eyed his wand dubiously, "I won't be able to levitate you up after, because I'm underage…and so are you, aren't you?"

"Turned seventeen in April," he grinned, "And I'm going to climb up after you."

"Why can't we both climb?" Harry bristled, "Because I'm a girl?"

"Because you don't know how to scale a building," Leo said.

"So teach me," Harry suggested.

"Right now?" Leo rolled his eyes, "What will the neighbors think? I'll teach you later if you really want to know how, just hold still for a second, will you?"

Before Harry could protest, he swished his wand at her torso. Her magic, a bit on edge after the Chamber incident, flashed into a shield and intercepted the levitation spell in an instant.

Leo raised an eyebrow, "Really? Now who's violating the Minister's law?"

Harry sighed, not bothering to point out that not using her wand meant not being Traced, and asked her magic to lay low, allowing Leo to cast the levitation charm and hoist her gently into the air. As she floated upwards, she couldn't help but notice that Leo's magic felt restless in a way most grown wizards' magic didn't. Was it because he was just now leaving adolescence?

She latched onto the windowsill and hefted the pane upwards as Leo held her steady in the air. When she had pulled herself halfway through, she felt the levitation spell dissipate, and not long after she had scurried inside, Leo followed lightly into the room.

When she looked around, the first thing she noticed was how full the room was. She stared, blinked, turned in a circle, blinked, walked into the kitchen, stared some more, and took a deep, calming breath. Every room was filled with appropriate furniture. The kitchen had a table, two chairs, a scattering of dishes, even. The living room had a settee, a coffee table, a bookcase—and there were books in it! Potions books, classics and newer editions, too. She ran her fingers along the spines, and turned to run her eyes wonderingly over a painting of Hyde Park that hung over the fireplace.

She suspected that if she went into the little bedroom, she'd find a bed, maybe even a chest of drawers. She looked at Leo, who was watching her with a twinkling grin, and swallowed hard.

She cleared her throat, "I was…ah, I've been wondering for a while where all this came from. I should have know it was you who—"

Leo shook his head and said, "Don't, lass, not with me."

Harry's hands trembled helplessly, but Leo caught them with his own and smiled kindly down at her, "I know you've got this place for a reason, and it looks less suspicious with actual furnishings, doesn't it? And I come here every now and then, make a bit of noise for the neighbors to hear…well, even if you only meant to use it as an escape hole, now it's ready for you."

Harry frowned, "That's not what—"

"Hush," Leo said, with no small amount of amusement, "I don't care what you want it for—I'll tell any tale you like, or none at all. I know I messed up at AIM. I won't send one of my men there again. I did this so you'd know I'm trying to help you, Harry. I'm on your side."

Somehow, even though Harry had understood Leo's point as soon as she'd seen the furnishings, hearing those words…

He was on her side. How many people could truly say that they were on Harry Potter's side, and have even an inkling of the trouble they were getting themselves into by declaring it? Archie, of course, and now Leo.

Harry stepped away from Leo and smiled with as much affection as she dared—it went all the way up to her eyes, and stayed there for a moment, vulnerable and true, before she let it fall again, "Thank you, Leo. I'm sorry I snapped at you."

"You're welcome any time, lass," Leo smiled back, "To the snapping, too, in fact. I suspect you don't let yourself shout as often as you deserve to."

"I'll leave most of the yelling to your mother," Harry grinned, "But thanks anyway."

She flooed back to the Leaky Cauldron before flooing to Godric's Hollow—you never knew when floo records could be traced—and when her mother asked distractedly where she'd been all morning, Harry told the truth.

"I've been visiting a friend."

The Potions Guild.

Harry knew plenty about it, but she had never dreamed of setting foot inside—not until she was about twenty, at least.

The building itself was intimidating, redone in the sixteenth century, and following the imposing Tudor style, all heavy arches, tall doorways, and steep roofing. It's wasn't beautiful, but it was noticeable, in the most tasteful of ways, of course. It sat in between the Ward Smith Guild and the Metallurgist Guild, on what most people called Craftsman Alley, which ran parallel to Diagon Alley, and was reached via an unnamed backstreet running next to an antique bookshop near Mr. Tate's shop.

Harry had known it would probably take the same amount of time to get to as the Serpent's Storeroom did, and she had still shown up fifteen minutes early. She hesitated outside the tall, narrow wooden doors. She could wait outside for fifteen minutes…and then just go home like the coward she was impersonating. She sighed, opened the doors, and stepped firmly into the rest of her life, closing the heavy oak decidedly behind her.

The front desk stood directly before her, so she approached it determinately.

A young man of about twenty sat at the desk, and as she drew nearer she could hear him muttering to himself as he shifted manuscripts from one place on the desk to another, seemingly at random.

She cleared her throat, "Excuse me, could you tell me where—"

"Yes?" the young man looked up with unfocused eyes, "What's that?"

"I'm here for the Guild internship," she said, "Where should I—"

"Down that hallway," he gestured to an archway to his left, "Down the stairs at the end, left until you see a sign for Lab 17. Master Rutherage will be down to meet you upon the hour."

"Thank you," Harry said, but the young man appeared too busy to notice.

She followed his directions, hiking up her new potions satchel as she went. She'd needed something unrecognizable as Rigel Black's—just in case—so she splurged on a potioneer-made bag with air-lock spells and manual pressure-adjustors built into the pockets. After all the brewing she was doing for Krait, she could certainly afford it, even after she set aside a good portion of her earnings for rent on number eight. Now as she approached the door to Lab 17, she had a moment of illogical fear that it would seem silly, her walking in with her new satchel, like a little girl with a new lunchbox on her first day of school.

She straightened her shoulders impatiently. She took pride in her work, which included owning top-notch equipment as well. She was a damn good brewer and had nothing to be ashamed of. She opened the door to Lab 17 quietly and calmly, as though it was no big deal. Just another door that needed opening. She only mentally cringed a little bit at how ridiculous her inner monologue was becoming.

Lab 17 was fairly small. Bigger than her personal lab, of course, but much smaller than the student labs at Hogwarts. She clamped tight on that thought—Harry Potter has no idea how big the labs at Hogwarts are—and distracted her mind by surveying the room, and the people within it.

The two other internees were already present. They were both boys, and both turned to face her at the sound of the door closing behind her. One was dark haired and dark eyed. He was relatively short for a boy who looked around nineteen, and his skin-tone suggested a southern-European ancestry. Maybe. Harry wasn't actually that great with guessing heritages in people. That boy looked at her curiously for a moment, then went back to the periodical he was reading—the most recent Potions Quarterly, she noted. She also wondered why he hadn't read it in May when it was released.

The other boy scowled at her from where he lounged with casual grace at the desk he'd chosen. When Harry recognized him, it took a direct assertion of will not to scowl back.

It was Caelum Lestrange.

She turned all the dislike that surfaced at the sight of his perfectly pretentious face into icy coolness, and walked across the room to sit at a desk on the other side of the European-looking boy—better to keep him between her and Lestrange, in case her magic got any funny ideas about what to do with the enmity he stirred in her.

"What are you doing here?" Lestrange asked incredulously, "This program is for talented brewers, not amateur children."

Harry turned her head to look past the other boy to where Lestrange was openly sneering at her. You don't know him, she reminded the part of herself pretending to be Harry Potter (ignoring for the moment how absurd it was that she had a part of herself pretending to be herself). "Have we met?" she asked quietly.

Lestrange's face went even paler with anger, and Harry had to admit she knew why. It was the highest of insults among High Society to forget a face—even higher if you were pretending to forget, as Lestrange no doubt suspected she was.

"Very amusing, Black," Lestrange spat, "Too good to remember your betters?"

Harry let her eyes widen in understanding, "Oh—you've met my cousin, then, Rigel Black? Don't worry, this sort of thing happens a lot. We're very similar in appearance."

Lestrange was taken aback only a moment before he regrouped, "Is that so? How convenient. Who exactly are you supposed to be, then? Regulus Black's bastard—"

"Careful," Harry said mildly, though with steel in her gaze, "Regulus Black doesn't take kindly to slights against the Black Family name. I'm not related to Rigel by blood, however. I should have said honorary cousin. My name is Harry, Harry Potter."

If anything, Lestrange's incredulity only grew, "The Potter Heiress?" He stared at her for a beat, sweeping his eyes down her body, then snorted, "You've got to be the ugliest girl I've ever seen."

Harry's eyebrows snapped together sharply, but she took a calming breath. The fact that Lestrange was here before taking his NEWT's meant he had some skill as a brewer. If he passed his Mastery, she would cross paths with him occasionally. Better to learn to neutralize his vitriol now. "Perhaps I am," she said evenly, "But I think it's awfully rude to say so."

Lestrange only lounged back at his desk unconcernedly, "Who cares what you think? A brat like you won't last a week in this program. They'll send you home crying like the little girl you are."

Harry bit down sharply on her tongue to stop it lashing out in retaliation. He's not worth it, she told herself, He's not what you're here for. Ignore him, and be patient. His opinion means dirt.

She turned her attention to the boy sitting next to her, who had yet to say a word, "I'm Harry," she said, "What's your name?"

"Renaldo," the boy said shortly, not even glancing at her as his eyes flicked lazily over the words of the article he skimmed, "Please don't talk to me, girl."

Harry turned back to her own desk slowly, blank-faced. She ignored the part of her that winced at Renaldo's dismissal, and crushed the part of her that growled at Lestrange's derisive snort of laughter at her expense. She took a deep breath, counted to ten in French, and retreated behind a calm outer indifference. So she wasn't destined to make friends here—so what? Great potioneers didn't need friends, only test subjects. Look at Master Snape—he didn't have many friends, and he was the best. She could be like that too; if her peers wouldn't give her the time of day, she would wear a watch.

A moment later, a great bear of a man with thick, wavy brown hair and sharp green eyes stepped into the small lab and surveyed them all cheerfully, "All here then? Good." The door slammed shut behind him and locked with an audible click at a flick of the man's wand, "If anyone is late, they will lose that day of instruction—so don't be. Welcome to the Guild's summer internship program. If you want to make anything of yourselves in the potions community, I suggest you start taking notes—NOW!"

Harry smoothly took out a sheaf of loose parchment and readied her quill. Lestrange and his pettiness retreated to the unimportant recesses of her mind. Finally, she was beginning her career as a potioneer. She was sitting in the Guild, learning from one of the senior Masters, as Harry Potter—not as Rigel Black or anyone else. It didn't matter if her classmates didn't like her. Harry was here, and no one could ever dispute that, halfblood girl or not.

Chapter 2

Diagon Alley was alive with the chatter and clatter of a bustling Friday morning, and Harry darted and dodged her way through the crowds with the same flustered urgency as any of the frantic shoppers filling the streets around her. Usually, she wasn't bothered by all the bustle, and would let it sweep her along to her destination passively, but today she was late.

At least, she thought as she jumped over a stray crup licking up someone's spilled ice cream from the cobblestones, I'm almost late.

If she wasn't there on the hour, Master Rutherage would lock the door. No one had actually been late, so she didn't know for sure, but Rutherage didn't seem the type to make empty threats. He had a brilliant mind, a keen understanding of the intricacies of potion theoretics, and an up-beat disposition, but not, Harry thought, a strong inclination toward forgiveness.

She sidestepped a woman selling True Love charms, and almost collided with a man carrying a tall tower of singing wineglasses. At the last minute, she threw herself out of the way—and promptly crashed into someone else entirely.

It was an older man, about her father's age, slightly heavy-set, with small, beady eyes that were nevertheless a pretty shade of light blue. He sat for a moment where he'd fallen in the street, apparently stunned by the abruptness of his tumble. Harry rolled to her feet with a groan and went to make a quick apology, but as she approached, the man's face took on a look of pure panic.

He was patting down his robes frantically, his eyes darting here and there among the throng of people stepping over and around the two of them in a rush. Harry, alarmed because he was so alarmed, began looking about as well. It was hard to even see the street because of the crush of passersby, but from her standing position Harry spotted a little brown sack that lay half-concealed behind the wheel of a cart vendor they had both nearly crashed into. She ducked down and snatched up the package quickly. The paper bag crumpled easily around her hand, as though it had been worked and worried over and over again, and she felt something hard and vaguely rock-shaped underneath as she carried it over to the man.

"Here," she said, thrusting the bag at him, "Is this what you're looking for?"

The man's eyes widened. He snatched the bag and felt the object inside possessively before taking a huge, gulping sigh of relief, "Oh thank Merlin, thank you Magic, it's here, it's safe, thank Morgana…"

He began to rise unsteadily, so Harry reached out a hand to help him up. He flinched minutely, but accepted her help with a nod of thanks. He shoved his package roughly into an inside robe pocket, and started dusting himself off. Harry stood watching anxiously, eager to get going again, but needing to make sure she hadn't injured the man as well.

"Are you okay?" she asked, "I'm sorry for running into you, Sir."

The man said nothing, only continuing to brush the street dust off of his cloak with single-minded attention. Strangely, the bottom third of his robes seemed to be covered with a silvery-black dust that Harry was sure couldn't have come from the street they were standing on. The dust in Diagon alley was whitish-tan, because that's what color the cobblestones were. She wondered where he'd been to pick up such dark-colored, metallic debris.

When he deemed himself satisfactorily dirt-free, he turned to her, as though he had only just then remembered her existence, "Hello, yes, do try and watch where you're going in the future, young man."

Harry nodded politely, "Of course, Sir, again, very sorry—er, I've actually got to run now—"

"Again?" the man shook his head, "Kids these days. Try not knocking into people on your way, won't you?"

"Yes, Sir," Harry said, bowing hastily, "Very sorry. Have a good day, Sir."

She took off running again, still feeling slightly guilty about her hasty departure, but she was really, really running late now.

She tore through the connecting street and emerged onto Craftsman Alley at a sprint. She didn't stop to greet the ever-hassled young man at the welcoming desk like she usually did, instead just running through the halls, down the stairs, and toward Lab 17, praying vaguely that none of the Masters saw her in such shameful disarray.

She ran straight up to the door to Lab 17, praying that is wasn't locked yet, willing it not to be locked. Be open, be open, come on, be unlocked, she chanted as she reached for the knob.

It turned.

With a huge gasp of relief, she hurried into the room, then froze as all three of its occupants turned to stare at her.

Master Rutherage was already inside. He was already lecturing, in fact, and both of his eyebrows rose in sharp question as she stood, unsure what to do, her hair windswept, bag slung haphazardly across her chest, panting like a lunatic who'd just run half a mile.

"It—ah—it wasn't locked," she said dumbly.

"Wasn't it?" Rutherage tipped his head toward her chosen workstation, but otherwise left it at that.

Harry had a sneaking suspicion. At the moment she couldn't feel her magic stirring beneath the blood still rushing through her veins, but it wouldn't take much to perform an unlocking charm…had she inadvertently forced the door to unlock itself? Or had Rutherage really forgotten to lock it? If he hadn't, why would he accept her unlocking it?

There was no time to decide which was the more likely scenario, as Rutherage was beginning to lecture again. Harry quickly found her seat and whisked out a sheet of parchment as quietly as possible.

Master Rutherage's lecture style was convoluted, sometimes difficult to follow, but always fascinating. He'd start on a random topic that had something to do with potions, introduce it generally, then ask penetratingly specific questions at random until he was satisfied that he knew the extent of their knowledge on the subject. Once he understood their level of knowledge, he adapted the rest of his lecture to filling the gaps in their knowledge as efficiently as possible.

On Monday, the topic was Classes of Ingredients. Tuesday had been Poisons and Antidotes, Wednesday Transformative Potions, and on Thursday…Harry mentally grimaced. Yesterday had been Love Potions, a subject she was admittedly woefully under-versed on. It didn't help that Lestrange had snickered softly every time she gave an answer that was merely correct, and obviously lacking in rigor and depth. He seemed to find it hilarious that 'the girl' didn't know her Love Draughts back to front.

She banished thoughts of yesterday from her mind and focused instead of what Rutherage was saying now.

"Apart from hieroglyphs found in Egyptian tombs and texts preserved for spiritual reasons among the Hindu, little is known of medicine in the magical sense before the Chinese mystics began to combine their impressive knowledge of Herbology with their rather rudimentary understanding of Alchemy," Master Rutherage said, "What we do know is that medically-purposed creams and tinctures evolved into the earliest beginnings of the field we now know comprehensively as Potions, and it is no accident that most potions have an intimate relation with the human body—for better or worse, depending on whether you're brewing up a Swelling Solution, a perilous poison, or a Draught of Desire. Other branches of magic were developed to effect changes on the world around us, but to this day the majority of potions are still meant to be ingested…"

A smile began to spread over Harry's face. Today's topic was Healing Potions. She couldn't think of a branch of potions she knew better, expect, perhaps, pranking potions, but somehow she didn't think those would be covered in the Guild's program.

"Casillas," Rutherage said suddenly, "What are the broadest categories of Healing Potions?"

"Restoring Potions and Repairing Potions," Renaldo answered in his usual monotone, "The former are used to restore a person transformed or otherwise altered due to a spell or potion gone awry, the latter to heal damage done to the body in the form of wounds or other trauma."

"What would you classify Skele-Grow as?"

Renaldo thought silently for a moment, "It would depend upon whether you used it because the patient had broken a bone or had his bones altered by a spell."

Lestrange chuckled in an infuriatingly smug way, which Harry knew infuriated Renaldo as much as it did her, even if the Spaniard was too collected to do anything besides grit his teeth.

"You disagree, Lestrange?" Rutherage asked mildly.

"A potion's classification can't change just because you're using it to treat different things," Lestrange rolled his eyes, "What a ridiculous assumption. Skele-Grow is always classified as a Restoring Potion."

"And why is that?" Rutherage asked, smiling calmly. Sometimes Harry thought Master Rutherage was trying to goad them with his unassailable good-cheer.

Lestrange sneered, "I don't know. I read it in the kind of useless book that teaches you how to classify things instead of teaching you how to use them."

"Ah, yes," Rutherage nodded sagely, "The world does abound with books such of those—unfortunately, those same books are rather highly regarded by the venerable witches and wizards who write your NEWT exams."

The unspoken 'so shut up and learn the information' was loud and clear, despite Rutherage's easy smile. The Master turned to Harry, saying, "Why is Skele-Grow always a Restorative Potion, Potter?"

"Because to use it you have to first vanish the bones you want to re-grow, regardless of what was originally wrong with them, so the direct problem the potion addresses is always vanished bones—or spell-altered bones, if you want to be technical," Harry's explanation might have been just a tiny bit overdone, and strictly-speaking she didn't have to glance as Lestrange's face as she said it, but there was something satisfying about seeing his too-pretty face pinch in an ugly scowl as she answered a question he could not.

Rutherage didn't say anything like 'correct' or 'good job,' but Harry didn't need him to. The fact that he moved onto the next question without further comment meant she had been completely correct, and that knowledge was enough for Harry.

"Lestrange," Rutherage said, "What are the most difficult kinds of Healing Potions to brew?"

"Ones that affect the mind," Lestrange said, his tone as lazy and indolent as ever.

"Why is that?" Rutherage pressed.

Lestrange paused, then said, "Because the mind is so complicated. It's harder to make potions that affect it without damaging it, because the potions have to be more complicated, too."

"Yes," Rutherage said, eyes laughing, "But is the body not also complicated? Why is the mind so much more so when it comes to Healing magic?"

Lestrange frowned, "I don't know. Ask Potter."

Rutherage turned to Harry, who lifted her chin in response to the challenging eyebrow Lestrange sent her way—as if to say, answer that one, if you're so smart.

"A person's magic manifests itself in three ways," Harry said, smiling slightly as she sent a silent thanks to all the books on auras and Occlumency she'd read, "There's physical magic, mental magic, and aura magic, which is a combination of the first two. You have to take into account a person's mental magic when you create a mind-altering potion, and since mental magic is more imprecise than physical magic, it usually takes a complicated combination of ingredients to enact sufficiently precise effects on the mind. Mental magic is also much less understood than physical magic, so it usually takes a Potions Master who is also a Master of Mental Arts to create or improve upon potions of the mind."

Rutherage smiled widely, "Casillas, can you name two Potions Masters who fit Potter's description?"

"Laverne de Montmorency," Renaldo said, "She invented several mind-altering love potions. Also…Damocles Belby. He invented Wolfsbane."

"Both good historical examples," Rutherage mused, "But potions is a cutting-edge field. Can anyone think of current Masters who are also Masters of mental magic?

"Master Severus Snape," Harry said, suppressing a smile with difficulty, "He's been responsible for the most recent breakthroughs with the Wolfsbane potions."

"Master Regulus Moonshine," Lestrange added, "He recently developed a potion that works on the minds of hags, suppressing their appetite for human flesh."

Rutherage smiled even wider, "We've moved away from the central topic somewhat, but it's never a bad idea to be well-versed in the current body of research. History is important," here he smiled at Renaldo, who was by far the best-versed in ancient and classical potion development, "But the reason this internship is research-based is that history is happening all around is—so try to keep up. Potter, what sort of questions would you ask if someone came to commission a dozen bottles of Goslinder's Solution for their niece?"

"Well, first I'd explain to them that Goslinder's Solution cannot be legally sold in quantities exceeding 0.5 liters, due to the possibility that someone could get around the Ministry's sanction against Firemu seed oil by distilling large quantities of Goslinder's Solution, because it's so easy to reverse-brew by evaporating the binding agent," Harry said thoughtfully, "And then I'd ask how old the niece was, because although it's commonly used as a cure for nervous stuttering, it can actually be damaging to a child's vocal cords if taken either before they fully mature—before seven years of age—or during the transition period between 13 and 17 when the voice begins to drop."

"Lestrange, what ingredient would you use as a substitute if you wanted to make Wheezer's Relief for someone allergic to honey?"

"Marshmallow plant sap," Lestrange said easily.

Harry glanced over in surprise—she wouldn't have thought of that. She'd have said ginger, also an antimicrobial like honey, or maybe sage, to tighten the mucus-producing pores that caused irritants in the throat in the first place. Still…marshmallow was a good idea, since it could coat the throat, and simply stop it from being irritated enough to cough. It would also probably make the potion taste better.

"Potter," Rutherage said, "You seem surprised by Lestrange's suggestion. Do you disagree?"

Lestrange shot her a glare that just dared her to argue with him. She was originally going to say that marshmallow was a good idea, but at the quelling look on his face, she bristled, then smiled slowly.

"It's not that it wouldn't work," she said sweetly, "But it would be difficult to incorporate into Wheezer's Relief without taking out the goldenseal root. With both the goldenseal root and the honey taken out, the potion would have no microbial agents at all, so you'd be treating the symptom, but not actually helping the patient get better. You could use ginger instead of honey, and still take out the goldenseal to balance the mixture, or just use sage, which would let you keep the goldenseal, while also letting you add marshmallow if you really wanted to…though marshmallow would also make the second stage of the potion more magically draining, because you'd have to add an oil of some kind to keep the red clover from sticking to the marshmallow until it had dissolved, and more oil would mean more magic to prevent the properties of the oil from affecting the firecrow feathers. That would in turn make the potion more taxing, both in terms of magic and ingredient usage, which means it would probably be too expensive for most people in need of it to afford, since the majority of people who come down with Wheezing Coughs work at low-wage, labor-intensive jobs. Really, it would be simpler if you didn't use marshmallow at all."

There was a moment of silence as all three men in the room stared at her. Harry had to fight to keep her smile polite and distant, instead of letting it slip into the smirk it wanted to become at the sight of Lestrange's patent disbelief. The older boy scowled, then turned pointedly away from her, clearing his throat at Master Rutherage expectantly.

Rutherage blinked, then smiled serenely again, "Casillas, what Healing Potions work best in tandem with spells or charms?"

And so it went. Harry was really on top of her game that morning, though she made sure to keep her expression either neutral or pleasantly engaged. The last thing she wanted was for her face to end up looking as smug or superior as Lestrange's did whenever he answered a question.

They got an hour for lunch each day, and rather than floo home and try to scrounge up something there, Harry had taken to walking down to the Dancing Phoenix to eat.

She walked into the cheerful inn and answered friendly greetings and inquiries from people who recognized her with a wave or a nod as she made her way to 'Leo's table.' It was the one closest to the central fireplace, and it was almost never completely empty. Today, Rispah was at the table, chatting animatedly with Solom and Marek and looking like a despoiled milkmaid, casually draped in creamy whites and browns.

Harry paused to bow courteously to Rispah before sliding into the seat beside her, "My Lady, how does the day find you?"

Rispah gave Harry her sauciest grin, "I could tell you, but Leo would have my ears for corrupting the youth."

Harry tried her hand at a conspiratorial leer, "He'd never hear it from me."

Even Rispah, player that she was, couldn't suppress a snort at that, "Your eyes are too narrow—you're supposed to be looking at me appraisingly, but it just looks like you're squinting to compensate for bad eyesight."

"And you should make your smile smaller," Marek put in, waving a hand vaguely to help articulate his point, "Not so wide, you know? It makes you look too juvenile. Curl the edges more."

"Like this?" Harry tried it out, widening her eyes and curling her smile upwards.

"No, no," Solom put his two knuts in, "Now you look like a crazed dictator. I thought you were good at facial expressions, kid."

Harry frowned, "So did I. Like this?" She smoothed out her lips a little, so they were quirked upwards, but not straining. She lowered her lids just a tad, and quirked an eyebrow for a dashing effect.

Rispah's own eyebrows rose, "Not bad. We'll make a rake of you yet."

Harry dropped the leer and grinned. She loved being able to practice her facial expressions where she could get honest criticism. She was already fairly proficient at subtle expressions—you had to be, to get by in Slytherin. She was also pretty good with all the variations on adorable and innocent, brought to a pinnacle in The Look, which she had perfected years ago. As time went on, however, she felt a larger repertoire of expressions was in order—ones more suited to adult features, and to 'obvious' characters.

"You really think so?" Harry put on her best 'simpering' face. She fluttered her eyelashes and tilted her face upwards, while holding her breath for good measure.

Marek laughed outright, "That's a good one!"

Rispah shook her curls, "For now, maybe—let me teach you a better one."

Rispah closed her eyes, and when she opened them they were shining at her. Rispah's carefully lined lips were poised in the most hesitant of shy smiles. She looked at Harry sidelong, her eyes swimming with pure admiration and esteem—esteem for Harry. Harry could feel herself freeze, and tried unsuccessfully to gulp. Rispah lowered her eyes secretively, and when she looked back at Harry, her smile widened slightly, as though she couldn't help herself.

Harry cleared her throat, "That's…wow, what is that?"

Rispah broke the expression and chuckled deeply, "That, is much more useful than your childish simper. That look will get you anything you want—and the guy will think it was his idea."

Marek broke in hastily, "You can't teach him that! It's a woman's look."

Rispah huffed, "So? It'll work just as well for a delicate-looking boy—no offense, Harry."

"None taken," Harry took a deep breath, summoned all her admiration for Rispah's acting ability, and funneled it into her gaze, tucking her chin a bit to appear uncertain, then smiled at the older woman with hesitant hope.

Solom guffawed, "Not bad at all! This lad's a natural, by Merlin."

Rispah eyed her critically, "Put a little more yearning into it. Like this." The rouged woman tossed her a glance that seemed almost desperate for…something.

Harry focused on not blinking for a few moments, letting moisture well up to make her eyes glisten naturally, then tried to match Rispah's look. She parted her lips and quickened her breath to seem a little more needy, then brought her eyebrows ever-so-slightly together, as though she were at once pleading and at the same time worried about being rejected.

Rispah blinked at her, "Well…yes, that's almost perfect."

Harry relaxed her face into a grin, "Thanks."

Solom gestured to a serving lad, and one came running over right away. "Get young Harry here a shepherd's pie from the kitchen," the older man said, glancing at Harry for confirmation.

"And a glass of milk," Harry added, smiling in a friendly way as she fished a galleon from her purse. She flipped the coin the way she'd often seen Marek do, and grinned as it arched into the boy's waiting hand.

"Do you even serve milk here?" Marek asked Solom, sending Harry a teasing grin.

"Milk is good for you," Harry said.

"So is ale," Marek returned, "It'll put hair on your chest."

"I've got plenty of hair on my chest," Harry said. A choking noise from behind her made her turn around to see Leo, pink-faced and half spluttering, next to a redheaded man wearing rough, Egyptian-style garb and a neck scarf pulled up over his nose to ward off the blistering afternoon sun.

"Take a seat, Highness," Solom grinned, kicking out a chair for Leo, "And Master Will, you're most welcome as well."

Leo and his friend took seats across the table, Leo saying, "What's this I hear about Harry's chest?"

"It's hairy, that's all," Harry said, ignoring the snickers that went around the table at her words, "Why, isn't yours?" Solom and Marek choked on their own spit and Rispah snorted with hastily suppressed amusement.

Leo favored her with a confident leer, "Wouldn't you like to know?"

Two can play that game, she inwardly smirked. She brought out the new leer they'd just taught her, raking her eyes across Leo's clothed chest for good measure, "Maybe I would. You offering?"

It was Leo's turn to once again choke as everyone else burst out laughing, including Harry. It was too hard to keep the expression going at the dumbfounded look on Leo's face.

"You—" Leo coughed and turned an accusing stare on Rispah, "Cousin, what have I told you about corrupting the youth?"

This only made Rispah, Marek, Solom, and Harry laugh harder, remembering what Rispah had said earlier.

"I feel as though we missed part of that joke," Leo's friend, Will, said wryly.

At the sound of his voice, muffled though it was behind the scarf, Harry stopped laughing and stared at the man. There was something…familiar about him, now that she looked.

"It probably wasn't that funny," Leo said sourly, though he grinned when his cousin shot him a vaguely apologetic smile.

"What brings you here, Master Will?" Solom asked, gesturing for another serving boy to come and take the newcomer's orders.

"Just paying my tithe," Will said. He chuckled as Solom leaned closer to hear better, then pulled down his scarf slightly so his voice wasn't so muffled, "Sorry. It's not due yet, but I won't be in the country much longer—not that I think His Highness would have trouble tracking me down, desert or no."

A tithe was another name for the taxes everyone who made a living in the Court of the Rogue had to pay to the King. As far as Harry understood, the King then used the taxes to provide things for the people in his Court who needed them.

"What sort of work do you do in the Court?" Harry asked, a suspicion forming in her mind as she traced his features mentally. His red hair was worn loose, so she couldn't see his ears, and his scarf still covered most of his lower face, but the long, freckled nose and sharp blue eyes were familiar.

Will eyed her warily, then seemed to do a double-take as he said, "Black? What are you…no, wait." He leaned toward her from across the table, searching her eyes. Harry gave nothing but mild curiosity away, even as her mind finally put a name to the face she was looking at. "Sorry, but you…look like someone I know. Not the eyes, but you're otherwise remarkably similar of face."

"You seem familiar, too," Harry said, her eyes dancing lightly across the young man's freckles.

'Will' stiffened and his face closed, "Maybe I've seen you in the alleys before."

"Yeah, that's probably it," Harry said, willing to drop it if he was. Clearly he was suspicious of her similarity to Rigel Black, and he had no doubt determined from the way she eyed his remarkably red hair that she suspected he had some connection with the Weasley Family. She hoped her message was clear: I won't dig further if you won't.

Not that she was worried if he did. She could easily tell him she was Harry Potter, and prove it, too. She just didn't want to expose her gender to the rest of her friends in the Court yet. They'd treat her like a foreigner if they knew she was a 'Lady' from the Upper Court, as they liked to call the folk who were connected to the officially recognized government in Wizarding Britain.

The shepherd's pies came out a moment later, so the awkward silence that followed Harry and Will's strange exchange was soon filled with the sounds of eating and exclaiming about how delicious the food was. It was always good, but Solom never tired of hearing it praised.

As he finished his pie, Will stood and excused himself, "See you next month, Highness. It was good seeing you all—and nice meeting you, Harry…"

He trailed off, waiting for her to supply her last name.

"It was nice to meet you, too, Will…" she answered sweetly.

William Weasley grimaced at her, but she thought it seemed relatively good-natured, so she grinned back at him in a no-hard-feelings sort of a way.

Once he'd gone, Harry asked, "So what does he do, Leo?"

"Will's a curse-breaker," Leo said, eyeing her questioningly, "He does fairly steady business hiring himself out as a curse-detector for those looking to re-sell old objects of…uncertain origin."

"He does houses, too," Marek put in, "He's not bad with wards, though he's better at deconstructing than setting new ones, I hear."

"What's got you so curious about him?" Rispah asked slyly, "He is rather handsome."

Harry colored and promptly stuck her nose into her own lunch, "He reminds me of someone I know. Where's he from?"

"That's his business," Solom said gruffly, "Where're you from?"

Harry acquiesced the point and concentrated on finishing her pie as the subject moved on to other areas of business in the Court. They didn't talk about anything terribly important around her, of course, but their Court gossip easily kept her entertained.

Soon she had to get back to the Guild for the afternoon practical. Leo offered to escort her back, but she waved him off, citing the fact that he hadn't finished his own pie as her excuse. In truth, she didn't want to be seen hanging out with Leo around the Guild. If the other two interns saw that she was close with the Aldermaster's son, they'd immediately assume she got the internship through connections, rather than merit. Harry wouldn't even be able to blame them for thinking it, as nepotism was extremely common in their world, and they had no way of knowing that Master Hurst was impressed with her potions before he knew she was his son's friend.

She was decidedly not late as she took her seat for the afternoon session, though Renaldo was already there when she arrived. She had not attempted to make conversation with him again after he brushed her off the first day, and he reciprocated her silence entirely. The only consolation to that was the fact that he didn't really speak to Lestrange, either. He seemed completely and entirely focused on learning, which Harry supposed was admirable in its own way.

When Lestrange came in, he took one look at her and sneered. "Don't think your little act this morning fooled anyone, Potter," he said as he stalked gracefully to his own station.

Harry heaved an inward sigh and counted to ten silently in her head. Un…deux…trois…eventually she gave up, realizing she wasn't going to ever calm down enough to be nice to Lestrange, and said, "Should I know what you're talking about, or do you want me to guess?"

"I watched Master Rutherage lock that door," Lestrange told her, "The only reason he didn't kick you out for forcing your way in is because it would look like sexism if the only girl intern in the last decade of this program got kicked out the first week. They'll probably let you stay long enough to shut up the feminists, then get rid of you so that those of us with real talent don't have to accommodate a child's pace."

Harry could feel her eye twitching, so she bit back the retort she wanted to make, and instead plastered an innocently curious look onto her face, "You think a child like me could overpower the Master's locking charm? It takes one and a half times the energy the caster put into a locking charm to unlock it."

"I know that," Lestrange snapped. He did that a lot, asserting that he knew things just after being told them. As though being told something twice could cause his brain to rot and die, or something. "He must have underpowered it so that you'd be able to get in—like I said, they can't get rid of you yet."

"I wonder why he'd bother locking it at all then," Harry thought out loud, "It would be more defensible to simply pretend to 'forget' to lock it, don't you think?"

"What do you know?" Lestrange said dismissively.

"A lot of things," Harry said seriously, determinedly not getting angry, "Most of them having something to do with Potions. Believe it or not, Lestrange, I do actually belong here. And I won't be going anywhere anytime soon."

She thought she saw something flicker in his eyes, but he turned to begin pulling out his brewing kit with a derisive snort, clearly deciding not to dignify her statement with an answer.

A minute or two later, Master Rutherage came in, followed by three other men, all middle-aged and all dressed in good-quality brewing robes. Harry flicked her eyes down and—yes, they all had on flame-retardant boots as well. These men were potioneers.

"Good afternoon, interns," Master Rutherage said jovially, "Today is the final day of group instruction. After this lesson, you'll each be assigned one of the Guild's Masters, who will guide your research for the rest of the program."

In other words, Harry thought, these three Masters were there to evaluate their last practical lesson, and would likely make their decisions about which intern they wanted according to what they saw.

"They've all been briefed on your respective levels of proficiency already, so don't worry if you make a mistake this afternoon—it won't affect their decisions," Master Rutherage said.

Harry glanced at the other two interns' faces. They looked as skeptical as she felt.

Rutherage flicked his wand at each of them, and a roll of flameproof parchment flew from his desk to each of their stations, "Here is the recipe for today's potion. Some of you may not have brewed this particular potion before, so I'll tell you that the trick is in following the instructions exactly. Feel free to read over the recipe several times before beginning. You have three hours to complete your potion. Begin." With that, Rutherage conjured four chairs at the front of the room, and all four of the Masters settled in to wait.

Harry unrolled her parchment and glanced over the ingredient list. She frowned, and looked over it again. These ingredients…made no internal sense.

First of all, it called for chicken feathers, which she had never seen called for in anything…ever. Pencil shavings were also on the list, as well as baking powder and…snow. It actually said 'half a liter of snow.' Harry could honestly say she had no idea why a potion would need snow in particular, since snow was frozen water, and it would melt in the cauldron almost instantly. In short, if someone had asked her to write a list of the most useless potion ingredients she could think of, half of the ones off the top of her head would be on this list.

Bemused, she looked at the title, and internally groaned. Jourdain's Amalgamation. She should have suspected, but she honestly never imagined the Guild would have them make something so completely pointless. And, she thought, looking at the three feet of small-print instructions, unnecessarily complicated.

Jourdain's Amalgamation was an infamous potion. It was said that nearly every NEWT practical for the last four decades running involved brewing at least the first stages of the potion as one of the components. The odd thing about this potion, and the reason Harry had never bothered learning to brew it, was that it didn't actually do anything. At all. It was extraordinarily complicated simply for the sake of being complicated. It was created by some sadistic individual to test how well aspiring brewers could follow directions and successfully complete a potion they were unfamiliar with.

Harry read all the way down to the end of the parchment, noting that the potion would go through several stages and changes, but would end up a bright green broth the consistency of liquid mercury when finished, and ought to smell slightly of peppermint.

She took out the materials she'd need at her station—no special equipment, thankfully, though she'd need knives of no less than four different materials depending on the ingredient she was preparing. She had a few of the ingredients called for in her own kit, but most of the ingredients were, well, useless, or at least impotent in reasonable quantities, so she'd have to collect the majority of them from the Guild's stores.

There was a storeroom connected to their lab, so Harry left her cauldron to begin warming up (after checking it for impurities and treating it with snake oil, as the recipe called for), and took her ingredient list with her to get what she needed.

Renaldo and Lestrange were already busy gathering their own ingredients by the time she got there. The storeroom wasn't very big, and they were all gathering the same ingredients, so it was quite crowded. Harry had to grit her teeth several times when Lestrange elbowed her 'accidentally' as he placed pre-packaged quantities of ingredients into his basket, but she wasn't inclined to pettiness when there was a potion to brew, so she ignored the older boy and focused on getting what she needed.

She had only collected a few of the things on her list when Renaldo fell suddenly sideways and knocked clumsily against her. Harry lost the grip on her basket, and wasn't fast enough to stop the ingredients falling to the floor. She sighed, knelt to pick them up, and glanced over with surprise when Renaldo knelt down beside her and helped her gather them. He looked upset, and Harry saw him glare angrily at Lestrange as the other boy swept out of the storeroom without a backward glance.

"Sorry," Renaldo said shortly, "Git pushed me."

"No problem," Harry said, annoyed at Lestrange all over again for being such a prick all the time.

Renaldo nodded, then stood. He seemed to hesitate, then said, "You'll have to get new lilac pollen—it's useless now, since you don't know what it came into contact with on the ground. New Madder root, too, I think."

Harry nodded, well aware of this, "You're right. Thanks." She turned to get a new packet of lilac pollen, hoping she wouldn't get in trouble for the one she'd spilled all over the storeroom floor. When she turned back, Renaldo was holding a bundle of roots in his hand, his expression still unreadable. She took the replacement Madder root with a grateful smile, which Renaldo returned half-heartedly. She wasn't offended—it was a start, at least. Maybe they'd be friends, by the time all this was over.

They gathered the rest of their ingredients in silence, and returned to the lab to begin what looked to be at least two and a half hours of intensive brewing.

Time passed quickly, as it always did while she brewed. For the first time that she could remember, however, Harry was looking forward to being done with a potion for the simple reason that brewing it was annoying.

Jourdain's Amalgamation was, frankly, a huge waste of time. Half of the ingredients she added did nothing except render inert other ingredients previously added. As she brewed, she couldn't help thinking up dozens of ways to make the process more efficient, mentally cutting out and shortening parts of the recipe that were entirely unnecessary. Then again, she supposed, if the recipe was expedient, it wouldn't be nearly so difficult.

As she added the Madder root, she couldn't help but feel like she was brewing one of her father's prank potions. Madder root was common in joke potions, because it's primary use was as a color additive. It would turn a potion bright yellow—though, because she had already added blueberry extract to the mix, this potion would actually be a very…pretty…green…

Harry's stomach dropped as her entire potion turned a vivid purple. "What?" she muttered, completely confused. How could it be purple? The Madder root was yellow. No possible combination could have made purple out of yellow. Even if she'd made a mistake before putting the root in—which she hadn't—this garish purple couldn't have happened unless the Madder root had been rendered inert by something else in the potion—or rather, not rendered inert, but corrupted to some kind of red.

Harry shook her head and pulled out her wand quickly. She cast a stasis charm on the cauldron until she could figure out what had happened—maybe she still had time to fix it. She couldn't get from purple to green directly, of course, so she'd have to first find a way to neutralize the Madder root, or perhaps extract it somehow—

Her thoughts were interrupted by a choked snort from across the room. She spared a moment to flash a glare at its emitter, and wasn't surprised to see Lestrange openly grinning in amusement at her obnoxiously purple potion. She offered him an unappreciative scowl, and turned back to her cauldron. On the way back to her own station, however, her eyes passed over Renaldo, who had the tiniest of smirks playing about his mouth as he stirred his cauldron.

Her face flushed and her hands clenched shut. She had to very carefully put her wand back into her pocket and focus on willing her magic not to overturn the jerk's cauldron into his lap. It was Renaldo who gave her the Madder root, after her own had fallen. I bet Lestrange didn't even knock him into me, she thought bitterly, recalling his half-hearted smile as he 'helped' her.

Harry took a deep breath, then narrowed her eyes at her cauldron. She was going to fix this. Her potion was going to be the best, or she hadn't studied under the greatest Potions Master of their age. She swept off to the storeroom once more, taking some comfort in the fact that they wouldn't dare sabotage her potion further while under the eyes of the Masters. She eyed the shelves around where Renaldo had been standing, trying to guess what he'd substituted for the Madder root.

There were several roots in that section (the cupboard being organized by ingredient type, not alphabetically), but there was only one other that was the same sort of off-tan color as the Madder. She eyed the Himalayan rubhada root, which was used in red dyes, and sighed. At least she knew how to get rid of it. She reached for the packets of actual Madder root, only to groan out loud as she spotted the empty shelf.

He'd taken all of the extra root, probably so that she couldn't fix it when she realized what had gone wrong. Harry scrubbed a hand through her hair, furious. Never in her life had she been the target of such low-handed tricks. Imagine, deliberately ruining someone else's potion. It made her sick.

What could she do? She didn't have Madder root in her personal kit, precisely because all it did was change the color of things. She'd have to use a different yellow-producing agent. She saw Larkspur, but as much as she'd like to use that, she couldn't. Larkspur was poisonous, and none of the ingredients in the recipe would neutralize it. No one would be drinking it as far as she knew, but it was illegal to create a poison unless sanctioned by the Guild for research purposes, not to mention just bad form. She debated Gamboge resin, but that would thicken the consistency of the potion, and cow urine (yes, really), would have a disastrous effect on the potion's smell. She looked in vain for weld, also called dyer's weed, which would produce a nice, sunny yellow with the right persuasion…but it didn't seem to be stocked in this storeroom.

Eventually, feeling the press of time passing, she decided on Indian gooseberry, which was edible, without being too aromatic. She hesitated over the Leucanthemum for a moment, but in the end grabbed a few Croton leaves instead. Both plants absorbed huge amounts of sunlight, a natural bleaching agent, but although the Leucanthemem was prettier, the Croton would be more efficient in releasing the energy it stored, in her opinion.

She hurried back to the Lab, knowing that she would have to work quickly to make up for the time she had lost. She took the potion off stasis, and turned up the heat as high as she dared, conscious that if she set it too high the integrity of other ingredients would be compromised. By heating up the potion, the red dye from the Himalayan rubhada root would unbind partially from the other ingredients. Harry de-stemmed the Croton leaves and cupped them in her left hand, pressing her right hand on top. The Croton leaves had a lot of energy in them already, but Harry needed them to be bursting with energy, to speed up the photons the Croton leaves had absorbed from the sun. She imbued the leaves until they felt warm to the touch, and dropped them in the cauldron, stirring quickly to dissolve their energy into the potion. Within a few minutes, the entire potion had turned white, as the energy from the Croton leaves bleached all color from the mixture.

She still had some of the blueberries left over, but they had been in balance with the apple seeds (for some reason that probably made no practical sense, but which Harry didn't feel confident enough to disregard), so she added more of both, and stirred until the potion was once again blue. Then she added the Indian gooseberry, and finally the potion turned the green it was supposed to be.

She was back on track.

Harry veritably flew through the rest of the potion, so fed up with the whole afternoon that she barely restrained herself when the recipe called for a five-minute wait while it simmered. She was pleased to note, as she added the last ingredient, that Renaldo had just finished his own potion as she set down her stirring rod, and by the way Lestrange was still packing up his utensils, he couldn't have finished that much ahead of her either.

She eyed her potion critically, but despite the detour she'd taken around the Madder root, it looked right. It was green, thicker than oil but thinner than honey—just the thickness of liquid mercury, and it smelt faintly of mint, as it was supposed to. The shade might have been a hair off, but she flattered herself that by looking at the finished result you'd never guess it had been purple not fifteen minutes prior.

Master Rutherage came over and peered into their cauldrons, seeing that they'd all finished. He made approving noises over Lestrange's caldron, hummed in a contented way over Renaldo's, and smiled at her as he leaned over to sniff at her own, "Got a bit lost there in the middle, did you, Miss Potter? What happened?"

"I'm afraid so, Master Rutherage," Harry said smoothly, "I'm afraid my Madder root may have been a mislabeled Himalayan rubhada."

"Ah, yes, that explains the…interesting deviation in color you experienced," Rutherage said cheerfully, "Good thinking to draw the color completely out, then reapply it. Any reason you didn't simply use actual Madder root as the recipe suggested?"

"Unfortunately, there was only enough Madder root stocked for three potions," Harry said, shrugging easily, as though she hadn't wanted to rip her hair out over the shortage earlier.

"Well it doesn't seem to have done any harm, your improvisation," Rutherage smiled again, "The potion is to specifications, so I suppose you've completed your task regardless."

"The task was to follow directions," Lestrange muttered sourly.

"How nice it must be that everything you do goes according to plan," Harry said, smiling politely at the Durmstrang boy.

"Hmm, quite right," Rutherage chuckled, "Adaptation is crucial to potion-brewing—though of course following direction is a good starting point, in best-case-scenario circumstances."

Harry barely suppressed a smirk at that. She wondered when her inner-self had become so vindictive, but it stroked something positively smug in her gut to know that Renaldo's little trick had backfired. Not only hadn't it ruined her potion, it had given her a chance to demonstrate quick-thinking and problem-solving on the spot, as well.

"Well, that's it for today's lesson," Rutherage said, waving his wand broadly and vanishing the contents of all three cauldrons, "And that concludes your group sessions, as well. From now on, you'll meet with your assigned mentor in the mornings, and do research in the afternoons. You'll need to have your topic chosen and approved by the end of next week. Experimental brewing is to be done only under your respective Master's supervision."

He stepped aside, and the three Potions Masters stood.

The first to speak was tall, poised, and classically handsome, with a straight nose and high cheekbones. His hair was long, like a pureblood lord, and Harry recognized him after a moment as Edgar Whitaker, the public face of the Guild. He looked different in color than in the black-and-white photos printed in the Guild's bi-annual press release, but Harry recognized the big, even teeth as he smiled at them.

"I am Master Whitaker," he said, his voice smooth and his demeanor friendly. He was rumored to be quite personable, and Harry could see why. "My specialty, as some of you may know, is Transformative Potions."

Who didn't know about Whitaker's work with Polyjuice? Harry thought, hoping she'd impressed him enough that he'd pick her. He would be perfect as a mentor—she already had a great interest in Polyjuice, and she'd heard he occasionally worked with Professor Snape on Wolfsbane, too.

"Mr. Lestrange," Whitaker continued pleasantly, "You're with me."

Lestrange smiled broadly, and Harry couldn't help but hate that his face was even more beautiful when he wasn't sneering.

"It's an honor to meet you, Master Whitaker," Lestrange said, and Harry couldn't even sneer at the awed tone of the other boy's voice, because she was feeling the same way just being in the same room at Whitaker.

The next Master to step forward looked vaguely familiar, but Harry didn't recognize him until he introduced himself. "Master Montmorency," he said, his voice slightly clipped, "I'll be mentoring Mr. Casillas."

Montmorency the Meticulous, some called him. He was known for his tediously extensive experiments and the slow rate at which he published his papers. That said, he never retracted anything, because he never released his findings until he was absolutely certain of their implications and shortcomings. His specialty, Harry recalled enviously, was Healing Potions. His latest research was on stasis potions, and if she remembered correctly he'd actually come up with the version of Snowhit she'd used during the Sleeping Sickness. And he was Renaldo's mentor.

Harry suppressed a sigh, and pasted an eager expression on her face as she turned toward the third Master. He surveyed her with half-lidded eyes, looking…rather bored, actually. She altered her expression into a politely neutral one, and offered her hand, "I'm Harry Potter, Master…"

He reached out a clasped her hand, but his grip was weak, his expression disinterested, "Thompson," he said lazily, "Guess you're with me."

She nodded, not sure what else to say. She'd never heard of a Master Thompson—though the name was so common, perhaps she just didn't remember reading it. He didn't offer his specialty, and she hesitated to ask, feeling embarrassed that she couldn't remember him from anywhere and not wanting to offend him.

Thompson turned his gaze to the ceiling and examined it idly for a moment, before looking back down at her, "We'll meet at ten on Monday morning. My Lab is number thirty-three. I'll leave it unlocked."

"Not that a lock would stop Potter," Lestrange sneered as he moved past them, amusement at his own joke glinting in his eyes.

Harry forced a pleased smile, "I look forward to it, Master Thompson. Good afternoon."

She gathered her things, stowed her cauldron away at her station, and walked slowly out of the Guild, ambivalence in her heart. She wasn't that upset about Renaldo switching her ingredients. It pinched a bit that the other two interns so actively disliked her, but, she reasoned, not everyone in the world had to like her. She was mildly disappointed that Lestrange had been picked by Master Whitaker, when she probably knew more about transformative potions than he did. More than that, however, she was disheartened at her own mentor. She knew it wasn't always the case, but usually when a Potions Master wasn't well-published, it meant he wasn't contributing much to the field. This was a research internship, so she had imagined she'd be mentored by someone really relevant to current research, as Montmorency and Whitaker both were.

She shook her head sharply to clear the nonsense out of it. What was she thinking? Thompson was a Potions Master, well-published or not, and to think that there was a Potions Master she couldn't learn from…well, that was sheer folly. Probably, on Monday, she would see that her anxiousness was for nothing. The bitter, suspicious part of herself that whispered poisonous thoughts—that maybe the Guild didn't think a real Potions Master should be wasted on the upstart female brewer who'd only been let into the program on Master Hurst's recommendation—well, that part was just wrong, wasn't it? It had to be.

Godric's Hollow was empty when Harry arrived home. It was late afternoon, but not quite time for her parents to get off work. James' schedule had been very reliable since he was taken off active duty, so he'd be home around five o'clock, but Lily sometimes worked late, still making up for the weeks she'd taken off for maternity leave, so Harry would probably see her around dinner.

If Harry were a better sister, she would floo over to Grimmauld Place and pick up Addy. Sirius watched her during the day, both because Addy still hadn't taken to Remus very well, and because her parents thought Sirius could use something other than his pet snakes to focus on.

She should go over and relieve Sirius of babysitting duty…but instead she changed out of her brewing robes and into her loose running clothes. Addy would only cry if Harry picked her up, and it was important that she keep her exercise regimen as regular as possible. Remus was disappointed by how much her stamina had suffered while the curfew was in effect at Hogwarts, and he wouldn't increase her weights until she could do a solid five kilometers again.

She pulled on her shoes and did a few stretches before heading out the front door. Godric's Hollow was a small village, and the Potters lived on the outskirts, so Harry usually made her run around the parameter. The sun hadn't quite set, so she didn't spare much thought to where her feet took her. As was her habit, the sounds of her breathing faded from her consciousness and her thoughts turned inward as her feet drummed on the earth.

She wanted to come up with a topic for her research with Master Thompson, but she found her mind drifting to other questions instead, like what Bill Weasley was doing earning a living in Leo's Court, when he already had a respectable job as a curse-breaker for Gringotts. That he wasn't open about his identity meant his family probably didn't know he worked for thieves in his spare time. She wondered what he needed to supplement his income for—he was young, single, and presumably debt-free if he still stayed at his parent's home on breaks from his job.

Maybe he has a gambling problem, she thought, before shaking her head in self-disgust. Who was she to speculate about someone else's secret life? If anything, she should be more concerned that he would figure out her secret life. She might have to make her trips to the Dancing Phoenix less frequent, though it would be a shame to do so. Leo and the other members of the Rogue were fun, and they let her relax. They never asked her very personal questions, never insinuated that she be grateful for their discretion, and seemed genuinely unconcerned with how secretive she was. With them, she could almost forget she had secrets. She didn't have to be Rigel Black, or even Harry Potter. She could be just Harry, a kid with a knack for potions.

Then again, 'just Harry' didn't get to study under Master Snape at Hogwarts, so she wasn't ready to run off and join the Court herself just yet. Maybe after I take my NEWT's, she told herself jokingly.

She made it home just before true dark set in, and quickly changed out of her sweaty clothes before flooing over to Grimmauld Place. The smells of dinner greeted her as she stumbled out of the grate ungracefully.

Her mother was directing her wand as it chopped vegetables adroitly, Addy strapped to a carrier on her back. Harry's little sister peered over Lily's shoulder curiously, seemingly entranced by the wand's quick movements. Sirius was squatting down in front of the oven, hands covered with pink and blue protective mitts.

"It won't bake faster just because you watch it," Remus said from his seat at the table as Harry walked in.

"It won't burn either," Sirius said absently, staring through the little oven window and wriggling slightly in anticipation, "It's almost done, I just know it!"

"Most people set timers for cakes," Lily said, her voice tired, but amused. She left off the vegetables and flicked her wand toward the cupboard to summon plates and cups for the table. Harry had thought her mother was rather lazy, growing up, as Lily tended to take any excuse to use her wand. When she got older, though, and realized that her mother had been raised among muggles, Harry decided she couldn't fault her mother for her near-constant use of magic. Lily no doubt appreciated her abilities more than wizard-raised witches would, and so included her magic as intimately as possible in her lifestyle.

"As if time has anything to do with baking," Sirius scoffed, "I am an artist, not a chemist."

"What would you know about chemistry?" James asked, setting the cutlery.

"I know it's a soulless, exacting pursuit that attracts only the most repressed and critical of individuals. Rather like potion-mak—" Sirius broke off in a cough as he caught sight of Harry's reflection in the oven door, "Harry! We were just talking about you—no, I mean, we were talking about…um…"

"The soulless and repressed nature of those pitiful wraiths who are drawn to become potioneers?" Harry suggested wryly. She bent down next to Sirius to peek in the over, "Chocolate? Or is it just burnt?"

"It's not burnt!" Sirius said, though he did peer worriedly through the window before turning back with an apologetic smile, "And I didn't mean you, of course. Just…certain other people who become greasy old Potions Masters because they can't find a way to actually participate in social reality."

"Professor Snape is your age, Dad," Archie said cheekily from where he was mixing Addy's bottle, "But I guess you are kind of old now that I think about it."

And he's probably improved more lives with his 'greasy' research than Sirius has giving prank toys to children at St. Mungo's, Harry thought uncharitably. She pursed her lips, immediately repentant. Sirius brought a lot of joy to the world, between the Marauder line and his volunteer work, not to mention the annual donations he made to a number of worthy causes. Harry didn't know where all these petty thoughts were coming from that evening, but suspected she was simply in a bad mood because of her afternoon at the Guild.

Sirius must have mistaken her pursed lips for disapproval of his comments rather than disappointment in herself, as he said, "Sorry, Harry, if I offended you. I was only joking."

Harry smiled unconcernedly, "I know, Uncle Sirius. I'm not cross with you, just tired—long afternoon, you know."

"So forgiving," Sirius grinned, ruffling her hair with an oven-mitt-clad hand, "Why can't you be more like Harry, Archie?"

Archie half-choked on a laugh, "I honestly don't think I could be more like Harry if I tried. We're practically twins, aren't we Harry?"

"Separated at birth, no doubt," Harry agreed, "It's the only explanation for you turning out so much cooler than Sirius—he must have snatched you from my mother's arms when he realized what amazing kids his friends were blessed with."

"Oi!" Sirius protested, "Archie is so not cooler than me."

"I've been meaning to tell you, Dad," Archie said mournfully, "But we all voted, and…I am definitely cooler than you."

"Impossible!" Sirius declared, tossing his head proudly even as he finally retrieved the cake from the oven.

"It was almost unanimous," Remus chimed in.

"The only vote in your favor was Lily's vote," James agreed apologetically, "And we counted her vote in Archie's favor simply because of how wildly off-mark her cool-detector generally is."

It was Lily's turn to gasp with affected dismay, "My cool-detector is just fine. I think you're cool, Darling."

"Exactly," Remus chuckled softly.

James threw a playful scowl at Remus and added, "You thought Snape was cool when you were younger, too."

"Master Snape is cool," Harry said automatically.

Sirius and James both turned disbelieving eyes on her, "Snape? Cool? That is just…wrong."

"How would you know, anyway?" James added, "Anyone can seem cool on paper. In real life, he's decidedly not."

Harry turned raised eyebrows on Archie, who froze for a moment, before shrugging sheepishly. "Uh, Professor Snape definitely has a…presence…" Archie fumbled, "I mean, he's sort of…intimidating, actually. But it's kind of cool…the way his cloak swishes when he turns…"

Harry resisted the urge to smack her own forehead as Archie somehow managed to compile the descriptions of Snape she'd given him into a litany that made him sound like a besotted idiot.

Sirius was staring with abject horror, "No…Archie, no, you can't think Snape is cooler than me. You just can't…." he trailed off into indistinguishable mutters of denial.

"I think you broke him," James said, looking disturbed, "Maybe we should all pretend you didn't say that, Archie."

"He's my Head of House," Archie said, flushing, "I can't pretend to hold him in contempt."

"Professional respect is one thing," Sirius said, snapping out of his daze with a vaguely ill expression on his face, "Personal admiration…is just so unnecessary. It's Snape."

"That's not an argument in and of itself, you know," Harry said, annoyed enough to speak up in Snape's defense, "Your dislike of the man has skewed your perception of him greatly, Uncle Sirius."

Sirius grimaced, "That doesn't really bother me, since I know his opinion of me suffers the same distortion."

Harry shrugged, consenting that point easily enough, "I guess neither one of you is better than the other, then."

"Salad's done," Lily broke in cheerfully, flapping her hands toward the table, "Let's eat."

Everyone grasped the change of subject readily, and exuberant praise and thanks for the meal were given and received until a general air of light-hearted gaiety returned to the kitchen.

It was only her cranky mood that made her wonder why her family was so good at ignoring the uncomfortable truths and focusing on the inane ones.

When they were clearing away the dishes, Sirius said, suddenly, "Archie, I forgot to tell you, but you got a letter today."

Archie left off teasing Addy with her pacifier and cocked his head curiously, "Who from?"

"Malfoys," Sirius said, half grimacing.

"Oh," Archie dug through the pile of mail on the counter and pulled out the square, off-white envelope addressed to him, "Looks more like an invitation."

"Another one of those summer parties the Malfoys had last year?" Harry asked with affected innocent.

Archie seized on the reminder, "No doubt Draco's birthday party as well." He ripped it open and scanned the embossed invitation briefly, "Cordially invited…hmm…it's this weekend—tomorrow! Dad, when you said I got a letter today, did you mean you just bothered checking the mail today? How long has this been sitting here?"

Sirius shrugged apologetically, "I don't check the mail often, so…two weeks?"

Archie laughed, but Harry frowned, "Will you have time to get Draco's present by tomorrow morning?"

"I'll go to Diagon Alley to get something before the party," Archie said.

"I'll tag along," Harry said nonchalantly, "I have a few errands to run tomorrow in the Alley anyway."

Archie agreed distractedly, still looking at the invitation with unease, "Dad…you're on here, too."

"What?" Sirius wasn't the only one who looked confused, "Let me see." He bent over Archie's outstretched hand, "Huh. So I am."

"Why's your name after mine?" Archie asked, frowning, "You're the Head of the Family."

Sirius shrugged, "Maybe they think if they make you the primary attendee and me the secondary, I'll disregard the Split and go. Or it might just be that your connection to Draco is stronger than my ties to the Malfoys, despite Narcissa's marriage, and decided to only invite me through proxy."

"Will you go?" Harry asked, trying to hide her unease at the idea.

"I…" Sirius trailed off, thinking, "The New Year's Gala was one thing. That was a political event…sort of. This, though…" he grimaced, "James, what do you think?"

James lapsed into thought, running a hand through his hair pensively, "It would be a stretch, but you could claim you went as a chaperone to Archie, not a real guest. If anyone asks. Do you want to go?"

Sirius shrugged uncomfortably, "I don't like Archie going alone."

Harry noticed he didn't really answer the question.

Remus spoke up tentatively, "Do you think the Split is still all that in effect? It's been so many years…principles are important, of course, but it's also your family, Sirius. This situation has always been harder on you than on others. Maybe you should reclaim your place in society."

"I never really had a place," Sirius said weakly.

"Exactly," Lily spoke up, "Sirius, I know you've chosen Light politics, but perhaps its time to become socially Neutral. For Archie's sake, at least. He'll be attending more and more of these gatherings as he grows older, with the friends he's made in school being who they are. It might be better if you had a bit of leeway in guiding him through society. You don't have to sympathize with Dark politics, of course."

"Please don't join the Cow Party, Dad," Archie begged comically.

Sirius barked out a laugh, "They wish! Once a Marauder, always a Marauder."

No one said anything about Peter 'wormtail' Pettigrew.

"Okay…I'll do it," Sirius said, more seriously. Then he grimaced, "Does this mean I have to get Lucius' whelp a birthday present?"

Archie rolled his eyes, "Yes, Dad, you have to get my friend a birthday gift if you crash his party."

"I was invited."

"After me," Archie smirked, "Guess I should be Head of the Black Family, seeing as I'm obviously more important than you."

"Don't forget cooler, too," Harry put in, smiling despite the sinking feeling in her chest. How was she going to pull this off?

"This new generation is a complete wash," Sirius complained.

"Whose fault would that be?" Remus asked, smiling pleasantly.

"Lily's, no doubt," Sirius sniffed.

"See if I let you watch Addy next week," Lily sniffed back.

"Who else would watch her? Remus?" Sirius laughed.

"I think she's starting to like me," Remus said hopefully, reaching out to pat Addy on the head gingerly. The infant's bottom lip trembled, and Remus retracted his hand quickly. "Or not," he muttered.

"And Harry can't watch her, with that Guild thing all day," Sirius said smugly, "Face it, I'm your best option."

Lily grumbled something about seeing if Alice Longbottom was available, and James turned curious eyes on Harry. "How is that going, by the way?"

Harry shrugged, "I'm learning a lot. I got assigned a mentor today from the Guild, and he's going to help me with me research starting next week."

"You're doing original research?" Lily frowned, "Is it safe?"

Harry hid a smile at her mother's naiveté. She'd hate to think what her parents would say if they knew Harry had already created—and tested—potions on herself. "Perfectly safe, Mum. Master Thompson will oversee any experimental stages."

"No one's better equipped than the Guild, Lily," Remus said reassuringly.

"Yes, you're right. Still, be careful, Harry," Lily said worriedly, "I think you're too much like your father, sometimes, and I've heard what he got into at your age."

Harry smiled reassuringly, but inwardly mused that no matter how much trouble James got into as a teen, it would never amount to what she had gotten herself into in the last two years.

That evening, Harry followed Archie up to his room. She needed to get back to her lab to work on Draco's present, but strategizing tomorrow's subterfuge was more important.

Archie shifted great, heavy tombs on Healing off of his bedspread to make room for them to sit. Harry knew many would be surprised by Archie's studiousness, but his carefree, often facetious nature was only the cheerful veneer that masked a deep, conscientious empathy for the world, and a sharp, engaging intellect. He was much like his father in that respect: he played the part of the jester willingly, finding laughter in any situation, but behind his smile lived an acute awareness of how sober reality could really be.

"So," Archie said, plopping down and hugging a pillow to his chest with the kind of ingénue affect that Harry couldn't help but envy. "What are we going to do about this?"

Harry took a seat beside him, wondering the same thing.

"We don't look exactly the same anymore," Archie said, thinking out loud, "It's close, but I think our actual bodies are starting to differ too much biologically—I'm growing to look more masculine, and you're starting to look more feminine. So my guess is the last dose of modified Polyjuice couldn't blend our features exactly without leaning slightly in the direction of the chosen biological sex."

Harry had been thinking the same thing. She and Archie were both androgynous and slightly awkward looking after the most recent dose of Polyjuice, but Archie had a masculine edge to his features that the Polyjuice couldn't replicate in her unless she changed herself into an actual boy.

Harry nodded, "There is a slight difference in our features now. The question is, is the difference noticeable enough that Sirius would recognize me as not you if you weren't there for the comparison? Could I style my hair in a new way and make him think any difference was due to something superficial like that?"

"As long as you give him no reason to look for deception…I don't think he'll notice," Archie said, "The change in our features is only a few weeks old, so he's probably not completely used to it yet." He didn't sound completely confident, but he nodded, as though trying to convince himself, "I have new robes that are cut in a different style than I usually wear. Put those on, comb your hair back from your face, and maybe put in a bit of product to change the texture slightly. Dad'll be preoccupied with those changes, and won't notice other changes."

Harry traced Archie's features thoughtfully, "It's our jaws that really differ, I think. Our shoulders, too—yours are a bit wider now. I could change my posture to make up for it—maybe put my shoulders back and lift my chin a bit when I'm with Sirius."

"Won't your friends from school think that's weird?" Archie said critically, "Rigel's personality is rather reserved from what you've said."

"They'll notice, but they're already under the impression that I act 'differently' around Sirius to fulfill some sort of perfect-son expectation they think he's projected onto me," Harry said, "The change in my behavior will be 'in-character' for Rigel, especially if I 'slip' and make it clear that I am changing my behavior for Sirius' benefit. Sirius is the one I have to fool. He can't know that I'm changing my behavior, because you wouldn't do that around him."

Archie grimaced, "I don't know whether to be impressed by us or disappointed in the rest of the world. It just shouldn't be this easy to lie to everyone."

Harry raised an eyebrow, "You think this is easy?"

"Well, not easy," Archie cast about for the right word, "It's just eerily effective. We create these personas that account for everything that goes wrong and seamlessly integrate all the parts of our stories that overlap—I keep expecting to be caught out, but it's the simplest thing to let other people rationalize away any contradictions or holes they see."

"I know what you mean," Harry admitted quietly, "Sometimes I come up with an answer to one of my friends' questions that not only satisfies their curiosity about that, but also answers other questions I didn't even know they had—as if they were looking for a reason to have their suspicions allayed."

"Maybe they don't want to admit you're doing anything wrong," Archie said, "They're your friends, and people all like to think they have good taste or judgment, even when it comes to other people. Maybe they value your friendship so much that they explain away some of the inconsistencies for you, because they know that maintaining the illusion is good for you and their relationship with you. Win-win."

"Those psychology classes really took, Arch," Harry said, grinning slightly, "But…you might be right. Sometimes when Draco questions something I do, he has this worried look on his face—underneath his angry, disappointed look, I mean. When I come up with a good enough explanation, he seems relieved. Maybe part of it is he's relieved there's not a more sinister explanation, but part of it could also be that he doesn't want to deal with the consequences of realizing the extent of my lies."

Archie hummed thoughtfully, "We can use that…but it's going to make us feel more guilty."

"I'm not sure I could feel more guilty," Harry said, sighing, "I try to open their eyes to my unsuitability as a friend as much as is safe, but usually my friends just ignore the veiled warnings, or get offended by them, as if I'm insinuating that they can't handle my friendship, when I'm only trying to explain that I'm unworthy of it."

"You're not unworthy of friendship, Harry," Archie said sharply.

"I didn't mean it like that," Harry said, "I'm quite comfortable with our friendship, Archie. You have to admit that it's hard to defend a friendship built on lies, though. Don't you feel like that with Hermione?"

"Not really," Archie said seriously, "My friendship with Hermione isn't dependent on details like what my name is. We're friends because of our shared interests, experiences, and the emotional work we've put into our time together. Lies can't destabilize a friendship like ours, because what I'm lying about isn't related to the reasons we're friends."

Harry chewed on that for a moment, "Maybe you're right." Then again, the lies she spun were a bit more complicated than the ones Archie lived with. He wasn't secretly a girl, after all.

"Enough moralizing!" Archie said suddenly, "You need to get some sleep. We'll switch places in Diagon tomorrow, and if anyone asks you're going book shopping—that's what I'll do until the party's over."

"What if Sirius wants to come to Diagon with you tomorrow?" Harry asked, frowning.

"Oh," Archie bit his cheek, "Maybe…can we switch now?"

"I have to go make Draco a birthday present," Harry said, shaking her head. "Tomorrow morning? I'll come over early, right after breakfast, and we'll 'study Healing' for a couple of hours before the party. That way Sirius and I can floo to the Malfoys' together."

"What will you say about the present, then?" Archie pointed out.

"I'll say Harry was kind enough to help me out last night, since I confessed I didn't know what to get Draco. In fact…come home with me now, so we can 'work on it together' in my lab," Harry suggested.

Archie agreed, and they explained the circumstances to Sirius, who shrugged and told Archie to be home before the late night floo wards went up.

Archie took a stool and watched curiously while Harry set up a standard pewter cauldron.

"So what are you making?" Archie asked.

Harry, already in brewing mode, twitched slightly at the question, but she said, honestly, "No idea."

Archie laughed, "What did you get him last year again?"

"A potion that would let him fly temporarily," Harry answered, recalling her success at incorporating formed magic into an already-complete potion the year before.

"What, really?" Archie looked interested, "Cool. You could do that again. I'd like to see you brew it."

Harry smirked wryly, "Give a repeat gift to the great Draco Malfoy? He'd never forgive me the lack of originality, not to mention the slight. He would think I didn't put much thought into it, and that would hurt his pride and his feelings."

Archie blinked, "Your friends are a lot of work. Hermione would love it if I got her a book for every occasion."

"It's part of his charm," Harry said absently. What could she brew for Draco? He didn't have any ailments, so he didn't need healing potions. She refused to brew anything dangerous, especially if Sirius was there to witness the gift.

"Think out loud," Archie said, "It's boring just watching you think."

Harry huffed, but complied, "It has to be something he can't buy at the local apothecary. Something he'd value as unique or useful." She was struck by a sudden thought. "Archie—you're not great at potions."

Archie raised his eyebrows, saying, "Gee, thanks, cuz. I'll have you know your scar-fading technique isn't all that elegant, either."

Harry shook her head, "I mean, you'd know better than I what kind of potions are interesting to someone who can't just brew them whenever she wants. If you could have any potion, what would it be?"

"The Potentialis Potion," Archie said at once, "Hermione told me about it last semester. She wanted to brew it for herself, but the Potions Master at AIM wouldn't give her extracurricular lab time. I actually had to talk her out of brewing it illegally in an unused bathroom stall."

Harry cocked her head, "The Potentialis Potion? I could brew that for you, if you want."

"Brew it for Draco," Archie said, "You can't get it in an apothecary, right?"

Harry nodded. It was a good idea. A really good idea, actually. The Potentialis Potion revealed a person's magical potential. When drunk, it pulled at a wizard's magic, forcing it to manifest in the ways it was most suited to. Generally drunk while the wizard was by himself, so the magic couldn't hurt anyone else when it manifested, the Potentialis Potion could reveal a wizard's Light/Dark affinity, elemental nature, and even the kinds of magic they were best suited to, like transformative magic, locomotion magic, mental or emotional magic, and so on. It had even been known to reveal magical gifts, like Parseltongue. Also, it normally wasn't recommended to children under thirteen, because their cores might not be developed enough to respond to the potion properly.

"It's very difficult to brew," Harry said thoughtfully, "And the ingredients needed are nothing to sniff at, but the real problem is it has to be imbued with the person's essence in order to be keyed to their use only. That's why you can't get it in shops—it has to be custom-made every time." Unlike Polyjuice, where you could add the essence after it was completed, the Potentialis Potion required the essence of the target to be added during the brewing process.

"Don't suppose you have 'essence of Draco' lying about," Archie said jokingly.

Harry hummed, "Actually…"

"What?!" Archie choked on a laugh, "You…you can't be serious."

Harry shrugged her shoulders defensively, and went to retrieve her travel potions kit, the one she used at Hogwarts. "You never know when something might come in handy," she muttered. She reached into one of the magically expanded compartments and pulled out a single, blonde hair.

Archie shook his head, "You seriously stole you friend's hair knowing you might use it in a potion one day?"

"I didn't steal it," Harry retorted, "I found it. Not my fault he left it on my pillow." Archie choked, but Harry ignored him, "I'm always telling people to be more careful about where they shed their essence, but no one ever listens to me."

"Because you're the only one who actually sees discarded fingernails as an opportunity for future potion endeavors," Archie chuckled, "That's really too much, Harry. What are you going to say when he asks where you got his essence for the potion?"

"I'll say 'I told you so,' and maybe he'll be more careful in the future," Harry sniffed, "It's a good life lesson."

Archie just laughed, "Whatever you say, Harry. Do you have all the ingredients you need, then?"

"I think so," Harry began moving about her lab stores, plucking things from shelves and drawers and arranging them in order of anticipated use on one of the lab stations. She collected everything she could remember, then moved over to the bookcases on the far wall where she kept reference materials, "I'm pretty sure Graham has a good recipe somewhere in Occasional Potions…"

It took nearly two and a half hours to brew the Potentialis Potion. The recipe had at least five distinct stages, and she imbued more magic into it than was required for three Snowhit batches, but it looked perfect by the time it was finished. Archie was yawning tiredly, but even he commented on how well the final product matched the description in the book.

Harry bottled the correct amount for a single dose, and Evanescoed the rest. It would be useless to anyone who wasn't Draco, and he didn't need more than a single dose to figure out his magic.

"I hope Master Snape didn't think to brew this for Draco," she said, frowning at the little bottle.

"You worry too much," Archie said tiredly, taking the sample from her hand carefully, "I'll see you tomorrow morning. Night."

"Thanks for staying, Arch," Harry said apologetically.

"Anything for you, Harry—or, for me, I guess," Archie chuckled, "All for the ruse, after all."

All for the ruse indeed, Harry thought, clearing and clearing her workstation. How far were they willing to go?

She shook her head, the answer obvious. As far as necessary.

Chapter 3

The Malfoy gardens were even more breathtaking than Rigel remembered them. Even Sirius, who had grown up amidst the splendor and decadence of pureblood high society, was moved to whistling as they descended the white stone patio to deposit their packages on the gift table. Sirius' was wrapped in beautiful silver, while Rigel had gone for the more understated green. She didn't know what Sirius' gift was, since he was being remarkably restrained in bragging about it, which meant it was probably some kind of prank. She just hoped it didn't embarrass Draco.

It was quite warm that Saturday, but a summer breeze swept through the yard with such consistency that it must have been spell-induced, and there seemed to be no shortage of iced beverages being passed around by beautiful serving girls. Rigel eyed one of them, noticed the way her fern-green eyes sparkled with an inhuman shine, and guessed they were nymphs, hired for the occasion.

Sirius caught her speculative glance, and nudged her, grinning, "Bit out of your league, Arch, unless you've got veela in you somewhere."

"Is that an impossibility?" Rigel let one of her eyebrows raise, "Don't tell me there was a pot our ancestors didn't dip their hands into—genetically speaking."

Sirius laughed lowly, "No telling. Still, no nymphs until you're sixteen, eh? They'll chew a boy up and spit him out a man."

Rigel fought a grimace, "I'm not sure Nymph Regurgitation is how I imagined that particular transition occurring."

Sirius nodded sagely, "I did figure you more for a were-cat type of guy."

"I was thinking valkyrie," Rigel said dryly.

Her uncle winced dramatically, "You're a better man than I, then."

"Surely that was never up for debate," another voice broke in.

Regulus Black stood there, looking as though something utterly mad was unfolding before him.

Sirius summoned up a grin, "Reggie! How nice to…well, you're here."

Regulus ignored his older brother's antics, "What are you doing here, Sirius? This is a private event."

"Haven't you heard?" Sirius said innocently, clearly enjoying himself, "I'm Neutral now. I can go to all sorts of private events if I want. I may even come to your birthday party this year."

"I haven't had a birthday party since I came of age," Regulus said absently, still eyeing Sirius suspiciously.

"That explains so much," Sirius said sadly, "I'll invite you to mine next year, how's that? It'll be space-themed, just like when we were kids."

Regulus didn't seem to relish the reminder of his childhood, for he sent Sirius a long-suffering expression and said, "Are you really Neutral? Now there's no getting away from you, I suppose."

Sirius smiled almost fondly, "Admit it, you missed me."

"Like a toothache," Regulus drawled.

Rigel didn't think Regulus' heart was really in his show of distain. Maybe the many years apart had thinned whatever bad blood ran between the two brothers, or maybe the Black family had always been somewhat…dysfunctional.

"Your Heir is looking well turned-out, at least," Regulus said, skimming Rigel's (well, Archie's) robes with a discriminating eye. The robes she wore were high-collared, with tapered sleeves. She thought they made her look more elongated than gangly, disguising her awkward elbows and knees with longer, more forgiving lines. Then again, what did she know about fashion? Perhaps she simply looked like a proper Heir was meant to, prudish and stifled.

"You look well also, Uncle," Rigel said, smiling politely, "Have you been here long?"

"I haven't made my rounds yet, if that's what you're angling," Regulus said, raising an eyebrow.

"My son doesn't angle," Sirius said stoutly, placing a hand on Rigel's shoulder, "If he wants to ask you something, he'll just ask it."

"I certainly hope that isn't the case," Regulus sighed, "Sirius, just because you've managed to live with your head in the sand doesn't mean your Heir won't need to learn politics eventually. You must begin preparing him now, or the family name will suffer for it later when he makes a fool out of himself."

Sirius' face flushed with anger, and Rigel hastily cut into the conversation, "Dad's already taught me all I need to know, Uncle. Please, don't trouble yourself worrying over our good name."

"He has, has he?" Regulus positively smirked, "Let's just see about that."

Before either Sirius or Rigel could protest, Regulus cast a proprietary hand around Rigel's shoulder and pulled her away from Sirius' grasp. Sirius had no choice but to follow swiftly as Regulus steered her toward a nearby group of adults making polite conversation.

At their approach, conversation paused for a moment, and the small circle of people, five at the most, parted politely to accommodate them. Most of them were quite venerable, looking to be at least a generation older than Sirius and Regulus, but that didn't stop one of the old witches from tittering girlishly when Sirius bowed gallantly over her hand.

"Abigail, it's been too long," Sirius said, grinning rakishly at the tiny crone.

She flapped a gloved hand at Sirius, patting at her white-grey hair with the other, "Who let a rascal like you into a well-to-do place like this?"

Sirius laughed appreciatively, waggling his brows, "You've got me, madam—I snuck in."

The old woman laughed gaily, "Not even you would be so audacious as to gate crash a Malfoy party."

"Anything to see your lovely face, Abigail," Sirius insisted.

The others in the group were chuckling softly now, and Rigel could only admire how good Sirius was at this. He acted out his own reputation as well as any of the players she'd met in the Rogue could have.

"And Regulus!" the woman, Abigail, clasped Regulus' hands between her own, "What a pleasant surprise—a rare treat to see you at one of these summer gatherings, isn't it?"

Regulus inclined his head in a way that was both charming and self-deprecating, "Precisely why I accepted this year. It never does to become predictable, Madam Burke."

As Madam Burke rewarded Regulus' ironic wit with another small titter, Rigel wondered if suaveness ran in the Black family, and hoped she could keep up. Then those sharp old eyes turned on Rigel, and she fought to keep from gulping. This lady was intimidating, never mind that she could be Rigel's great-grandmother.

"And who've we here, eh?" she peered at Rigel from approximately eye-level, though Rigel was a tad bit taller, "This wouldn't be your Heir, Sirius?"

"Sharp as ever, Abigail," Sirius said, smiling proudly, "This is my son, Arcturus Rigel Black. Rigel, may I present Madam Abigail Burke?"

Rigel stepped forward to bow deeply over her gloved appendage, and when she rose, said, "It's a pleasure to meet a lady who has so enchanted my father and uncle. Any relation to one Horace Burke, Madam?"

Madam Burke blinked bright eyes at Rigel, and smiled warmly, "My nephew, in fact. Have you made his acquaintance, Mr. Black?"

"Just Rigel, please," Rigel said with a coaxing smile, "Being on such distant terms with a lady of your charms would wound me to the quick. I have not had the pleasure of meeting Mr. Burke, myself, but I hear excellent things about his owl-order business, particularly the potions side of it."

Madam Burke sighed exasperatedly, "He'll be glad to have it known as such, but when is he going to settle down and give me some grad-nieces? Daughters, that's what a man like Horace needs, not rushing after that business of his day in and day out."

"You think everyone needs daughters, Abby," another woman in the circle said, "Some of us do find fulfillment in our work, you know."

"Yes, yes, Suzie," Madam Burke said, "But you can't deny that having daughters helps."

"Perhaps that's where I've gone wrong," Sirius said, gazing at Rigel speculatively.

Playing her part, Rigel affected an expression of veiled hurt, "I told you I would take that gender-changing potion if you really wanted me to, Dad."

She thought she heard a muffled choke from Regulus, but couldn't be sure as the others in their little circle has all burst into startled laughter just then. Sirius positively beamed at her, which Rigel took to mean she was doing well in passing off as Archie.

After a few minutes more of meaningless chatter, they politely excused themselves and Sirius turned to Regulus with a triumphant grin, "How about those apples, brother mine?"

Regulus merely shrugged delicately, "He can charm a few old biddies, I'll give you that—but what about serious politics?"

Sirius scowled, "Enough of these games, Regulus, my son is not a trick pony."

"Are you saying you think I don't have any other tricks, Dad?" Rigel smiled cheekily, "I think I'm offended."

"Your Heir isn't complaining," Regulus said silkily, reminding Rigel of Master Snape for a moment, "Don't be so uptight, Sirius."

Sirius winced, but could say nothing to that without breaking character entirely, and so conceded that round to his brother, saying, "Lead on, then. Perhaps when you see my son's social competence for yourself, you'll be satisfied that I've not run our House into ruin quite yet."

That was about what Rigel had been thinking, actually. Regulus obviously wanted to prove something, so why not let him try and prove it? She knew she could act as long as she needed to—she did it all day every day anyway, just in different ways. Once he had what he was looking for, he would leave them to enjoy the party, and she could find her friends.

The next group of people Regulus led them to was a little more mixed—Rigel recognized Mr. and Mrs. Parkinson right away, though Pansy was not with them. There was also an elderly wizard who looked vaguely familiar, standing next to an equally elderly witch who smiled with reserved friendliness at Rigel as they approached. She started wracking her brain to recall if she'd met either of them before—and whether it was as Rigel or Harry—but still hadn't placed them when Sirius gestured her forward to be introduced.

"Some of you already know my Heir, Rigel," Sirius said, nodding at the Parkinsons in acknowledgment of their daughter's friendship with Rigel.

"It has been too long, Rigel," Rose Parkinson said, leaning in to embrace Rigel's shoulders lightly. It was the greeting one might give a close friend, and Rigel was honored to be considered so well by her best friend's mother. "My, how you've grown!"

"The better to admire your beauty, my lady," Rigel said easily, "Your eyes are surely most beautiful when viewed from an equal level."

"Then I trust you'll take care not to grow any taller," Rose said conspiratorially.

"I will certainly put effort toward such an endeavor," Rigel assured her solemnly, "And how does the summer air find you, Mr. Parkinson?"

Mr. Parkinson seemed to consider the question carefully before responding, with a tilt of his head that caused his glasses to catch the sunlight, "Quite invigorated, thank you, Rigel." Rigel tried not to blink at the use of her first name, reminding herself that it was to be expected, with her 'father' and 'uncle' there to make 'Mr. Black' rather confusing. "Pansy will be glad to see you here—she always entertains the idea that you'll disappear over the summer and never be heard from again, for some reason."

Rigel tried to hide her unease at that ominous statement, "I can't imagine why. I would never miss Draco's birthday party, after all. I will reassure her of my continued existence when I see her, however."

"You pay commendable attention to your friendships, Young Mr. Black," the familiar-looking witch said approvingly, "I knew we had the right impression of you last summer."

Rigel suddenly placed her—it was Griselda Marchbanks, who she had indeed met last year at the Malfoys' party. That meant the wizard next to her was Tiberius Ogden, the man who had almost ingested Nimue-laced nightshade. She had a fleeting hope that they wouldn't mention the incident, but—

"Dreadful circumstances, of course," Ogden said, looking a bit pale at the memory, "But you certainly did make an impression."

"Elder Marchbanks, Elder Ogden," Rigel bowed to them, "You are too kind to me, as always. I'm surprised you still remember such a little thing."

She could feel Sirius' gaze burning the side of her head, but she assumed a mildly sheepish expression and pretended ignorance to his curiosity.

"Little thing indeed!" Ogden said, huffing, "Never met a more modest Heir, Lord Black. You've certainly done well by him."

Sirius accepted the compliment gracefully, if a tad uncertainly. She was certain Archie had never told Sirius about the poison attempt, though Rigel thought she had confided the circumstances to Archie at some point, just in case it ever came up.

"There are many of us with cause to be proud," Marchbanks nodded imperiously, "This next generation is turning out quite handsomely."

"We know whom to thank," Rigel said, glancing up at Sirius warmly. She could see the way the others in the circle softened at the obvious affection between father and son, and even Regulus, who Rigel suspected recognized the ploy easily, looked approving when Rigel glanced at him.

When that group broke up a little later, Sirius silently raised an eyebrow in Regulus' direction.

Regulus looked down at Rigel, his delicate face impassive, "He isn't a total loss, at least."

Rigel gave Regulus her best fake-smile, and was rewarded when his right eyelid twitched slightly in annoyance. She let her smile melt into a more natural smirk, and said, "Never doubt a Black, Uncle."

"Couldn't have said it better myself!" Sirius crowed, clasping her shoulder with true affection. His face took on a more serious cast as he said, "That was a bit cryptic, though. I don't recall you mentioning making nice with two Wizengamot elders. What's this 'impression' you gave them, Arch?"

Rigel hesitated, looking between Sirius and her 'uncle,' both of whom stepped closer in response to her furtiveness, "It wasn't a big deal, really."

She could feel her expression slipping, but was too busy figuring out how to explain without making Sirius upset or worried in any way to hold onto her guile, "I did a favor for Mr. Ogden—not a political favor, I mean, it just sort of…happened."

"Spit it out, boy," Regulus snapped.

He sounded so much like Snape in that moment that Rigel blurted, "They kind of owemealifedebt."

Sirius blinked, "What?"

"I'm sorry," Rigel said, frowning apologetically, "I know you told me not to make friends with any politicians, and I wasn't, but—there was poison—and—"

"Two elders of the Wizengamot owe you a life debt?" Regulus looked like he didn't know whether to laugh or to growl, "How on earth did such a thing come to be?"

Rigel sighed, and spilled the whole story, from noticing the Nimue's Breath to Madam Marchbanks' insistence that she take full share in the debt. Since Marchbanks and Ogden obviously weren't keeping it to themselves, it would probably be common knowledge sooner or later. Better for Sirius to hear it from her now, when she could explain.

"It's not a big deal, though," Rigel assured them, "I tried to talk them out of it—"

"You did what?" Regulus bit out.

"—but they were insistent!"

Sirius just shook his head wonderingly, "First the Malfoys, now a couple of Wizengamot representatives…these life debts are getting out of hand, don't you think?" It was a weak joke, and no one laughed.

Regulus inhaled sharply, "The Malfoys owe such a debt to you as well?"

Rigel nodded cautiously, "I saved their son from the sleeping sickness."

Regulus nodded slowly, as though remembering something he'd heard but not really paid attention to before. "Well," he said, visibly gathering himself, "Well. It seems your son does know something about politics, Sirius. Though it will be a wonder if there's anything left of politics when he's finished," he added under his breath. Rigel wondered when he'd start addressing her directly, instead of indirectly, but decided to be glad he'd found what he was looking for, at least.

"That's my boy," Sirius said, though his smile was a bit forced, "I'm going to get a drink. Ar—I mean, Rigel, will you be all right if I—"

"I'll go find my friends," Rigel said quickly, "Catch you later, Dad. It was nice to see you again, Uncle."

Regulus nodded to both of them, and all three went their separate ways, Sirius to flag down a moss-eyed nymph, Regulus to rub elbows with more of his acquaintances, and Rigel to search the gardens for a tell-tale splash of purest blonde.

She weaved through the crowd slowly, knowing that moving at any pace less than completely dignified would only draw attention to her in a gathering like this. Several nymphs tried to push sparkly drinks on her, but Rigel refused them all politely. Eventually, she found her friends in the same place they'd been last year—the gazebo.

"Rigel!" Draco jumped up from his seat in the center of the group and came to stand before her, grinning widely, "You came."

He seemed to be holding himself back from hugging her, so she smiled in return and put a hand on his shoulder in genuine affection, "Of course I did. Happy Birthday, Draco. Thirteen is an auspicious year."

Draco smirked, "That's what I told my father when he said I to choose between a new racing broom and a customized wand-holster."

"Did it work?" Theo asked with amusement.

"You'll have to watch me open my presents to find out," Draco said, though his eyes were on Rigel as he said it.

Rigel resisted the urge to duck her head guiltily, since she had missed his gift-opening the year before. "It's embarrassing to watch someone open your own gift," she said.

Pansy smiled teasingly, "Only you think so, Rigel. To everyone else it's a perfectly gratifying experience."

Rigel sat next to Pansy with a tilting smile of her own, "Gratification feels a bit like self-indulgence, doesn't it?"

"And what's wrong with that?" Millicent asked pointedly, "You could probably afford thirty seconds of self-indulgence, don't you think?"

"It's a slippery slope, I hear," Rigel said dubiously, enjoying the relaxation of casual banter immensely. The internship was turning out to be more stressful than she'd bargained for, but that was probably because she put so much pressure on herself over it.

"None slipperier," Nott said cheerfully, "That's what makes it so much fun."

"I'm not sure that's a word," Draco scrunched up his nose in thought, "Though it doesn't sound any worse than 'more slippery' I suppose…"

Rigel looked around when a certain dark-skinned erudite didn't offer to settle the matter, "Where's Blaise?"

"Not here yet," Millicent said, "For once you're not the last to arrive, Rigel."

"I shall have to reprehend Blaise for usurping my rightful position," Rigel said.

"Which position would that be?" Theo snickered, "King of Lateness? The Minister of Well-Timed Entrances, perhaps?"

"The Prince of Un-Punctuality," Millicent suggested.

"The Belated Baron," Draco said, grinning.

"He's more like a Delayed Duke," Pansy said.

"It is so difficult to find good subjects these days," Rigel sighed.

"Our deepest apologies, Your Tardiness," Theo bowed deeply in mock reverence.

"What's this? You didn't tell me you'd been Knighted, Rigel."

They turned welcoming smiles on Blaise, who took up a seat with a curious expression.

"You have the immense pleasure of addressing Sir Sluggard, the Dilatory," Rigel said snootily, turning her nose up and sniffing exaggeratedly, "You may grant me obeisance now."

Blaise swept a hand before his hastily bowed torso in a mockery of an old gesture of deference, "This ignoble plebian can only be grateful for your magnanimous patronage—may your clocks run ever slowly."

They all dissolved into laughter, drawing curious looks and indulgent smiles from many adults within hearing.

"I've missed this," Rigel said suddenly, surprising herself as the words came out spontaneously. Her friends turned serious eyes on her, and she shrugged sheepishly, "Sorry, didn't mean to kill the moment. I just…the summer's not the same without you guys around, and I just realized it, and…maybe they should call me the Baron who Blurts-Things-Out instead."

Pansy curled her hand around Rigel's elbow and squeezed briefly, "We miss you too, Rigel."

"Yeah, I for one can't wait for school to start up again," Theo said, smoothing over the awkwardly poignant moment easily, "The summer is boring—your birthday being the obvious exception, Draco."

Draco nodded, "I know what you mean. Father's arranged tutors for me most mornings, but learning is dull when there's no Gryffindors to compete against."

Blaise rolled his eyes at that, "Learning is only a competition with yourself, Draco—it's a challenge to learn something every day that you didn't know the day before."

Millicent wrinkled her nose, "How can you learn anything over the summer? I wouldn't set foot indoors if I wasn't expected to eat dinner with my family."

"I agree with Millie," Pansy said, "I spend most days out of doors, riding or enjoying the forest life. It does get a little lonely, though."

"We should have play-dates," Theo said suddenly.

Most of them wrinkled their noses immediately and Draco went to far as to shudder.

"No," the blonde haired boy said, "Just…no. Never again."

"Not like when we were kids," Theo rolled his eyes, "I mean, not with our mothers arranging everything—and none of those stuffy formal robes, either. Just us, meeting up sometimes."

Pansy tilted her head consideringly, and Blaise looked intrigued.

"Once a month?" Millicent suggested, "It would be nice to keep in touch."

The others nodded, then turned expectant eyes on Rigel.

Rigel inwardly grimaced, "I'm not sure if I can..."

Draco frowned, "You're the one who went all nostalgic on us when we've only been apart a few weeks. Why can't you?"

"I'm pretty busy this summer," Rigel said vaguely, "Potions and stuff, you know."

"We really don't," Blaise pointed out bluntly.

Rigel was silent for a moment, not sure how to explain that she was busy with an internship that wasn't Rigel's. "I'm working on a research project this summer," she said slowly.

"Really? You didn't tell us you were planning something like that," Pansy said.

"It wasn't planned," Rigel said, making up a story as quick as she could, "I guess I was inspired by my cousin. Harry has an internship at the Guild this summer, so she's doing independent research, and it looked like fun, so I decided I would try something similar."

"Oh? Which Guild?" Blaise asked.

"Potions," Rigel said, blinking.

"You've mentioned Miss Potter's interest in brewing before," Pansy said, probably recalling the time Sirius had brought it up in front of them, "Is she on your level?"

"At least," Rigel said, a bit uncomfortable, "I'd say she's better than me, though."

Draco snorted, "No one is better than you."

"Professor Snape is," Rigel said.

"No one our age," Draco returned, frowning slightly.

"Harry is," Rigel insisted, "We've grown up together; I know her skills better than anyone."

"Why didn't you get an internship at the Guild as well, if you're so interested in researching?" Blaise asked.

"I wasn't offered one," Rigel shrugged, "Harry's work was noticed by the Aldermaster, Malcolm Hurst, and he granted her the opportunity based on that."

"She didn't even apply?" Millicent whistled, "Her stuff must be really good."

"It is," Rigel said, smiling a bit proudly.

"She sounds interesting," Theo commented, "You should bring her around sometime."

Rigel raised an eyebrow, "When? To Hogwarts? Or maybe to one of these Dark pureblood gatherings?"

Theo winced, "Yeah, on second thought…maybe not. I forgot she was a halfblood."

Pansy glanced a Rigel's blank face, then shot Theo a narrow look, "More importantly, her family is Light-affiliated. With the Split, she'd never be able to attend."

"Rigel's father is here, though," Millicent said suddenly, "You can see him charming his way through the ranks of elderly matrons from here."

Rigel resisted the urge to turn and look, knowing that Sirius didn't need her checking up on him anymore than she needed him worrying about her. They both knew what they were doing.

"Sirius has changed his affiliation," Rigel said.

Most of her friends gaped at her. Changing one's affiliation was not something done lightly, though Sirius acted as though he was changing hairstyles.

"He's…Dark again?" Pansy asked, clearly taken aback.

"Neutral," Rigel said, not wanting to get anyone's hopes up. Sirius Black was the Lord of a very powerful family, whether he used that power or not.

"So he hadn't really changed his affiliation," Blaise said shrewdly, "He just wants to be able to come to these kind of events, to keep an eye on you."

Rigel smiled at Blaise's insight, "Essentially, yes."

"Won't that be difficult for you?" Millicent said. She grimaced a moment later, as if realizing she shouldn't have said that.

"I don't begrudge his supervision," Rigel said.

"She meant with you pretending to be a different person around him," Theo said helpfully.

Pansy and Draco both grimaced uncomfortably, and Blaise rolled his eyes while Millicent flicked Theo's ear, "Thanks, Theo, that really needed to be clarified out loud. Twit."

"It's all right," Rigel said, smiling reassuringly, "It's nice of you all to worry about me. I'm not concerned, though. Sirius sees what he wants to, most of the time."

When Draco narrowed his eyes at her, she realized she'd called Sirius by his name instead of 'Dad.' She mentally berated herself for the slip, knowing she had given in to the illusion that her friends were somehow in on this part of her deception, when in reality they knew very little.

"A-ha!" Theo burst out.

Rigel turned her head to see Theo with his chin jutting stubbornly while Millicent glared at him.

"I'm sure I saw it, this time," Theo told Millicent.

Millicent hissed back, "And I'm telling you that's impossible."

Pansy cleared her throat delicately and Blaise inquired, "Mind letting the rest of us in on your secret conversation?"

Theo opened his mouth but Millicent nudged him into silence, saying, "Nothing. Just Theo being paranoid, as usual."

"There's nothing wrong with paranoia!" Theo said, "But it isn't this time, anyway. Riddle's done it four times already."

"Done what?" Draco asked apprehensively.

"Stared at Rigel," Theo said.

Rigel blinked, "I'm sure you're mistaken, Theo. Mr. Riddle has no cause to stare at me."

"That's what I've been saying," Millicent rolled her eyes, "I told you to keep quiet about your delusions, Theo. You're going to upset people for nothing."

Theo flushed, "I know what I saw, and I'm not ignoring it anymore. Lord Riddle is definitely staring at you, whenever he moves between groups of people."

"Lord Riddle doesn't stare," Pansy said reasonably, "He's too well-bred."

"Well he keeps glancing over like he's checking on Rigel," Theo said defensively, "But Rigel hasn't moved."

Rigel considered this information. She had ended up semi-accidentally eavesdropping on one of Riddle's conversations during the last garden party. Perhaps he wanted to know where she was at all times, since he couldn't sense her aura. Or maybe he's heard about the basilisk, she thought suddenly. It was sort-of-allegedly his basilisk that she had chopped up and sold for parts, and the donation of parts to various places hadn't exactly been low profile, despite Snape's delicate handling of the task.

Out loud, she said, "Maybe he's looking at Draco. It's his birthday, after all."

Theo shook his head, "It's definitely you, Rigel. I know how to read a line of sight."

Rigel shrugged, "Okay, I believe you. What should I do?"

"Do?" Millicent looked slightly alarmed, "Don't do anything."

"Shouldn't I see what he wants, though?" Rigel asked.

"What? No, Rigel, you can't just—"

"I'll just go ask," Rigel said, standing. She met Draco's worried gaze with an unconcerned smile, "I'll be around for gift-opening, Dray, I promise."

She left the gazebo to the sound of someone muttering, "What is wrong with that boy?"

In truth, Rigel needed an excuse to seek Riddle out in any case, and his 'staring' at her was as good a one as any. There were a few loose ends that needed tying, and a certain leather journal was silently burning a hole in her robe pocket. It should be easy enough to arrange a private conversation with the man—the hard part would be avoiding Sirius' notice as she did so. He'd had enough of a shock already that afternoon, with the life-debt thing sprung on him the way it had been.

She began walking slowly in Riddle's direction, pasting an idle expression on her face, as though she were simply wandering through the crowd, observing. Riddle was talking to the Malfoys, it seemed, and several people Rigel didn't recognize on sight, but whose expressions of simpering adoration made Rigel think they were minor members of the SOW party.

She caught Narcissa's eye as she strolled, smiling politely as Mrs. Malfoy's face softened in recognition. When she neared Riddle's group, the elegant lady turned outwards slightly to address her.

"Rigel, how good it is to see you," Narcissa held her hand out in expectation, and Rigel did not disappoint.

She pressed the hand gently between her own and bowed over it, "My lady. The beauty of your gardens is only surpassed by your own breathtaking splendor this summer's day."

Narcissa smiled and reached up with her other hand to arrange a piece of Rigel's hair almost fondly, "I shall become unforgivably vain, with two Blacks now dripping honey into my ears."

Rigel allowed herself a grin, guessing that Sirius had already paid his respects to his hosts, "Is it vanity, when there is naught but truth in the admiration?"

"Pride, then," Narcissa conceded with a light laugh, "Soon my chin will be higher than my ears, and my feathers as bright as my husband's peacocks'."

"You would look charming in any palette, my lady," Rigel assured her.

"I have often said as much," Lucius Malfoy interjected lowly, glancing sidelong at his wife, "Alas, she still refuses to don chartreuse."

"Green is your color, Darling," Narcissa shrugged artlessly, "I would not dare to usurp it from you."

Indeed, Mr. Malfoy was resplendent in a green so light it was almost silver. Before the discussion of fashion could proceed any further, however, Mr. Riddle made his presence known.

"Rigel Black," he said quietly, and it was a mark of the respect he commanded that all conversation in the vicinity stuttered for a moment, before continuing.

"Lord Riddle," Rigel bowed to the appropriate degree, then tilted her head in a way that conveyed polite interest, "How does the day find you?"

"Alive," Riddle said, his face revealing nothing, "And yourself?"

"Abashed," Rigel said, affecting an apologetic half-smile, "I've been terribly remiss, Lord Riddle, and your patience has extended beyond what I deserve."

"Surely your imagined sin is nothing so irredeemable," Riddle said, amusement playing about his mouth, "Confess it, if you seek atonement in earnest."

"The tome I begged you to lend me in the fall," Rigel said, widening her eyes every-so-slightly as she looked up into his, "When you mailed it to me, your letter mentioned no expected date of return, but that is no excuse for the unconscionable length of time I've kept it. I hoped to remedy its loan today, before it slips my mind again."

It was a simple ploy, but a relatively effective one. By referencing an item or event that was innocuous, yet did not exist, she was silently asking for a private audience, to discuss a matter unsuited for public ears.

Riddle's eyes searched her face for a brief moment, and whatever he saw there did not rekindle his previous amusement, "In truth I had forgotten it myself, Mr. Black. It was not my book, but one of Lucius', you see."

Riddle cast a quick glance toward Mr. Malfoy, who spoke up with smooth surety, "Indeed. If you would simply leave it in the library, I will see it returned to its proper place."

Rigel bowed once again, and bid the three a polite farewell. She understood the message completely. She would go to the library and wait. If they had understood her message correctly, either Mr. Riddle or Mr. Malfoy would unobtrusively slip away to meet her.

Slipping away wasn't terribly difficult. Finding the Library…was.

Malfoy Manor was enormous from the outside, and she suspected undetectable extension charms had been used to great effect, as the ceilings seemed impossibly high for there to be multiple stories, and yet the number of staircases she came across insisted their existence. She kept to the main floor, because a family's main library was always on the first floor, though it was sometimes supplemented with a more private study library on the upper levels. Eventually, however, it became clear that she wouldn't find it on her own without considerable snooping.

She retraced her steps until she found the Floo Room, where all the guests arrived. There was no one within, as the party was already in full swing, except a single house elf, who seemed to be twisting his ears almost idly as he hovered nervously by the fireplace.

"Excuse me," she said, waiting for the elf to turn around. It did so, and she recognized it as Dobby, the elf usually in charge of greeting guests, apparently.

Dobby bowed low and squeaked, "How is you needing assistance, sir?"

"I was told to meet your Master in the library," Rigel said, "Could you show me where that is?"

Dobby hesitated, looking between her and the grate, "Dobby is watching the floo…"

He looked ready to wring his ears some more, so Rigel quickly said, "I understand. Just directions, then?"

Dobby nodded his head fiercely, "You is leaving here and turning away from the patio. You is following the corridor until you is reaching the end, then you is turning left, then right when you is seeing a painting of the Black Sea. You is going straight past the next two corridors, then you is seeing big wooden doors with dragons being carved on them. They is being the library doors. You is remembering, sir?"

Rigel nodded, "Yes, thank you." Dobby's eyes welled up, and Rigel winced. She'd forgotten how sensitive this elf could be.

She smiled in what she hoped was a reassuring way and left the room quickly. The directions were relatively easy to follow, though there were several ocean-themed paintings down the hallway Dobby directed her, and figuring out which one depicted the Black Sea required her to recognize the Port of Varna in the background.

The library itself was magnificent, which Rigel supposed she had expected. It was multi-storied, like the Potter library, but at casual glance there was no obvious system of organization, much like the Black library. There were no ungraceful stacks like the Hogwarts library, with barely enough room for two people to squeeze down an isle. Instead it was an open concept, shelves of mahogany lining the walls and only broken up by two imposing fireplaces, one on either end of the room. A split-staircase flowered in the far, center wall, allowing access to the upper balconies. There were no windows, and as a result the room felt cloistered and private, despite its large size and impressive chandeliers.

The shelf closest to the left-side door seemed to contain mostly histories, and very old ones at that. The titles were faded and worn, but the spines unbroken and clearly well cared for. Rigel thought she would approve, if anyone had asked her opinion on the state of Malfoy's books. She resisted the urge to pick up volume one of Chroniques Nationales Françaises, just to see how her French was progressing.

Instead, she chose one of the many high-backed armchairs and settled in to wait.

It was another fifteen minutes before the doors opened, and as Rigel rose from the chair she was surprised to see both Riddle and Malfoy step into the room. She wondered that Riddle included Malfoy in the conversation, but it was his business, and Malfoy was certainly involved, if what she had heard at New Year's could be believed.

"Mr. Black," Riddle said, stepping closer as Malfoy closed and warded the doors behind them. Rigel determinately didn't think about how vulnerable that made her feel, "I trust you were not kept waiting long—one never likes to waste another's time, after all." He pierced her with the simplest of looks, "I sincerely hope you haven't arranged to waste mine."

Rigel bowed her head deferentially, "I would merely do as I said—return an item I've no claim to." She pulled the journal from her pocket and offered it, keeping her head steady with an iron will.

Riddle looked down at the little leather-bound book and raised an eyebrow without saying anything.

Rigel realized he wasn't going to admit to anything right away, so she said, "If I am mistaken, then I truly apologize for wasting your time. I was told by a semi-reliable source that this book belonged to you at once point, but perhaps I was misled."

Riddle's eyes searched hers, and though Rigel didn't feel the creeping sensation of a Legilimency attack, she lowered her lids slightly just in case.

"Perhaps if you explained how you acquired this book, Lord Riddle could say with better surety whether it might have been in his possession at some point," Malfoy suggested, his own expression blank as a board.

Rigel understood then that these two powerful men were nervous—of her. They didn't know which cards she held, or how she intended to use them. That knowledge didn't make her feel powerful or important, however. Instead, she felt more terrified, knowing that she had somewhat unwittingly cornered two predators as dangerous as Riddle and Malfoy surely were. If she wasn't careful, they would lash at her with deadly intent.

She started speaking, twisting facts and events as she went, unalarmed, though slightly ashamed, at how easily lying with the truth had become for her. "This journal appears to be blank," she said calmly, "But it was at one time a powerful magical artifact. It housed a magical construct of impressive complexity, one that seemed to have a personality and life of its own. It called itself Tom Riddle."

"A common name," Malfoy attempted.

"But a name tied to an uncommon collection of character traits," Rigel said smoothly, "The construct claimed to be the creation of a boy with the same name. It was a complete imprint of the boy's personality, it said. The construct wore the robes and badge of a Slytherin prefect, and spoke with the serpent tongue. It would be hard to create a construct with a magical ability the creator himself did not possess, would it not?"

"But not impossible," Riddle said, smirking slightly, "And what makes you think I possess the ability? Parselmouths are so rare."

"Not that rare," Rigel hissed challengingly. Riddle's face went blank, giving nothing away, but that reaction alone was enough for Rigel to guess that he'd understood her. That was one mark against him.

Malfoy, on the other hand, looked slightly awed, despite already knowing she was a Parselmouth. Perhaps it was one thing to know it, and another to hear it.

"You haven't proved anything," Riddle said mildly.

"You aren't being accused of anything yet," Rigel said staidly, "I'm giving my understanding of what happened at Hogwarts this year, with the expectation that with greater understanding we can prevent such a thing from happening again."

Something like surprise flickered in Riddle's gaze, before he smiled politely and gestured for her to continue. "I'm fascinated to hear what you have to impart, Mr. Black."

Rigel took a breath, then said, "The construct's original purpose was quite innocuous, I believe. It claims to have been a kind of safeguard against its creator's…evolution. It essentially captured a moment of extreme hubris and attempted to preserve it for eternity. A kind of immortality—but limited in the way that a child turned vampire would be limited: unable to change, unable to grow or mature."

Riddle's face was darkening, but Rigel hurried on, "Obviously, the boy who created this memory grew up. He became wiser and more worldly, but in the eyes of his creation, he had become deviant and untrustworthy. When the construct found itself out of its creator's immediate control, it betrayed him. The magical construct believed itself to be the superior version, and acted according to its own agenda."

Malfoy cursed softly and Riddle's mouth twisted as though he'd bit into something sour, but neither interrupted her.

"The construct was sent to the school to influence a member of a prominent Light family," Rigel said, fighting to keep disapproval from her voice, "Instead, it designed a more violent agenda. It used its Parseltongue ability to open the Chamber of Secrets and unleash the basilisk within on unsuspecting students."

"Thus the petrifactions," Riddle said, as though in dawning understanding.

"What is interesting," Rigel said, "Is that the Chamber of Secrets was opened once before, while one Tom Riddle, whom the construct was fashioned after, attended Hogwarts."

"Along with hundreds of other students," Riddle said unconcernedly, "Any of whom might have assumed I opened it due to my prominent position in Slytherin House, and constructed an artifact that would believe whatever lies it was told about 'its creator Tom Riddle.'"

"That's true," Rigel nodded, "Except that the construct knew how to open the Chamber, which means its creator imparted that knowledge to it. Why would someone else capable of opening the Chamber and controlling the basilisk want to give Tom Riddle the credit?"

"A simple means of foisting blame," Malfoy said stiffly.

Rigel acknowledged the possibility, and continued, "Eventually, petrifying students was not enough for the construct, which had, I believe, gone a bit mad in its years of isolation. It attempted to possess another student, with the intent of permanently taking over their life and magic."

"You," Riddle said, staring down at her, "Once your Parseltongue became common knowledge, you were the perfect vessel."

"That's the very reason the construct gave," Rigel said evenly, silently marking another tick against Lord Riddle's innocence, "It kidnapped me, and took me to the Chamber. Its possession was unsuccessful, in the end, but the construct was so grossly overconfident that it told me everything before attempting to kill me." She said this in a mocking tone, knowing that if the construct had been a true representation of Riddle's younger self, such derision would be an affront to him personally.

Sure enough, a muscle jumped in Riddle's cheek before he could control it.

Strike three, she thought, almost disappointed. Now that she was virtually certain Riddle was responsible, she would have to do something about it, and the weight of responsibility sat heavily on her.

"An interesting story," Riddle said after a moment, "Though of course, more serious parties might not find it very pertinent, as no one suffered lasting harm."

"On the contrary," Rigel said, more sharply than she'd meant to, "A young girl was killed fifty years ago by whoever imparted the construct called Tom Riddle with the ability to control the basilisk."

Riddle froze, and his eyes narrowed, "It would be very difficult to reopen a murder that occurred fifty years ago on the word of a raving magical construct."

"It would," Rigel agreed, "I myself don't consider the word of a mad artifact to be convincing testimonial. I don't like to accuse people without proper evidence, which is why the name Tom Riddle never passed my lips when Headmaster Dumbledore asked me what happened in the Chamber. The circumstances are rather suspicious, though, all thinks considered."

There was definite surprise on Riddle's face now, though he masked it quickly with cunning, "Circumstantial evidence will never be enough, Mr. Black. Recent events simply can't be convincingly connected to me, which means ancient history certainly wont be re-examined, dead basilisk or no."

"There is also the fact that Ginny Weasley remembers Lucius Malfoy slipping the artifact into her cauldron before term began," Rigel said, ignoring the guilt she felt as dragging her friend's father into it. He chose to involve himself, after all.

"Polyjuice is easily obtained," Malfoy said stiffly, though his throat muscles clenched restlessly.

"And if someone had witnessed a conversation between yourself and Mr. Malfoy on New Year's Eve that did link you to recent events, Lord Riddle?" Rigel was pushing, now, but she needed Riddle to give before the matter could be settled, "Would you claim Polyjuice for that, as well?"

"Excuse me?" Riddle's voice was positively silken, and Malfoy's face had gone completely white, bar two spots of color high on his cheeks.

"Sound carries rather well in the Rosier gardens," Rigel said steadily, "Your conversation beneath the balconies was entirely clear."

"Hearsay," Riddle murmured, leaning forward in a move that was admittedly intimidating, "Not even the muggles consider it enough to convict."

"It is enough to slander a reputation, though, isn't it?" Rigel said quietly.

She saw the moment when Riddle decided she was a threat. Her magic stirred restlessly, but he didn't lash out as she half-expected—instead, his face relaxed, and he leaned back almost casually.

"Very well, Mr. Black. Consider me concerned," he said, lips curling almost pleasantly, "You've not told my political opponents your little tale, so you must have some idea as to how you think this story ought to end."

Rigel inclined her head carefully. He was agreeing to hear her demands, but now was not the time to act arrogant; "I think it would be best if you didn't interfere at Hogwarts anymore, Lord Riddle. All the evidence is loose-fitting, as you say, but combined with the Sleeping Sickness last year, and the current anti-Dumbledore agenda the SOW party is pushing…well, some might think it a little convenient," Rigel took a breath, "If you became disinterested in Hogwarts affairs, I'm sure people's suspicions would be alleviated. After all, no one really wants to believe a great wizard like you would use schoolchildren as pawns in his political schemes."

"I'm sure no one will have any more cause to think such a thing," Riddle said, a politician's smile on his handsome face, "Was that your only concern?"

Rigel let her face fall into a serious expression, "I will be frank with you for a brief moment, Lord Riddle. I think you created the construct that lived in this book, and that you were every bit as arrogant and cruel as it was. I think you killed Myrtle, whether by accident or by choice, but I also think you felt remorse for it. The boy who created that construct wanted to destroy the world. I don't think that's who you are anymore, but I also don't think anyone should be able to cause the death of another without paying for it in some way. I'm not a judge, Lord Riddle. I'm not going to hand you a sentence and demand it be carried out. In any case, Myrtle's parents are both deceased, so I can't think of anyone who would benefit from a re-hashing of her story now. All I ask is for you to never forget the crime. Remember the mistakes of the past with shame, so that you never repeat them. You're a powerful man, Lord Riddle—too powerful to be playing games with innocents. Please leave Hogwarts out of your plans in the future, no matter how provoked you feel by Albus Dumbledore."

Riddle considered her for a long moment, no longer smiling. "Hogwarts is my political enemy's seat of power," he said. At her darkening expression, he held up a hand, "I say that so you will understand the weight of what you ask. It seems a simple thing to you, I daresay, to leave children out of political maneuverings, but Hogwarts is implicated by Dumbledore's involvement—it was he who put children on the front lines of our war, and now you ask that I ignore them. I will do so—but I require reassurances of my own."

Rigel tensed. She should have expected him to add terms, but she couldn't imagine what she had that he'd want. "What reassurances are those?" she asked.

"First, the assurance that the particularities of the events you've described today will live on in our memories only—that you will spread the name Tom Riddle in connection with the basilisk no further," Riddle said, his tone brooking no disagreement on that ground.

"You have it," Rigel said. That demand was easily met, as long as Riddle kept his plots out of the school from now on, and as long as he did keep the lesson in his memory, "As a gesture of good faith, I will also tell you that Ginny Weasley is the only other who knows anything beyond the public story, and she will not speak of what she knows to anyone."

"You would trust a Weasley to—" Malfoy began.

Rigel cut him off rudely, because he had been rude himself to question her assurance, "She owes me a life debt—this is the price I've asked of her. She will not speak of it, and she has dedicated herself to learning Occlumency already, so no one will take it from her mind, either."

Malfoy inclined his head in silent, though graceless, concession.

"There is one other thing I require," Riddle said softly, "I would know what happened in the Chamber. I would know how the basilisk died. How you escaped. How the construct was…defeated."

Rigel hesitated, "We've been absent from the party a long time already, and the story isn't pleasant."

Riddle smiled thinly, "I care not for another of your stories. I would have the memory."

She blinked in plain surprise. He wanted her to give him her memory of that night? That was…potentially dangerous. "I'm not sure I feel comfortable doing that," she said slowly, her mind racing. What could be gleaned from a memory? It would be from her perspective, but outside of her body—he wouldn't see what happened in her mind, which meant her thoughts and emotions during the event wouldn't be revealed. Was it safe? Could it give her away?

"I'm afraid I must insist," Riddle said coldly, "It is not so much to ask, in return for respecting Hogwarts' neutrality from this point forward."

Rigel took as long as she thought she needed to think it over, before saying, "Do you have a pensive, Mr. Malfoy? I don't want to give you the memory, but I will let you view it, with the understanding it be returned to me before I leave today."

Riddle inclined his head regally, and Malfoy led them through his manor to a small, private study, where he unlocked a panel in the wall to reveal an elaborately carved pensive. He lowered it to the desk, and gestured with his wand questioningly. Rigel nodded her permission, knowing that she probably wouldn't be able to remove the memory herself, having never tried it before.

She cleared her mind, and brought forth the memory of that night. She examined it carefully from all angles, reassuring herself that Riddle would learn nothing from it that she didn't want him to. It was a risk, letting him view it, but Ginny had essentially entrusted Rigel with the responsibility of Riddle's involvement. If this was what it took to see that involvement neutralized where Hogwarts was concerned, she would do it.

Malfoy gently touched his wand to her temple, and a silver strand of memory was drawn slowly out. Looking at it as it settled into the basin, she could almost imagine it was a happy memory, shiny and ethereal, like the liquid mercury of Pansy's mental core.

She felt she should explain, "Part of it will be very uninteresting. Some of the struggle between the construct and myself was mental, so you won't be able to see that part."

"What happened?" Malfoy asked, raising an eyebrow.

"I kept it distracted in my mind while I freed Ginny from its possession—you'll see her wake up suddenly," Rigel explained succinctly, "Once it was cut off from her magic, it was easily banished from my own mind. The rest…" She still shuddered when she thought of the reanimated basilisk corpse, but she was interested to note that without the memory in her head any longer, the idea of it was softer, and more abstract. Some compassionate impulse made her warn, "It isn't pretty. The basilisk met a rather…sticky end, I'm afraid."

Something unfathomable flashed in Riddle's eyes, but he merely inclined his head, contemplating the innocuous-looking memory silently.

Knowing it would take a few hours for Riddle to view the memory, Rigel said, "I should get back—if I'm not there when Draco opens his gifts, he'll be very cross."

"I will accompany you back," Malfoy said, likely for the same reasons—it was his party, after all. "Lord Riddle," Malfoy bowed deeply to Riddle. Rigel thought he was a bit too deferential to Riddle, for all that he was Malfoy's boss, and hoped that the megalomaniacal child wasn't still living inside the politician, buried deep.

Riddle glanced at her as they made to leave, "You will find these memories in your possession before you leave, Mr. Black, and our business will be concluded to our mutual satisfaction, will it not?"

Rigel nodded, though she did offer Riddle the journal once more.

"Keep it," he said, his voice disinterested, "May it remind you that the folly of one's youth is not easily purged."

She could not tell if he meant her folly or his own, but she decided in that moment that she would keep it. Not as a reminder of youthly arrogance, but as a warning against setting into motion forces you couldn't control.

Lucius Malfoy was not sure what to make of Rigel Black. A year ago he would have called him a curiosity, made important only because of the friendship he shared with his son, and the life debt that hung between them. Curing the sickness his first year may have been a fluke. Slaying a basilisk, however…

It bore contemplation, at the least.

He turned a sidelong glance on the child as they walked slowly through the manor. Black was at the awkward stage of adolescence that offered no clue as to what sort of man he might become. All elbows and knees even under the finely-cut robes, the boy walked cautiously, as though he were ever-fearful of drawing attention to himself.

If he did wish to avoid attention, Lucius noted, he was doing a phenomenally bad job of it. Killing a basilisk—had ever there been a feat more attention-grabbing? And donating the parts to charity. It was disgustingly selfless, almost as if the boy had a point to prove. Everything he did curried favor with someone, it seemed. The boy was a Parselmouth, yet he killed a basilisk. He was an unassuming academic, yet he carried life debts from several prominent members of wizarding society. He was the child of Sirius Black, perhaps the least subtle wizard in Britain, yet he successfully blackmailed Lord Riddle himself. He seemed to be everywhere, yet no one knew anything about him. He was Draco's best friend, Severus' protégé, on good terms with seemingly all of the prominent pureblood Heirs in his House, and yet everyone who knew him described him as quiet, non-confrontational, politically unambitious, and socially stifled to boot.

These reports simply did not mesh with one another. There had been no sign of the bookish introvert a few minutes ago as Black stared down one of the most powerful political figures of the age. There was also no sign of that coolly calculating young man when the boy was anywhere near his father's purview. The only thing constant about him, it seemed, was the unreliability of the information about him.

"Draco doesn't know," the boy said suddenly, glancing up at him in a way that didn't suit his current pushed-back hairstyle, but which would have been perfectly unassuming through bangs.

Lucius tilted his head in a prompting gesture, willing Black to elaborate.

"He suspects that you were involved in things this year, but I haven't confirmed it—he doesn't know you gave Ginny the book," the boy clarified, "I thought he shouldn't have to. It hurts him, to think that his father might gamble with his life, however good the odds seem."

Lucius suddenly had difficulty swallowing through the remorse that rose up in his throat. He beat it back, as he always did, because it was unnecessary. Draco's life wasn't in any danger—wouldn't have been, if things had gone to plan. No one could have foreseen the madness that book would cause. Not even Lord Riddle could have anticipated such a deviance. That true danger had come to the school, twice, was an accident. Unfortunate, but not preventable.

Still, it was good that Draco be kept unaware of his part in these accidents.

"I would thank you, Rigel," he said, deliberately using the boy's first name, "Both for your discretion, and for your…negotiation with Mr. Riddle. I will always support my party leader, but in light of certain accidents, it is not unwelcome to know that such mistakes will not be repeated."

The boy hid his surprise well, but not well enough that Lucius didn't catch it.

"Think nothing of it," Rigel said, ever cautious, "Draco is my family. Anyone would do as I have, to protect their family."

Lucius took a moment to attempt to dissect the meaning in those words. Was he intimating that Lucius himself had not done enough to protect his family? No, Lucius chided himself. He was reading too much into a simple statement. Perhaps this was part of the deception of Rigel Black—people made much of him, when underneath there was a simpler, less threatening explanation for all he was.

Although, Lucius thought darkly, There aren't many non-threatening explanations for why a twelve-year-old boy was able to slay a basilisk.

Rigel parted ways with Mr. Malfoy when they reached the patio, neither acknowledging that it was anything other than a coincidence they exited the manor at the same time. She wandered through the crowd, pausing to refuse a drink from a nymph every now and then, and eventually found herself back at the gazebo, where Draco was getting ready to open his gifts.

She sidled up next to Sirius to watch, and her uncle looked down at her with an easy smile, seeming to have forgotten their awkward parting earlier, "Wondered where you'd got to."

He didn't make it a question or an accusation, just a simple statement that he'd been wondering. That was one of the nice things about Sirius—he rarely entertained suspicions about people he cared about, simply accepting at face value that he didn't always know everything about them.

Because he didn't ask, Rigel said, "I was in the house," and because someone might have overheard her initial conversation with Riddle, she added, "I had to return a book I borrowed to the Malfoy Library."

"They had a book the Black Library didn't?" Sirius asked, a bit incredulous.

"It was an old family journal, actually," Rigel shrugged, "Written by a Malfoy Healer some centuries ago. It was interesting, but didn't contain anything groundbreaking."

"Ah," Sirius said unconcernedly, "We have a few of those, too, but I suppose you've read them all by now."

"Most likely," Rigel agreed.

They watched Draco smile brightly as he ripped the paper off a pair of seeker's gloves. Even though Rigel knew for a fact that Draco owned about six pairs already, the blonde boy still expressed his heartfelt thanks to the giver.

"Not a bad actor, your friend," Sirius muttered with amusement.

"I'm not sure he's acting," Rigel admitted quietly, "He's probably genuinely delighted to get another pair of Quidditch gloves."

"I don't think I've ever seen a Malfoy smile so much," Sirius said thoughtfully, still speaking just loud enough for Rigel to hear, "Is he always like this?"

"Not always," Rigel said, thinking of the times Draco became put-out or smug for one reason or another, "A lot of the time, though…yes. He's a generally pleasant person."

"Generally spoiled, maybe," Sirius chuckled, eyeing the huge stack of gifts Draco was still tearing through.

"Because you wouldn't know anything about spoiling kids," Rigel said archly, "What was that you gave Addy the other day? Was it a gold spoon, perchance?"

"Platinum," Sirius said, utterly unrepentant, "With her name engraved on the handle."

"Q.E.D.," Rigel muttered.

"The Blacks have always spoiled our children," Sirius said proudly.

"Is that why you turned out so well?" Rigel asked.

"Results don't lie," Sirius said, "Just look at your friend, Draco—that's a product of Black upbringing if ever I saw one. Confident, outgoing, happy. What could be wrong with that? Cissy's done right by him."

Rigel just shook her head, well aware that she had no room to debate the merits and drawbacks to spoiling children, having been rather blessed in her own upbringing.

Draco, as it turned out, did receive both a customized wand holster and the newest model of racing broom from his parents. He positively cooed over the Firebolt as he set it reverently to one side, and strapped the Malfoy-crest-engraved leather into place over his forearm with no small amount of pride.

Mr. Malfoy and Narcissa looked on indulgently, content in their son's obvious enjoyment.

Draco soon came to a silver-wrapped gift that Rigel recognized as the one Sirius brought. She stole a glance at her uncle and caught him grinning with restrained anticipation.

Please don't let it explode, she thought nervously.

It didn't. Draco opened the little square-shaped box and pulled out a perfectly spherical piece of crystal. It was smooth, and fit comfortably in Draco's hands as he turned it this way and that to examine it.

Narcissa, who had been standing off to the side with her husband, inhaled sharply and moved to look over Draco's shoulder, "Is that…?" the blonde woman looked up and found Sirius in the small crowd of onlookers. She smiled beautifully at Sirius, who tipped his head in pleased acknowledgement.

"What is it, Mother?" Draco asked curiously.

"This is a gift traditionally given to children of Black blood on their thirteenth birthday," Narcissa said, "It is called a Star Light, and it shines only for the star-born, those named in the light of the stars. You were named for the constellation Draco, and this, if I am not mistaken, is the light of Eltanin, its brightest star." Narcissa said, a fierce light of pride in her eyes as she gazed at her son.

"It's light?" Draco's eyebrows rose and he cradled the crystal sphere more carefully, "That's what makes it glow?"

"It glows only to your eyes, Draco," Narcissa said, somewhat wistfully, "It will light your path, no matter what dark trails you travel. Keep it with you, for it is said that when starlight guides a son of Black, he will never lose his way."

Draco clutched the little orb close to him, and pocketed it carefully. He made a deep bow to Sirius, saying, "Thank you, Lord Black. I am honored to be considered a child of your House."

Sirius inclined his head almost regally, Rigel thought wonderingly. She couldn't believe he'd given Draco something so thoughtful and generous, and she felt a little bit of shame for thinking he would do something to embarrass him instead.

"You are more than worthy of the House of Black, Draco Malfoy," Sirius said, smiling, "Use it well—or use it to raise hell, if you'd rather."

The moment of solemnity was effectively broken, and many of those watching tittered and chuckled at Sirius' irreverent suggestion. There was a certain grace to her uncle's personality, Rigel realized. It worked, for all of its eccentricity.

Draco moved on to other presents, and they settled back into watching him ooh and ahh quite convincingly. Rigel wondered where her present had gone to, but figured it had been separated from Sirius' when the house elves moved the gifts to the gazebo.

"That was a fitting gift, Brother," Regulus had found them once again.

"I did take a second to think about it," Sirius said, grinning lazily, "You don't mind, do you? So many of those orbs are just sitting around in the main vault, without anyone named for their stars to use them, and it will likely be returned upon the boy's death, as no one else will get any use from it."

Regulus smiled slightly, "I don't begrudge the boy his Star Light, Sirius. I still keep my own around, so I know how useful they can be."

"How are they made?" Rigel asked, curious. She didn't think Archie had ever mentioned anything like it before, but it might not be something he'd think to talk about.

"You'll get one when you're thirteen, don't worry," Sirius said, ruffling her hair affectionately, "The Arcturus Star Light, naturally. We all have them—Regulus, Bellatrix, Andromeda, and me. They're made by capturing the light of a specific star on certain equinoxes. The rituals have been lost, now, but our ancestors created a star light for every star they could, and bound them to shine only for those Black descendents named in the light of their stars, or a constellation containing them. When left alone, they go dormant, but they awaken when held and form an attachment to their first holder until he or she dies, at which point the light goes dormant again until the next holder."

"Does Lady Malfoy have one?" Rigel asked, frowning slightly. Narcissa hadn't been named for a star, as far as Rigel knew.

Sirius looked sad for a moment, "No, she never received one. She was born blonde, remember, and before her father came to his wits and decided she must be his after all, he refused to name her as a Black. Even after he acknowledged her, it didn't matter. She wasn't named in the light of a star, so the Star Lights won't shine for her."

Rigel thought that was rather sad, and she could see that it would mean all the more for Narcissa that Draco could receive such a gift.

The last of the gifts were opened and exclaimed over, and still no sign of the one Rigel had brought. Troubled, she walked with Sirius and Regulus in tow to where Draco was happily thanking his parents yet again for organizing the party in general.

Draco turned when he caught sight of them and smiled brightly up at Sirius, "I really like the Star Light, Mr. Black—that wasn't just posturing for the crowd. It's one of my favorite gifts this year."

"You're very welcome," Sirius said, reaching out to ruffle Draco's hair in a gesture that seemed entirely unthinking. He froze, hand on Draco's head, and snatched it back sheepishly, "Sorry."

"That's okay," Draco said automatically, seeming a bit taken aback himself. He patted his hair back into place, and Rigel took the opportunity to speak up.

"Draco," she said hesitantly, "I really did bring you a present, but it seems to have been misplaced—"

"Oh!" Draco chuckled and began fishing in his robe pockets. He pulled out a slightly rumpled green package and grinned at Rigel apologetically, "Sorry, I forgot I'd done that."

Rigel tilted her head sideways, "You don't want to open it?"

Draco laughed unrestrainedly, "Of course I'm opening it. I didn't see you at the beginning when I started unwrapping, so I put your gift to the side to wait until you showed up. Last year you weren't there when I opened your gift, and I felt just horrible that you didn't have a chance to see my grateful expression."

Rigel fought a grimace, suspecting that Draco knew exactly how uncomfortable people's gratitude tended to make her.

"Open it now, Draco," Narcissa chided gently.

Draco carefully peeled back the paper, likely guessing that the gift was fragile. He was grinning happily, but with a complete lack of surprise, when he held up a vial of potion almost triumphantly, "What does this one do? Will it make me fly again?"

Rigel felt a smile tug at her lips as she shook her head, "Read the label."

"Potentialis," Draco read. He frowned for a moment, clearly trying to remember if he'd heard of it somewhere.

"It's supposed to reveal your magical potential," Rigel explained, still smiling slightly, "You can only take it after you turn thirteen, when your core finishes maturing. It will tell you your affinities, strengths, any gifts you might be able to unlock, that sort of thing."

"Really?" Draco peered interestedly at the little vial, "Can I take it now?"

Rigel shook her head, "There's no telling how the magic will manifest, so it's best to take it alone, or with one of your parents there to help you interpret the results."

Draco looked pleadingly to his father, who smiled indulgently, "I will assist you with taking it tonight, if you wish."

"Thank you!" Draco handed the vial of potion ceremoniously to his mother, then turned and launched himself at Rigel. He stopped short just before actually touching her, and grasped both her hands tightly instead, smiling directly into her face and saying, "Thank you, Rigel," very quietly.

Rigel wasn't sure what to do with such intense gratitude and admiration directly right at her. She blinked a bit, and squeezed Draco's hands back helplessly. "It's nothing," she said, her tongue feeling a bit thick. Draco stepped back after a moment and Rigel gave herself a mental shake. Her friend had a smile like a sunbeam, she decided, unmistakably warm, but blinding at times, as well.

Theo came to ask Draco to show him his Firebolt just then, and Draco, with one last smile at Rigel, went off to do just that.

Rigel looked around to see Sirius staring at her with raised eyebrows. For some reason, she felt her cheeks grow warm, but she pushed the feeling down and raised her chin in silent question. Sirius just shook his head slowly, his face melting into a secretive smirk.

Mr. Malfoy drew both of their attention when he said, "The House of Black has been generous and thoughtful in its gifting today. Draco is fortunate in his friendship with your Heir."

"It is the House of Black that benefits from Malfoy hospitality," Regulus returned smoothly.

"And I am the fortunate one in my friendship to Draco," Rigel added, meaning every word. Draco had been a very good friend to her, almost from the moment they'd met, and she was constantly aware of how paltry her contribution to their relationship had been in return. After all her lies and artifice, nothing she did would ever repay the gift of Draco's friendship, or Pansy's either, for that matter.

Narcissa seemed about to say something, but she caught sight of someone headed their way and smiled welcomingly instead, "Severus, there you are. We thought you weren't gracing us with your presence this day."

Snape strode to Lucius' side, pulling out a small package and handing it to Narcissa as he did so, "Even I am not so remiss a godparent as to neglect my charge's birthday, Narcissa."

Narcissa received the gift gracefully, "I was rather expecting an owl, in fact."

Regulus and Lucius let out low chuckles at Snape's expense, but the Potions Master didn't seem ruffled by the gentle teasing, "An owl couldn't do it justice."

"Oh?" Lucius looked intrigued, "What have you made my son, Severus?"

Snape merely smirked, "Have him open it in private."

Seeing that he would say no more about it, Narcissa excused herself to stow the present in the manor somewhere. Sirius squeezed Rigel's shoulder tightly, then slipped away without even a word to their hosts. It was rather rude of him, but Rigel thought it a monumental success that Sirius hadn't immediately set to insulting Snape on sight, and silently thanked her uncle for his discretion, however graceless. It was a step in the right direction, and she certainly appreciated it.

"Mr. Black," Snape acknowledged her only after Sirius had left, which probably served some subtle purpose that Rigel didn't even try to guess, "I trust your summer has been uneventful."

"Productive as usual, Professor Snape," Rigel said evenly, ignoring the doubtful look in her professor's eyes—he seemed to always think her up to something.

"Productive in what way?" It was Regulus who asked, his eyes flicking between Snape and Rigel with veiled curiosity.

Rigel tilted her head to look at Regulus, saying, "Academically. I generally spend my summers studying or researching."

"Potions?" Regulus clarified, glancing again at Snape.

Rigel nodded, "Professor Snape is kind enough to guide my studies, when my interest alone does not drive me toward a topic."

"You must have made quite an impression, for Severus to go out of his way to assist you," Regulus mused aloud.

"It is he who assists me, in fact," Snape said smoothly, his eyes glinting at Regulus, "Your nephew has made himself indispensable to my current research."

Rigel couldn't help but flush at such exaggerated praise. She was certainly not indispensable in any way. "Professor Snape is too generous with his praise. He humors my assistance, for which I am very grateful."

"Ever humble, is he not?" Mr. Malfoy said, his voice not revealing whether that was a compliment or an insult.

"Don't sell your gifts so cheaply," Regulus said sharply, "A Black must always be conscious on his own worth."

"I am too conscious of it," Rigel said, "Which is why I could not let Professor Snape's hyperbolic comment go unqualified."

Snape's expression was positively challenging as he replied, "You think I embellish my words, Mr. Black? The last time you assisted me, how many variants of Aconite Alleviation did we brew?"

Rigel thought back carefully, "Four, Professor."

Snape smirked as both Regulus and Mr. Malfoy stiffened slightly.

"Four?" Malfoy pinned Snape with a glare, "You assured me that your unaccountable mania over this project would not lead to unconscionable risks. For all your pride, you haven't the magic to afford brewing that more than twice in a—"

"I did not," Snape interrupted, his expression unmistakably smug, "Mr. Black supplied the magic."

Malfoy reared back from his diatribe and narrowed his eyes at her, "Did he indeed?"

"As I said," Snape looked down at her with subtle triumph, "Indispensable. The experimentation stage proceeded exponentially quicker with Mr. Black assisting me."

Rigel swallowed, but did not protest this time. She had known Aconite Alleviation was draining, but it wasn't that dangerous to brew consecutively, was it?

Regulus was looking down at her with undeniable calculation in his gaze, but Rigel wasn't sure how to respond. Every time she thought she understood her own power-levels, something happened to make her realize she hadn't quite grasped them yet. She would have to do something about that. Perhaps a detecting potion would do the trick.

"Have you made any progress this summer?" Rigel asked, both genuinely curious and hoping to steer the conversation away from herself.

Snape smirked, "I have. No doubt you'll hear something about it soon."

"I'll keep an eye on the journals," Rigel promised, burning with a mix of intrigue and hope—it could mean great things for Remus, if Snape had made an improvement on the Wolfsbane potion. She thought of something else she wanted to ask Snape, while she had him there, and said, "Professor, have you heard of a Potions Master named Thomas? I can't remember reading any of his papers, but he belongs to the English Guild."

Snape raised an eyebrow at her, "I know him, yes. He rarely publishes, and when he does it generally isn't in English. Where did you come across his name?"

"He is overseeing my cousin Harry's internship this summer," Rigel said, "She hadn't heard of him either, so I thought I'd ask if you knew his specialty?"

"Miss Potter acquired an internship at the Guild?" Snape's eyes were suddenly piercing, "They don't take on students below NEWT level."

Rigel took the opportunity for shameless self-promotion with alacrity, "Harry is really good. I wouldn't be surprised if she's NEWT-level. The Aldermaster came across some of her work and recommended her. So you do know Master Thomas?"

Snape inclined his head, "He studied under Master Liu as well, though removed by several years—he is older than I am. I wasn't aware he was in the habit of mentoring anyone, much less participating in the Guild Internship program."

"Harry said he didn't seem enthusiastic about it," Rigel said thoughtfully, "Perhaps the Guild pressed him into it."

"Likely," Snape said wryly, "Thomas was never one to involve himself in Guild activities more than absolutely necessary. He is brilliant, but his specialties are as obscure as they are occult. It will be interesting to see what Miss Potter learns from his tutelage."

Rigel wasn't sure how she felt about that answer. Obscure and occult? What did that mean in relation to Potions? "I'll let her know," Rigel said.

From there the conversation moved to other things, and once the men started talking about people Rigel didn't recognize, she excused herself to go find her friends once more.

She whiled away the next couple of hours in good cheer, chatting with her friends about whatever caught their attention. She ate too much of Draco's succulent birthday cake, but usually when she came by cake Archie ate it for her, so she didn't realize she'd over-indulged until she sat down again and groaned, much to her friends' amusement.

"Who knew Rigel was a closet glutton?" Millicent teased.

"I didn't realize how much I was eating," Rigel said weakly, slumping slightly in her seat, "Why didn't' someone stop me?"

"We assumed you knew what you were doing," Pansy sighed, eyeing Rigel sympathetically.

"In the future, assume I have no concept of proportion when it comes to cake," Rigel said.

"Do you want me to get you a stomach soothing potion?" Draco asked, not bothering to hide his amusement at her expense.

"You mean the Rigel Black doesn't carry every potion known to man on his person?" Theo joked.

"Not to parties," Rigel huffed. As her stomach cramped again, she grimaced.

"That's it, I'm getting you a potion," Draco said, making to rise.

Rigel's stomach didn't hurt that badly, but she realized this was an opportunity to go collect her memory from Riddle, so she waved her friend back down, "I can get it. Will Dobby get one for me if I ask?"

"Who?" Blaise asked, unable to let any reference to anything he didn't know pass by, apparently.

"Draco's house elf," Rigel answered.

"You know Draco's house elf by name?" Millicent snorted, "You've been here what, twice?"

"If something has a name, you should use it," Rigel shrugged, "How else will you differentiate things?"

They laughed at her idea of good manners, but Draco did confirm that Dobby would fetch a potion if asked. Now she would have to actually ask him for one, of course, in case Draco inquired, but taking an unnecessary stomach soother wouldn't hurt her.

She wandered back into the manor, and, after getting the potion from Dobby, made her way through the halls to where she thought she remembered Malfoy's study to be.

When she reached the door, her magic hummed under her skin the moment her hand brushed the doorknob. Wards, she realized, powerful enough to set her teeth vibrating, but not designed to react to physical contact, thankfully. Of course Riddle would have put wards up while he watched her memory—entering a pensive always put the physical body at risk.

She thought he would be done viewing the memory soon, if he wasn't already, so Rigel decided to simply wait. There was a portrait of a graceful lady in blue silk directly across from the Study door, and she eyed Rigel somewhat distrustfully as she leaned against the wall uncomfortably. Rigel smiled, and the lady sniffed.

"What are you doing in this part of the manor unescorted?" she finally asked, her voice haughty.

Rigel shrugged, "I'm waiting for Mr. Riddle. He hasn't left the study, has he?"

"What business is that of yours, boy?" the portrait sniffed, "Lord Riddle is a frequent, honored guest here at Malfoy Manor, and you are merely—"

She was interrupted by the muffled sound of a small explosion, and Rigel looked around and stared as though the door to the study would suddenly become transparent and allow her to see what was going on within. A moment later, more sounds of muffled destruction came through the wood, followed by the unmistakable hiss of angry Parseltongue.

If Rigel had been uncertain that Riddle possessed the gift, that settled it rather succinctly.

She wondered if she should do something, and when the sound of something else being blown up reached her ears, she cleared her throat and knocked thrice on the wards, feeling the vibrations echo deep in her skull. The sounds of destruction immediately ceased, but it was a good minute before the wards dropped abruptly and the door opened.

Riddle's face was black with a rage so thick Rigel thought she could feel it in the air around him. She fought the temptation to step back, and instead looked up into Riddle's forbidding expression, wondering which part of her memory had made him so incredibly angry.

"Black," Riddle snapped, "You should return in twenty minutes."

He made to shut the door, but Rigel stepped forward just enough that he would have to shut it on her foot. Riddle's hand clenched the doorframe in a way that suggested he was sorely tempted to do just that.

"If I could get my memory back now, I'll be out of your hair right away," Rigel said, "The party is winding down, so I need to get it before Sirius suggests we go."

So intimidated was she by his menacing stare, she didn't notice she'd called her 'father' by his name again until it had slipped out, but as angry as Riddle appeared, he probably didn't notice.

Riddle jerked away from the doorway and stalked back into the room. Rigel followed quickly, strangely relieved to see the memory still swimming in the pensive innocuously. She'd been half-afraid the pensive might have been one of the things smashed. Several of the bookcases had not been so spared, by the looks of things.

"Can you put it back in?" Rigel asked, "I'm not sure how…"

Riddle made an impatient noise that was almost a growl, and drew his wand briskly. As he turned it toward the memory, however, his hand trembled too much to draw it from the basin. The man cursed eloquently, in English this time, and turned from the pensive to pace the length of the room and back, "I require a moment—just sit, Black."

Rigel looked around her, but both chairs that had once occupied the office were now smoldering piles of ash, so she remained standing. "Was it the memory?" she asked, "I tried to warn you—the basilisk—"

"It had clearly gone mad over the years," Riddle made a dismissive gesture with his hand, "Its end was…regrettable, but would have been necessary in any case. Severus intimated the parts would be used for research?"

Rigel nodded, "It seemed the best way to make sense of its death."

"I quite agree," Riddle drew a slow breath, and pinned Rigel with a fierce look, "You don't know what you've spared the world, Mr. Black, by doing away with that construct. It would have…" Riddle broke off to flick his wand toward another bookcase, which promptly burst into flames, twisting and writhing under the spell before exploding into splinters and torn scraps of parchment. At Rigel's mildly reproachful look, Riddle actually barked out a short laugh, "Don't worry about the books—Lucius doesn't keep anything interesting in this study."

Rigel gave the man a moment to collect himself further—she hadn't anticipated the effect seeing his own sixteen-year-old self (albeit a half-mad, raving version) attempt to murder someone might have on Riddle himself. She had to ask, though, "Mr. Riddle? Do you think the construct was destroyed? At the end, it said 'this isn't over' or something to that effect. Could it have survived without a host?"

Riddle's face was white as he replied, "I do not know. It would have had to find one immediately, but the Chamber is not far removed from the Forbidden Forest, which teems with inhabitable creatures. It is unlikely the construct survived, but the whole scenario was unlikely to begin with. That its purpose could have become so deluded…"

He cut himself off with a defensive glare in her direction, but Rigel merely shrugged, "I heard you curse in Parseltongue, earlier. I'm pretty convinced it was your construct, now, but our earlier deal stands."

Riddle narrowed his eyes at her, and with a sharp gesture the door to the study slammed closed and wards sprang up once more over the doorway. Rigel did step back this time, and drew her wand from her waist pocket quickly. Had Riddle decided she was too much of a risk? Surely he knew Sirius would miss her, if she disappeared, not to mention Draco and her other friends. Perhaps he didn't care?

He seemed almost amused at her defensive actions, and waved his hand lazily toward the two piles of smoldering chair-ashes. They reformed themselves into two very comfortable looking armchairs, and Riddle took a seat in one, waving her toward the other.

Rigel sheathed her wand, and sat, because, really, what else could she do? Try and tear down Lord Riddle's wards?

"I was a foolish adolescent, Mr. Black," Riddle said suddenly, his hands clenched on his armrests and a bitter twist pulling at his mouth, "I grew past that foolishness, but not without learning hard lessons. Have you ever learned a hard lesson, Mr. Black?" he didn't wait for her to answer, continuing, "Pray you never have cause to. I killed a girl, fifty years ago. I could claim it was an accident—how could I know she was loitering just outside she entrance?—but at the time I truly didn't care if someone died by the basilisk's gaze. Silence a girl to protect my secrets? I thought nothing of such an act…until it happened. I felt a part of my soul tearing that night, Mr. Black. Literally, I perceived my soul cracking, and I was tempted, for a moment, to let a piece of it go forever—to sacrifice that piece of myself, for power."

He didn't look ashamed, or angry at his past self, more…disgusted. There was a sneer in his voice, as though he held the memory in such contempt that he almost couldn't bear to give voice to it.

"But you didn't," Rigel said, "You didn't walk down that path, in the end."

Riddle inclined his head slowly, "It would have been easy to complete the ritual I had planned, to let that death fracture my soul irreparably. I hesitated, however. I realized in that moment that I wasn't just sacrificing another to my ambitions, but myself as well. Give up a piece of my soul? My very essence? I could not bear the thought, in that instant, and I regretted that I had come to it. The pain of true remorse—you cannot fathom. It nearly killed me to reabsorb that fracturing piece of my soul, but I did it. I closed the Chamber permanently, stopped writing in that ridiculous book, which I had come to see was just homage paid to a misguided ideal, to ego, the kind of pettiness I had thought myself beyond, pathetically enough."

Rigel had no idea why Riddle was telling her all this—perhaps he'd never told anyone, and figured she was a safe outlet, since she'd already agreed to keep quiet about the Chamber and Riddle's connection to it. Maybe he'd forgotten she was there, and was talking to himself now. Or maybe he simply wanted her to understand, to learn from his past even as he had, or to offer him some kind of forgiveness that he couldn't give himself.

"I might have known my youth would catch me up one day," Riddle said bitterly, "Yet I had forgotten how fanatic I was back then—even when Lucius told me of the petrifactions, I never dreamed how far things had spiraled out of control. Mad, you called it—but not all of that insanity was magic degeneration. I was nearly crazed, then, only it has been so long…the mind plays tricks, dulls the distasteful parts of memory, makes reasonable the irrationality of the past."

"You aren't that person anymore," Rigel said, though she wasn't sure if she was reassuring Riddle or herself, "You chose a different future. The past doesn't matter anymore."

"Doesn't it?" Riddle raised sardonic eyes to hers, "You yourself expressed concerns that the construct may not be destroyed completely. If it finds a willing host—worse, if it gains a body of its own—"

"We'll be ready," Rigel said firmly, "You'll keep watch for such a thing, and Mr. Malfoy, too. And me."

"You?" Riddle's mouth twitched slightly.

"Yes, me," Rigel said, brows drawing together, "I am its enemy, now. It will come after me once it gains a body, if for no other reason than because I know its plans, now. I can be on guard, and between the three of us, we'll be able to stop it if it does come back. In any case, it may be already destroyed, withered from lack of host."

"Fate is not so kind, I fear," Riddle said knowingly. Rigel felt a shiver go down her spine, and earnestly hoped they were both simply paranoid.

Rigel glanced toward the pensive, and said, "I need to go."

"An oath first, I think," Riddle said, not moving from his chair.

Rigel froze, "What sort of an oath?"

"One that insures anything learned in this room is not passed on," Riddle said, his eyes stern once more, "You inspire trust, Mr. Black—but I am not a fool."

"Very well," Rigel said, keeping her voice from shaking with an effort, "You will take one as well, of course. I want nothing you may have gleaned from my memory being spread around."

Riddle agreed, and they both pulled out their wands. The oath Riddle asked for was different from the one she'd made with Flint. That one simply insured that Flint couldn't speak of her deception. The one she and Riddle swore would warn her if she got too close to revealing something she shouldn't, but it would let her reveal it, if she insisted. Doing so had consequences, however. If she revealed something she shouldn't, the oath's magic would immediately inform the other party, in this case Riddle, and her life would be forfeit to him, if he chose to take it. The same could be said of Riddle, of course, if he revealed something of their conversation, or her memory.

At last, Riddle carefully transferred Rigel's memory back into her head. Her breath caught as the full horror of that night settled once again in her mind, and she had to blink back startled tears as her brain re-processed it at hyper-speed.

She swallowed, and thanked Mr. Riddle.

"Thank you, Mr. Black," Riddle said, stowing his wand, "It had been an enlightening afternoon."

"It has been interesting," she agreed, mouth dry, "I'll be looking forward to a boring summer, after this."

"Somehow I doubt your life is ever boring, Mr. Black," Riddle said, a hint of a smirk crossing his lips.

"One dares to dream, Mr. Riddle."

Chapter 4

On Monday morning Harry knocked with trepidation on the door to Lab thirty-three. There was a long pause before it opened slowly and Master Thompson blinked down at her.

"It's ten, Sir," she said, wondering if he'd forgotten he was mentoring her, "I'm Harry Potter."

There was a flash of amusement in his eyes, but it vanished as he stepped back and waved her in, "I said the door would be unlocked."

"I thought it polite to knock, in any case," Harry said.

"You'll find I don't care much for niceties—tedious, and time consuming. That will be the first thing I train you out of," Thompson sat down at a modestly-sized desk, situated on the opposite side of the Lab from the brewing stations, and waved her into the lone chair facing him.

Harry sat, feeling off-balance, but determined to make the most of this opportunity.

Thompson stared at her for a beat, then said, "Well? Have you a research topic?"

Harry blinked, and said, "I've thought of several possibilities, but I wanted to discusses them with you before finalizing one."

"And?" Thompson prompted lazily when she paused.

"I'm very interested in Transformative potions," she began, "Polyjuice and Wolfsbane being two I'm most fascinated—"

"No," Thompson said bluntly.

"No?" Harry frowned. Perhaps he thought her too young or inexperienced to tackle such high-level potions.

"No," Thompson agreed, "Those potions are too complex to make significant experimental progress on in the few short months of this internship. Choose a project you can finish."

Harry privately thought that you couldn't finish a project in only a few months, but wracked her brain for a different topic, "I'm also interested in Healing potions. Perhaps I could research the effects of modifications to one of them."

"No," Thompson sighed, "How would you conduct such research? By experimenting on sick people, perhaps? You don't have time to organize such a study, so unless you plan to infect people you know with a disease first, it's worthless."

Harry bit her lip, but couldn't refute the point. What could she do? "I don't have any other ideas," she admitted, "Do you?"

"You want me to come up with your research topic?" he drawled.

She flushed lightly, "No, Sir. Could I ask you about your own specialty to get ideas? I heard you studied under Master Liu—"

"Where did you hear that?" Thompson snapped, his eyes turning sharp in an instant, "It is far from common knowledge."

Harry frowned, "My cousin heard it from Master Snape, who also studied under Master Liu. My cousin told me because he knew you were mentoring me."

Thompson's eyebrows rose, "Snape? Haven't seen him in ages. Heard he has a new paper in the works, though—you know anything about that?"

Harry kept her face politely neutral, "If he does, I'm sure it will be brilliant, as usual."

Thompson hummed, but didn't press, "So you want to know my specialty? It won't be much use to you, I daresay."

"All branches of knowledge are useful," Harry said, "Some are just lesser known."

"Truer words," Thompson muttered, his face relaxing into a bored expression once more, "Very well. My primary realm of inquiry is noningestibles. Potions whose effects are visited on the environment, not people."

"Like cleaning potions?" Harry hazarded. She hadn't studied many potions that weren't meant to be drunk or applied to humans, though she knew of their existence in household products.

"Not exactly," Thompson smirked lazily, "I wouldn't worry about it. The point is, my field is rather limited and specialized—you'll want to do something else."

She took in his lazy expression—almost too perfect to be sincere—his evasive answers and the lack of general knowledge she had about him, and several things clicked into place at once, "You study Battle Potions!" she blurted. It made so much sense.

Thompson blinked at her, seeming genuinely surprised, then his face twisted into a wary frown, "How on Earth did you come to that conclusion?"

"It's obvious," Harry said, smiling slightly, "I wondered why I've never read one of your papers—you don't publish any, because your research is protected by the Guild as dangerous information."

"It is, as a matter of fact," Thompson scowled slightly at her, "My subject of research is, itself, rather confidential. Common knowledge will reveal only that I have an interest in 'occult' branches of our art, which usually keeps the generalist snobs from poking around my research. You will not tell anyone your conclusions."

Harry nodded in agreement, but said, "You ought to publish a paper about something occult, then, at least once. In English, too, as that is your mother tongue. The noticeable lack of publications makes you suspicious."

"No one else seems to think so," Thompson said dryly.

"Maybe they just haven't said it to your face," Harry suggested innocently.

Thompson favored her with a droll look, "Aren't you supposed to be picking a topic?"

"Can I do Battle Potions?" Harry asked, very interested in a subject she'd never studied.

"No," Thompson said, leaning his head back against his chair with an expression of annoyance, "Why can't you pick something easy? Study…I don't know, the effects of different soil compositions on limbus grass or something."

Harry scrunched up her nose, "Everyone knows the effect of soil compositions on limbus grass. DeBlanc did an extensive survey on the subject a few decades ago."

"No one expects you to come up with original research," Thompson said, "It's an internship. You just have to do something not-wrong, and the Guild will publish your project in the newsletter, and the PR will be good all around. Your actual topic doesn't matter that much."

"It matters to me," Harry said, more sharply than she'd intended, "I'm not here to waste my time."

"Just mine, apparently," Thompson muttered.

Harry drew in a breath, then let it out slowly, "Forgive me, Master Thompson. It wasn't my intention to detain you. I'll return when I have a research plan."

She got up and made for the door. Thompson sighed, but didn't say anything as she let herself out and carefully shut the door behind her. She made her way through the Guild, silently fuming. How could he expect so little of her? Of course she wanted to do something meaningful. And she did have several ideas, all of which Thompson had rejected without even hearing them out. The least he could do was offer a direction or subject or—or—anything.

She was walking up the stairs when she heard brisk footsteps mounting the stairs behind her, so she moved to one side, but the person fell into place beside her. She looked over to see Lestrange's smirking face and groaned out loud.

"What do you want?" she asked ungraciously, not in the mood to be polite.

"So cold," Lestrange laughed cruelly, "What's wrong, ugly duckling? Master what's-his-name not all you hoped for? Master Whitaker is wonderful. He spent all morning going over ideas for my project with me—we settled on Wolfsbane."

Harry's head jerked involuntarily at that, which only made Lestrange laugh again.

"Jealous? It is a rather prestigious topic. Cutting edge. What've you decided on? Going to develop a new prank potion?" Lestrange's too-pretty face was absolutely horrid in its mocking amusement.

"If I do, I hope you'll volunteer as a test subject," Harry bit out, "Good day, Lestrange."

They had reached the entry hall, and Harry sped up as much as she dared to put some distance between them. Wolfsbane. Apparently Master Whitaker didn't think it too much of a challenge for an internship topic. She'd bet her favorite cauldron that Montmorency would let Casillas (she was not going to call him by his first name after he'd sabotaged her) research some sort of Healing Potion, too. Was she going to be the only intern with a dull—or worse, useless—topic?

She wound her way through the alleys toward Kyprioth Court, even though it was not quite lunchtime yet. She needed a friend to talk to, and Leo was currently closer than Archie.

Strangely, the common area in the Dancing Phoenix was completely empty, save for a lone mop, called Ben by the regulars for no discernable reason, twirling lazily in the corner. She was early for lunch, but she'd never been to the Phoenix when there was no one at all around. Even Solom was nowhere to be seen.

She was about to leave when she heard a muted cheer and turned around, curious. It was coming from the kitchen, she thought, so she ducked behind the curtain that separated the serving staff from the customer's domain. There were a couple of lads tending to lunch preparations, but the majority of the kitchen staff were crowded around another door, which led to a back courtyard Harry hadn't known was there.

They sent her curious looks as she wandered over, but obligingly made room for her. She looked out into the courtyard to see Leo and Marek faced off against one another, settled into semi-crouches and each brandishing weapons at the other. It was only the jeering grin on Marek's face that stopped Harry from pushing her way through the large crowd watching to try and put a stop to it. The fight wasn't serious, then. A practice bout?

Interested, she shifted slightly to get a better view.

"Go on out," one of the cooks chuckled, pushing her toward the door, "You don't have to watch the soup like us."

Harry smiled sheepishly, but made her way out into the private courtyard to watch the show. Both men were dressed in short breeches and nothing else, their tanned skin sweating slightly in the midday heat. Marek carried his wand in one hand and a long knife in the other, while Leo held a shorter knife that seemed to be made of crystal in addition to his own wand.

They circled one another carefully, not breaking eye contact for a second. In a sudden movement, Leo darted forward. Marek didn't react, and Harry thought he was caught off guard until Leo aborted the movement just as quickly. It was a feint, though Harry didn't know how Marek had guessed it would be. Leo feinted several more times before turning mid-feint and lashing a kick toward Marek's left knee. Marek swung his left leg out of the way and up toward Leo's stomach, causing Leo to lean back slightly as his left hand stabbed his knife at Marek's calf. Marek's knife came up to meet it, in a strange grating of steel against crystal, and Leo took the kick to the stomach with a soft grunt. He held his ground, however, and brought his own right leg up to lock around Marek's retreating left foot, using momentum to hurl them both to the ground.

Leo landed atop Marek, who jerked his wand toward Leo's chest, but Leo jabbed his elbow into the older man's throat, choking him before he could utter the words. He twisted instead, angling his knife at Leo's side, so that Leo was forced to disengage and roll away, unable to block across his body in such close quarters.

Leo was on his feet in no time, flinging a spell that would have caught Marek in the shoulder had he not ducked at that moment, returning with a red jet that looked like Stupify a moment later. Spells were traded so quickly that Harry had trouble keeping track of them all. Leo and Marek never stood more than five feet apart, it seemed, so shielding was largely out of the question. Instead, they dived and dodged and twisted around each other's spells with reflexes that could not have been natural. Intertwined with the spells were kicks, punches, and knife swipes, and Harry was amazed at how adeptly Leo and Marek avoided it all—neither one had been scratched, so far as she could tell.

The heat grew stifling as they fought on, never giving their bodies a moment's break. Harry watched, hypnotized at the sheer athleticism involved in this—freedueling, it must be. The crowd gasped when Leo actually threw his knife toward Marek's throat, but Marek dived sideways, twisting his wand in Leo's direction as he fell. The knife sailed harmlessly over Marek's shoulder, but Leo was caught in the arm with a petrifaction charm, and froze, hand still outstretched in a parody of a knife-throw. Marek's chest heaved with exertion as he rose shakily to his knees, but he was grinning even as he gasped for air.

He didn't notice the knife, now behind him, change direction just before it reached the ground. It swung around and buried itself in Marek's shoulder. The crowd cheered, but all Harry could do was stare in horror as Marek collapsed forward into the dirt with a pained groan.

Leo was released by a helpful spectator's counter-charm, and he grinned widely, accepting congratulations leisurely, seemingly indifferent to the man lying prostrate in the dirt. Harry pushed through the crowd to Marek's side, and knelt down to check his pulse.

"Harry! What are you doing here, lad?" Solom clasped her shoulder jovially, and Harry looked up at him in disbelief.

"Help me, Solom," she said frantically, "We've got to get this knife out—"

Solom and several others nearby laughed gaily at her suggestion.

"Now Harry, stop your fussin' over the lad," Rispah appeared and knelt down beside Harry to knock on Marek's head, "Swift! You still in there? Stop worrying people."

Marek groaned again, "Get Leo's thrice cursed knife out o' me back, then, Risp."

Harry blinked, and felt her pulse begin to calm a bit, "He's okay?"

"Course he is," Solom said, shaking his head, "His Majesty doesn't kill his subjects—no matter how hard-headed and foolhardy they are."

"My head has to be hard to survive my King's underhanded treachery," Marek grumbled, hoisting himself up onto his knees.

"You didn't think I was above stabbing my subjects in the back, did you, Swift?" Leo made his way over to examine the wound, almost dispassionately, "Not too deep. Next time I'll do better." His hand swooped down and quickly removed the crystal knife, then took out his wand and cast a cleaning charm on it, polishing it against his breeches for good measure.

Harry couldn't believe how casual they were all being about Marek's wound, which was now bleeding down his back. Were injuries so common in their daily life?

She dug around in her bag until she found one of the bloodreplenishers she kept in her potions bag. She uncorked it, and held it out to Marek to drink. He blinked at her in mild bewilderment, but drank it without complaint. Harry pulled out her wand, hesitant, but reasonably sure no one here would report her for underage use of magic.

"Do you want me to heal it?" she asked.

"Let him go see my ma," Leo said, shaking his head.

"That's several blocks," Harry pointed out.

"Maybe the pain will teach him not to challenge Leo again," Rispah rolled her painted eyes, "What is this, the eighth loss this year?"

"Seventh," Marek grunted, "That one in March was definitely a tie." He reached back to finger the wound and grimaced at the blood that coated his fingers.

"Let me heal it," Harry asked again, unable to stand the sight of her friend hurting when she knew how to fix it.

Marek shrugged, then winced, "Go ahead. Please."

Harry moved to crouch behind him and let her left hand hover just over the wound, keeping her wand pointed steadily at it with her right hand. She stretched out her magic and forged the connection between her core and the wound carefully. She directed her magic into the wound, coaxing it gently in the cajoling way she found worked best when she practiced Healing. She encouraged the flesh and nerve endings to knit together seamlessly, sending soothing waves of calming magic through the surrounding muscles simultaneously, so that Marek's shoulders relaxed completely under her hands.

A minute later, the wound was healed, and Harry stowed her wand again.

"Nice work," Rispah said admiringly, "Very neat. Not even a scar."

"What?" Marek craned his neck over his shoulder in dismay, "No scar?"

"You wanted a memento for your latest loss?" Solom guffawed.

Marek sighed, "I supposed not. Thanks, Harry."

Harry smiled and followed the crowd back through the kitchen and into the dining area for lunch.

Leo snagged a seat between Rispah and Harry and threw his right arm around Harry's shoulder, "So? Now that you're done nursing my fallen enemies, tell me what you thought. Was I great?"

Harry rolled her eyes, "You're getting sweat on my brewing robes."

"It's the juice of victory," Leo insisted, wrapping his hand around her right bicep and pulling her into his side.

Harry pushed away from Leo's playful hold, wondering at the boisterous mood he was in. Perhaps a result of the adrenaline left over from the fight?

"So Marek challenged you for the Kingship?" Harry asked as Solom served up a meaty stew, "If he'd won, would he be King?"

Leo nodded, seeming unconcerned, "It's a monstrously unsatisfying system, for the King at least. If he wins, he gets my position, but if I win, I get nothing for my troubles."

"You get to stay King," Harry said.

"I'd get that if Marek didn't challenge me," Leo said, "For a lot less trouble." He glanced sidelong at Harry with a teasing grin, "In the past, freedueling tournament winners would receive a kiss."

He didn't seem to notice Rispah choking delicately on her drink behind him. Harry widened her eyes innocently and said, "How interesting."

"Shame the practice fell by the wayside," Leo said, still smiling down at her.

"Maybe people decided sweaty, bloody tourney winners kissing twelve-year-olds didn't make an appealing sight," Harry deadpanned.

Leo winced, "Are you still twelve? That's…disconcerting. Grow up already, won't you?"

"So you can do what, exactly?" Rispah poked her cousin with her fork, "Stop playing the rake, Leo—it doesn't suit you, and it makes your subjects uneasy."

"Everything makes my subjects uneasy," Leo shrugged, though he did stop angling glances at Harry as he ate.

"How did your knife change direction like that?" Harry asked a moment later.

Leo smirked, "Summoning charm."

"You can do that while petrified?" Harry asked.

"Petrificus Totalus is a physical spell," Leo explained, "It doesn't affect your magic. That's why Aurors will always go for the stunning spell over the petrifaction, though the petrifaction works well enough usually. It's hard for most people to cast wordlessly and without moving their wands in the right patterns."

"Hard?" Rispah snorted, "Impossible, you mean. Never seen anyone pull a trick like that before."

"How did you do it?" Harry asked, "Practice? Or was it more of a in-the-moment desperation?"

Leo looked thoughtful, "I just let my magic do what it wanted."

Rispah laughed lowly, "That again. Leo gets ideas about his magic—thinks it's smarter than he is."

"It is," Leo said easily, "Pretending otherwise won't make me feel better, and magic doesn't like to be ignored or belittled."

Rispah just shook her head, but Harry found herself drawn by Leo's account of his magic. How often had she said something similar about her own?

"I believe you," she told him, "I think magic is more aware than people recognize. You say listening to it helps control it?"

Leo tilted his head at her, "Can't say for anyone else, but listening works for me."

Perhaps she would try that. It seemed there was a lot she could learn from Leo—not just about magic, either. She could still see he and Marek dancing around death in her mind's eye. If she could have moved like that, the basilisk never would have even caught her. She would see Remus about taking her training up a notch.

She spent the rest of the afternoon coming up with possible research topics, and by dinnertime she thought she'd found a decently interesting one. Dinner was at Godric's Hollow that night, and it was once again Harry's turn to feed Addy.

By the time she got Addy settled and stopped her squealing with a bottle, everyone else was well into their supper. She piled her plate, but didn't start eating yet, toying with her fork instead. She was slightly nervous, but she took a breath and said, "Dad? Sirius? Remus? I have kind of a favor to ask."

The men paused in their eating and eyed her curiously.

"This is rare," Remus said, "What do you need?"

"I've found an idea for my potions project," she said, "For this internship at the Guild. It's sort of based on one of your Marauder products, though, so I wanted to clear the idea with you. If it's successful, it might pose competition for your product."

Sirius looked intrigued, while James looked simply bemused.

"I can't imagine we'll be upset," James said, "Which product inspired you?"

"The Barrier Button," Harry said. "I'm interested in the idea of making a charm or spell more permanent, like the way the buttons are a kind of shield-spell that was attached to an object. I want to look into imbuing spells like that into potions."

"Like the gift you helped me make for Draco last year?" Archie piped up, "The one that made him fly?"

"Fly?" Lily echoed, seeming startled out of her exhaustion for the first time all evening, "You invented a potion for flight, Harry?"

"Not really," Harry said quickly, "It's more like a variation on the weightless draft that gives you a controlled hover-charm centered on the drinker. It wouldn't be good for long distance travel, because it only lasts an hour reliably."

"Even so, that's very impressive," Lily said.

"Sounds like fun, too," Sirius said, "You should sell it—we'll buy the rights from you, if you like."

"Sure," Harry shook her head at their enthusiasm, "But what do you think of my project idea? Is it okay to create a potion-version of the Barrier Button?"

"Go ahead," James said after sending conferring looks toward the others, "Sounds like a great project. Good luck with it."

Harry smiled, "Thanks." Now all she had to do was propose the topic to Thompson.

After dinner she walked with Remus to the fireplace.

"Were you going to ask me something, or just hover anxiously until I floo away?" He finally asked, holding the jar of floo powder in one hand.

Harry said, "I was wondering if you could teach me something new this week—if I was ready to start really learning to defend myself yet."

"Did something happen to you?" her uncle asked with gentle concern.

"No," she shook her head to emphasize her words, "I saw a duel recently, and I was impressed by how well the participants controlled themselves and their magic. I thought, if I learned to defend myself better, maybe my magic would be easier to control."

"Well, there's a thought," Remus said, consideringly, "I wonder if there's a correlation between wizards' training in the dueling arts and the level of control they have over their magic."

"Could you start teaching me? For real?" she pressed, feeling in her gut that this was something she needed to do.

Remus thought it over, but in the end smiled down at her, "You're in good enough shape, I suppose. The rest of the necessary muscles will only come with practice. Sure, Harry. Come by…Thursday evening, and we'll get started."

Harry thanked him, and headed down to her lab to finalize the outline her research project would take.

The next day she knocked on Thompson's door at eight in the morning, surprising an incredulous look on his face when she then proceeded to open the door without waiting for his permission and let herself in.

"Back so soon," he said lazily, the sarcasm positively dripping from his lips.

"I've got my research topic," Harry said, "It's a really good idea, and you're not going to talk me out of it."

"Is that so?" Thompson leaned back in his chair, "Do tell."

Harry took a deep breath, then launched into her explanation, "I want to combine the idea you gave me for area-effect potions with a type of potions I've already experimented in a bit, namely imbuing shaped magic into potions. My actual goal will be to invent a new potion entirely, but the focus of the research paper I write will be on the benefits of using shaped magic for imbuing, and how it can expand the uses of already known potions as well as give rise to new ones."

Thompson frowned slowly at her, "I've never heard of anything like that."

"That's why I think it's an important topic," Harry said, "I've never read anything that seemed to refer to it, either. But it seems to be an extremely useful aspect of conscious imbuing, so I want to do research to find out why it's not more commonly discussed. If my research pans out, I'll work on creating a new potion. Something useful, but not too complicated."

"Sounds interesting," Thompson said shrugging slightly, "I'm not sure 'imbuing shaped magic' is a thing, but feel free to give it a go. At least it's original."

Harry smiled brightly, "Thank you, Sir. I won't let you down."

"Just don't make up your results, and we'll call it a win," Thompson shrugged, "So…do you really need my help for anything, or did you just come in here to brag?"

Harry held in a sigh, "I actually have a related question. How does one go about getting a new potion vetted by the Guild, to make sure it's safe to distribute?"

"That's a little premature, don't you think?" Thompson said.

"I'd like to know now if imbuing shaped magic into potions could be dangerous—I assumed it wasn't, in the past, and I've taken such potions myself without any noticeable side effects, but I thought it would be good to go through official channels, just in case," Harry said. She hadn't considered the flight potion she gave Draco to be a new potion, so she hadn't had it checked out other than a few personal tests, but what if the magic was somehow dangerous? She needed to be sure.

"You've been taking experimental potions?" Thompson said exasperatedly.

"I didn't consider them experimental at the time," Harry said, a bit sheepishly.

Thompson heaved a long-suffering sigh, "If you give a copy of the potion and the recipe to me, I'll pass it along with the correct paperwork to the Guild's safety division." Harry reached into her bag to rummage through the various pockets, eventually pulling out the doses of the modified Weightless Draught she'd brewed late last night just in case Thompson wanted to look at them. "Of course you have them with you," he sighed. He picked one up, tilted it toward the light, skimmed over the recipe, then said, "This is a Weightless Draught."

"It's like a Weightless Draught," Harry said, "Except the kind of magic imbued is different. It should be a good indicator as to whether the magic itself will be dangerous due to its changed nature, since, yes, the rest of the potion is just a Weightless Draught."

Thompson raised an eyebrow, "Does it…do anything a Weightless Draught doesn't?"

Harry rolled her eyes, "Of course it does. I'm not trying to plagiarize known potions, Sir. This one makes you fly."

"Fly," Thompson deadpanned.

"Controlled hover," Harry allowed, "It's like the Weightless Draught, but you actually leave the ground, and you can control your movements with your mind."

"Really?" Thompson looked speculatively at the little vial, "What's it called?"

"The…Modified Weightless Draught," Harry said.

Thompson snorted, "I can't tell if this is all a big cosmic joke, or if you're a figment of my imagination."

"Do you think your imagination is that good?" Harry asked.

"I think that's enough for today," Thompson said wearily, "I'll pass this…modified whatever along, and you get started on your ridiculously esoteric research project." When Harry hesitated, he pinned her with a look, "Unless there was anything else?"

"Is Thompson your real name?" she blurted.

"I beg your pardon?"

"It's just…I thought maybe Thompson was a cover, since you were trying to keep your research low-key," Harry explained. "It's almost suspiciously ordinary, so I thought maybe you'd published papers under your real name at some point in time, and if so I wanted to read a few—"

"Get out, Potter," Master Thompson (if that was his name) groaned, "Just…go."

"That's not a no…"

The door to the lab banged noisily open, which Harry figured was her cue to go. She waved goodbye to her mentor, who made a great show of burying his head in his hands.

I think he's starting to like me, she thought, suppressing a grin.

It was still fairly early in the morning, so she decided to visit the Serpent's Storeroom. She hadn't been to see Krait in a while, being busy with her internship, so she at least ought to make sure he wasn't replacing her with a new brewer.

The alleys were busy, as they always were in the summer months, but she made her way easily onto Knockturn, weaving deftly around old ladies selling fingernails and various unsavory types in moth-eaten overcoats. She ducked into the dim apothecary, looking around for the owner, and instead froze at the sight of an elegant man in rich robes and long, blonde hair standing at the counter.

What in Merlin's name was Mr. Malfoy doing in the Serpent's Storeroom?

A moment later, she mentally winced. What does any well-known figure in society go to an out-of-the way, semi-shady apothecary for? Something illegal, dangerous, or both. She pushed the door behind her open slowly, intending to creep back out and pretend she hadn't seen anything, but Mr. Malfoy happened to glance up from the paper he was bent over, and he caught sight of her shadow on the wall.

He looked over sharply at her, and drew himself up to his full height, "Why are you loitering there, boy?"

He couldn't see her, she realized, with the sun glaring behind her. "No reason, Sir. Sorry to bother you. I'll be going—"

"Harry?" Krait had recognized her well enough, but, she supposed, he had good reason to think a kid coming in would be her, not anyone else. Mr. Malfoy had no such reason to think Rigel Black would be there. "Come in, come in. I'll be with you in a shake."

She ducked her head as she entered the shop, but from Malfoy's sharp, indrawn breath, it hadn't been enough.

"Rigel? What are you doing here?" he said urgently, looking swiftly through the dirty shop window, "What is your father thinking, letting you wander this far south of the main alley?"

She affected a confused but disinterested expression and cocked her head at the Malfoy patriarch, "Who?"

"Rigel—" Malfoy stopped, peered at her eyes, and stepped closer, "You look remarkably similar to another boy I know, about your age."

"That's interesting," Harry said, though her tone intimated it was anything but, "Who're you?"

"That is none of your concern," Mr. Malfoy said, raising his chin haughtily.

"Then I guess it's none of your concern who I look like," Harry said bluntly. She knew she was being rude, but the point was to seem un-Rigel-like.

"Harry," Krait said exasperatedly, "Sorry, Sir. Harry's a good employee, but sometimes the tongue runs away with a kid's manners."

"And sometimes kids have more manners than adults," Harry rolled her eyes for good measure, "Least we don't talk about someone who's right there."

"Why don't you go wait in the storeroom, Harry?" Krait said, exasperated.

Harry shrugged and did just that. A few minutes later Mr. Malfoy left the shop, and Krait came into the backroom with raised eyebrows.

"Want to tell me why you were so rude to that customer?" Krait asked, "It's never too late to fire you, you know."

"What did Mr. Malfoy want?" Harry asked directly.

Krait blinked, "You know him?"

"Everyone knows who Mr. Malfoy is," Harry said, "My cousin goes to school with his son. What did he want?"

Krait scratched his neck and held out a roll of parchment. Harry took it, then skimmed it over as Krait explained, "He wanted to know if I could brew that, as soon as possible."

"It's some kind of power-suppressor," Harry mused, looking over the ingredients and steps, "Looks a bit like the potion Aurors use to suppress the magic of short-term prisoners, but milder. What did you tell him?"

"I told him I'd ask my brewers," Krait said dryly, "So? Got time for it?"

Harry looked thoughtfully at the recipe. It didn't seem any more complicated than Snowhit, and the ingredients were common ones. Why didn't Mr. Malfoy get Snape to brew it for him? Was it illegal? No, it was too mild to be really dangerous—a wizard would probably be able to break its effects, if he had to. It was more like something you'd give a child to soothe accidental magic. So what did Malfoy want with it? Draco was long past his accidental magic incidents, as far as Harry knew.

Should she do it? She couldn't see any real harm in it. Maybe Malfoy simply didn't want to bother Snape with a potion he could get elsewhere? Snape was probably rather busy, if he was in the process of publishing his latest finds on Wolfsbane.

"I can brew this," Harry said, "I'll go do it now, in fact. Owl Mr. Malfoy that he can pick it up this afternoon."

Krait nodded slowly, "Very well. He'll pay a good sum for it, I'd wager."

"Don't overcharge him, Krait," Harry said, "He's…a friend."

"He didn't seem aware of that," Krait said.

"Still, I'd appreciate it. And, hopefully this goes without saying, but keep my name out of it, please," Harry said.

"Whatever you say," Krait said, putting his hands up in a sign of defeat, "You brew 'em, I just sell 'em, lad—er, lass."

"'Lad' is fine," Harry said distractedly, "I don't care."

Krait grimaced, "Not sure that's a good thing."

Harry was as good as her word, brewing and delivering the potion by early afternoon. She made two batches, unsure what quantity would be appropriate, and Krait assured her later that Malfoy had bought every dose. She put the oddity of Mr. Malfoy's purchase to the back of her mind, however, and continued to do research for her project for the rest of the week, occasionally checking in to meet with (read: annoy) her mentor. It served him right, really, for being so faux-lazy, unhelpful, and secretive.

On Thursday evening she flooed to Remus' house before dinner and found he and Sirius warming up in the downstairs gym, on the mats that made up the sparring floor.

"Hello, Sirius," Harry said, "Are you here to help Remus teach me?"

"We're going to show you a practice duel," Sirius said, looking excited, "So you know generally what the art's about before you start."

"Thanks a lot, Uncle Sirius," Harry said genuinely. Then she grinned a bit, "I promise not to think less of you if you lose."

Sirius spluttered and Remus laughed heartily.

"This just goes to show that children clearly know nothing about anything," Sirius sniffed, "I happen to be an amazing duelist. .ING."

"I hear Remus is better," Harry shrugged, not sincere in the slightest. It was nice just joking around with her uncles, sometimes.

"You must have heard that from Remus," Sirius pouted, "Just you watch. I'll be the one laughing in the end."

Harry made a show of looking upwards, "I think you just gave Fate an engraved invitation to your own undoing, Uncle Sirius. Good luck, though."

Remus couldn't contain a snort of agreement as he set up the dueling barrier that would protect their surroundings from any stray spells.

Sirius and Remus squared off on the sparring mats, a good ten paces from one another, and bowed formally. Harry watched with interest as they sized each other up, both standing with knees slightly bent, but nowhere near the half-crouch that Leo and Marek had fought in.

Remus began the duel with a quick stunner, which Sirius easily countered, but from there the curses got a lot more…interesting. She recognized a jelly-leg jinx and a curse that turned the victim's hair pink for twelve days, but most of the curses were said too quietly for her to hear, and blocked too quickly for her to see their effects. The exchange was rapid, but Harry was struck by just how much of it was an exchange. They almost seemed to take it in turns, casting and blocking, then casting and blocking again. She wondered if this was some kind of dueling etiquette, or for her benefit, so she could see each move clearly.

She also noticed that the two kept the distance of ten or so paces between them about constant throughout the duel. When one gained a bit of ground, the other gave it, and vice versa. They never came close enough for physical contact, so none of the spells were ever fired point-blank. Perhaps because of this, there wasn't much dodging going on. As one cast a curse, the other would cast something else to block it—a shield or a counter-curse. As the hexes and jinxes got more elaborate, their methods of counter became more specialized, too, and most of the magic being performed was stuff she'd never seen before, as opposed to Marek and Leo's fight, where she'd recognized almost every spell thrown.

Remus cast a mirror shield at one point, which bounced Sirius' own curse back at him, forcing him to deal with it and the hex Remus sent right after it. He caught the first, but the second got him square in the chest. He immediately began laughing, bent double and gasping for breath. It was short word for Remus to summon his wand, as Sirius couldn't stop laughing long enough to even protest, much less negate the spell.

Remus undid both his hex and the barrier spell, and Harry walked over to join them as they drank deeply from water bottles on the side of the mats.

"So?" Remus asked, wiping his brow, "What did you think?"

"I think Sirius was right," Harry said, nudging him with her knee as she sat, "He really did have the last laugh."

"Ha. Ha. That's clever, Harry. I suppose Remus cast that last one on purpose, too," Sirius shook his head in mock betrayal.

"Guilty," Remus grinned, "But what did you think of the formal dueling style?"

"It seemed sort of…showy," Harry said honestly, "You won because you didn't wait for him to deal with a hex before casting another one, but why weren't you both doing that from the start?"

Remus and Sirius both nodded.

"It was an exhibition duel," Remus said, "So the point was to see the exchange of spells clearly. In true battle, it would have been just as you described."

"We'd move around more, too," Sirius said, "Avoid more curses than we countered, at least if we had a clear battleground—when you're fighting in a group, it becomes more important to negate spells than to let them hit one of your comrades. A good duelist can think up a range of creative responses to any given spell—and in the moment, too."

Harry nodded in thought. Traditional dueling had its advantages, too, then. She wondered if there wasn't a way to combine formal dueling with freedueling, to defend in a way that was both quick and appropriate to the situation, to respond creatively to a threat, but also unexpectedly, as with a knife or a fist.

"I want to learn," she decided.

"Then I hope you're fast, little niece," Sirius grinned, "Because lesson number one is don't get hit."

She looked trepidatiously at him, but Remus shook his head.

"We'll start lesson one tomorrow night," he promised, "For now—dinner."

They all flooed back to Godric's Hollow, where Lily promptly sent Sirius and Remus back to their respective houses to "shower, for Merlin's sake." Harry began to set the table as Lily and James finished up preparations, and Lily said, "Harry, are you busy this weekend?"

Harry shook her head, "I don't think so. Do you need me?"

Lily nodded, "I promised Alice I'd meet her for tea on Saturday, but your father told Sirius they could go to Zonko's to renegotiate a few terms of their contract that afternoon. Can you watch Addy for us for a few hours?"

Harry was tempted to say no, but, really, how could she? "Of course, Mum," she said, trying not to imagine what a few hours of constant crying was going to be like. Could babies even cry that long without stopping? Probably Addy could, from what Harry had seen.

"It'll be fine, Harry," Lily said, sensing her hesitance, "Addy just needs to get used to you."

"You're probably right," Harry said, though inwardly she did not think it was going to be fine. Not at all.

Friday morning found her making use of the Guild Library to search for references and precursors to her project.

Unfortunately, she wasn't the only one.

Lestrange, who had been sending her gloating looks whenever they passed in the Guild halls, was also in the Library researching. The trouble was, he didn't seem to be at all focused on his own research. Every five minutes or so she felt eyes on her as she worked, and though she did her best to ignore him, being silently watched grated on her nerves the longer it went on.

When he finally said, "Potter," her patience was already worn thin.

"What?" she snapped, re-shelving a book she'd been perusing in a single, sharp gesture.

Lestrange's face morphed into a sneer so fast, you'd think it was his default setting, "You know a werewolf."

Harry's eyelid twitched, "Is that an accusation?" She'd already known he knew about Remus' condition—his words at the New Year Gala had made that clear enough. Why would he want to rub it in now?

"I need information on specific werewolves," Lestrange gritted out, "For my research."

That didn't do anything to help Harry's mood. She'd almost forgotten he'd been allowed to study Wolfsbane when she wasn't. She scowled harder, "Good for you."

He smirked as though he knew exactly why she was irritated, "Don't be jealous—it's not my fault your Master doesn't have much confidence in your abilities. It's a shame, really—Master Whitaker has been so accommodating to my own ambitions."

She focused all her willpower on convincing her magic that no matter how angry she was, Lestrange was not a threat. Not-a-threat not-a-threat…Merlin, but she hated that look on his face.

"Anyway, I need data," Lestrange went on blithely, "Subject's age, sex, date infected, severity of transformations, years spent taking Wolfsbane, if any, noticeable side effects on the body, but most importantly on the subject's magical—"

Harry wasn't getting her magic under control. It was boiling and hissing in her veins, and she literally couldn't stand listening to him go on about his project for one more second. She tucked the book she was borrowing into her bag and strode toward the doors.

"—and—hey, wait!" Lestrange called.

She left the library, thinking it would about serve Lestrange right if he couldn't get the information he needed to complete his project. Smug jerk.

The book she'd taken from the Guild Library was a rare tomb on the use of stones in potion making. Her theory was that imbuing shaped magic was quite similar to using different kinds of stones in potions, in that the kind of magic added wasn't precisely 'free' magic. She was curious to see how far potioneers had experimented with stones, and whether anyone had connected the practice of using stones to shape the magic added to a potion with actively shaping the magic the potioneer imbued himself. Surely the two methods couldn't be so different.

She wanted to know how stones had been used to expand the uses of known potions, for surely she was not the first to think of adding properties to the magic of a potion itself, rather than adding ingredients that changed the properties of the potion indirectly. Her working hypothesis was that adding stones with symbiotic magic would enhance a potion's effects, but she wondered what adding a stone with properties that didn't complement the potion would do. Would there be mixed effects, or would the potion's effects be tempered or even negated?

She also wanted to know if anyone had created a potion that didn't have any properties, specifically for use with stones or other kinds of imbued magic. If not, she would have to invent that herself, though in theory it wouldn't be too difficult, because she wouldn't be trying to get the potion to do anything—just the opposite. It certainly bore more in-depth research.

By the time she left the Guild, she had almost forgotten the smug, gloating look on Lestrange's face. Well, let him goat. Her project was going to be just as interesting—and a good deal more original—by the time she was through.

Harry dove out of the way just as a stinging hex hit the mat where she'd been standing a moment before.

"That was way below the belt, Uncle Remus," Harry complained, pushing to her knees only to roll to the side as yet another hex whooshed toward her ear.

"Tired already, Harry? This was your idea," Remus said, forcing her to abort her roll and twist to the side to prevent herself from colliding with a cleverly aimed hex.

She managed to stand up before Remus cast again, and dodged three more stinging hexes by weaving on her feet. Then Remus' eyes moved one way and his wand moved another, Harry hesitated too long in picking a direction, and Remus' hex hit her thigh before she leapt away.

"Ow," she hissed.

"What's that?" Remus called mockingly from across the practice arena.

"I said 'wow,' Uncle Remus," Harry said, panting slightly, "I think your stinging hexes are getting better with all the practice."

"Maybe I'll be able to do it nonverbally by the end of the night," Remus said cheerfully, before sending another hex her way.

She was learning how to dodge, or else Remus was a closest sadist. It was hard, frustrating work, trying to train her reflexes into something workable, instead of panicked reactions that did more harm than good. Twice already she had dived into a hex instead of away from it. It seemed obvious—move away from the painful magic—and yet her body didn't listen to her brain on the few occasions when her brain had enough time to formulate a message for it to hear.

"You're over thinking it again," Remus scolded her and Harry wavered and second-guessed herself once more, "Just move."

Harry tried to empty her mind, to relax her muscles and just do what felt right, but her mind felt scattered. Maybe it was the enclosed space, maybe it was that she felt foolish jumping around like a grasshopper as Remus lazily tossed hexes her way, or maybe it was that half of her attention was spent on making sure her magic didn't react and her body did. It wanted to defend her, or to attack the source of her difficulties, but the point of the exercise was to hone her body, not her magic, to help her practice avoiding danger instead of simply reacting to it. Magic, Remus had explained, didn't always need to be wasted on minor threats. Dodging was efficient and effective, and so dodging she would learn.

But it was so frustrating.

"We're picking up the pace a bit," Remus warned, "Don't think, just react."

Harry chanted it to herself as she began moving faster. Don't think. Just react. The spells came closer together, not letting her get very far at all before forcing her to change directions. She pivoted, ducked, jumped, and spun in a dizzying, exhausting dance. Her muscles protested, her lungs felt close to revolting, and her vision narrowed to Remus, his hexes, and her body. She couldn't even hear him casting as her focus zeroed in. Don't think. Just react. The sweat was dripping down her spine, her stomach cramping as she used her abdominal muscles again and again to arrest her momentum and redirect it.

She leapt over a hex aimed at her feet, but when she touched down she slipped on a sweaty spot and went down hard on the mat. She snapped her head up in time to see one last stinging hex come barreling down toward her face, and flinched, bracing herself for the sharp pain, knowing she didn't have time to scramble aside this time.

The sting never came. She opened her eyes to see the too-familiar red of the Despaco Shield coloring the air before her face. Through it, she saw Remus frowning as he lowered his wand.

"Harry?" he asked, approaching her slowly.

"Sorry," she gasped, forcing her shaking limbs to move until she was on her knees, at least, "One second." She reached for her magic in between pants, asking it to stand down, to stop powering the shield. That's what happens when I really act without thinking, she thought dejectedly. Was she never going to be able to control this?

"Was that a Despaco Shield, Harry?" Remus was still frowning as he helped her to her feet and over to the containers of water on the sidelines, "How did you cast it silently? Didn't you leave your wand with your shoes?"

"Yes, sorry," Harry said, very embarrassed, "I swear I didn't mean to. My magic just does that sometimes. I mean, not just anytime, obviously. When it thinks I'm being threatened. I did try to control it, Remus. I'll do better next time."

Remus shook his head slowly, "That's a dangerous shield. Where did you learn it?"

"Nowhere," Harry said, wincing, "My magic just takes on that form when it thinks I'm in danger. I didn't even know what it was, until Professor—" she bit her tongue before saying 'Dumbledore.' "Well, anyway, I didn't really learn it," she finished awkwardly.

Her uncle looked very troubled, "If you didn't have a wand, it must have been accidental magic. You're almost thirteen, though…usually that sort of thing stops long before a wizard's core finishes maturing."

"Are you sure you never saw anyone using that spell?" he pressed, "Did Lily show it to you?"

"Mum?" Harry shook her head bewilderedly, "Never. Why would she?"

Remus hesitated, but said, "I think you should talk to your mother about the problems you've been having with your magic. She might be able to help."

Harry thought that was odd—surely James would be a better help, with his Auror training, but she told Remus that she would.

"Very well," Remus said bracingly, "You did just fine today, Harry, just fine. If we do this often enough, your body will learn to move without you telling it to."

"How often is that?" Harry joked, stretching her sore limbs carefully.

"As often as it takes," Remus said, amused, "Once you can dodge my fastest spell-casting, we'll get your father down here to have a go—if you think I'm quick, it's nothing to what a decade's field work as an Auror will produce."

They parted to shower and get changed before dinner, Harry turning over Remus' suggestion in her head. Why would her mother be able to help her with her magic more than Remus could? She was a talented witch, but not an expert in accidental magic, as far as Harry knew.

When she looked at her mother's tired, determinedly upbeat expression at dinner that night, however, she couldn't bring herself to bring it up. Why bother Lily with her own troubles when her mother already had so much on her plate between Addy and work and everything else? She'd bring it up some other time, when Lily didn't look so worn out.

Saturday found Harry walking up the stairs from her basement lab like one mounting the executioner's platform. It was nearing one in the afternoon, which meant Lily would be leaving for tea with Lady Longbottom soon. Addy would be staying with Harry.

Harry found her mother burping a gurgling Addy in the kitchen.

"There you are," Lily smiled, "I was just going to call you. She's just had a bottle, so you shouldn't have to feed her before I get back. If she gets fussy—" Harry silently thought that to be a distinct possibility, "—check to see if she's soiled herself. The fresh nappies are in the cupboard—"

"I know, Mum," Harry said, smiling slightly, "Just because Addy doesn't like me, doesn't mean I don't pay attention. I'll change her if she gets soggy, and I won't let her play with knives. Don't worry."

Lily shrugged self-deprecatingly, "I'm not worried, I just don't want to forget anything. Well, if you have trouble I'm just a floo call away."

She transferred Addy to Harry's tentatively waiting arms and pecked both Addy and Harry on the cheek before she made a silly face in Addy's general direction and said, "Buh-bye, darling. Sissy's going to take good care of you. See you soon."

Lily flooed to the Longbottom's, and Harry held Addy up in front of her face consideringly.

"Hi," she said, "You don't know me very well, but I'm your big sister, Harry."

Addy's face slowly screwed up into a heart-breakingly upset expression, tiny tears bursting from the corner of her eyes without warning as her little vocal chords started emitting distressed whimpers.

Harry hurriedly clasped Addy to her chest, rocking in place as she'd seen James do over and over to soothe the child. "Shh, it's okay, don't cry…please."

Addy began to wail, a thin, gasping sound that wracked her tiny frame alarmingly. It built up into a stronger cry even as Harry patted her back and hummed a frantic lullaby under her breath. Soon Addy was outright screaming, and Harry could only think this was the worst idea her mother had ever had.

She took Addy into the nursery and quickly set her down into a baby-sized chair that had a colorful mobile attached to the top of it. Harry buckled Addy in for good measure, then stepped back, tilting her head to consider the crying child.

Addy's screams had decreased in intensity, but she was still sniffling pathetically, and Harry didn't know how to make that stop. She'd already been fed, so she couldn't just stick a bottle in her mouth. She tapped the mobile to activate the revolving charm, and was gratified to note that Addy paused in her crying to state curiously at the moving bees and flowers hovering over her head.

Harry settled into a criss-cross position across from Addy's chair, watching the baby watch the spinning toys, not sure what she would do if Addy started crying again. She noticed one of Addy's little socks had come off, but when she looked around she didn't see it lying around. Maybe it had fallen in the kitchen? She probably shouldn't leave Addy alone to go look for it, but what if her foot got cold?

She debated with herself for a moment, then reached out to cup her hand over Addy's pink, wrinkly foot. She asked her magic for a gentle warming charm, and felt the soft heat flow easily into Addy's skin.

When she looked up, Addy's eyes were fixed unblinkingly on her. Harry took her hand away, and Addy's eyes scrunched unhappily. She put her hand back on Addy's foot, but her sister didn't look any more pleased, and started sniffling again. Cautiously, Harry sent another gentle warming charm up Addy's leg.

Addy sneezed, then gurgled happily. Her blue eyes looked at Harry almost adoringly, and her mouth parted in a big, toothless grin. Harry felt her own mouth part in complete astonishment. "Addy?" she said, moving her hand up to stroke the baby's soft cheek. She let a warming charm float across the baby's skin, and was rewarded with another happy giggle. "So you like magic, huh?" Harry smiled down at the infant, "That makes one of us. Want to see some more?"

Taking Addy's rapt gaze to be a kind of assent, Harry summoned a small ball from the nursery's toybox. She held it up for Addy to see, then turned it blue with a tug at her magical core. She turned it green, red, and yellow, but Addy didn't smile, merely watched it happen, a bit perplexed. Defeated, Harry looked down at the ball in confusion. Wasn't it her magic that made Addy happy?

The truth hit her suddenly—it wasn't just magic, it was the feeling she liked.

Harry tugged Addy's hand forward to rest on top of the ball, and asked her magic to warm the ball with her other hand. When the ball heated up, Addy hit it excitedly with her hand. Harry turned it cold a moment later, and Addy shrieked with laughter, smacking at the ball until Harry made it warm again, then giggling again.

Harry kept at it, laughing herself every time Addy did something particularly adorable. She could see why people liked babies so much, now—they were cute, when they weren't screaming, and it felt good to make them happy.

An hour later, with only a small interruption in their game to change Addy's soiled nappy, Lily found them in the same position, both staring at the little ball and smiling delightedly.

"She likes you!" Lily exclaimed, clapping her hands at the sight.

Harry turned and beamed up at her mom, "She does—well, not me, really. She likes my magic."

A look of discomfiture flitted briefly across Lily's face, and Harry hastened to reassure her, "I didn't do anything dangerous around her. I've just been using warming and cooling charms on this ball over and over again. She thinks it's a blast."

Lily smiled, "Yes, babies are often soothed by the feeling of magic. It's why mothers are encouraged to hold their newborns as much as possible; the mother's aura is instinctively soothing to the child, because some of the mother's magic goes into forming the baby's magical core in the womb, so the baby recognizes it. Eventually, the infant comes to recognize other auras as well, the father's, of course, and other people who are around often enough. I knew she'd get used to you eventually, Harry."

Harry stared at Lily, a sudden suspicion hitting her. She didn't have an aura—it was suppressed, according to Snape. Was that why Addy didn't like Harry? Because she couldn't sense her in the same way she sensed others? But that didn't explain why she didn't like Remus…or did it? Could his own aura be different, because of his condition? Would it feel different to Addy?

Feeling her respect for her little sister's perception abilities raise slightly, Harry vowed to research infant care when she got the chance. Maybe there were other ways she could convince Addy there wasn't anything strange or frightening about her.

Monday she didn't go to the Guild, as she had enough to keep her busy researching the use of stones in potions, but she did stop by the Dancing Phoenix for lunch, just to get out of her lab for a while. Lily was sure she wasn't getting enough sunshine, but she didn't know about Harry's frequent excursions around the alleys during the day.

She had found out after asking that although Marek only seriously challenged Leo every few months or so, they and others from the alleys could often be found practice-dueling in the courtyard behind the Phoenix. They practiced there because, despite looking as though it were open to the air, it was actually a heavily warded section of the inn itself, built into wizardspace during the construction, and accessible only through the inn's kitchen. Free dueling wasn't technically illegal, as long as it wasn't part of an official tournament, but it was heavily frowned upon, and so the denizens of the alleys took care to keep it away from disapproving eyes.

Harry had taken to stopping by an hour or so before lunch, just so she could watch. It was fascinating, and frankly impressive, to see magic used in high-speed, creative combination with physical defense.

That morning she found 'Will' the curse-breaker, to her surprise, in a practice bout against Aled Flint. The redhead was once again wearing his scarf pulled up over his nose, but from the way his blue eyes were curved in amusement, she would guess he was grinning as he sent spell after spell at Aled's shields.

Aled laughed, and spat out a stream of Latin, wiggling his wand at his shields, strengthening them, it seemed, with a different layer of magic that blended seamlessly with the first. Will sent another spell at the shield, a twisting yellow light that looked at though it was trying to burrow its way through the layers. Just as the shield seemed to give for a moment, it sprang back outward, tossing the drilling spell aside and into the dirt.

"Give up, boy," Aled grinned fiercely, "Nothing gets through my shields."

Will shook his head, "We'll see, won't we?" He moved his wand in two sharp flicks to either side of his body, and two jets of orange magic streaked in wide curves away from him. They turned at the peak of their sideways arcs and impacted both sides of Aled's shield at once. Violent tremors spread from each impact point, and sparks of bright orange shot out from where the vibrations caused by the two spells met. Aled cried out and averted his eyes from the blinding sparks that probably lit up his vision, and Will sent a stunning hex, thick with the power behind it, into the middle of the shield.

The shield burst apart around the stunner, which sailed right through to knock Aled several meters backwards. When the dust cleared, Aled was sprawled on the dirt, and Will hurried over to revive him.

"What in Kyprioth's name was that?" Aled coughed, standing up once more, "Felt like lightning exploded in my face."

Will smiled, "It's a good spell for breaking layered wards. It creates two opposing currents, and where they meet, the power keeping the layers of shields meshed is disrupted, causing the different spells within the ward to collide and destabilize. After that, one good-powered spell will bust it wide open."

Aled brushed the seat of his pants off, and peered at the redhead consideringly, "How does one defend against it?"

Will smirked, "That would be telling."

Aled scoffed at Will's sudden reticence, but clapped him on the shoulder good naturedly, "Good bout, Will."

"Indeed it was," Will agreed, "But I'm famished—join me for lunch, Master Flint?"

Aled laughed, "You're a mouthful of manners, Master Will." He affected a high instep to his walk and said, in a snotty voice that didn't suit his low baritone at all, "I'd be just delighted."

Will laughed, "And our little watcher must come too," he waved Harry over with an broad gesture, "Come, Harry, won't you grace our party for lunch?"

"I wouldn't dare intrude on such lofty company," Harry said airily, playing along even as she stood and walked over to them, "A poor player like myself would never do it justice."

"But a mite like yourself wouldn't dare refuse our gracious invitation, surely," Will tugged her along by the sleeve in a casual gesture that belied his stuffy words.

"Well, if my lord insists," Harry grinned, shrugging, "Then my lord won't be adverse to paying."

Will shot her a disgruntled look, but snorted agreeably, "That'll teach me to play games with tricksters."

Harry's only response was an innocent look that said, 'who, me?'

Will was quite friendly once he stopped being careful, she discovered, and he chatted easily with she and Aled as they waited for Solom to get lunch going.

"Didn't you say you'd be out of the country for a while?" Harry asked eventually, "What brings you back so soon?"

He grimaced, "In truth I haven't left yet. The job I was going to do keeps getting postponed, so I'm hanging around here to pick up work until I get the go ahead."

Harry tilted her head, curious to know if this was the same job she'd heard about at the Burrow earlier in the summer (for she was about as certain as she could be that Will was Bill Weasley, considering she'd only met the elder Weasley brother once). "What country will you be working in?"

"Egypt," Will said slowly, "I do a lot of work there—most curse-breakers do, actually, as the oldest and most interesting curses are all found in Egypt, India, and China."

"Is that why you dress this way?" Harry gestured to his desert-style clothing, the light, loose pants and tunic.

"That, and it's comfortable," Will said, shrugging. Then he grinned, "Plus it makes me look exotic—the ladies love it."

Harry raised an eyebrow "Your red hair kind of kills that effect, don't you think? You just look like an Englishman in costume."

Will looked affronted, "I do not—I look adventurous, and interesting. Women get all excited if you have a dangerous job. That's why they love Aurors and Quidditch players so much." He spoke as if he was imparting deep words of wisdom to her, and Harry wondered if he actually believed such nonsense about girls.

"Aurors and Quidditch players get their names in the paper a lot," Harry pointed out, deciding she would be ridiculous if he was, "Maybe it's the fame, not the danger, that attracts people. Curse-breakers don't get very famous, though, do they?"

"We're well enough known," Will said defensively, "Our work is very important, and highly specialized."

Harry put on her best 'musing' expression, "I don't think I can name any curse-breakers off the top of my head."

Will narrowed his eyes at her, but said, "It's better if we aren't famous. It would be dangerous if everyone knew who the gifted ward-breakers were."

"A lot more jobs would probably come your way, though," Harry said, unable to suppress a grin.

"That's—" Will sighed at the amused look on her face, "You're having me on, kid."

"I'm not a kid," Harry frowned.

Will sized her up, "You look about eleven. Have you even got a wand yet?"

"I'm almost thirteen," Harry said.

"Still a kid, then," Will smirked, "You're not a real wizard until your core is fully developed."

Harry didn't agree, "Anyone who holds a wand is a real wizard. An eleven-year-old can kill with one as easily as a thirteen-year-old can."

"Killed many wizards, have you?" Aled put in gruffly, clearly dismissive.

"I'm not saying I have," Harry said, "I just think magic is powerful, and shouldn't be dismissed just because of the age of its bearer."

Will looked at her consideringly, then nodded his head slowly, "Perhaps you're right. You have to admit there's a big difference between a wizard before his thirteenth birthday, and one after, though."

Harry only shrugged, "I haven't had my thirteenth birthday, so I wouldn't know. I respect my magic, though, no matter that it isn't considered 'fully matured' yet."

"Enough word-mincing," Aled said, "I want to know that lightning-spell you used on me."

Will grinned again, "I really shouldn't. You could put me out of business if I taught you all my tricks."

Seeing he wasn't outright refusing, and quite curious herself, Harry chimed in, "It's just one trick—it looks hard, anyway. We might not even be able to reproduce it, we just want to see it explained." She wasn't being entirely truthful. If she could, she absolutely wanted to learn that spell—it looked dead useful. From the look in Aled's eyes, he agreed.

"And we're not going in to curse-breaking any time soon, are we, Harry?" Aled said easily.

Harry shook her head, "Better money in potion brewing—more fame, too," she added, just to see Will grimace.

He didn't grimace, though, but looked interestedly at her, "You want to be a potioneer?"

"He is a potioneer," Aled laughed shortly, "Haven't you heard what Harry does around here? He works for Krait."

"He's twelve," Will blinked.

"I'm right here," Harry reminded him.

"You're twelve," Will told her, "Not old enough to work."

"Technically there is no legal age requirement for work in magical Britain," Harry informed him, "People hire based on skill, not age. I could take aging potions every day if I wanted to, and it wouldn't change my skill or experience."

Will looked unconvinced, but shrugged, "I suppose if it's what you want. You still go to school, don't you?"

Harry smiled, "Of course. I'm not going to work for Krait forever. But you've changed the subject—are you going to show us the spell or not?"

The redhead sighed, "After lunch?"

They agreed, and even Will seemed to be looking forward to it once he'd given in. Harry thought he seemed the type to enjoy sharing knowledge with others, a bit like Blaise Zabini in that respect.

Leo dropped in by the time lunch was served, as he usually did, though he didn't join their table until they'd almost finished. He spent a while talking to a pair of women at a corner table first, then spoke to a man who came in carrying a dirty toddler, before eventually sitting down at their table and calling for a bowl of soup.

He snagged Harry's cup and said, "Do you mind? I'm parched," before gulping at its contents thirstily. A moment later he made a face and peered into it, "This is milk."

"It's good for you," Harry said, rolling her eyes, "And you'd have known it was milk if you asked."

"Sorry," Leo said, seeming genuinely apologetic as he looked from her to her cup, "I'll get you a new one."

"I was done anyway," Harry shrugged. In the alleys she didn't want to be treated like she was a high-class lady, unable to drink after a man—but at the same time, she didn't really want to drink after Leo.

Leo shrugged, and finished the beverage with equanimity, "Thanks. So, how's your internship going?"

"Well," Harry said, "I'm still in the research phase, but I think the final project will be interesting."

"What's your topic?" Leo asked.

"Experimental methods of imbuing," Harry said, "I think it has a lot of potential for innovation in the field."

"You weren't kidding about being a brewer," Will said, laughing self-deprecatingly, "What is the world coming to when twelve-year-olds are the innovators in their field?"

"Makes you feel old, don't it?" Aled chuckled, "Our Harry's going to change the world."

Harry grinned, flushing slightly with pleasure. It was nice to have people believe in you, even if they were poking fun at you, too.

"The world needs changing," Leo said, glancing at Harry out of the corner of his eye, "Harry, at least, will change it for the better, I think."

"Not many try to change the world for the worse, Leo," Harry said, thinking of Mr. Riddle.

"As long as you try," Leo shrugged, "If everyone is trying, the result should be somewhere in the middle, right?"

Harry was struck by how true that was, and merely nodded in response to his inquisitive look. Will and Aled were finished, so Harry pushed her plate away and started digging in her pockets for her purse.

"My treat, remember?" Will said, flashing her a grin.

Harry shook her head, "I was kidding. I wouldn't make you pay."

"A kid like you shouldn't be paying for his meals anyway," Will said stubbornly, pulling out the coins for both of their meals and placing them gently on the table.

If nothing else had told her Will didn't have money to waste, the serious way he treated even the few coins he spent on lunch would have made it clear. Harry felt doubly guilty for accidentally freeloading off of him, and promised silently to pay him back when he wasn't looking.

"I told you, I'm not a kid," Harry said, standing from the table, "Next time, I'll pay."

Leo shot her a hard-to-read look as he slowly stirred his soup, "Where are you off to now, Harry?"

"Will's going to teach Aled and me a spell," Harry said, smiling slightly with anticipation.

Leo cocked his head and stood as Aled did, picking up his bowl so he could keep eating as he followed them out to the courtyard, "What kind of a spell?"

"A ward-breaker," Aled spoke up, anticipation clear, "What's it called, Will?"

"It's referred to officially as the Double Current Spell," Will said, "But most of us call it the Pincer."

"It turned my shields against one another," Aled told Leo, "Disrupted all the meshing I'd done to weave them together until they destabilized."

Will patted his pockets down and came up with a worn, white handkerchief. He placed it on the ground, and then proceeded to erect a basic ward around it. Harry watched carefully as Will moved his wand in a circle around the handkerchief, once, twice, then a third time. Faint indents in the dirt around the handkerchief showed that the ward had been erected, and with another twist of his wand, Will turned it red, so they could see the shield clearly.

"The incantation is fulgur flumen," he said, repeating it twice more while Aled and Harry tried to imitate his inflection. "The wand movement is two quick sweeps at chest height to either side of your body, like so. Not too broad." He demonstrated by moving his wand quickly back and forth before his chest.

Harry pulled out her wand and imitated the back and forth flick several times before trying to combine it with the words. She said them a few times, moving her wand back and forth until she felt the movement was in synch with the incantation. At this point she paused, and took a moment to wrap her will around what she wanted to accomplish. She envisioned the twin arcs of orange light she remembered, the way they would turn and bore into the sides of the shield. I want to disrupt it, she thought to her magic, Help me cast this spell to disrupt that shield?

She felt the magic stir, a bit impatiently. Perhaps it didn't enjoy languishing so much during the summer months. Harry bound her will to her magic, and moved her wand sharply, saying the words aloud, this time with intention.

At the end of each sweep-flick, a jet of orange flew from her wand. She noticed Aled taking a startled step back as it came toward him, but he needn't have worried. Before it got very far, the orange light moving in his direction curved, mirroring the movement of its twin, and both collided into the sides of the shield. It held valiantly for a moment, but orange sparks licked their way across it and it wavered visibly.

Sensing victory, Harry shot a color-changing charm at it, and the wriggling ray of magic burst through the failing ward easily. An instant later, the handkerchief was a spectacularly bright green, and Harry laughed in triumph.

"Sorry about your handkerchief, Will," Harry said, turning to grin at him, "I can change it back, if you like."

Will just stared at her, "How did you do that?"

Harry's smile faltered, "You just showed us. Thank you, by the way. That's a really interesting spell. It's sort of fun, too. It tingles, going through your veins, doesn't it?"

Will let out a weak laugh, looking uncertain, "I haven't noticed. You…haven't learned that before, have you? Only, you picked it up pretty quickly."

She shrugged a bit, not sure what to say. She always picked up spells quickly, but it would seem like bragging to say so. She also didn't think she could take credit for it—her magic just liked being used, and when she asked nicely, it was always eager to help her.

"It wasn't that difficult," she said, shifting uncomfortably, "Aled can do it too, I bet."

Aled just shook his head, "I'll give it a go, of course, but, blimey. You've got a knack for ward-breaking, lad."

Will kept shaking his head with bemusement, but shrugged it off a moment later as Aled asked to see the wand-movement again.

Harry chanced a glance at Leo, who was observing her calmly from where he leaned against the wall. There was no sign of his bowl, so presumably one of the kitchen boys had come to collect it while she'd been distracted learning. She walked over to join him as Will began constructing the basic ward once more, this time around a lime-green handkerchief.

"Don't you want to learn the spell?" she asked, settling in to watch Aled's first few attempts.

"I know the Pincer already," Leo said, smiling a bit, "Though the man who taught me called it the Lightning Jaw. It's come in handy, a time or two. Wizards who layer their wards think they're so clever, but you'd be surprised how many of them aren't clever enough to include failsafe buffers between the layers, in case their elegant meshing spells are disrupted."

"The spell doesn't just work on meshing spells, though, does it?" Harry asked, "The ward Will constructed for us is just a basic, unilayered shield, isn't it?"

"The Pincer's usefulness is that it creates a weakness to exploit, even if the shield is all one piece," Leo explained, "The currents produced by the two sides jar the magic they encounter, shaking it briefly out of the patterns that keep it stable. The weaker the magic, the more easily it's shaken. If there was just one point of contact, the shaking wouldn't matter, because the magic would just settle right back into its patterns, but with two opposing currents, the magic gets jostled out of it patterns and into other bits of magic that have also been jolted briefly from their shape. Everywhere the currents meet, magic clashes. When there's one spell, it simply collapses, but when there are multiple layers, the currents cause them to collide and destabilize one another. It can get pretty messy, depending on how many layers they are, and how dangerous they are to one another."

Harry raised her eyebrows, "Will used it on Aled's shields while he was behind them—is that dangerous?"

"For you and me, probably," Leo acknowledged, "But Will's an expert. He probably knew what shields he was dealing with, and how they'd interact with the spell, before he cast it."

Harry's esteem for Will rose a bit more, hearing that. He may have an alter ego, but at least he was responsible with his magic.

"So why the sudden interest in ward-breaking?" Leo asked, "Thought nothing could tear you from a cauldron for so long."

Harry smiled in acknowledgement of the friendly ribbing, "There's nothing about this spell in particular. Will just happened to be willing to show us this one. I was watching them duel, earlier."

He must have heard the wistful tone that slipped into her voice, for he said slyly, "So you're interested in dueling. Ever thought about learning?"

Harry shrugged, "I've been learning a bit of self-defense from my uncle, but it's nothing like what you guys do here. Freedueling is fascinating. Is it okay that I come here to watch when people use the practice yard?"

"Of course," Leo said, smiling, "You could join in, if you want to learn."

Harry frowned uncomfortably, "I'm not good enough to learn anything yet. I'd just be in the way, I think."

Leo considered her for a moment, "You sure about that? I think you'd be handy in a duel, with magic like yours."

She wasn't sure what he meant about 'magic like hers,' but she pointed out, "Freedueling doesn't only test magic. It's the physical stuff I'd have trouble with."

Leo eyed her gangly frame with a grin, "Because you're…small for your age?"

Harry rolled her eyes, suspecting he was ribbing her about being a girl, "Because I don't know how to fight physically, and I don't fancy learning on the fly."

"I could teach you the basics," Leo said, his tone changing from teasing to coaxing in an instant, "No offense to you're uncle, but I can show you a few tricks you won't see in any formal duel."

Harry rather thought he could, at that, but… "You've got enough to do around here," Harry said, a bit regretful, but unwilling to encroach on his free time, which was rather limited from what she gathered.

"You can never have too much to do," Leo said easily, "Come on, Harry. Let me teach you how to throw a punch, at least."

Harry snorted softly, "I know how to throw a punch." James had seen to that, practically the moment he'd noticed her hair getting long. "I'd rather learn how to avoid one."

"I can teach you that, too," Leo said, "You might as well, if you're going to show up here anyway to watch."

"I really don't want to impose on our friendship," Harry said again, "You do so much for me already. It feels unequal."

"What do I do for you?" Leo raised an eyebrow, "You don't brew much for Krait these days, so I can't help with the crates."

"You helped me get furnishings for my place," Harry said lowly, glancing over to make sure Will and Aled were still preoccupied.

"That was in payment for a debt of stupidity I owed you," Leo grimaced, not liking the reminder, apparently, "Tell you what, you want to trade?"

"Yes," Harry nodded. She felt good about trading favors. Maybe she'd spent too much time in Slytherin House, but it felt more comfortable and straightforward than letting Leo one-sidedly help her until she found a way to pay him back for things.

Leo took a moment to think, then grinned, "Come with me to see my ma this weekend."

"Mrs. Hurst?" Harry tilted her head, "I'd love to. How would that be a favor to you, though?"

"She interrogates me about you all the time," Leo huffed a laugh, "If I bring you home with me, she'll have to lay off me for a night."

Harry blinked, "You want me to come to your house? I could just swing by the clinic, couldn't I?"

Leo's eyelids lowered as he considered her, "You don't want to have dinner with my family and me?"

"I don't want to intrude," Harry said carefully, "And…I'm sort of interning at your father's Guild, in case you've forgotten. If anyone finds out he had me over to dinner, it'll look even more like he played favorites to get me a spot."

"Don't let anyone know," Leo shrugged, "Are you really worried about what anyone else thinks? Once they see your work, the doubters will either quiet down or risk looking like fools."

Harry nodded slowly, "All right. If it's agreeable to your parents, I tentatively accept—I have to ask my parents too, but I don't think they'll mind."

"I forget you have parents, sometimes," Leo said thoughtfully, "They can come too, if they want."

Harry blanched, "That's not funny."

"Who's joking?" Leo said seriously, "My parents will probably extend the invitation to them anyway, now that I think about it."

"Maybe this isn't a good idea," Harry said, trying not to imagine her parents and Mrs. Hurst and Leo all in one room. What if they traded information about her?

"Relax," Leo said, reaching over to ruffle her hair, as if to physically brush the worry off of her, "I'll warn my parents not to bring up your job at Krait, or anything about the time you spend in the alleys. Everything will be fine. It's just dinner."

Harry silently wished people would stop telling her things would be fine, but then…babysitting Addy hadn't been as bad as all that. Perhaps she was over-reacting. It's not like her parents would be having dinner with the Malfoys. The Hursts couldn't reveal anything too dangerous. They didn't even know about Rigel Black.

"Ask them, then," Harry sighed, hoping she wasn't making a big mistake, "I'll ask my parents when yours give the okay."

Leo grinned, "Cheer up, Harry. It'll be fun."

Harry smiled back gamely, "I'm sure you're right."

"And come here tomorrow morning," Leo added, "We'll work on not getting punched."

"Can't wait," Harry said, her smile a little more genuine this time. An awkward dinner would be worth it, if she got more defense lessons out of it. How much could go wrong, really, between appetizers and dessert?

She threw herself into research for the rest of the afternoon, taking a break for exercise, defense instruction with Remus, and dinner before diving back in until the short hours of the night. When the words on the page she was reading began to blur, she realized the fire in the library grate was running low. Judging by the headache she could feel pulsing behind her eyelids, she'd been squinting without realizing it for some time.

She yawned, scribbled out a few notes on what she'd been thinking, then shut the tomb on a thin bookmark and stood, stretching. She was learning a lot about the use of stones in potions, but she'd found no recognizable references to imbuing shaped magic. She knew it existed—she'd done it! So why wasn't there any theory? Perhaps there was a technical name for it, and she was overlooking the references or simply not looking in the right categories of research? Tomorrow, she would have to ask Master Thompson for his guidance. If he was unwilling to help, then maybe she could start with the practical part of her research, and backtrack to the theoretical in retrospect.

Wondering about the professional implications of reverse-engineering ones own potion, she crept along the dark hallway toward her bedroom.

Her room wasn't terribly interesting, with plain walls barely visible behind the many bookcases, the contents of which were mostly journals, not books, and were numbered in order of publication. It was one of her indulgences, keeping old potion journals, and she was quite proud of her collection. She even had a few noteworthy editions that had been published before she was born, containing the most exciting and controversial of breakthroughs in the field.

Beyond that…she could admit her room was a bit sparse, with just a bed and doors leading to the closet and bathroom. She'd had a bedside table once, she vaguely remembered, but had gotten rid of it to squeeze another bookcase in. The austereness didn't bother her, since she didn't spend much time there, but it sometimes felt a little barren in the middle of the night, without anything to even throw interesting shadows on the wall.

She set the tomb she was reading at the foot of her bed, where she could find it easily when she woke, and quickly changed into her pajamas. Most people would find it odd how much she enjoyed turning back the covers and slipping between them, dressed only in a short nightgown, but in September she would be back to sleeping fully dressed, on top of the covers, so she shamelessly enjoyed the decadence of sleeping normally, for now.

Eight-o-clock found Harry striding determinedly into a glowering Master Thompson's office.

"I need help with my research," she told him, not bothering to sit down, "Are you busy?"

"I'm always busy," Thompson huffed, casting a quick obscuring charm over his desk's surface so she couldn't see what he was working on.

"So now's as good a time as any?" Harry asked, smiling sweetly, "Great. I can't find any references to shaped imbuing, and I need to know if it might be catalogued under a more specific designation."

Thompson sighed, and reached into one of his drawers to pull out a packet of papers, "I told you, I've never heard of what you're trying to research. What would it even mean to imbue magic that wasn't unshaped, at least without casting a spell at the cauldron, which wouldn't in fact be adding anything to the potion?"

Harry started to answer, but Thompson held up a hand.

"While we're on the subject of things no one understands, the safety division sent your potion back to me last night," Thompson said, passing the paperwork over, "This is their preliminary evaluation, but they want you to make three more doses so they can do additional testing."

Harry glanced over the report, "It says it's 'tentatively approved for magical human consumption.' That's good, isn't it?"

"Read the rest of it," Thompson snorted.

"They request an additional copy of the recipe," Harry said, puzzled, "What was wrong with the first one?"

"They think it was miscopied," Thompson said plainly, "The recipe you gave them was for a weightless draught."

"The potion is a weightless draught," Harry frowned, "I explained that. All the ingredients and steps are the same—only the kind of magic imbued is different."

"No one understands what that means," Thompson sighed, "Potter, you seem to have hit on something—the report agrees the potion acts like you claim, as a self-controlled hover charm. It's your methods that don't make any sense. You can't change the nature of magic you imbue, without changing the nature of whatever's doing the imbuing. If you use a different kind of stone to add the magic, it would make sense. Your recipe doesn't reflect that, though."

Harry could feel herself getting frustrated, and bit her lip to stop herself from snapping. How else could she explain it? "When you cast a spell, you aren't releasing raw magic into the air," she said, "You shape it first, and then it gets released as a spell. Usually when you imbue, you just channel raw magic into the potion, but you don't have to do it that way. You could shape the magic first, then imbue that into the potion."

Thompson frowned at her, clearly not following.

"Imagine you cast a hover charm at a potion," Harry said, "But instead of pointing your wand at it and letting the magic manifest as a hover charm and then travel the distance to the potion, you shape the magic without releasing it, then channel the shaped, unreleased magic directly into the potion, so it doesn't manifest as a spell in the air, but as an effect of the potion once the potion is drunk."

"Casting a spell on most potions would make them explode," Thompson said.

"You're not casting it on the potion, you're incorporating it as part of the potion," Harry said, "It probably wouldn't work to imbue a spell that had opposite effects of the potion you put it into, but for the hover charm and the weightless draught, it works just fine. I'm not sure, because I can't find any actual theory, but I think the imbued magic gets trapped by the structure of the potion's magic, and works symbiotically with it—just like when you use stones to imbue kinds of magic into potions. It's more specific and useful than stones, though, because their properties are so general and vague."

Thompson sucked in his cheeks and seemed to chew on them for a moment, "Theoretically, I understand the point you're making. If you could imbue something as complex as a spell like you can imbue the passively shaped magic of stones, it would be an enormous asset to manipulating the effects of potions." Harry nodded, but Thompson shook his head ruefully, "But you can't just do that. Physically, you can't shape magic without releasing it. The shaping happens too close to the releasing."

Now Harry was the one who didn't understand, and said so.

"Merlin knows I'm no expert in magical theory," Thompson grumbled. He took in her frustrated expression, and sighed, "Okay, it's like this: why do you think you learn incantations and wand movements when you learn to cast a spell?"

Harry blinked, "Because, that's how you cast spells?"

Thompson favored her with a condescending look, "Do you really think you're pulling some mysterious lever in the universe when you speak an incantation? The ability to shape magic doesn't come from the universe, it comes from you. You exert will over your magic, and a spell is the result. The incantations and wand movements help you shape the magic. The magic is channeled through the wand, and as it moves through the wand, the movements you make create a familiar pattern for the magic to follow. Wand movements are worked out based on which patterns best coax the magic into the right shape for the spell's effects."

"So the wand movement helps with the physical shaping," Harry repeated slowly, "What about the incantations?"

"An incantation helps you mentally," Thompson said, "It provides a mental trigger, or pathway, to help you shape your will along. The incantation can be dispensed with, if you perform a spell often or if your will is phenomenally strong, which is why silent magic is possible."

"Wandless magic is possible, too," Harry said, frowning, "You can shape magic without the wand movements and without incantations."

"But the point is that incantations and wand movements shape the magic as you're already channeling it," Thompson said, obviously trying to explain something he wasn't entirely sure about, "It's a simultaneous process, external to simply drawing on your magic. You can't shape magic without releasing it, because it's shaped as you release it, usually through the wand itself. When you imbue a potion, the magic goes straight from your core to the potion, unmanipulated."

"But it doesn't have to be," Harry said, feeling like she was repeating herself, "If you can do silent, wandless magic, why can't you shape it without releasing it, too?"

"You just can't," Thompson exhaled sharply, "All right, clearly one of us is missing something." His tone made it fairly clear which one of them he thought that was, "Why don't you show me? Show me what you're doing, exactly, and I'll try and explain it after the fact."

"Now?"

Thompson pushed his chair back and stood, running a hand over his face tiredly, "Might as well. We'll use the student lab."

Harry followed him down the hall gamely, more than tired of arguing about it abstractly. When he saw it for himself, he wouldn't be able to say it was impossible, right?

The lab was empty when they arrived, and Thompson, rather than taking a seat and watching, began setting up a cauldron at one of the stations. Harry quickly went to the storeroom to collect the ingredients needed for the Weightless Draught, and when she came back Thompson had everything ready for them to begin.

With the two of them working together, the potion was prepared in no time. Harry found herself thinking how convenient it was, working alongside someone who didn't need to see a recipe any more than she did, and who was always ready with the next step even as she completed the last.

When it came to the imbuing stage, Harry connected her core to the potion. On impulse, she reached out a rope of her magic to Thompson's magical core, too, and sent a pulse along that cord, saying, "Can you focus on the connection? Watch what I do."

Thompson grunted, but she saw him close his eyes and assumed he was sending his awareness along the connection she'd made and toward the channel between her core and the potion. She closed her own eyes, and concentrated on the feeling of casting a hover charm. She asked her magic to shape itself like it would shape a hover charm, waiting until she felt a ball of shaped magic coalesce in her gut, before asking her magic to send that magic down the connection to the potion. It was getting easier, she noticed, the more times she did it.

When she opened her eyes and broke the connection, it was to see Thompson staring at her as though she had grown an additional head.

"What was that?" Thompson breathed, looking between her and the potion, "Never mind, don't try and explain it to me again. Potter, can you perform wandless magic?"

Harry nodded cautiously, well aware that her magic's propensity to act without her wand's direction at times was unusual.

Thompson took a deep breath, let it out, and pinned her with a weighty gaze, "Okay, here's what we're going to do. I'll stall the safety division for the time being. You keep working on this project of yours. Don't worry about finding theory to back up your claims—I can almost guarantee you won't find it in any resources you have access to. I'll take a look around myself, but you need to focus on experimentation. You said you want to create a potion?"

Harry nodded, "I want to create a sort of neutral base, a potion that by itself doesn't do anything except act as a receptor for shaped magic. That way, it would be versatile. My goal was then to try to imbue a shield charm into potion form."

"To act as a continuous shield when drunk?" Thompson asked, "That could be interesting, though it might cause a few problems, depending on whether it could be taken down or if you'd have to wait for it to wear off."

"Actually," Harry said, "I thought it would make a good area-effect potion. Like a portable ward."

Thompson's eyebrows rose, "Yes…yes, I see. All right. Get to work, and report to me the moment you think you've made significant progress. I'll help you with composing the base potion, of course. It should be simple, but elegant…" He began ladling the Modified Weightless Draught into beakers, lost in thought. When he was done, he leveled a serious look at her, "Tell no one of this, understand?"

Harry nodded, taken aback, "I've already told my parents a bit, though."

"No one else," Thompson said, "This is important, Potter. I still don't know what you've done, but it was something, and the potential is…" he shook his head, "We must act carefully. Quickly, but carefully. I'll speak to Master Hurst myself." He grinned, suddenly, and Harry felt deeply gratified that he no longer looked bored with her, at least, "This is going to be a very interesting summer."

Harry, taken in by the excitement Master Thompson was exuding, found herself in cautiously hopeful agreement.

Her theoretical research put on hold, the research for the experimentation portion of the project proceeded at once. The first step was to come up with a potion that would act as a neutral base, a potion whose effect was essentially to prolong the effects of the input variable. She thought she might use amber in it, for its permanence properties, but other than that she wasn't sure.

She fell into a routine easily over the next week: wake up, research until she went to the Phoenix to learn self-defense with Leo, lunch, then more researching. Training with Remus before dinner, then back to her lab to try out different combinations until she caught herself yawning.

Come Saturday, Harry took a break from experimentation to spend the day with Archie, who it seemed she'd hardly seen all summer, despite eating dinner with him every night. She flooed to Grimmauld Place and wandered about until she found Archie flipping idly through a medical journal in the front parlor. Draped around his shoulders, flicking its tongue at Archie's cheek repeatedly, was one of Sirius' little snakes.

"Thisss isss boring," the snake hissed at Archie's face, "Feed me."

Harry couldn't suppress a snort, which bloomed into a grin as both Archie and the snake turned their heads toward the doorway in identical expressions of mild curiosity.

"Harry," Archie smiled, "Please say you've come to entertain me. I'm so bored."

Harry chuckled, "So is that snake—by the looks of it," she added, in case Sirius was around to hear, "Want to hang out today?"

Archie tossed the periodical aside immediately, "Flying? We'd have to floo back to your place, but it's a nice day outside."

Harry agreed, and they split up to change clothes and grab their brooms.

Potter Place in Godric's Hollow had a decent-sized backyard. It was warded against muggle eyes, as the community was a mixture of wizards and muggle relations of wizards, who might have unsuspecting muggle visitors over at times.

With only the two of them, they couldn't play a proper game, but they could race. They flew in laps, playing follow the leader and improvising obstacle courses as they went. Harry grinned as Archie barrel-rolled over her head, and swiftly rolled after him. They twirled around one another in a dizzying whirl of speed, over and under, one leading until the other raced ahead, both laughing and calling out care-free taunts.

No matter how close they got, they never collided. She and Archie were completely different in terms of personality and interests, but they'd been flying together since they were four. Something just clicked when they were in the air together, and Harry honestly thought she and Archie could give the Weasley twins a run for their money in terms of synchronicity.

Archie sent her a grin, and dropped into a vertical dive. Harry was after him in a heartbeat, the wind blasting her hair back from her face as she chased Archie's tail. She pushed forward and drew level with him, laughing a challenge when he glanced over. They had been quite high in the air, but the ground was closing fast. She could see the dandelions among the slightly overgrown grass now, and still neither of them flinched. She saw Archie stretch out his hand from the corner of her eye, as though he were reaching for an invisible snitch. With a grin, Harry stretched out her own, and, as one, they jerked their brooms sharply upwards in the nick of time. Archie glided to a stop, hopping his broom and cheekily presenting Harry with a grubby handful of dandelions he'd picked just before pulling up.

Harry accepted them with a makeshift curtsey, then held out her closed fist with a smirk. Archie cupped his hands, raising an eyebrow, and Harry dropped the butterbeer bottle cap she'd nicked from the grass at the end of her own aborted dive.

Archie flipped it up with his thumb and caught it again, whistling appreciatively, "Nice, Harry. I think you win this one."

"The flowers are prettier, though," Harry said slyly, "More useful in a potion, too."

Archie rubbed his chin, "I don't know, I think this bottle cap has a lot of potential. You could start a whole new branch of potions using old bits of scrap."

"What would we call it?" Harry asked, "Garbage Goo?"

"Secondhand Sludge."

"Mishmashed Muck."

"Broken Brews."

"Salvaged Slop."

"Junkyard Juice."

"Recycled—"Harry floundered, "Uh…Recycled…Runny Stuff."

Archie laughed, "I totally win this one! So we're even."

"For now," Harry smiled teasingly, "Let's go again." She got back on her broom, waiting for Archie to mount up as well.

"Want to see who can fly the highest before passing out?" Archie joked.

"Whoever didn't pass out would have to dive pretty quick to catch the one who did," Harry said thoughtfully, eyeing Archie, "You're looking a little heavier than I remember you being. I'm not sure I could compensate for your weight."

"We could take Weightless Draughts first," Archie laughed.

Harry blinked, a slow grin spreading across her face.

"Oh, no, what have I said?" Archie chuckled, not looking at all alarmed. He never really objected to her wild ideas. That's what made Archie so great. Looking into his equally mischievous expression, she could almost pretend they were kids again, daring one another to sneak into Grimmauld Place's attic.

"I have this potion I've been meaning to test…" Harry said, smiling innocently, "When you mentioned the Weightless Draught, you reminded me about it."

"You want me to be your guinea pig?" Archie said, shaking his head, "I hope you intend to pay me."

"I'll compensate you if something goes wrong," Harry said, smiling widely, "Unless you're too scared."

Archie gave her an unimpressed look.

"Come on, Archiiee," Harry said, stretching out his name like she used to when they were very young, "Don't you trust me?"

"Not a lick," Archie said, "But Aunt Lily would kill me if I let you try it alone."

That was always his excuse for agreeing, but Harry didn't mind. "Whatever you need to tell yourself," she grinned, "Come, we can leave our brooms in the shed for now."

They stored them quickly, and, still riding the high of flying so daringly, traipsed into the house. Lily and James caught sight of them as they passed through, and Lily sighed loudly, "What are you two up to?"

"Up to?" Archie's guileless grin was positively flawless.

"Up to?" Harry echoed innocently, employing The Look on her parents with a complete lack of shame.

She could see James melting a bit in appreciation of their facetiousness, but Lily, Addy cradled in one practiced arm, frowned, "I know those excited grins. Whatever you're about to do it dangerous and unnecessary."

"And fun," Archie added helpfully.

"You had the same air of excitement right before my grandmother's Persian rug was found, charred beyond recognition, in the backyard," Lily said distrustfully.

Harry remembered vividly the day she and Archie had tried to create their own magic carpet, so they could fly to Diagon Alley and buy themselves an ice cream. At the time, their brooms still had charms on them to keep them from leaving the backyard.

"I'm pretty sure you never proved conclusively that that was us, and not Uncle James," Archie said.

"One of these days I will petition the Ministry to allow parents the right to use Veritaserum on their children," Lily muttered darkly, stalking into the kitchen in defeat.

"Don't blow yourselves up," James said, probably only half-kidding.

Archie and Harry just grinned at one another, and disappeared into Harry's basement lab.

Harry started setting up a cauldron, smiling as she did so, "I've been working on a base with Master Thompson. We finally came up with a good recipe yesterday, but I haven't tested it yet."

"Are you supposed to be testing it on humans?" Archie asked nervously.

"Well it's not made for muggles," Harry said thoughtfully, "I'm not sure what it would do to someone without a magical core to interact with. Maybe nothing. You're a wizard, though, so you'll probably be fine."

"I'm going to look for a bezor," Archie said, "But try not to make it poisonous."

Harry shook her head—as if she'd give anyone something that could be poisonous, no matter how excited she was. Still… "Third cabinet on the right." Better safe than sorry.

The beauty of the recipe she and Thompson had come up with was that it embodied simplicity. Most of the ingredients were neutral, and the rest were perfectly balanced by other ingredients, so that the result was a potion that acted much like an impression mold, almost completely featureless until the imbued magic made its 'impression' on it. At least, in theory.

It took less than fifteen minutes to complete. She spent a moment considering what to imbue in it, and decided a simple, harmless spell would be the best way to test its efficacy. She asked her magic to shape a simple hair-changing charm, and imbued that into the potion carefully.

The potion turned blue. It changed gradually from the murky-white color that it had been before she imbued, and by the time she finished it was a steady cerulean. The hair-changing charm would have been blue if she'd cast it with a wand, she noted, so the color change could be related to that. She hypothesized that the color of magic was related to its pattern and shape, not necessarily its manifestation, and it carried the color even when it wasn't released from a wand. Perhaps this would help in reading auras? The levitation charm was clear in color, so perhaps that was why she hadn't noticed its effect on the Weightless Draught.

Harry cleared away her workstation, while Archie examined the dose curiously, "Looks cheerful. Bet it tastes like sludge."

Harry smiled. That was one of the things she'd argued with Master Thompson about. The potion didn't have to do much, so there was no reason not to make it taste okay. She'd also insisted they limit themselves to inexpensive ingredients. Thompson had grumbled, but mostly attempted to comply with her requirements. There were still a few ingredients Harry wanted to look into substituting for cheaper ones, but on the whole the recipe had turned out well.

"Bottoms up," Harry said, eager to see if it worked. She was curious to know if the magic would be affected at all by its inclusion in a potion that wasn't designed with complimentary effects in mind, as the Modified Weightless Draught was.

Archie saluted her, keeping the bezor clutched in one hand, and tipped the vial into his mouth with the other. He smacked his lips thoughtfully, "Tastes like vanilla." He paused for a moment, then jerked his head in an odd half-twitch, "Tingles. Is my hair growing?"

Harry grinned as Archie's hair bled blue. Then she frowned. It was a sort of light brownish-blue, not the bright cobalt blue that the color-change spell itself should have produced. Had the effects been muted through the potion?

"What's wrong? Am I bald?" He reached up and patted his hair, looking relieved as he ran his finger through it.

"Let's go find a mirror," Harry said, leading the way upstairs.

They clustered into the main-floor bathroom, peering at Archie's hair from every angle. "Looks more like a muggle dye than a charm," Archie noted curiously, "Do you think it's permanent?"

Harry tilted her head, "Maybe. The charm isn't permanent—it wears off after a few hours, right? I'm not sure what a potion-form would do, though. The base potion doesn't have a temporal component, unlike the Weightless Draught, so…I don't know."

"That fills me with confidence," Archie drawled.

Harry shrugged, "That's why it's an experiment—I'm pretty sure it's safe, but I don't know exactly how the magic will interact with the potion base yet."

Archie laughed, "Still, it's pretty cool. Maybe there's a way to intensify the color? Or you could imbue two different versions of the charm and end up with a multi-color effect."

Harry blinked, turning it over in her head, "That's a great idea, Arch. Multiple imbued spells…I wonder if that would be sufficiently stable. Usually magic is the stabilizing agent in potions when ingredients clash. If the magic itself was unstable…it bears looking into."

"What are you two—" Lily peered into the bathroom, then groaned, "You aren't supposed to be doing magic over the holidays. No, not even a color charm Arcturus Rigel Black."

Archie held up his hands, "Harry did this to me, and it wasn't a spell."

Lily looked uneasy, "I've told James not to test experimental products on you two."

"We tested it on ourselves," Archie said proudly.

Lily sighed, "I'm not sure that's any better." She pulled out her wand and flicked it toward Archie's hair. It stayed blue. Frowning, Lily performed the wand-movements more accurately, and said "Finite Incantatum" out loud for good measure. Still, Archie's hair remained blue. "What on earth…?"

Harry and Archie broke into identical grins.

"Told you it wasn't a spell," Archie said happily, admiring his reflection.

"Muggle dye?" Lily raised an eyebrow, "You'd better hope it washes out."

"A potion," Harry said, "We sort of invented it. You can't cancel it with a spell."

Lily looked impressed, "Do your fathers know about this? It would really take pranking to a new level. Not to mention the potential for espionage…I assume it's easier to brew than Polyjuice?"

"And cheaper," Harry said, a bit smug, "And you don't have to look like someone else."

"Could you modify it?" Lily asked, thinking, "To change more than hair color?"

Harry shrugged, "Maybe. It's still in the experimental stage, but it seems like you can do a lot with it."

"Keep me posted on your progress," Lily said, eyeing Archie's hair seriously, "I think you're onto something big, Harry."

"You and Dad can come to the open house at the Potions Guild," Harry said, smiling. The interest in her mother's voice was gratifying, to say the least, "All the interns will present their projects."

"We'd love to," Lily assured her, "When you know the date, put it on our calendar."

Harry agreed, and she and Archie hurried back down to the basement so that she could record a few notes in her research journal. As she wrote, Archie absently poked about her lab, inspecting anything that had changed or moved since the last time he'd been down, and tossing questions at her over his shoulder.

"Why can't you cancel it with Finite?" Archie asked.

"It's not a spell," Harry said, "Spells that affect people's appearance are cast on people, like a piece of clothing that hangs on a person's body or aura, altering the way others see them. A potion isn't cast on you, it runs through you. Because it's in your physical system, spells cast to negate external magic won't work on it. That's why you can't Finite poison that's been ingested, and why potions like Polyjuice are so difficult to catch. Usually, you have to wait until a potion has run its course, or administer a counter-potion to the drinker's system."

"So that's why there are spells that dissolve glamours, but not any that negate Polyjuice," Archie said thoughtfully.

"There is a potion that undoes the effects of Polyjuice before it wears off," Harry said, "I've heard rumors that the goblins use it as a waterfall to protect the deeper vaults. I've never seen a recipe for it, though, and I'm not sure how a potion applied externally would be able to affect the Polyjuice in someone's system…maybe it's related to a person's aura? I think that can reflect the magical effects a person is under, sometimes."

"What?" Archie stared at Harry, alarm in his voice, "Someone could know I'm under Polyjuice by looking at my aura?"

Harry paused in writing, "Theoretically…yes." Why hadn't she considered that before? It was no problem for her, because she didn't have an aura, but Archie…

"That's bad, isn't it?" Archie said, looking pale.

"Not necessarily," Harry hastened to reassure him, "Most people can't see auras, and most of the people who can see auras can't read more than the strength of someone's magic. Even if you met someone who could read the nuances of your aura, I think it would still be difficult to tell exactly what was affecting you. No one knows about Modified Polyjuice, so even if they thought it looked like you were taking Polyjuice, if they saw you for more than an hour they'd know you couldn't be."

"Still, that could be dangerous," Archie said uneasily, "You never know who has skills like that."

"Mr. Riddle," Harry admitted, "And Professor Snape. Possibly the Weasley Twins, though I think they mostly read one another's."

Archie didn't look reassured, "You've met four people personally who can read auras? And you didn't think to mention that they could detect the use of Polyjuice?"

Harry frowned, "I don't have an aura, remember? They can't learn anything from me."

"Oh, yeah," Archie sighed, "But that's tricky, too, right? What are the odds that Rigel Black and Harry Potter both don't have an aura?"

"I know," Harry said, "There's supposed to be a way to manipulate your own aura. I've been studying, but I haven't got the hang of it yet."

"Well that sounds more important than you learning Healing, at the moment," Archie said, "So use the hours I've been tutoring you to work on aura manipulation as well. After everything we've been through, it would sure chafe to get called out on something so obscure."

Harry nodded, "I will. I've been meaning to look into it more, anyway. I think my lack of aura is why Addy doesn't like me."

Archie smiled, "You sure you can blame that on your aura? Maybe she's just discerning."

Harry maintained that Addy's unease wasn't personal, while Archie made disbelieving noises until they agreed to go to the Potter Library to settle the debate.

They dragged out various books on magical parenting and childcare, and set to work skimming through them.

"Look, this one says, 'magical children at times seem to have an instinctual awareness of those around them most likely to be dangerous to them,'" Archie skimmed further down the page, "It cites a case where a child refused to go on an outing with a family friend, and then it turns out later the guy was part of a rogue werewolf gang wanted for 'wanton destruction of property and bodily endangerment.'"

"That doesn't mean children can sense dangerous people—it just means they can sense werewolves," Harry pointed out, "We already knew that from Addy. She doesn't like Remus any more than she likes me, and Remus would never wantonly destroy anyone's property."

"Well here's one that says, 'magical children are superb judges of character.' Apparently very young babies were used to judge a person's worth back in the Dark Ages," Archie said, skimming his finger down the page, "They—oh, wait. It looks like they were actually being used to test for squibs. That's just wrong."

Harry blinked, "No, that's right."

Archie's face screwed up into a disturbed frown, "Harry, if you think using babies as squib-detectors is all right, you've definitely twisted something in your left frontal lobe. That's the part of the brain that makes moral judgments," he added after a moment.

Harry rolled her eyes, "I know. What part of 'I read your Healing textbooks' is confusing to you?"

"The part where you have time for that between curing incurable diseases and slaying basilisks," Archie said drolly.

"I told you I didn't slay anything," Harry said, mildly irritated, "I don't like insinuations that I kill things."

"Get used to them," Archie said, "Because the official story on the rumor mill in that you slayed that basilisk and then personally hacked it up for potion ingredients. And when I say you, and mean I, the real Arcturus Black. If anything, I should be annoyed at you for making me into some sort of ruthless demigod. I'll never be able to live up to my own reputation."

"You'll just have to do something so amazing that people forget all the things I did while I was you," Harry laughed, "Good luck with that, Arch."

"Thanks ever so," Archie said, a bit ruefully, "Back to our research, though. I still think Addy's Aversion (which I did just come up with all by myself) is indicative of your inferior moral character."

"And I say it's my magic," Harry said, "Here, look at this one. It's references by the author of the book you were just reading, and it talks about various theories for the deep, abiding prejudice that most wizards hold toward non-wizards."

"What does that have to do with children?" Archie asked, his interest clearly piqued.

"Everything," Harry murmured, still reading the rest of the passage herself, "This guy basically thinks wizards hate muggles because of an instinct that is carried over from childhood, rather than because of a cultural prejudice they learn later."

"That sounds like hippogriff dung," Archie said frankly.

"Yes, but listen to this," Harry cleared her throat and read aloud, "'magical children are able to sense the auras of those around them, an ability they normally lose by the time they are two years of age. It is theorized that the child develops this ability in the womb, as a way of recognizing the mother's magical core as distinct from the child's own developing core. Without the ability to differentiate between the two, the magic might meld together. There are also reports of expecting mothers who, for a short period of time during their pregnancy, develop the aura-sensing ability as well."

"That's why babies can tell wizards from muggles," Archie said slowly, "Because they can sense a magical aura—or lack thereof."

"And apparently they are comforted by the feeling of another magical core nearby," Harry said, gesturing to the page she was looking at, "The author argues that magical babies associate the feeling of an aura with the feeling of safety, because they think it means their parents or guardians are nearby to protect them. If they see someone their other senses tell them is humanoid like them, but they don't sense a magical aura, it confuses them. So Addy's just confused, because I don't have a magical aura."

"And she doesn't like Remus because there's something unsettling about a werewolf's aura?" Archie asked.

"I don't think it would have to be unsettling, necessarily," Harry said thoughtfully, "Just different. If the baby saw a human but felt something different from a normal wizard's aura, it would account for the same kind of confusion that muggles cause—at least according to this guy. He thinks wizards hate muggles because of that instinctual confusion and unsettlement a magical child feels around aura-less people. He thinks it carries over unconsciously into adulthood."

"That sort of makes sense," Archie said, "Except for the fact that rational human beings have the ability to act in ways that don't conform to blind instincts. You can't use biology to excuse conscious prejudice—you just can't!"

Harry shrugged, "I agree, but I could see how it could be a contributing factor. I wonder if the prejudice works both ways—are muggles unconsciously suspicious and uncomfortable around magical people? Can they feel something different, or would they not have that ability, not being able to sense magic in the first place? Do you think muggleborn children feel it too? Do you think they know instinctively that they are different from those around them?"

Archie cocked his head, "You know, Hermione said something the first time we stepped foot in AIM. She said she felt like she'd come home. I thought she meant it reminded her of her house of something—her parents are pretty well off for muggles, I think. Maybe she meant the feel of the magic, though."

"You should ask her," Harry said, "I'd be interested to know if that's the case."

"It would be rather heartbreaking, if it were," Archie said, rubbing his jaw slowly. He looked a bit silly doing it, but Harry didn't say so. "I mean, imagine feeling lost all your life and not knowing why. What if she cried and cried as a baby, instinctively searching for the comfort of magic that simply wasn't there? Or what about Halfblood children—what if one parent was magical and the other was a muggle, and the non-magical parent never had as close a connection with their child, just because they didn't have an aura? Or what if—"

"Archie," Harry put a hand on her cousin's shoulder gently, "Stop. You'll make yourself sick."

"It's just so unfair," Archie said, biting his lip.

"We don't know if it's true, though," Harry reasoned, "Ask Hermione. From what I hear, she seems to get along just fine with her parents, doesn't she? I don't think an instinct like this, even if it exists, can matter as much as actual love and care in the long run."

Archie sniffed, "You're right. Sorry. Anyway, I guess this means you won the debate."

"Forget the debate," Harry said, "Let's go steal some ice cream from the kitchen."

Archie smiled slightly, "Don't you have a dinner at your boyfriend's house later?"

"He's not—" Harry bit off what would have been seen as encouragement to Archie's teasing and affected a shrug, "I was going to steal the ice cream for you, Arch, but if you don't want any…"

Archie grinned, "I want you to know that I am in no way fooled or manipulated by you. That said, I would love some ice cream, Harry."

They laughed and started putting away the books.

"You are looking into this aura thing, though, right?" Archie asked, seeming genuinely concerned as he peered at Harry's calm expression.

"Of course," Harry said, "I know it's important for our rouse. I'd also like to hold my little sister before she turns two, come to that."

"I think you'll find the novelty wears off rather quickly," Archie said, shaking his head, "Babies are surprisingly heavy. And they spit."

"I bet they smell better than camels, though," Harry said.

"Not always," Archie said ominously as they closed up the Library and made their way to the kitchens.

Archie did indeed help himself to a bowl of ice cream. Harry was vaguely tempted, once she saw it in front of her, but she reminded herself that it would be impolite to show up at Leo's house and not eat anything, so she settled for writing up a few more notes on the potion they'd made. Archie's hair was still a dull blue, much to Harry's satisfaction. She didn't think it would wash out, either, so it would be interesting to see when it wore off, and whether it was a sudden or gradual fade.

She was of mixed feelings about the dinner at the Hursts' house. On the one hand, she was rather good friends with Leo by now, and he'd invited her specifically—not as part of a group, but a real, one-on-one invitation. Harry couldn't remember ever having received a personal invitation to someone's house before. It was both flattering and a bit overwhelming, and she did enjoy the company of both Healer Hurst and Aldermaster Hurst.

On the other hand…it smacked of favoritism, as Master Snape would say. Lestrange would have an absolute field day if he found out she had attended a private dinner at the Aldermaster's house. It also represented a danger that one or more of her secrets would be revealed. The only comforting thing about the situation was that the Hursts, at least, all knew that her job at Krait's and her familiarity with the Lower Alleys were secrets, and might at least attempt to help her steer the conversation away from more dangerous topics.

Lily and James were both ready to go by the time Harry changed into the only semi-formal dress robes she owned and joined them at the floo grate.

"You look marvelous, Harry," Lily said, hugging her spontaneously.

Harry looked down at the elegantly draped robes that didn't quite hide her gangly limbs, despite their rich fabric and beautiful burgundy tone. She thought she looked rather odd, but then she was used to wearing male-cut dress robes, and never felt quite at home without her brewing boots in any case. The delicate embroidered slippers just didn't feel secure on her feet.

"Thanks, Mom," she said, shrugging a bit uncomfortably. Taking in Lily's subtle silver-blue robes, which made her fiery hair look like bursting firecrackers around her face, Harry smiled more genuinely, and said, "You look beautiful."

"What, no sweet words for your dear old dad?" James asked, pouting playfully.

Harry eyes his sharp navy robes critically. He was the perfect foil to Lily's lighter blue ensemble, but Harry simply shrugged, saying, "You look the same as you always do."

James affected a blow to the heart, stumbling back dramatically, "Can it be? Is all my primping for naught?"

"Hang on," Harry's eyes widened, "I do see something different." Just as James' eyes widened hopefully, Harry shook her head, "No, my mistake. I thought your abs looked flabbier, but I'm sure that was just a trick of the light."

Lily laughed, and helpfully retrained James while Harry made a quick getaway via floo.

She landed gracelessly on the other side, and looked up to see Leo grinning down at her in trim dress robes of forest green, which brought out the flecks of green in his bright hazel eyes. As he reached a hand down toward her, she realized she was sprawled on her bum still, and accepted the hand gratefully. She stood just in time to avoid colliding with her parents, who flooed in together.

They made a sickeningly cute couple, arms wrapped around one another and in matching dress robes, laughing as they dusted the ash from one another's clothes. Harry appreciated their closeness, but felt a bit apart from the picture they made, at times. She wasn't relaxed enough or likable enough, she sometimes supposed, to really complete the picture. Archie was, but Archie was Sirius', and Harry knew from experience that she didn't fill that spot any better.

"Lord Potter," Leo held out his hand toward James, his smile turned up to its most charming, "Lionel Hurst. It's a pleasure to finally meet you."

James' smile was lazily friendly, "Just James is fine," he said, "This is my wife, Lily. We're delighted to say the least to finally make the acquaintance of the only male friend Harry's ever had." He finished his statement with a shark-like grin in Leo's direction, which prompted Leo to grin back appreciatively.

Harry half-groaned, "Is that really necessary, Dad?"

"Necessary? No. It's fun," James said ruffling Harry's hair irrepressibly.

Leo led them into a drawing room done in rose and white, where his parents were waiting by the wide window. "Mother, Father, may I present Lord and Lady Potter? And of course you know Harry."

"It is wonderful to meet the parents of such a bright and engaging young woman," Mrs. Hurst stepped forward in robes of lilac silk, clasping Lily's hand between her own and encompassing both she and James in a smile that was warm and familiar.

"She's pretty remarkable," James agreed, smiling proudly, "We couldn't believe she'd gotten the internship—I suppose we have you to thank for that, Master Hurst."

Aldermaster Hurst waved his hand artlessly, "Harry has only herself to thank. Her natural talent is remarkably well honed for a student her age."

"The Aldermaster is too kind," Harry assured her parents, "I'd never have been offered the internship if not for him."

"The man who discovers a gem cannot take credit for its color and shine—that must go to the ones who molded it," Master Hurst inclined his head in a mock-bow to Lily and James, "To you, I give heartfelt thanks for the obvious care that has been put toward her raising. Facts and theories I can teach, but drive and initiative come from a good upbringing."

Harry could feel her face flushing at the bold praise, and even her parents seemed unsure what to say to such a blatant compliment. Leo didn't hesitate to add his knut, though, saying in a lazy drawl, "Some of it must be natural, Father, else I'd have turned out as fine as Harry did."

Master Hurst laughed, and the others joined in just after, "True enough, my son, true enough. Merlin knows I tried."

He eyed Leo with a mock-disappointed look that was obviously meant to be amusing, but Harry felt compelled to defend her friend nonetheless, "Leo turned out just fine. He's a highly responsible and driven young man."

"That's odd," Master Hurst raised an eyebrow, "I was certain you'd met my son."

As Harry bit her tongue to keep from saying that she probably knew Leo better than he did, Mrs. Hurst said hastily, "Let's leave our poor children alone, shall we? Goodness knows we can critique them enough on our own time. We're all here for dinner, are we not?"

"I hope so," Lily said, smiling, "If that's what I'm smelling, it promises to be divine."

She and Mrs. Hurst began comparing recipes, and Harry freely admitted to tuning out the entire conversation. She wasn't interested in cooking, unless it was done with potion ingredients. Leo engaged James in a conversation about one of the Marauder joke products he'd seen used in a particularly creative way, and Aldermaster Hurst sidled over to speak to Harry.

"How's your project coming along, Harry?"

"Well, Master Hurst," Harry said, "I'm in the experimental stage. Has Master Thompson spoken with you about it yet?"

"He has given me a general overview," Hurst acknowledged, "But I admit I did not entirely comprehend the explanation."

"One of the difficulties I'm having is relating it to known theories," Harry admitted, "But I've hope that more experimentation will reveal something about the processes at work."

"Hmm," Hurst peered thoughtfully at her, "Well, let me know if you hit any snags. Thompson seems to think the project has real potential—I'm inclined to trust his judgment, knowing what I do about you."

"Please stop praising me, sir," Harry said, gazing seriously up at the man for a moment, "I really haven't earned it yet."

"Yet, is it? That's why I like you, Miss Potter," Hurst laughed, "You've a nice thirst to prove yourself, but you won't take handouts."

Harry gave up trying to mentally squirm away from the uncomfortable feeling of flattered guilt that was welling up in her. She didn't deserve such high esteem. Most of what she learned in the last two years came from Snape, who would never get credit for his teaching of her. Apart from not deserving it, she also just wasn't used to it. Snape was a brilliant Master, but he didn't exactly dole out praise with any amount of liberalness.

They moved into the dining room and Leo dutifully carried the platters of food out from the kitchen while the rest of them sat down. Harry's seat was next to Leo, with her parents on the opposite side and the Hursts' at either end of the rectangular table.

"So I expect we'll be seeing you again at the Open House for the student showcase," Master Hurst said as they all dug into the meal.

"We'd love to come," Lily agreed, "We're all very excited to see how Harry's project turns out."

"So are those of us at the Guild who've heard about it," Hurst said, shooting Harry an amused smile, "I don't think we ever seen anything quite like it in one of our intern's projects. Usually they all want to study the Big Five—Amortentia, Wolfsbane, Polyjuice, Draught of Living Death, and Felix Felicis. Those are the potions that fascinate and draw people to our field. Speaking of—Harry, has Mr. Lestrange approached you about the information he needs? I told him you were a good source for that sort of data, and I know how keen you are to see the potion improved."

Harry felt slightly sick all of a sudden, and it had nothing to do with the delicious bowl of soup she was eating. Hurst had sent Lestrange her way asking for data on werewolves? What would the Master think if he found out she'd snubbed the older boy—a fellow potioneer no matter how inflammatory his speech—simply because she was jealous?

She was saved from answering immediately by James, who said, "Lestrange?" with a polite frown on his face, "What information could Harry provide to one of them?"

"The Lestrange Heir is a fellow intern," Harry told her father, ignoring the mildly surprised look on Master Hurst's face as he realized she hadn't filled her parents in on much of what she'd been doing at the Guild, "He's studying Wolfsbane, and asked if I could get a few statistics from Uncle Remus for his research." Harry silently vowed that she would get the information from Remus and give it to Lestrange on Monday. As the sick feeling she got at possibly disappointing the Aldermaster, to whom she owed her internship, began to fade, another feeling welled up in its place.

Shame thickened the back of her throat as she took a hard look at what she'd actually done by brushing off a fellow potioneer's request. She couldn't believe she'd been so petty. Lestrange was a researcher, for all that he was obnoxious. What if he did make a breakthrough? Remus would be the one to benefit. As a researcher, and as Remus' friend, she couldn't, in good conscience, stand in the way of that.

"Is he likely to make any new finds?" Lily asked, interested, "We've heard rumors around the office that there's a new breakthrough in Wolfsbane about to be published."

"That'll be Master Snape," Hurst beamed widely, "Brilliant man. I can't tell you the details of his work, though—he's devilishly tight-lipped about his research."

Lily and James both looked uncomfortable at the mention of Professor Snape, but when Lily hesitated too long in responding, Leo continued the conversation smoothly.

"Lestrange may still make some progress," he pointed out, "Wolfsbane is such a complicated brew, we need as many minds as possible working on it. What's the third intern researching, Harry?"

"Renaldo Casillas?" Harry frowned, "I'm not sure. His mentor specializes in Healing potions, so perhaps something in that field."

"I think it was the Draught of Peace," Master Hurst said, "Something about trying to make it more susceptible to preserving charms."

Harry privately thought that the Draught of Peace didn't need to be preserved for long periods of time, because it wasn't an emergency-use potion like a Blood Replenisher; you could brew it in twenty-five minutes if you really wanted to, and if you needed to feel peaceful right away, you could just take a Calming Draught.

Still, she murmured something that sounded interested, to be polite. She supposed there was always room for improvement, even if there were other potions in the field that needed it more.

The conversation moved on, and it was surprisingly lively. Lily's conviviality, Master Hursts' engaging banter, James' sense of boyish humor, Leo's good-natured charm, and Mrs. Hurst's calm amusement all blended extremely well together over the mouth-watering smells of dinner and the many things they all had in common despite the variety of their professions and interests.

Harry found herself relaxing into the warm atmosphere, and was somewhat taken by surprise when James eyed Leo, not unkindly, and said, "So where did you kids meet, again?"

Harry's mind blanked, before she remembered what she'd told James all those months ago, "Tate's apothecary. We're both in there so often, we were bound to meet eventually."

From the corner of her eye, she saw Leo's lips slowly stretch into a sly smirk, "You make it sound so dull, but as I recall it our first meeting was anything but!"

Harry's eye twitched, but she pasted a relaxed smile on her face, and said, "I doubt our parents would be interested in all the details." She had no idea where he was going with this, but she could guess it wasn't going to be good.

"Nonsense," James grinned, perhaps sensing that Harry didn't want him to press—he had a knack for knowing when people were most prone to being embarrassed about something. It was what made him such a good prankster. He leaned forward with an anticipatory twinkle in his eye, "We're all ears."

"The first time I met Harry, she was eight years old," Leo began, ignoring the raised eyebrows from their parents. Harry wondered how he was possibly going to invent a believable story about her when she was eight, but resigned herself to simply listening. "Harry was a tiny little thing back then, all long, floaty hair and big, green eyes. I walked into Tate's shop, just there to check on an order for my dad, and almost tripped over little Harry on my way to the counter. She looked up at me with the most serious expression I'd ever seen, and this little line of irritation between her brows, as though I should know better than to be so tall."

"That's Harry!" James exclaimed, clearly delighted, "I was always tripping over her around the house at that age—she'd just plop down on the floor somewhere with a book, and give you exactly that expression if you loomed over her accidentally."

Leo smiled, "She was rather adorable, though at the time I couldn't fathom what she was doing in the apothecary."

"She used to sneak out whenever we forgot to ward the floo," Lily said ruefully, "She was so quiet we didn't even notice she'd gone until an hour later when she'd show up, cool as you please, with a bag of potion ingredients."

"I always had my emergency portkey necklace," Harry said, stirring her peas, "It's not as though I was in any danger on Diagon." She had no idea how Leo knew what she'd looked like when she was younger, but maybe he'd asked around in preparation for just this kind of questioning.

"Go on with the story, Leo," Mrs. Hurst said, smiling, "I want to hear the rest."

Leo leaned forward slightly, lending his tale an earnest quality as he said, "So I stop short of running into Harry, and I look up to see a middle-aged woman with dark, curly hair at the counter in front of us both. I assumed she was Harry's mother, until I saw the basket Harry was carrying. It's full to bursting with ingredients, probably dead heavy, and when Harry stops frowning at me for nearly colliding with her, she goes back to scowling at the lady talking to Tate at the counter, tapping her little foot impatiently, her arms nearly shaking with the effort of holding up her basket."

Master Hurst chuckled as the image Leo painted, and Harry severely hoped her 'adorable impatience' was the extent of the story. Then Leo started talking again.

"I realize pretty quickly that the lady at the counter isn't talking with Tate—she's arguing with him. Waving her hands and gesturing at a pink-tinged potion on the counter between them. 'I'm telling you I did it right,' the lady says, 'it's your ingredients that are the problem.' They argue for a few minutes more, until finally Harry just snaps," Leo smiled in what seemed to be fond remembrance, "She sets down her basket with a little huff, walks up behind the lady, and pokes her on the hip until the lady looks down and goes, 'what, kid?' I could tell by Harry's expression that she did not like being called a kid, but her voice is all polite and sweet when she says, 'Mr. Tate doesn't sell bad ingredients. Are you sure your recipe isn't wrong?'"

"She didn't," Lily groaned into her hands, "Harry, what were you thinking, getting in the middle of an adult conversation like that?"

Harry shrugged, but inside she knew exactly what she had been thinking—she remembered that day, when the rude lady in the blue pencil skirt almost made her late getting home for lunch. She remembered everything Leo was describing—but how did he know about that? Had he really been there, that day? She vaguely remembered someone being in line behind her. Maybe it had been a young teenager of Leo's coloring, but she wasn't sure. She was sure Leo didn't invent the tale out of thin air, however.

"The lady looks down her nose at Harry," Leo went on, "All puffed up indignation, and says, 'I paid top-galleon for this recipe, and the result looks just like Venus Juice ought to. There's nothing wrong with it except the potency of the ingredients.' Mr. Tate is blushing at this point, and I'm a bit embarrassed myself that this lady is talking openly about trying to brew such a strong lust potion, but Harry picks up the potion from the counter and holds it up to the light like a little expert. She puts it back down and says, 'the consistency is off for Venus Juice, actually. I can't smell the rose oil, either. Only the color is right.'"

Leo paused to take a sip of water, and James took the pause to ask, slightly horrified, "How did you know so much about lust potions at that age?"

"The Guild did a special issue on them that year," Harry said.

"We didn't buy you a subscription to their journals until you were ten," Lily said weakly.

Harry fingered her bangs uncomfortably, "I bought them in Diagon whenever I was there."

"Whenever you snuck out, you mean," Lily sighed, "We must have changed the password on the floo connection twice a month."

"Dad left the passwords in his sock drawer," Harry pointed out.

James choked, "The sock drawer was warded, too!"

"Not as well as the floo," Harry said, smiling at the flummoxed look on his face.

"Wait, what happened with the lady's potion?" Master Hurst protested.

Leo smirked, "Oh, it gets better. The lady gapes for a moment, then digs around in her robes until she comes up with this wrinkled roll of parchment. She unrolls it, then holds it toward Tate so he can take a look, to see if Harry is right about the recipe being wrong. Harry snatches the scroll before Tate even gets a glimpse. She looks over the recipe, which is all gilded and embossed like an invitation to some grand party, and clucks her little tongue disapprovingly. 'This is a recipe for a mild cough suppressant,' Harry says, 'Has your throat been dry since taking it?' The woman splutters and says, 'but it's pink!' Harry just looks up at her like she can't believe anyone so stupid could have learned to breathe air, and says, 'lots of things are pink. That doesn't automatically make it a love potion. There are pomegranate seeds in it.'"

Everyone had a good laugh at that, though Harry didn't see what was so funny. It was ridiculous to think a potion was a lust inducer just because it happened to be pink.

"The lady looks like she had no idea what to say to that, but Harry isn't finished yet," Leo smirked at her as he said, "Harry nods her head real seriously, saying, 'you really shouldn't trust a recipe unless its been reviewed by a potioneer first. Especially lust potions.' The lady's face goes all red, cause now she's embarrassed, being lectured about lust potions by a little girl. Harry doesn't even notice, just says, helpful as you please, 'the Potions Guild put a warning out in its last news letter about this kind of thing. A lot of people are selling fake recipes for lust potions, and they get away with it because people get placebo effects from drinking the potion, and think their increased lust is because of what they drank, when really they just expect to be lustful, so they are. It's lucky you've got a good mental handle on your bodily reactions, or you might never have noticed.'" Leo laughed a bit himself, then said, "The lady looked ready to crawl into a hole at that point, but Harry still wasn't finished."

"Poor woman," Mrs. Hurst murmured, smiling nonetheless.

"Harry says, 'if you want a real lust potion, try the bookstore. There's a perfectly good one in Potions of the Mind, but I expect it will be a bit harder to brew than this cough syrup was. Make sure you read the legal warning, too,' Harry adds, gazing seriously up at this poor woman, 'it's fine if you take it yourself, but you should know it's illegal to administer one to someone else, even if they're a willing partner. They have to take it themselves.' The woman just walked out of the shop," Leo said, grinning, "Not even taking the pink potion with her, and Harry shrugs, picks up her basket, and starts unloading it onto the counter—which she can barely reach—like nothing happened."

Everyone dissolved into laughter, except Harry, who was busy wondering how Leo recited all that with such alarming accuracy, and Leo himself, who took the moment everyone was shaking their heads and exclaiming over Harry's precociousness to give Harry a slow wink with one bright, hazel eye.

"I can't believe you were such a sharp-tongued youngling, Harry," Mrs. Hurst said eventually, "You're so soft-spoken, now."

"She was back then, too," Lily sighed, "Except when it came to potions."

James nodded, "She's always been unnaturally serious about the subject. At first we thought it was a laugh—she'd get a hold of Remus' prank recipes for our Marauder line and brew a few now and then. After a while, though, we realized she was in earnest about it. Still takes me aback, sometimes, how much energy she devotes to the subject."

Harry privately wondered if James omitted the part where he'd actively discouraged her from studying potions on purpose, because Master Hurst was there, or if he'd really forgotten how unsupportive he'd been when she was younger. She hadn't snuck out so often to Diagon because she liked the adventure—it wasn't until she was ten that her parents actually started sanctioning the trips, even setting up her school account a year early so she wouldn't use all her chore money on ingredients.

The rest of the dinner went smoothly, and her parents flooed back to Godric's Hollow well-fed and amiable to repeating the experience, though Lily mentioned they'd do it at Potter Place next time.

Harry lingered, wanting a word with Leo, and the Hursts magnanimously gave them the room while they began clearing away the dessert plates.

"Were you really there that day?" Harry asked Leo, "I don't remember."

"I was," Leo looked at her with a soft fondness that brought warmth to his bright eyes, "I didn't realize it was you until much later, of course. Only after I found out you were both a girl and Krait's brewer did I begin to suspect. The age fit, and your coloring, of course. I asked Tate the other day, just to be sure. I thought it would make a convincing anecdote for dinner, and if you father believes I still think of you as a little kid, maybe he won't glare at me whenever he remembers I'm male."

Harry winced, though she wasn't sure if it was at James' assumptions or at Leo's insinuation that he had to pretend to think of her as a child because he didn't.

She realized just then how close he stood to her, so close she could see exactly how the skin at the corner of his mouth twitched as he suppressed a smile, and was abruptly too embarrassed to look up into his eyes again. She huffed a soft cough, and took a few steps backward toward the floo, "Thanks for inviting us, Leo. Dinner was wonderful."

"You're welcome here anytime," Leo said, not seeming bothered by her abrupt retreat, "Floo safely. I'll see you Monday for practice."

Harry nodded, gave an awkward wave, and flooed home as fast as she could without choking on soot.

On Monday morning, Harry wheedled Master Thompson until he told her which lab Lestrange was using for his research. After ascertaining that she wasn't planning to sabotage his work (and receiving a rather offended look for even suggesting such a thing), he directed her to lab eight.

Harry hovered outside of the door for a long moment to mentally brace herself for the unpleasant chore she was about to undertake. Do it for potioneers everywhere, she told herself wryly, before knocking three times.

It took a good minute for the door to open, but when Harry glanced behind Lestrange's impatient expression she caught sight of a brewing cauldron, so she couldn't be too annoyed.

"What?" Lestrange snapped, "In case you haven't noticed, I'm a bit busy,"

"Brewing Aconite Alleviation?" Harry asked, sniffing curiously.

"Mind your own business," Lestrange said, making to shut the door.

"Wait," Harry thrust the rolled-up parchments of information she carried at Lestrange's torso, "Here."

Lestrange actually took a step back to stop her hand coming into contact with his clothes before deigning to inspect the parchment. Only after ostentatiously checking it for halfblood cooties did he pinch it gingerly between his fingers and unroll it with a resigned expression on his face, "Is it from Master—" He stopped, and began skimming through the information at a ferocious speed.

"Sorry it took so long," Harry said, slightly sincere, "I had to ask Remus whether he felt comfortable revealing personal information to a stranger." Lestrange stared at her, something unreadable burning behind his eyes. Harry went on blithely, "I told him you were a professional, and would of course treat his information as respectfully as a Healer treats the data he gathers on his patients."

"This is very detailed," Lestrange said, openly suspicious, "I didn't ask you for half of this."

Harry affected a sheepish expression that Rispah had claimed dangerously guileless, and said, "I'm afraid I interrupted you before you told me everything you wanted, so I just included everything Remus and I thought you might need. If there's anything else, just let me know."

Far from looking grateful, Lestrange scowled at her, "What is this? I suppose Renaldo put you up to this, and after I base all of my experimental data on this information I'll find out it's fake."

Harry suppressed an eye roll with the force of long habit, "Look at the watermark on the paper—it's the same parchment the Guild requires for recording experimental results, so you can't write data that's been knowingly falsified on it."

"Why are you doing this?" Lestrange burst out, frustrated. Harry peered at his face, which she usually avoided looking at too carefully due to its permanently unpleasant expression. His skin was waxy and his eyes bloodshot. His fingers trembled slightly where they clutched the parchment, and Harry didn't think it was from frustration or rage. He looked exhausted.

"We're on the same side," Harry said slowly, "If you make progress on the Wolfsbane potion, Remus and hundreds of other werewolves will be the ones to benefit. If no one researches it, they'll be the ones to suffer."

"I find your sentimentality disgustingly naïve," Lestrange sneered, "Of course we're not on the same side. We're competitors."

"We're potioneers," Harry corrected. She wondered how she could explain it in terms that Lestrange would appreciate, or at least understand. "You've heard of Menesthes and Zosimo, right?"

"Of course," Lestrange sneered, glancing back at his potion with exaggerated impatience, as if Harry couldn't tell he'd used a temporary stasis charm on it, and could therefore afford at least an hour talking to her before the potion became unstable, "What's your point?"

"Only petty people refuse to cooperate with one another because of personal grudges," Harry said flatly, "Didn't you think, when you first heard the story of Menesthes and Zosimos, how incredibly stupid they both were? Their useless rivalry set the invention of the Smallpox Suppressant back nearly forty years. When their apprentices collaborated and published their private notes, and people realized that each Master alone had enough information that together they could have perfected the recipe, it was a mark of shame on all potioneers."

"It's a bit premature to compare yourself to Zosimos, don't you think?" Lestrange drawled, glancing over her head with affected disinterest.

"Probably," Harry agreed, "But my point is that I'm not going to fight with you. Not about potions. You can be in an imaginary competition if you want, but I care more about advancing the field of potions than I ever will about beating you, so if you need anything else for your research, just ask."

Lestrange looked like he had no idea what to make of that. His mouth twisted several times before he clenched his fist around the roll of parchment he still held and bit out, "You're still a halfblood."

"And you're still a jerk," Harry said, "Good afternoon, Lestrange."

She turned and walked away, only allowing herself a tiny smile of satisfaction at the huff she heard before the door slammed at her back.

The hours she spent at the Dancing Phoenix learning rough and tumble self-defense with Leo compounded heavily with the training she went through in the evening with Remus, but the intensity of her physical routine over the next couple of weeks was nothing compared with the rigor of her mental exertions. Every day she poured over various combinations of imbued magic and brewed ingredients. She and Master Thompson toyed with different ideas for imbued spells—imbued glamours, as an alternative to Polyjuice, was one that Thompson was particularly interested in seeing perfected, while Harry was more interested in imbued protective charms, herself.

Thompson was very helpful as a practical soundboard. He gave advice on which kinds of imbued magic would be favorably received commercially, as well as which would be fascinating academically, and he was invaluable in helping Harry work and rework the base recipe for the potion she wanted to imbue, but theoretically, he was lost.

He grumbled about not understanding what she was talking about half the time she tried to explain the imbuing process, and eventually started muttering that he'd have to find a Potions Master who was better at wandless magic to help work through the theory. Thinking of Masters who were adept at wandless magic only made her think of Professor Snape, and the pressing problem of her aura. What if he appeared at the student showcase during the Guild's Open House? Her complete lack of aura would be suspiciously familiar to him. How easily could he connect Rigel Black to Harry Potter, if he was given even a hint in that direction?

She needed to learn how to fake an aura, but she had no idea how to go about doing so. The book on auras she'd borrowed from the Weasley twins contained some information on aura manipulation, but it required having an aura to manipulate to start with. Nothing she'd found in the Potter and Black Libraries was very helpful, and she was beginning to despair of finding a solution when the answer quite literally landed in her lap.

"Ow," Harry said unconvincingly, looking down at the heavy tomb that had just been plopped atop her crossed legs.

"You haven't anything down there to be injured," Leo reminded her, dropping down beside her in the dirt of the Phoenix's courtyard.

"As far as you know, anyway," Harry said archly, examining the cover. There was no title or author, just an etching of a mirror, draped with a translucent cloth covering.

"You've been spending too much time about Alec and Marek," Leo complained, "You never used to banter so crudely."

"You're the one I spend the most time with around here," Harry pointed out, "If anyone's to blame for my expanding range of humor, it's your bad influence."

"I liked you better when you were withdrawn and uncertain," Leo complained.

"No you didn't," Harry said distractedly, now flipping through the table of contents, "'Glamour and Glimmer'…'What's in a Name?' What is this book, Leo?"

Leo reached over and leafed through the pages until he found the dedication. It read:

To anyone for whom becoming another is the only way to be oneself.

"It's a book on disguises," Leo said, smiling into her cautious expression, "I picked it up from a guy who owed me a favor. It's a bit Dark, but there's loads of useful little spells in there. I know your birthday isn't for a few more weeks, but I thought you ought to have time to learn the spells you like before going back to school. There's one in there to make a girl's voice sound more masculine, for instance."

"Why…" Harry couldn't finish the question properly, but Leo understood.

"It's to help you keep your secrets," he said.

"You don't approve of my secrets," Harry said, frowning down at the book.

Leo plucked at her chin, raising her eyes to his bright hazel ones, "I want you to be safe. I think your secrets are dangerous, but if you can't give them up, then I want to help you keep them safely."

Harry bit her lip to keep from doing something ridiculous like trembling with the gratitude coursing through her, "Thank you, Leo. This is…thank you."

He probably had no idea what his gift might mean for her, but Harry had caught a glimpse of the possibilities it stored as she glanced through the table of contents. One heading in particular made her itch to get home so she could read it: Building the Aura: Suppression, Projection, and Re-Construction.

It was hard not to grin a bit predatorily as she tucked the book into her potions bag, but Rispah's lessons in facial control hadn't been for nothing.

Chapter 5

Her hair was plastered to her forehead with a gel of perspiration. Dust from clouds of kicked-up dirt stung her eyelids. There were areas of her arms and legs that she couldn't even feel anymore, so many times had she blocked punches and kicks with them. Her heart was racing, her muscles shaking, and Harry had never felt so alive.

Sparring was exhilarating. It was like running—like flying, even—thrilling her spirit and satisfying a physical instinct to just move that she sometimes forgot she had after days cooped up in her lab, but better than running and flying—it was challenging. It wasn't instinctual, and it wasn't automatic. Her mind had to be there, in the fight, every second, striving, pushing, grasping every moment in a vice of concentration and anticipation.

Leo never hesitated, never pulled his strikes when her guard slipped. Her body remembered as well as her mind did what happened when she made mistakes, and it learned how to avoid pain even as her mind figured out how to reconcile strategy with instinct, instead of grappling against it.

She went sprawling across the courtyard when Leo twisted a foot under her guard and into her ribs, and Harry tasted metal where her tongue got caught between her teeth on impact. It was the second time that morning she'd bitten it, and she was seriously considering putting a roll of cotton between her teeth before the next bout.

"That'll do for today, Harry," Leo said, wiping his brow with the bottom of his tunic, "Tomorrow we'll go over low blocks again—you still tend to block higher than necessary when you react without reminding yourself. Good work."

Harry put her fist over her heart in a tired salute to her teacher, then bent over to stretch out her back muscles by reaching toward the dirt and arching. Her flexibility wasn't anything impressive, but she was slowly working her way toward 'limber.'

She turned her mind over the spar, mentally freezing certain moments and acknowledging that Leo was right about the way she blocked. She held her hands high on her chest more often than not, even when the blow was toward her center. Leo was right to correct her, not least because most boys tended toward just the opposite habit—blocking lower than necessary on a purely instinctual basis. Still, Harry felt her mistake was understandable if one considered how sensitive the upper part of her chest was these days. Understandable, but undeniably correctable. Correct it she would.

Her body was growing up that summer, Harry thought ruefully. It wasn't visible, thanks to the modified Polyjuice, which only showed the androgynous body she'd assumed, but Harry felt phantom pain where the changes of her real, presumably more feminine, body would be happening if the potion wasn't suppressing them. She'd read studies that detailed what happened when people with terminal illnesses polyjuiced into a healthy person in an attempt to escape the reality of their condition. They looked healthy, but their true form was still rotting away somehow, and they experienced the pain of that deterioration, even though the body they wore looked and seemed medically fine. A person's true form was something magic couldn't easily get around—it only hid it away or altered it temporarily, most of the time.

Not all of her aches were from growth spurts, though. Most of them came from plain hard work. She could run nearly five miles in one stretch now, if she pushed it, and she suspected that her increased physical endurance was having a positive effect on the temperament of her magic, which had seemed almost docile in the last few weeks. Perhaps willful magic was a bit like lycanthropy, and being strong in body helped with control? She'd have to look into it.

When she and Leo had finished their cool-down stretches, they adjourned to the Phoenix for lunch. She found that she got along even better with Leo now that they'd started sparring. They were still friends, but there was a teacher-student element to their relationship now that added a layer of respect and deliberateness that had perhaps been missing before. She learned a lot from him about protecting herself, though he didn't think her ready to mix magical and physical sparring just yet. Remus had been drilling her in dueling, though, so she couldn't say her development in that subject was being neglected.

It was just she and Leo sitting at their table until Krait slid into the seat across from Harry and thrust a scroll at her.

"Glad I caught you," the man said, "I've got another express order, if you've the time."

"Always time for potion-brewing," Harry said, shoving her half-eaten soup to the side despite Leo's disapproving gaze and opening the more interesting roll of parchment, "The suppressant potion again? I brewed a ton last time."

"He wants more," Krait shrugged, "An army's worth, it seems like, but I told him it'll keep and keep if the bottles are sealed right, so no reason not to order it all at once."

"And if he decides later he doesn't need so much—well, it's not your fault he already bought it, right?" Leo drawled.

"It's a living," Krait grinned like a shark, "So? How soon can you do it?"

"This much?" Harry did a quick calculation of how much free time she'd have if she cut back some of her research hours temporarily. "Three days," she said eventually, deciding to just get it out of the way so she could concentrate fully on her research once more, "But I'll need a lot of bottles, so I'll make several trips over the next three days until you have the full order."

"I'll tell the customer to expect it then," Krait said. He then pointed to a hastily scribbled addendum at the bottom of the order, "He also wants to know if you can modify a potion for him. I told him I'd ask, but you might need time to work out a substitute for the ingredient he wants taken out."

"For an allergy?" Harry guessed, reading over the request quickly. It was for a fairly standard nutrient potion—not one she'd made before, but common enough that she had a vague idea what it contained. She wondered why Mr. Malfoy was having Krait do the nutrient potion—which wasn't nearly as suspicious as a magic suppressant potion, and could easily be procured at a shop that wasn't in Knockturn. She mentally shrugged a moment later, thinking that maybe it was just convenient to get it from Krait, since he was making such a large order already. Seriously, what was with all these magic suppressant potions?

"What's the ingredient he wants taken out?" Harry asked distractedly, "It doesn't say."

Krait frowned, and summoned a quill from Solom's ledger book to jot a note down in the margin, "Sorry about that. It's acai."

"Acai?" Harry couldn't help but jerk slightly and stare at the neatly noted word, "Are you sure?"

"Yes," Krait said, "Will it be a problem?"

Harry shook her head slowly, "No…no, I'll just use Ginseng." The market for which had mysteriously recovered in recent months, "The two are interchangeable in most cases. I just…it's the same customer as last time, right?"

"Yes…" Krait narrowed his eyes, "What's wrong? If you suspect something shady, I'll tell him to piss off, kid."

Harry shook her head again, "No. Sorry, don't pay me any mind. I'll have the nutrient potion ready with the rest of it. It won't take but thirty minutes itself."

Outwardly she bade Krait a polite good day, and began eating her soup again slowly, but inwardly her mind was churning.

Draco was allergic to acai. The nutrient potion was for Draco, then, to be sure, and maybe it was a coincidence that Malfoy was buying the magic suppressant at the same time he bought a nutrient potion for Draco…but maybe it wasn't.

She hadn't considered, before, that the suppressant might be for Draco. It was a potion for kids—little kids, usually no older than nine—who had extreme bouts of accidental magic. Harry had taken a similar one herself once, when she was seven, and she couldn't remember much but her parents never gave it to her again, so she assumed it hadn't worked very well. It wasn't a strong suppressant—just enough that if the one taking it wasn't actively trying to use magic, the potion would keep the person's magic from being expressed accidentally.

Harry wasn't sure what would happen if a wizard capable of voluntary magic, like Draco, took the suppressant. It probably wouldn't stop him from doing magic if he really wanted to, so it was very unlikely that Malfoy Sr. meant to give the potion to his son, even in such large quantities—an increased dose of this potion did nothing to increase effectiveness, after all.

Still, Harry's brain niggled at her, and a few minutes later she recalled the Potentialis Potion she'd given Draco for his birthday—his thirteenth birthday, when young wizards were known to sometimes come into unexpected magical gifts.

Could it be that Draco had come into a gift? One he couldn't control? The odds were astronomically low. The potion almost never revealed anything other than a wizard's basic strengths and weaknesses. If a child inherited a magical gift, chances were that it would manifest naturally by the time he was thirteen—like Harry's Parseltongue had. It could be that the potion had revealed a power Draco hadn't known he possessed, but if its passive effects were enough to need a suppressant to control, then the potion hadn't just pointed out an existing gift, but rather activated a dormant one. Draco would have to have some phenomenally strong recessive magic for that to occur. It simply wasn't likely.

Harry shook her head. She would ask Draco when she saw him on the train back to Hogwarts, but for now she wouldn't worry. After all, Draco didn't have her luck with Fate. The chances of him exhibiting a long-buried trait just because of a potion she gave him were virtually nonexistent. She pushed the traitorous little thought that Draco might be a target of Fate because he was her friend right out of her mind. No need to get a big head, Harry scolded herself, Not everything is about you.

Harry stopped by Mr. Tate's apothecary on her way home from the Phoenix, needing to grab a few ingredients she was running low on, and peered around the familiar shop as she slipped quietly in the door. Mr. Tate was at the counter, his curly hair escaping the confines of its tie as he rang up…Caelum Lestrange. She held in a sigh. It wasn't enough that she passed him in the Guild hallways several times a week? Why did she have to see him at the apothecary, too?

She tried to step into the isles of ingredients before she was spotted, but Mr. Tate glanced up and paused in his measuring and calculating to call jovially across the shop, "There's my favorite customer! How's brewing lately, Miss Potter?"

Lestrange turned at the counter to glare at her, and Harry ignored him as best she could, "Hello, Mr. Tate. Everything's been great, thanks to the excellent quality of your ingredients, no doubt."

Tate chuckled and waved a large hand with false modesty, "Well, look around, look around. There's some wonderfully fresh salamander skin just in."

Interested, Harry peeked at the salamander skin for a few minutes before grabbing a basket and picking out the ingredients she knew she was running low on, including a bundle of ginseng. She eventually found everything she needed, and was surprised to see Lestrange still at the counter when she left the isles.

"Just come down a few sickles," Lestrange was saying urgently, though quietly, "I can pay thirty."

"And it costs thirty-five," Tate said, apologetic but firm, "Either pay the whole, or pick what you can do without."

"I need it all," Lestrange snapped, "I'm a researcher, I can't afford to cut corners on costs—give it to me on credit. I'm good for it."

Harry wondered why he didn't use the Guild's research allowance to pay for ingredients, but then realized he'd probably spent it all—Aconite's Alleviation was not cheap to brew, and the allowance only stretched so far. Harry herself had spent her internship's allowance in the first few weeks of experimenting with Master Thompson.

"I'm sorry, Sir, but I can't extend credit to everyone who comes in here and can't pay," Tate shook his head.

Harry waged a fierce internal debate, one side pleading to let Lestrange go stuff himself and the other reluctantly suggesting a nobler course of action. Her newfound determination to treat Lestrange solely in terms of his brewing ability stepped in, and she couldn't keep quiet, "I know him, Mr. Tate. He's good for the credit."

Lestrange whirled, "I don't need your charity, halfblood! Mind your own."

"Now, that's no way to speak to a nice young lady like Miss Potter," Tate reproved.

"It's all right, Mr. Tate," Harry said quietly, even as her brain railed at her with mental I told you so's for helping the ungrateful git, "Mr. Lestrange likes to poke fun at my parentage when he feels embarrassed—it's sort of an inside joke between the two of us."

"Stop interfering," Lestrange hissed.

"No need to be so proud, Caelum," Harry said, smirking slightly, "Mr. Tate, you really should extend him the credit. He's doing research for the Potions Guild. I'm sure one day when he's a famous brewer he won't forget which apothecary showed him a kindness."

Mr. Tate coughed uncomfortably, but did ring the purchases up at thirty sickles. Lestrange took them with ill grace, but his sneer was missing some of its usual heat as he left the shop.

"Tough nut, that one," Tate said, huffing, as Harry piled her items onto the counter.

She shrugged, "He's a bit unpleasant, but not a half-bad brewer."

"And that's all that matters to you, I suppose," Tate chuckled. He added everything up in short order, "That'll be sixteen sickles, and three knuts. Shall I put it on your school account as usual, Miss Potter?"

"Yes, thank you," she said. She dug in her purse for five sickles and pushed them across the counter as well, "In case he doesn't pay you back the credit."

"Oh, no," Tate said quickly, "I couldn't, Miss Potter."

"If he pays you back, you can credit them toward my next purchase," Harry said, "And if he doesn't, then it's my fault for recommending him. Good day, Mr. Tate."

"You as well, Miss Potter. Don't let Krait overwork you, now."

"I never do, Mr. Tate."

The next day when Harry stepped into the Guild she was startled by the amount of people milling about the lobby. Upon closer inspection, all the strangers seemed to be reporters, armed with dicto-quills and pushy cameramen. Harry wondered what had happened to draw so much attention so early in the morning. Judging by the different languages some of the reporters were rapidly swapping confidences in, the news was big enough to garner international attention.

Harry slipped around the multitudes and trotted down to Thompson's lab. When she walked in, Thompson looked up from reading what looked like one of the Guild's journals, except she could see Professor Snape's striking features on the cover, and he hadn't been on the cover of a journal in several years. Was Thompson reading back issues for research? Unless…

"Is that it?" Harry asked, suddenly excited, "Master Snape's breakthrough on the Wolfsbane?"

"Just published this morning," Thompson said, grinning a bit, "Special edition and everything."

Harry eyed the periodical longingly. Special edition bulletins were only printed for the biggest of potion breakthroughs. She wondered if Thompson would mind if she read over his shoulder, then wondered if she could take the morning off of research to hunt down a copy for herself.

Seeing Harry's torn expression, Thompson laughed and held the journal toward her, "Go on, then. I've read it twice already. Brilliant stuff."

"It's Snape, of course it's brilliant," Harry said distractedly, holding the thin magazine like it was made of fairy wings. She groped blindly for a chair to sit, her eyes already scanning the front page.

Taming the Wolf, the headline of the edition read. Harry snorted at the melodramatic title, and skimmed down to where Snape's actual article title was quoted. "Argument for a New Modification of the Wolfsbane Potion," it was called. That sounded more like Snape—clear and informative.

She settled in to read, and noted with no small amount of pleasure that some of the information in the article she already knew from working on Aconite Alleviation with Snape those months ago. The article essentially outlined the methods and results of Snape's prolonged experimentation with both Aconite Alleviation and Wolfsbane itself. It detailed the exact effect each proposed change in the recipe would produce, and concluded with an analysis of the modification's usefulness and viability.

Some of the modifications called for more expensive ingredients, but that was balanced by the decreased amount of imbued magic necessary to bond the potion in the final stages, so cost-wise the improved version was approximate to the original. Snape had managed to reduce the brewing time by a full fifteen minutes, and provided several alternate instructions for ingredient preparation—Harry was especially interested to find out why heating the fire slugs before mashing them resulted in significantly higher potency in the final product.

More important than the aesthetic improvements, though, were the effects the modified potion would have once ingested. According to Snape, his version of the potion, if taken before the sun set on the first night of the full moon, would remain potent for all three nights of potential transformation. Such a thing was unimaginable before, but Snape had essentially decreased the probability of a werewolf forgetting his potion during the full moon by 2/3rds. Instead of remembering to take it three nights in a row, and paying for three doses of the potion, the werewolf would only need it once a month.

That wasn't even the best of it.

In addition to only needing to be taken once a month, the modified recipe lessened the pain of transformations by an average of sixty percent, and in the few trials performed thus far resulted in significantly decreased reports of tiredness, nausea, and irritability in the days following the transformation as well. Snape had used the full moon to his advantage, incorporating ingredients that were influenced by its cycle, meaning that they activated when the full moon rose and deactivated when it set. It made the side-effects of taking Wolfsbane stronger during the night and weaker during the day.

There were drawbacks, of course, which Snape detailed carefully toward the end of his report. The modified potion acted as a sedative on the transformed wolf. While the human was unaffected during the day, the wolf became extremely docile and sleepy once transformed. While this would seem like an advantage to many—docile werewolves meant fewer attacks, surely—Snape cautioned potential drinkers to secure their resting place carefully before transforming, as the werewolf's ability to defend itself if threatened would be drastically reduced.

Even with the minor drawbacks, the new modifications were more than Harry had expected—more than anyone could have anticipated. Snape had single-handedly changed the way werewolves would manage their illness. A once-a-month potion was the same way most women handled the effects of their menstrual cycles, and from the sound of things the werewolf transformation under this potion wouldn't be much more painful or tiring than severe lower-abdominal cramps could sometimes be. It would still be a struggle for some to afford it, but with the monthly cost a third of what it had been, the new recipe would go a long way toward helping those who had never had reliable access to it before.

On the last page, the New Wolfsbane recipe was detailed in all its complex glory. Harry had to sternly remind herself, as she read it, that she had promised Professor Snape she wouldn't attempt to brew Wolfsbane without a licensed Master to assist her. Her fingers itched to gather the listed ingredients and find out right now how difficult this new recipe was, but she forced herself to calm her excitement and re-read the entire recipe twice so that she would remember most of the major modifications. She couldn't wait to get back to Hogwarts and discuss it with her mentor.

She was about to put the article down when a footnote on the very last page caught her eye. She read it with growing disbelief, and then read it again, just in case she'd been hallucinating.

"Credit for the timely release of this modification must be given in part to my occasional assistant, Arcturus Rigel Black."

Severus Snape had mentioned her in his breakthrough article on New Wolfsbane. Master Snape, the greatest potions master in England and possibly the world, had given her partial credit for his success. It might say Archie's name, and it might only be a footnote, but it was there in black-and-white, and she would always know what it meant. Even if nothing else came of her years of study at Hogwarts, even if everything fell to ruin and her reputation as a potioneer was forever tarnished by a discovered deception, no matter what, she'd still have this feeling of complete perfection.

"You look awfully pleased," Thompson said, "Are you secretly a werewolf or something?"

Harry shook her head but couldn't suppress the smile on her face, "This is an astonishing accomplishment, that's all. Every academic in the world should be pleased today."

She went to hand the periodical back to Thompson, but he waved a hand, "Keep it. They'll be sold out most places by now, and you collect them, don't you?"

Harry blinked, "How did you know?"

Thompson favored her with a bland look, "All aspiring Masters collect the Guild's journals. I had quite a collection myself, until I gained complete access to the Guild's archives and had no need to hoard second-hand copies of ancient articles any longer."

Harry smiled a bit embarrassedly, but didn't hesitate to tuck the special edition safely away in her bag. It had her name in it…sort of. She'd probably frame it, after she made Archie read it, of course. If he was getting credit for being part of the process, she'd have to make sure he understood all the pertinent parts of the modification, in case anyone else noticed the footnote and asked him about it.

Although she had drilled Archie on the Wolfsbane potion for over an hour that afternoon, neither of them was expecting the subject to come up as quickly as it did. Lily brought a copy of the article home from work with her, however, and pointed out the footnote with obvious curiosity and puzzlement over dinner.

"I had no idea you were assisting Se—Potions Master Snape," Lily said, "You must be very talented, Archie, for him to single you out among all his students."

"I learned it all from Harry," Archie said, chuckling a bit self-deprecatingly, "But I guess I am pretty good at potions, compared to a lot of people our age."

"But Snape?" Sirius couldn't seem to wrap his head around it, "How long have you been assisting him?"

"It's an on-and-off thing," Archie shrugged, "I didn't mention it because it didn't seem like a big deal."

"He mentions you by name in a high-profile publication," Lily protested, "That sort of press is hard for a journeyman to get. For a Hogwarts student to receive the honor…it sort of is a big deal, Archie."

"Why would Snape make you his assistant?" James blurted out.

Remus shot his friend a slightly admonishing glance and said, "What James means is that Professor Snape must have passed over a lot of older students in favor of your assistance. Do you know what persuaded him?"

Archie looked uncomfortable, so Harry decided she ought to jump in.

"He did it for me," she said, casting a grateful look at Archie across the table, "I love AIM, but first year I was a bit disappointed not to be going to Hogwarts, if you remember. I felt like I would be missing out on invaluable potion instruction by not studying under Master Snape. In exchange for me sending him information about the Healing tract at AIM, Archie approached Snape for extra potions lessons."

"Yeah," Archie chimed in before the adults could comment on the odd exchange of knowledge, "At first he would just give me extra work, but it turns out he needs an assistant sometimes, and he was tired of retraining the NEWT students every time one graduated, I think. He decided just to use me, since I wasn't busy with exam prep, and I wasn't going anywhere for a while."

"Well," Lily said, looking nonplussed, "It's still very impressive that you assisted him with such difficult experimentation."

"It was completely safe," Archie hastened to assure them, "I helped mostly with fetching ingredients and other auxiliary stuff. I'm certainly not allowed to brew Wolfsbane on my own. Honestly, I didn't do much. The footnote was just a courtesy, I think. It was nice of him to remember my involvement, though."

"Nice? Snape?" Sirius sighed, "The world's gone all wonky these last few years."

"Old people always say that when they don't like the way society develops," Archie said archly, "Soon you'll be bitter and judgmental, too, and in a hundred years your great-grandson will roll his eyes at your portrait for being so stuffy and old-fashioned."

"Why you—" Sirius promptly dumped the kale salad over Archie's head, "I'll show you stuffy!"

"Not the vegetables…" Lily sighed, "Why did you have to ruin the only healthy thing on the table?"

"Addy's still eating healthy," James pointed out helpfully.

They all looked at Addy, who gurgled at them around her bottle when she noticed.

Lily sighed, "Hurry and grow up, Adriana. I need more people on my side."

"You assume Addy will be on your side," Archie said, grinning, "But every time she comes over to my house I let her listen to the Weird Sisters. She's going to be on my side, if anyone's."

"But I'm the one who feeds her chocolate," Remus said innocently, "I really think she'll be partial to me by the time she gets old enough to figure out how awful vegetables are."

"Rock music and sweets?" Sirius scoffed, "That's not the way to a lady's heart. I take Addy shoe shopping."

He puffed out his chest proudly, and Lily narrowed her eyes at him. "Were you the one who charmed her shoes to hiss like tiny snakes when she bounces them?"

Sirius's face was too innocent not to be guilty, "Me? I thought you did that, Lily."

Lily raised an eyebrow, "Why would I?"

"So she doesn't get eaten by my courtyard snakes when she comes over to play, of course," Sirius said cheerfully, "They think she's one of them now. They love peering their little faces into her basket while she's sunning."

"Sunning?" This was apparently too much for Lily, "Merlin help you if my baby gets freckles, Sirius. I'll have your snakes for skins, and then we'll see who has a new pair of shoes."

James and Remus couldn't hold their laughter in any longer, and their loud guffaws set off the rest of them. Even Lily rolled her eyes eventually and picked Addy up to cradle her in her arms, "Please be sane when you learn to talk, little one. I can't take much more of this nonsense."

Harry cursed as the handwriting charm slipped and smudged the label she was spelling until it was unreadable. She didn't want to spare the time to redo it, but she also didn't want one of the Malfoys to recognize Rigel's writing. She wiped the label clean and reapplied the charm with more concentration, then hurriedly stowed it in the crate with the others. It was the last batch of suppressants she'd been working on for Malfoy, and she was almost past her deadline. She'd said she would have the rest by three that afternoon, and it was twenty minutes till by the time she cleared away her lab station and headed for the floo.

She couldn't move quickly with the crate of potions in her hand, and the alleys were busy with afternoon shoppers, so it was another fifteen minutes before she reached the Serpent's Storeroom.

She nudged the door open with her foot, saying, "Sorry, Mr. Krait. I lost track of time at the Guild this morning."

"Not at all, you're right on time, kid," Krait said, taking the crates from her and setting them in a pile with the other crates, which were waiting by the register. It was then Harry caught sight of Mr. Malfoy sitting behind the counter, looking unreasonably poised in Krait's dingy shop. "Here's the last of them, sir." Krati said proudly, "Quality guaranteed."

"By who?" Mr. Malfoy drawled, "Your little errand boy?"

Harry bristled, but didn't say anything other than, "See you around, Krait."

"One moment, boy," Malfoy said imperiously, "I require a word about the brewer who employs you."

"Krait employs me," Harry said shortly, not interested in letting Malfoy get to know Harry the way he knew Rigel.

Malfoy frowned down at her closed expression, "The brewer who gave you those potions, then."

"What do you want to know?"

"Do you watch him brew the potions?" Malfoy asked.

"Sure," Harry said, shrugging dismissively.

"Is he sober? In control? How many cauldrons does he attempt to brew at once?" Malfoy fired questions at her without giving Harry a chance to answer, "Are the ingredients fresh? Stored properly? Does he—"

"Here now, my brewer is perfectly competent," Krait protested.

"You'll excuse me if I don't simply take your word for that, Mr. Krait," Malfoy sneered.

Harry recognized the sharp edge in Malfoy's eyes, and if she hadn't been convinced at least some of the potions were for Draco before, she was now certain. "Mr. Malfoy," she said carefully, "These potions are perfectly safe. I can assure you that they were brewed responsibly and with proper attention to Guild-recommended safety regulations."

Malfoy shot Krait a rather dark look, "Complete anonymity indeed."

Realizing she'd said Malfoy's name out loud, Harry quickly said, "Don't blame Krait—you're not exactly low-profile, Mr. Malfoy. A picture of you at your garden party was in the society pages just a few weeks ago."

"You read the society pages?" Malfoy sneered skeptically.

"Doesn't everyone?" Harry said, a bit sarcastically.

Malfoy was looking faintly amused now, though he still raised an eyebrow imperiously when he asked, "If you read the article you'll know who did our catering for the party, won't you?"

Harry raised an eyebrow right back. She hadn't read any such article, of course, but there was only one wizarding entertainment company that hired nonhuman waiters and waitresses, and they were quite well-known for it.

"Mystique Event Management," Harry said airily in the face of Krait's nonplussed look, "Usually known for their cutting-edge taste, but I hear the nymphs at your party were rather tackily overdone."

"You insolent little—" Malfoy visibly gathered himself, then said, "Dobby."

Harry was confused for half an instant, and then Dobby the elf popped into the shop.

"Master's crates is being ready?" Dobby asked, half looking up at Mr. Malfoy, half cringing away.

"This stack," Malfoy gestured at the crates, "You know where to take them."

Dobby bowed hastily, and with a snap of his fingers, he and the crates both vanished.

"Good day, Mr. Krait," Malfoy said, inclining his head an infinitesimal amount toward the shopkeeper, "And as for you…" he turned to Harry with a threatening gleam in his eyes, "Since you so earnestly insured these potions' quality, you won't mind if I take any imperfections out of your impertinent hide."

It was not a question. Harry had always known this dangerous, pitiless predator lay beneath Lord Malfoy's socialite exterior, and the only surprise she felt at his threat was that he should bother intimidating a street kid like her, who should rightfully mean nothing to the rich lord.

"Good luck finding any," she said, false sweetness in every note.

He turned on his heel and left the shop without acknowledging her further.

"You've got to stop being rude to my customers," Krait sighed.

"Only that one," Harry said, "And he came back for more, didn't he?"

"It's just not like you," Krait pointed out.

"How well do you really know me, Mr. Krait?" Harry asked, somewhat rhetorically.

"Well enough to know that no matter how rude you are to Mr. Malfoy, he's not going to forget you any faster," Krait said knowingly.

Harry cleared her throat uncomfortably, "Any other orders come in?"

"None that my other brewers can't handle," Krait said, scratching his head as though wondering when Harry had become not one of his brewers, but his best brewer.

"See you around, then," Harry said, waving a bit before slipping out of the shop.

She spent most of that evening researching and practicing the shield spell she would use in her final project, but the last hour before bed was reserved for perusing the Dark Disguise book, as she'd taken to calling it. Since she'd received the book from Leo, she'd mastered the voice-changing spell, along with a spell to thicken her hair—it worked on everything, from the hair on her head to her eyebrows, leg, and arm hair, but unfortunately it only worked on hair that already grew, so it wouldn't help her grow facial hair.

In between learning useful little spells like that, she'd been studying auras. Interestingly, the majority of the chapter on auras was about how to suppress your aura so others couldn't recognize it. Suppressing was supposed to be the difficult part, and projection was only explained briefly as a reversal of suppression. In theory Harry could learn how to project her aura, but it involved undoing the suppression, which seemed like a waste when suppressing was supposed to be so difficult to achieve. Luckily, there was another option. The rest of the chapter covered constructing auras. After suppressing one's own aura, one could apparently learn to project a false aura that, while rudimentary, would fool most aura-sensors.

The Dark Disguise book helpfully broke down the process mentally, and while much of the explanation seemed overly metaphorical, Harry could see how it might work. It wasn't something she'd thought to try, but it made a certain amount of sense. It would require meditation, and she wouldn't know if it worked unless she found someone who could read auras to test it against, but it was definitely doable.

"Miss," Remus said, flicking his wand to send another disk into the air.

Harry took aim and shot a stunner at it. The disk sailed gracefully through the air like a swan, and the stunner impacted against the wall behind it with a sad little fizzle.

"Miss," Remus commented cheerfully, sending another disk flying.

"I can tell when I miss," Harry huffed, taking aim again and watching the disk serenely reflect the light of the stunner as it passed.

"But you can't talk and shoot at the same time, apparently," Remus said, flicking up another disk.

"I can't shoot regardless," Harry said, missing once again.

"You're over-thinking it," Remus said.

"I really don't think I am," Harry said wryly. Take aim, shoot. Not that complicated a concept, really. The disks were just so small, and the jet of light coming out of her wand was even smaller. It wasn't exactly like aiming bludgers at people-sized targets. More like aiming a needle at a poker chip.

"I suppose you could take a step forward," Remus said, faux generousness oozing from his amused expression.

Harry was too much a Slytherin to turn her nose up at the handicap, so she took a step forward and tried a few more times. All misses.

"I think that one was closer," Remus said supportively.

"I think you're making fun of me," Harry said, raising an eyebrow as Remus simply flicked another disk into the air.

Harry tracked its arc the way she might predict a bludger's movements. She'd watched enough disks fly across the room by now that she had a pretty good idea of their speed and weight, even though she'd never picked one up. When she was fairly sure where it would start descending, she shot three stunners in a row. The first two missed, but the third one was timed just right. The disk turned green and dropped to the floor.

Harry smirked, and Remus sighed.

"That's cheating."

"If it was an enemy, he'd be down for the count," Harry said, "How is it cheating if I win?"

"What do they teach you in America?" Remus muttered. He looked down at the disks, and shrugged, "All right, try this on for size, my little opportunist."

He flicked three disks into the air, and although Harry fired as fast as she could, she only knocked one out of the air.

"So it seems a 33% success rate is only a problem when there are multiple enemies," Remus said thoughtfully. He shrugged artfully, "Ah, well, that probably won't happen."

Harry sighed, "Point taken. Let it fly, Remus."

Remus launched another one, and practice went on.

After aiming practice was dodging practice, and then they cooled down with a couple bottles of water.

"Thanks for the practice, Remus," Harry said.

"You don't have to thank me every time," Remus said, smiling, "You're a good student."

"You're a good teacher," Harry said honestly.

Remus looked hesitant for a moment, then said, "You really think so?"

"Of course," Harry said, surprised that he was uncertain, "You know exactly how to make the lesson stick, without frustrating me or getting frustrated yourself."

Remus's smile widened, "And you know exactly what to say to people. You get that from your mom, I guess."

Harry smiled. It seemed like anytime someone recognized something good in her, they inevitably suggested she'd gotten it from one of her parents. Even at school, she heard teachers wondering whether it was Sirius or Diana who contributed to Rigel's talent for transfiguration or polite disposition. As if children didn't have any light of their own, only reflecting their parents' rays.

"I've been offered a job," Remus said suddenly.

Harry looked over at him with interest, "A paying job? Is it an independent company?"

The ministry had laws against employing dark creatures, but there were some corporations that got special dispensations, provided they didn't employ them the week of the full moon.

"Something like that," Remus said. He looked hesitatingly at Harry from the corner of his eye, "It's…Hogwarts, actually."

Harry couldn't stop the jerk she made in surprise, and to her dismay Remus misinterpreted it immediately, "I know how badly you wanted to go when you were younger. I don't want you to feel like I'm rubbing it in, or—"

"Remus," Harry said quickly, "Don't. I'm not—I'm happy for you, Remus. I'm amazed, actually. How did this happen?"

Remus ran a hand through his hair and shrugged, "The New Wolfsbane. If it does all Snape says it does, Dumbledore feels there's no reason not to hire me."

"Is the ministry reconsidering the anti-werewolf laws because of Snape's potion?" Harry asked excitedly.

"Not yet," Remus said, "But Dumbledore controls personnel at Hogwarts, so they can't stop him unless, well, unless I give them a reason to."

Harry's eyes widened, "Remus, this is huge. I mean, this is landmark. The first high-profile werewolf hiring in a decade, a live test of Snape's new recipe…if nothing goes wrong, it will show everyone how ridiculous the prejudices against werewolves are!"

"If nothing goes wrong," Remus said bitterly, "And if something does…it could ruin the pro-werewolf campaigns for years to come."

"You have to try," Harry said, gazing worriedly at her pseudo-uncle.

"I do, don't I?" Remus sighed.

Harry leaned her head on Remus's shoulder, ignoring the sweat, "You'll make a brilliant teacher, Remus. Nothing will go wrong." She would be there to make sure of it, somehow.

Remus huffed out a laugh, "I hope Archie feels the same. I haven't told him I'll be coming to Hogwarts yet."

"I'm sure he'll be as excited for you as I am," Harry said.

"Excited?" Remus sounded skeptical, "I can't think of many teenagers who'd be excited their uncle was going to be tagging along to their boarding school."

"Archie isn't like that," Harry said automatically, the rest of her mind busy catching up to what a huge problem it was going to be for the ruse if Remus came to Hogwarts.

"You're right," Remus said, bucking up again, "You're always right, Harry. I'll tell everyone tonight at dinner."

He did.

Archie spouted effusively about how great it would be to have a real Marauder back at Hogwarts to witness his 'work,' all the while shooting discreetly panicking looks in Harry's direction. Harry eyed him steadily over her peas and silently conveyed calm acceptance. This was unforeseen, she told him with her eyes, but not unmanageable.

Archie settled down, and managed to keep the conversation lively until they were both excused from the table.

They met up in Harry's room, and Archie rolled his eyes as he moved several stacks of books off one side of the bed so they could both sit.

"Where do you sleep?" Archie asked playfully.

"On the other side," Harry said, "Obviously."

"How do you pull back the covers?"

Harry opened her mouth, then shut it again, thinking. When was the last time she'd slept under the covers? She was so excited at the prospect at the beginning of the summer, but sometime over the last few weeks, she'd just…stopped.

"I don't," she said eventually, "Got used to sleeping on the spread, I guess."

"That's sad," Archie commented.

"What's sad is your acting abilities, cousin," Harry said, "I think Sirius noticed you had mixed feelings down there."

Archie shrugged uncomfortably, "I'll play up the forlorn prankster angle—I want to spend more time with my uncle, but I don't want my friends to think I'd rat them out to a teacher, and I don't want anyone to think I get special treatment, etc. Dad will comfort me, and I'll agree with him, summon up a cheerful smile, and then he'll feel better, and useful as a parent, and forget I ever acted strangely."

"All right," Harry said, pretending it didn't make her sad that someone as innocent and earnest as Archie was becoming so manipulative, "I can work that angle at school, too. Avoid Remus for the most part, pretend to be uncomfortable—but apologetic about it, of course."

"What about in classes?" Archie asked, "If this new potion does all it says, Remus will be teaching the week of the full moon. His senses won't miss that you don't sound or smell like me."

"Sound I can fix," Harry said, taking out her wand and pointing it at her own throat, "Mutare Vocem."

"What's that do?"

"What's that do?" Harry mimicked. The sound was virtually identical.

"That's pretty good," Archie laughed, "Say something else."

"I don't take orders from slimy Slytherins," Harry drawled.

"Oh, very nice," Archie said, "It's not perfect, though. Remus would be able to tell the difference."

"If he heard them next to one another," Harry agreed, "But I'll try to go as long as possible without speaking to him once school starts. That way, his memory of what you sound like will be a little dull."

Archie nodded, "I'll minimize the words I say to him in the weeks before school starts. He'll second-guess himself before he guesses the truth. And he'll be on that new potion—he might attribute the change in his senses to a side effect."

Harry nodded, "That will help with smell, too, but I'm still going to need several vials of your sweat."

Archie stared at her for a beat, "You're kidding."

"I'm not," Harry said, blinking. Wasn't the solution obvious? "I'll distill your scent and make a musk out of it. I'll just spray it on my clothes before I go to Defense class."

"You're going to make a perfume…out of my body odor?" Archie looked torn between laughing and gagging.

"Have any better ideas?" Harry asked.

"Well…no," Archie said, "But do you have to make me the smelly kid?"

"It's only one class," Harry said, exasperatedly, "And it probably won't be strong enough for anyone but a werewolf to smell."

"Won't Remus wonder why you're so sweaty?" Archie asked, clearly not thrilled with the idea.

"I'm going through puberty," Harry said sweetly, "A growing boy. It's not my fault my hormones are out of control."

"Okay, just stop," Archie stuck out his tongue, then let his face relax tiredly, "So you really think this is going to work?"

"If it doesn't we'll need to start collecting blackmail material on Remus," Harry said, a slight smirk on her face.

"I can't tell if you're joking," Archie said, "And that worries me."

"Me too, Archie" Harry said, no longer smiling, "Me too."

When Harry walked into the Guild Library, her fellow interns were both already there, feverishly paging through various manuals and journals, searching for theories and experiments that would lace their work with the credible tint of authority.

Harry joined them, pulling out a few instruction booklets on advanced brewing techniques to try and find ones that were similar to imbuing shaped magic. She thought there ought to be a few wandless brewing techniques, like the one Snape had shown her while brewing Aconite Alleviation, that would be comparable.

She'd only been reading for twenty minutes when Master Hurst came into the Library and beamed at finding them all there.

"All hard at work, I see," Hurst said lightly, "Very good. I've come to see how many tickets you'll be needing for the Open House. The caterers need to have an estimate for the buffet, and I think there's been talk of seating charts, though considering we don't own any chairs, Merlin knows how they'll work that out."

"I require three," Casillas said at once, "My parents and my elder brother will all be attending."

"All right," Hurst said, noting the number down, "Miss Potter, I assume your parents are both still planning to attend?"

"Yes," Harry said, "And could I have three additional tickets for my cousin and uncles?" There was no need to get a ticket for Addy, as Lily had arranged for Alice Longbottom to watch her that day.

"Certainly," Hurst said, smiling, "Mr. Lupin will be excited to see Mr. Lestrange's project as well, I imagine."

"I daresay he will," Harry agreed.

Lestrange had a bored look on his face, "At least one person will be seeing it then. I don't require any tickets, Master Hurst."

"None?" Hurst looked taken aback, "Well. If you're sure. You can always change your mind later, Mr. Lestrange."

"Thank you, Master Hurst," Lestrange inclined his head, and went back to his reading.

Harry wondered why his parents wouldn't be coming to the event. Maybe they had a prior engagement? She shook her head and reoriented herself in the materials she was looking through. It really wasn't any of her business.

It was Saturday morning, two weeks before the Open House, and although Harry had planned to spend the morning experimenting, Archie had other plans.

"You're birthday is in sixteen days," Archie reminded her as he bounced around her room, picking up various things and placing them on her bed, "And I don't have a present for you yet."

"That sounds like your problem," Harry noted, "I have work to do."

"You always have work to do, so that's not an excuse," Archie said, tossing her shoes on her bed next, followed by her coin purse.

"Always being true actually makes it a very reliable excuse—"

"You have to come with me to Diagon Alley to pick out your birthday present!" Archie insisted.

"Won't it ruin the surprise?" Harry said absently, thumbing through the copy of Snape's article that Thompson had given her. She'd read it several times, but she hadn't memorized it yet, so it was still interesting.

"Surprise is less important than enjoyment," Archie said, "You can be surprised by other people's gifts—I want you to like mine."

Harry raised an eyebrow, and thought it over, "If I have to pick out mine, you have to pick our your birthday present, too."

"Deal," Archie said, grinning, "Now put your ugly shoes on, and let's go."

"They're serviceable," Harry said, pulling on her fire-proof, acid-proof, water-proof boots.

"They're inappropriate for summer," Archie said, "But it's your feet that have to suffer."

"Anti-sweating charms," Harry said.

"Too much information," Archie drawled.

They told their parents where they were headed—or rather, Archie told them, and Harry didn't protest—and emerged from the Leaky Cauldron floo into a veritable herd of people milling around the pub.

"What a crowd," Archie said, tugging Harry along toward the alleys, "Is it always like this on Saturdays?"

"No," Harry said, frowning, "There must be some kind of event going on."

"You think Lockhart's signing books again?" Archie wagged his eyebrows.

"If he is, you won't be getting a book for your birthday," Harry said, wrinkling her nose at the thought of wading through people to get to the shelves.

"Who wants books for their birthday?" Archie asked incredulously.

Harry raised an eyebrow.

"Oh, no," Archie shook his head, "You're getting something fun this year—and don't say 'learning is fun' or something like that."

"Let's get your present first, then," Harry said, "It'll give me time to come up with something."

"Quality Quidditch it is," Archie grinned, "Come on!"

He led her through the throngs of people, as though she didn't walk through the alley every day. She could probably find all the shops on the alley blindfolded, by now. They slipped into the shop, but the press of bodies inside made it even harder to maneuver.

"Is there a sale?" Archie wondered, looking around, "I don't see any signs."

Harry shrugged, "I'm not sure what's going on, but let's find something quickly."

"I already know what I want," Archie grinned, "Check this out, Harry."

He moved over to a brightly lit display, where a sleek new broom model was proudly advertised as 'the fastest on the market.'

Harry looked it over, impressed by the stats quoted on a plaque at the base, "The Firebolt?" she said curiously, "This is new."

"Just released," Archie said, "I hear it's going to be the official broom of the World Cup."

"That's not until next year," Harry said, "It's that advanced?"

Archie nodded, "Nothing's going to top it in at least two years. They've got patents for miles on the spellwork designs."

"It's beautiful, Arch," Harry said softly, "But I don't think I can afford one for you."

Archie laughed, "You're not buying me a broom, Harry. I asked Dad for it, anyway."

"Of course you did," Harry smiled, "What do you want from me, then?"

Archie pulled a bright yellow piece of paper from behind his back and handed it to her somewhat bashfully.

"A subscription form?" Harry said, reading it over.

"It's for a year's subscription to Quidditch Weekly," Archie said excitedly, "See, if you fill it out with all your schooling information, it'll come to me at AIM all year."

Harry smiled, "Clever. What will I say when our parents ask what I got you? A subscription for myself?"

Archie laughed, "Yeah, you always were the selfish one."

"Careful," Harry said archly, "Or I'll sign up for a subscription to Witch Weekly as well."

"I'd just say I got it for Hermione, and she'd sigh over my misguided, well-meaning generosity," Archie said, unrepentant.

"Give it here," Harry said, shaking her head with amusement, "Do you have a quill?"

"There's one at the front desk," Archie said, craning his neck to see over the heads of those around them, "You can fill it out while you pay."

"Let's get in line, then," Harry said, "And get out of this madhouse."

They wove through the crowd, and were almost at the registers when Harry heard someone saying, "Rigel, Rigel!" over the noise around them.

She froze for half a second, then said, "Archie get out of here."

"What?" Archie said, "No, I can wait with you."

"Archie, someone who knows Rigel is here," Harry said, "You have to go."

"Can't we just switch places?" Archie said, alarmed, "I'll be you and—"

"Our eyes are the wrong color," Harry hissed, "Make for the door, I'll meet you at Fortescue's when I'm done here."

"Okay," Archie shot her a worried look before he melted into the crowd and disappeared.

Harry kept her face impassive, shifting in a show of casual impatience as she shuffled forward in line, even as she heard, "Rigel!" more pressingly behind her.

"Rigel?" The last came with a hand on her shoulder.

Harry affected a start of surprise as she glanced over her shoulder with a politely inquiring expression, "Yes?"

Theo's face blinked at her as he took a step back, "Uh…sorry. I think—you look like someone I know."

"Oh?" Harry let her face relax into a smile, "That's the second time someone's said that this week, actually. You mistook me for my cousin Rigel, didn't you?"

"I did," Theo's expression melted with relief, "Thought I was crazy, but you do look like him."

"Yes, it's uncanny, I'm told," Harry said, adding in a low laugh for good measure.

"So," Theo said embarrassedly, "I'm Theodore Nott, a friend of Rigel's at school."

"He's talked about you," Harry said, still smiling in a friendly way Rigel wouldn't usually bother with, "You room with him, right?"

"Yes, that's right, uh…" He trailed off, looking a bit uncertain.

"Harry Potter," Harry offered her hand for him to shake.

He looked at it for a moment, "Potter…"

Harry offered her best self-deprecating grin, "I know, I don't look like a girl. It's the hair, I think."

"Not at all," Theo said, clasping her hand gently, "Very pleased to meet you, Heiress Potter."

"Just Harry," Harry said with an artless shrug. She thought she was doing rather well at portraying a relaxed, confident girl who wouldn't remind anyone too much of Rigel's reserved, stiflingly polite manner.

"Then call me Theo," Theo said, moving up with her as the line crawled forward, "Forgive me for saying so, but I didn't think your family supported the SOW Party."

"What?" Harry tilted her head curiously, "Why would you think they did?"

Theo looked incredulous, then tossed his head in a gesture that encompassed the crowd milling around them, "This is an SOW fundraising event. Why did you think all these people were here?"

Harry blinked, "Oh. I just figured Lockhart was doing another book signing."

Theo laughed, "Really? You know we had him at Hogwarts last year—utter idiot."

"No kidding," Harry said, "So what's the event? Is there a booth somewhere?"

Theo grinned at her, "A booth? Funny. Lord Riddle's arranged it so that a percentage of all the sales in Diagon Alley today go toward the Party's campaign fund."

"What kind of incentives do the shopkeepers get for participating?" Harry asked, intrigued.

"I'm not sure," Theo shrugged, "Probably guarantees that the Party members will advertise their services or something to that effect. Plus a lot more business than they'd get otherwise."

"Interesting fundraising strategy," Harry said, "Does it only apply to Diagon Alley, or are Knockturn and the Lower Alleys participating as well?"

Theo raised an eyebrow, "Why? Going to take your business to Knockturn if it's not participating?"

Harry laughed a little, "I doubt my paltry patronage will make much of a difference in the Party's proceeds today. I just wondered if I should expect large crowds over there as well."

"Well I think it's just Diagon," Theo said. He jerked his head a moment later, saying, "Looks like you're up."

"It was nice to finally meet one of Rigel's friends," Harry said.

"Likewise," Theo said, inclining his head to the correct degree with an ironic grin, "Enjoy your day—try not to spend too much money."

"I'll do my best to resist the urge," Harry laughed easily, giving a little wave before hurrying over to the counter to pay for her subscription.

She finished getting Archie's present squared away, and she surreptitiously glanced around the alley as she left the shop. She spotted a couple of Leo's folk hanging about, keeping an eye on the swarm of people, but didn't see Theo anywhere. Figuring it was safe, she made a beeline to the ice cream shop and spotted Archie at a corner table with his head down.

She slipped into a seat across from him and sighed, "That was too close, Arch."

Archie grimaced, "I know. What are the odds one of your friends was here at the same time as us?"

"It's apparently a Party fundraising event," Harry said.

"Oh," Archie glanced about, "That explains why half the people here look too stuck up to shop in the alleys."

Harry snorted, "And it means there are probably other people here who know me. We should go."

"But your present…" Archie looked very disappointed, "I really wanted to get you something good, and I know you won't have time next weekend, because you'll be preparing for the presentation."

Harry hesitated, not really wanting to take more time for shopping that day, but the look in Archie's eyes made her say, "Why don't we floo to Hogsmede?"

Archie brightened immediately, "You mean it?"

"If everyone supporting the Party is here today, it's the perfect time to go," Harry said.

"I bet it'll be empty," Archie said excitedly, "Great idea, Harry! Let's go."

They moved quickly through the waves of bustling witches and wizards, and before long joined the cue for the outgoing floo.

"See you there," Archie said, tossing powder into the grate, "Three Broomsticks!"

Harry stepped up to the clay jar, measuring out the necessary floo powder carefully. She tossed the powder into the flames, turning around so that she would be facing outward when she arrived. Just as she opened her mouth, she looked up, and her eyes caught those of Master Snape, who had just stepped out of the incoming floo beside her.

"Three Broomsticks," Harry managed to say through numb lips, and before Snape's eyes could do more than narrow at her, she was whisked away through space.

She stumbled out of the floo like a drunkard, but Archie, who knew only too well how clumsily she floo-traveled, was there to catch her and drag her out of the pub.

"So I was thinking we could go to Zonko's, because you can always find something good there, and—Harry? What's wrong?" Archie stopped watching

"Nothing," Harry shook her head, "I mean, Professor Snape walked into the pub just as I was flooing out. It was a close call."

Archie paled, "Too close. You haven't figured out the aura thing, have you?"

"I'm working on it," Harry said, "But no…not yet."

"Okay," Archie said, "Well, the room was crowded. There's no way he recognized you."

"Right," Harry said, "Okay, so, Zonko's?"

They headed down the street, which was virtuously empty compared to Diagon. Zonko's was well stocked with fun new products for the school year coming up, and Archie had a blast suggesting various things Harry might like for her birthday.

"How about this one?" Archie said, holding up a handkerchief that would turn its user's nose blue.

"No one would fall for it," Harry said, smiling slyly, "The Black Heir with a handkerchief that wasn't monogrammed? Unlikely."

Archie rolled his eyes, "I'll give you that one, but I'll have you know that monogrammed handkerchiefs are very useful when you hand them out to crying girls as often as I do."

"I don't think Hermione is going to forget who gave her all those handkerchiefs," Harry teased.

Archie sniffed, "I give other girls handkerchiefs."

"Really?" Harry affected a hurt expression, "But you've never given me a handkerchief, Arch."

"You never cry," Archie pointed out.

"Plus, I have my own monogrammed handkerchiefs," Harry smirked.

Archie laughed, and picked up a different product, "How about this one? It's called a teacher-tracker. Hmm, looks useful, actually."

Harry looked it over. The package contained three small, black disks. They were all extremely thin, and about the size of Harry's smallest fingernail.

"It says you put the disk on a teacher's robe, and activate the sticking charm with the pass-code in the box. That piece of paper in there is connected to the disks somehow—maybe a modified Protean charm?" Archie shrugged, and kept reading, "Once the sticking charm is activated, the map shows you where it is in relation to itself—so if you're holding the map, it will tell you how far, and in what direction the teacher you stuck it to is."

"How would you stick it to a teacher without them noticing?" Harry asked, "They're small, but the teacher would see it eventually and just un-stick it."

Archie nodded, "Yeah, I wouldn't use it for teachers, though. You could track your friends with it—or your enemies."

"I have the Marauder's Map for that at Hogwarts," Harry said.

"But it doesn't show everything," Archie said, "If you'd gotten one of these on the basilisk last year, you could have tracked it."

"Yes, Archie, why didn't I think of putting a tracking device on the basilisk?" Harry scoffed, then paused, "Actually, it could be useful outside of Hogwarts. We could put one on Addy when she gets older."

"Planning on losing her?" Archie asked.

"You never know," Harry said wryly. Then, a little more cheerfully, "I could put one on Leo. If I put it on his shoes, it might take him weeks to figure it out. He's always popping up behind me—let's see how he likes it."

Archie grinned at her sidelong, "You've been hanging out with this Leo bloke a lot. He's older than you, isn't he?"

"A few years, yeah," Harry said, tucking the teacher-tracker package under her arm.

"And pretty good looking, if I recall correctly," Archie said lightly.

"Not as good looking as you, Archie," Harry said, rolling her eyes as his lack of subtlety.

"Oh, come on," Archie wheedled, "You liiike him, don't you?"

"He's my friend," Harry said dismissively.

"He's your boy friend," Archie said.

"I have a lot of male friends," Harry said.

"Most of them don't know you're a girl," Archie returned.

"Leo doesn't care that I'm a girl—he thinks I'm funnier as a boy, actually," Harry laughed, "Give up, Archie. There's nothing there to tease me about—now you and Hermione on the other hand…"

"Oi!" Archie backpedaled quickly, "Hermione is completely sexless to me."

Harry winced, "Don't ever tell her that, if you want to keep your face the way it is."

Archie blinked slowly, "Yeah…maybe forget I said that."

Sunday morning she ate a big breakfast, asked her parents not to disturb her until dinner, and settled into a comfortable position on her bed to meditate. It was time to get this aura thing straightened out.

She entered her mindscape. It was odd how satisfying she found it that every time she came back it was just the way she'd left it. Like her own private world that no one else had access to. She entered the hidden cave, and wondered, as always, what she was going to do with the manikin boy who just sat in one of the armchairs by the fire, waiting for a mental intruder who would hopefully never come.

In the space room, she got to work. She'd always sort of taken for granted the floating orbs that represented various aspects of her mind—memories, personality traits, ambitions, fears. All the Occlumency books said every mind was different, and not to be surprised by what you found in your mindscape. She hadn't thought her ice mountain was odd, but the fact that when she'd found her mindscape her mental manifestations of self—the orbs—were already inside the mountain was, according to the Disguise book, very unusual.

Most people started Occlumency with their manifestations out in the open, and it took a lot of time and effort to gain the mental flexibility to develop safeguards for them. The process of hiding the manifestations behind a layer of mental defenses, was, in fact, the art of suppressing one's aura. The reason Harry had never had an aura was because her manifestations naturally existed behind barriers. Through Occlumency, Harry had simply elaborated on and complicated the defenses her mind had already unconsciously developed.

Projecting the aura was apparently as simple as removing the protections on the mental manifestations one wanted to let project. Harry thought this would be a waste, however, since her mind was already fairly secure. It was also apparently very difficult to move pieces of your mind around, or to drastically change the landscape in order to shield them, so it would be easiest to simply leave the orbs where they were.

That, and it felt wrong to even imagine exposing the bits of her mind like that after keeping them cloistered for so long.

Instead, she could learn to construct an aura of her own design. She was in the space room to learn to identify all the important mental manifestations, so she could create her own, fake manifestations and allow them to project the facets of her new aura.

It was a tedious task, examining all the orbs of a decent size and trying to first figure out what they were, then, if they were one of the facets the book said most people could recognize in an aura, making a credible facsimile of the thing.

She created copies of the orbs that designated her age, various bits of her personality that she liked—her patience, drive, and determination, to name a few—and some of the obvious features she and Archie shared—dark hair, fair skin, relative health and fitness. It was amazing how many things that represented her had a mentally represented equivalent in the orbs. When she came to the orb that embodied her femininity, she hesitated, but in the end reproduced it faithfully. Harry Potter would have an aura, and it should be female. She could always pick through Archie's mindscape to figure out how to make it male later, if she really needed to.

The only thing she didn't reproduce faithfully, which the book said would be very obvious if omitted to anyone who could read auras, was her magical power level. If her magical core was shielded, her power level wouldn't manifest in her aura. The books that said a person's aura was a combination of physical and mental magical energy were correct, but they didn't explain that the physical energy got transferred through the mental manifestation of the magical core. Because her core's manifestation was contained deep within her ice mountain, it didn't get projected.

She couldn't have an aura without any magic being projected—that would be suspicious, and obviously contrived. She also couldn't just move her sun out into the first level of her mindscape—it would be vulnerable, and it would tell everyone who could sense auras exactly how much magic she was capable of producing. Rather than have her enemies know her exact strength, she would make them underestimate her.

She held out a hand toward her sun, and curled her fingers coaxingly, "Come on. Just a little, please."

A small stream of fire drifted into her palm and wrapped itself into a ball of flame that danced between her fingers. She carried it before her like one of the Black's starlights, and the copied orbs she'd been creating trailed after her like a bizarre, ghostly parade of burning souls.

She stepped out onto the mountainside, but despite the raging storm, her train of lights didn't flicker. She spent the next little while setting the orbs up in a parameter around the mountain. When she'd willed them all into the sky they formed a circle around the mountain, but well away from the mists that enclosed the edges of her mind. With an effort of will, she set the false orbs in motion, orbiting the mountainside at a steady, almost mesmerizing pace.

Alone with her handful of flames, she climbed the mountainside to the very top.

At the summit, she shaped the rock upwards into a thin protrusion that ended in an upwards-grasping claw. Amused at her own sense of drama, Harry deposited the small ball of flame into the clawed torchbearer, and watched it rotate in place for a moment, as though the magic were getting comfortable in its new home.

As she waited to make sure it would stay, the flame settled, then slowly began to expand. By the time it seemed to be done expanding, it was a little bigger than Harry's head, and could be seen no matter where she stood on the mountainside.

Finally satisfied, Harry left her mindscape, and woke to sweeping pins and needles throughout her limbs. She groaned and moved her body very, very slowly, blinking as she stretched her neck and back.

She wandered downstairs, wondering what time it was. She was starving, so it must be almost dinnertime.

The house seemed unusually quiet until Harry realized that it must be so late that Addy was already asleep. The kitchen light was on, but the rest of the house was dark and still.

"I guess I missed dinner," Harry said softly, padding through the kitchen toward the pantry. She half-hoped that Lily had left something under a warming charm for her, but the counters were clear. Her mother probably assumed Harry could fend for herself—and she wasn't incorrect. It was the work of a minute to put together a peanut butter sandwich and a glass of milk.

She shut the lights out on her way back upstairs, and flopped on the bed, nudging aside the spines of books where they poked her in the side. She had trouble falling asleep, whether because her body had been essentially resting all day or because her mind was restless without exhaustion brought on by a day of hard work and research to distract it.

Two weeks until the Open House. Two weeks until she stood in front of everyone she'd ever respected and admired and tried to make them see why she was important, to convince them that someday she would be worthy of respect and admiration. Even though she was a woman. Even though she was twelve years old. Even though she was trying to explain methodological theory that apparently didn't even exist.

Harry groaned into her pillow and tried not to imagine all the things that could go wrong.

Two weeks until it was all over, at least.

"Stop pacing," Thompson said, his eyes tracking her movements across the lab.

"I can't," Harry said absently, mind racing and palms sweating.

"You'll be fine," Thompson said, unusually reassuring, "Better than fine—your project is going to blow them away. You just need to calm down."

"What if no one gets it?" Harry asked, "What if the demonstration doesn't work?"

"You don't think your potion works?" Thompson asked.

"Of course it works," Harry scowled, "But what if—"

"Miss Potter, sit down," Thompson snapped.

Harry sat. "Thank you," she said.

She was down in Thompson's lab, because she couldn't bear to be up in the Guild's event room, watching the assistants setting up chairs and twitching every time someone glanced at her presentation materials. The Open House started at four, and Harry thought it was sheer torture on Aldermaster Hurst's part to make the interns arrive over two hours early. It had taken Harry under twenty minutes to set up her materials to her satisfaction, and the rest of the time had been spent reading and rereading her speech, and then driving Thompson up the wall with her pacing.

"Don't let yourself get riled up," Thompson said, his tone soothing, as though she were a wild beast, "When we go up, most of the Masters will already be present. These are very busy people, and they don't like to waste their time. Keep your remarks short and to the point. The demonstration will speak louder than anything you say, and most of them would rather peruse the theory at their own leisure—that's what the paper you'll write in the next two weeks is for."

"Okay," Harry said, starting to psych herself up, "I'll just introduce the concept, then demonstrate. Results are more important than theories."

"Exactly," Thompson said, "Your paper will be picked over for the exact methodology and theory later, but for now the buzzards just want to see what your project can do."

Harry nodded, "I can do this."

"You can," Thompson agreed, "If you don't panic."

"Easier said," Harry muttered, "This is only my future career on the line."

"Go ahead and panic, then," Thompson shrugged, "But don't you dare show it. No one likes a nervous potioneer. Nervous people make mistakes, try too hard, and usually get someone killed. Present a calm, dignified façade. You know what your project is worth—make sure they know it, too."

Harry took a deep breath and summoned up the calmest mask she could find. Her muscles settled into smooth planes, and her eyelids shuttered the dilated wildness of her pupils. "What's the presentation order, again?" Harry asked, voice even.

Thompson's eyebrows rose, "That's eerie. You ever thought of becoming a player?"

Harry shrugged fluidly, "Who has the time? The presentation order?"

"You're last," Thompson said, "I expect the Aldermaster arranged it that way—he's quite excited to see the results of your project."

"I'll try not to disappoint him," Harry said. Her breathing had slowed, and rising up over the panic came a steely determination that she was completely familiar with. This was her day. She deserved this moment, and she would make the most of it.

With those thoughts in mind, Harry was utterly poised by the time Thompson led her upstairs.

Severus Snape despised social events, but a man in his position could not afford to ignore politics, be they Party or otherwise. That said, the Guild's annual Open House was perhaps the most odious event of the summer season. Every year three unfortunate adolescents were paraded before the Masters of their field and made to feel as though, somehow, the project they'd worked on for a couple of lazy summer months mattered to the potions community at large.

Inevitably, the would-be potioneers chose ambitious and impractical topics, spurred on by their softhearted mentors and deluded with visions of intellectual renown. They presented their hasty research on notorious potions their immature brains could not possibly comprehend, and the Masters clapped and smiled as though they'd learned something listening to snot-nosed upstarts lecturing them on the subtleties of their own art.

It was sickening, but the press adored the spectacle, and Aldermaster Hurst could have been given a Mastery of Manipulation for the way he played on the imagination of the masses. The Potions Guild was so supportive of today's youth, furthering intellectual horizons everywhere. It was enough to turn his stomach.

The decorations were as drab as ever, and no doubt the catering would be somehow worse than last year's slop, but there was one thing Severus admitted to anticipating at this particular Open House. This year James Potter's whelp was one of the upstart brewers, and it would be deliciously amusing to watch the child stutter and blush her way through an embarrassingly patronizing and tedious presentation. Miss Potter would be unlikely to appreciate the mortifying irony of the spectacle, but that didn't mean Severus couldn't privately revel in the pathetically inane speech his rival's offspring would no doubt attempt to deliver.

"Severus!" there was Hurst in all his press-mongering glory, "So pleased you found the time."

"How could I miss the opportunity to witness the next generation of potioneers on the rise?" Severus drawled. He doubted the member of the press corps currently drooling over the Aldermaster's shoulder caught his sarcasm, but Hurst's eyes flashed with amusement.

"You won't be disappointed," he said, smirking in a way that said he knew exactly how low Severus' expectations were, "We've found particularly innovative interns this year."

"I'm sure," Severus said, holding back a sneer, "What potions did they attempt to improve this time? Polyjuice, again?"

"No, not exactly," Hurst smiled in rueful acknowledgment of Severus' unspoken critique, "One young man did attempt to improve the shelf life of the Draught of Peace."

"Really?" Severus murmured, when what he dearly wanted to ask was why? Who would bother storing a Draught of Peace long-term, in case it was suddenly needed one day? That's what Calming Draughts were for.

"Mmm," Hurst said, still smiling slightly, "And another one of our interns researched the effects of Wolfsbane on long-term users. No doubt you'll be interested in that."

As if there was something a child could discover in two months that Severus hadn't learned in his decade of research on the subject.

"That would be Potter, I assume?" Snape did sneer a bit this time. No doubt the girl had used Lupin as her test subject. Only a spawn of James Potter could choose so arrogant and presumptuous a topic for their first project.

"No," Hurst looked slightly surprised, "Mr. Lestrange did the work on Wolfsbane, actually. You are acquainted with Miss Potter, though? Wonderful girl—bright young mind, and such drive—"

"Please excuse me, Aldermaster Hurst," Severus cut in, semi-politely, "I've just seen someone I must catch up with." He could not listen to the drivel coming out of Hurst's mouth another second. He would speak to the man later, when he was not performing for the cameras.

Most years he could easily fade into the background at such an event, but this year his breakthrough on the New Wolfsbane, as it was being called, was too fresh, too sensational. Some of the congratulations and proclamations of esteem came from those he considered something like friends at the Guild. Most came from people eager to learn his story, the secret to the success he enjoyed in the community. As though hard work and mind-numbing perseverance were somehow mysterious forces for fame and glory.

Because he had not arrived earlier than absolutely necessary, he did not have to bear the weight of attention for long.

At precisely four o'clock, Hurst claimed the stage at the front of the event hall and addressed them all through a Sonorus Charm.

"Welcome friends, family, and potioneers young and old to this year's student showcase," Hurst said, smiling rather grandly. There was a brief round of applause, which Severus somewhat reluctantly participated in. He could already tell it would be a long afternoon.

"For those of you new to our Open House, the format will be as follows," Hurst said, finally getting to the point, "Each intern will present his or her project, after which he or she will take questions from the crowd—try not to be too hard on them!"

Severus was disgusted by the number of people who laughed at that. So much for peer review. He also noted that Hurst was taking much too great a pleasure in adding 'or she' to the end of everything he said, as though having a female intern were really something so novel. He wouldn't be surprised if Potter's chit had gotten her internship on sheer novelty alone. Who'd ever heard of a thirteen-year-old intern? If Severus had known the Guild was so desperate for interns, he'd have nominated Rigel Black in a heartbeat. At least the boy had talent, for all his youth made him a bit volatile.

"After the presentations there will be a chance to mingle," Hurst said, still smiling in a way the press no doubt found charming, "Really get to know these youngsters—they are the potioneers of tomorrow, the artisans of future progress, and the vessels of our field's longevity."

Severus mentally resigned himself to seeing that quoted in every sensationalist media outlet the next day.

"First up is Renaldo Casillas," Hurst began the applause as he exited the stage, and a young man that appeared to have no idea how useless his topic was began to wax poetic about the importance of extending shelf-life of potions, presumably so that potioneers could grow lazy in never replacing the ones that went sour.

After the first mind-numbing presentation came Caelum Lestrange, Bellatrix and Rodolphus' boy. In some ways, the Lestrange Heir's speech was less mind-numbing than his predecessor's—there were a few conclusions that would have required at least a modicum of intelligence to come to. In other ways, however, it was more annoying, because as the leading expert on Wolfsbane in the field, Severus was required to maintain a facade of polite engagement despite his growing boredom.

There was also the political fallout to be dealt with should Severus publicly snub the Lestrange Heir, and with that in mind Severus found himself doing the unthinkable as Lestrange finished his self-important presentation. He asked a question.

A moment after asking it he'd already forgotten what puerile utterance he'd probably undermined his own credibility to give voice to, and he didn't bother to acknowledge the answer beyond a faux-solemn nod, but the gesture had done its duty. The Lestrange boy was puffed up with satisfaction, and the Aldermaster sent Severus a grateful smile. He would collect that debt at a later date.

He toyed with simply leaving after that. He'd done his part to make the event a success. Whatever the third intern's project was, he doubted it would have anything to do with his specialties. He'd been seen and heard, and he doubted anyone would notice if he slipped out between speakers.

He hesitated, though. He could admit that some small part of him was…curious. This Potter girl was Rigel's pseudo cousin. Rigel spoke rather highly of the girl, likely due to residual affection left over from mutual childhood bonds. Rigel's estimation of the girl was likely to be exaggerated because of his biased opinion of her, but all the same the boy may be…disappointed to learn that Severus had opted not to remain and hear his cousin's presentation out. In fact, the boy may be here now, come to support his cousin's first foray into the potions community. He really ought to stay, if only so that after the presentations he could seek Rigel out and discern how his summer assignments were progressing.

When Harriet Potter stepped on stage, it was not immediately apparent that she was the female Hurst was so proud to have appropriated for the Guild's good press. Her hair was as short as any boy's, her bearing relaxed and unselfconscious—very unlike the demure, half-cringing nature of most adolescent females who roamed the halls of Hogwarts.

There was something annoyingly familiar about her. Beyond the Potter hair and chin, of course. Severus sharpened his senses and examined her aura, but it was utterly unfamiliar to him—not to mention vague and rudimentary. She looked to be barely above squib-levels. He took slight amusement in the knowledge that the girl's magical power was somehow stunted. No child of Lily's should be so mundane, but that was the price for procreating with an idiot like Potter, wasn't it? Though now that Lily was in his thoughts…

Those eyes. Severus hated himself for recognizing something in them. They were duller than the ones in his mind's eye, but they burned him all the same. He begged Merlin to make her presentation even slightly engaging. Anything to distract his mind from the dark paths it wanted to travel.

In this, at least, his wishes were granted.

"My name is Harry Potter," the girl began, "For my project I invented a new way of conscious imbuing."

An inventor? Severus raised an amused brow. The field could certainly use a little genuine innovation, but a new imbuing method? The one they used worked just fine. Unnecessary innovation was almost as bad as no innovation—worse, if you counted time and materials wasted.

"I know," the Potter girl smiled wryly, "Why a new method of imbuing when the one we have is perfectly adequate to our needs? Simply, our needs are not the reflection of our reach. This new method of imbuing broadens the very definition of what a potion is, and expands the possibilities of what a potion can do beyond the currently accepted limits."

She certainly had a way with words, he reflected sardonically, but he would wait for substance before he deigned to be intrigued.

"I call it Shaped Imbuing," Potter said, her speech cadence quickening as though she knew how tedious the crowd would find her explanations, "It is essentially the imbuing of already shaped magic into a neutral base."

What? Severus sharpened his attention without consciously recognizing that he was doing so. Surely he had misheard.

"This is not like casting a spell on a potion," Potter said, anticipating the objections many were mentally making, "Nor is it the same as imbuing free magic into a potion. It is a wandless brewing technique that necessitates great control over one's magic, but which yields many and varied results. Imbuing a potion with shaped magic has advantages over both potions and spells—the results are more specific than potions alone can sometimes achieve, while also being cheaper and simpler in some ways to create. In addition, the results last longer than a spell, and are not dependent upon their castor. The method will be explained thoroughly in the paper released through the Guild's newsletter, so for now I will conclude with a demonstration."

Many in the crowd perked up at those words—demonstrations were rare, and generally more attention grabbing than dry speeches. Severus was still attempting to comprehend what the girl had just proclaimed. Imbuing shaped magic? Was such a thing even possible? He eyed the young intern as she collected the materials she would use from a stand at the back of the stage. No doubt the demonstration would be rather ordinary, achieving something she would claim came from her 'new' imbuing method, but in reality was probably effected some other way.

Potter placed a small, glass figurine on the floor of the stage, and with a quiet spell enlarged the glass doll until it was almost waist high. "This unfortunate fellow, call him Stan, is many things. He is a toddler who tends to wander at night. He is a wizard caught outside collecting herbs on a full moon. He is—well, you get the idea."

Several people chuckled at the girl. What imbeciles. Could they not see what an outlandish claim she was about to make?

"A mother could cast a barrier charm around the child while he sleeps, but the charm would fall as soon as the mother fell asleep herself," Potter said, pacing the stage slowly, "She could set wards around him, but she would spend an hour every evening setting them up, and longer each morning to dismantle them. Or," Potter held up a vial of clear liquid for all to see, "She could pour this around his crib."

She poured the liquid in a steady stream around the child, connecting one end to the other to form a complete circle. She set the vial down at the back of the stage, then without warning brandished her wand and said, "Stupefy," and fired a stunning charm at the glass figurine.

Many people close to the stage ducked, but the glass didn't break. A shimmering, ward-like projection intercepted the light where it tried to cross the circle of potion, and it fizzled out harmlessly. There were a few impressed claps, but most people waited for the explanation.

"This potion has had a Fortis Shield imbued inside it through the use of Shaped Imbuing," Potter said, smiling a bit proudly, "It doesn't cause damage to anything that touches it, but neither will it allow anything to pass through it. This includes both magic and physical objects, as those of you familiar with the Fortis Shield might have guessed. The toddler can't wander, and neither can he be abducted or attacked until the shield dissipates, or the antidote is applied."

She took out a knife and attempted to penetrate the barrier physically, showing how the shield snapped into place everywhere the circle was approached, all the while speaking clearly and confidently, "If Stan is caught out on the full moon, he can cast the potion on the ground around him, and stay safely ensconced in the shield for up to twelve hours—much longer than most wizards and witches could ever hope to hold a Fortis Shield. It will hold against Vampires until the sun rises. You can take it camping to protect your food from wild animals, or use it in your dormitory to keep your roommates out of your things."

More laughter. The girl knew how to work a crowd—though he supposed that wasn't surprising. James Potter had always been a blowhard. More importantly, her potion appeared to work. A mobile, ready-made ward? It was remarkable to say the least, particularly if it really would hold for half a day.

"There are several obvious drawbacks," Potter acknowledged, carrying another vial over to the circle, "The antidote negates the shield immediately, so I would not recommend its use against other wizards, or as a substitute for real, solid wards around one's home. It is designed for temporary use, not permanent, but if the antidote is misplaced, little Stan might be very hungry by the time his mother manages to reach him again."

She poured the second vial, this one orange in color. She poured it across one section of the original circle, and immediately the entire ward wavered under a barrage of orange sparks before flickering out completely. "The antidote is imbued with shaped magic as well," the girl informed them, "A ward-disruptor, this time."

The Lightning Jaw, if Severus didn't miss his guess. All and all it was a very interesting performance. Perhaps Hurst was not wrong to recommend her, despite her young age. He still had doubts that her methodology was all it appeared to be, but he would definitely be reading the full report.

"This is just one example of what Shaped Imbuing can accomplish," Potter concluded, re-shrinking the figurine and vanishing the potion residue on the floor efficiently as she spoke, "I hope that through relentless experimentation and careful understanding we can push the boundaries of what potions makes possible even further in the coming years. Thank you. I will take any questions you have now."

There were no few inquiries.

"Will you publish the recipe for the base, Miss Potter?"

"Yes, of course. I'm not looking to patent this process."

"Have you experimented with any other special-imbued potions?"

"A few. I've experimented with simple imbued magic, like color-change spells, and even combining Shaped Imbuing with potions that already have an intended purpose. The results were, in general, very successful."

"Are there any noticeable commonalities among different kinds of shaped-imbued magic?" People were clearly fumbling over the new terminology.

"It is generally the case that imbued shaped magic lasts longer, but the effects of some spells may be muted in potion form."

The questions died out once it became clear that they'd have to read the exact theory and methodology in order to gain any in-depth understanding of the process, but the atmosphere was excited as the interns each took a final bow and exited the stage.

It was the first time in a long time that Severus could remember impatiently anticipating another brewer's work. Perhaps true innovation had returned to the English potions community at last. At the very least, Harriet Potter's potions career promised to be intriguing.

A halfblood with a modicum of talent and original ideas? Severus smirked. Not a bad combination at all.

Harry's face hurt from suppressing the foolish grin she wanted to release, but she held her poise until the last of the guests had gone. Her family had offered to stay and wait out the crowd with her, but she sent them off with a self-deprecating smile.

"It'll be boring for you," she said earnestly, "I'll just be answering questions for the next hour and smiling with the other interns for the press."

"We'll celebrate properly when you get home," Lily said, fixing Harry's hair absently.

"And we'll eat while you finish up," Sirius said, lowering his voice, "Because the food here stinks."

"Sirius," Remus shook his head, "Never mind. Well done, Harry. Very nice speech."

"Thanks," Harry said, "I practiced for ages."

"She really did," Archie sighed, "This is the fourth time I've heard it, actually. Can we go now?"

The adults shot Archie an exasperated look for his impatience, but Harry knew he was just nervous. If Professor Snape came over to this side of the room, he would have to hightail it out of there. Until Archie learned to suppress his aura, there was no way he could pass as Rigel around Professor Snape.

Harry's aura, on the other hand, seemed to be working perfectly. She'd seen Snape in the audience watching the presentations, and while he didn't look as riveted as her ego would appreciate, he didn't look suspiciously at her, either. There was no obvious recognition in his eyes, only quiet evaluation.

All and all, Harry thought her first debut into the potions community had gone rather well. She felt invigorated long after the event hall was cleared and her presentation materials were all safely relocated in Thompson's lab.

"Well done," Thompson said, sinking down into the chair behind his desk when it was all over, "Very well done. You sparked just the right amount of curiosity and speculation. The next two weeks will be spent drafting and editing the final paper, but I expect you won't need much of my help for that. Essentially, your internship ends here."

"You're not going to cry, are you?" Harry asked, smirking a bit.

"Brat," Thompson sighed, "I'm well rid of you."

"Oh, you'll see me around," Harry promised, "My uncles are going to sell some of the more harmless potions I made with Shaped Imbuing in their prank line, and I'll need the Guild's safety division to approve them."

"And you'll need someone to help name them," Thompson chuckled.

"I am perfectly capable of naming my potions," Harry said.

"What was it again? The 'Modified Weightless Draught?'" Thompson grinned, "What are you going to call the Shield Potion?"

"The Ward Maker," Harry said, "Rolls off the tongue, doesn't it?"

"But it's got no flair," Thompson shook his head, "How about, 'Potter's Portable Protection Potion?'"

"That's awful," Harry wrinkled her nose, "What a mouthful."

"You've got to put your name in it, though," Thompson said, "Otherwise people will forget who invented it."

"So what?" Harry said, "The name should be descriptive, so it's obvious what it does."

"Potter's Portable Protection Potion is perfectly descriptive," Thompson defended.

"I'll think about it," she said, smiling a bit fondly, "Goodbye, Master Thompson. Thank you for all your help, sir."

"Thank you, Miss Potter," Thompson said, "For not wasting my time this summer."

Figuring that was about the highest form of praise she could get from the man, she bowed her thanks, and left the lab.

She saw a light on in a lab down the hall, and as she approached the stairs she realized it was the lab Lestrange had been using. She started to climb the staircase, but something indefinable slowed her steps to a stop. She stood there, halfway to the landing, and closed her eyes. She should keep walking. She should go home, have dinner with her parents, bask in their approval and pride, and forget she ever saw the light coming from Lestrange's lab.

But she didn't.

She turned around slowly, mentally berating herself all the way down the stairs and up the hall. She stood outside the door for a long moment. Am I really doing this? She knocked. Apparently so.

She had a fleeting thought that perhaps someone had simply left a light on, but then the door opened, and Lestrange's sour expression glared out at her.

"What?"

Harry gave a casual shrug, and nudged the door open with her foot, striding past Lestrange's irritated huff. "I'm glad I caught you," Harry said, turning back to see Lestrange still scowling from the door.

"What do you want, Potter?" Lestrange said, shutting the door with a resigned sigh. He almost sounded tired.

"Just to tell you how much I liked your final presentation," Harry said.

Lestrange scoffed, "Don't bother—I know no one was actually listening. This showcase was a waste of time. Anyone important will just read the actual reports."

"I was listening," Harry disagreed, "As were many others. You got some good questions at the end."

"I got patronizing questions at the end," Lestrange sneered, "And you were too busy preparing your own presentation to listen to mine."

"Not so," Harry said, "I thought you made a really insightful point about the connection between long-term survival rate and mental acuity. Too many people overestimate the role of physical fitness in werewolf health. It's important, but not as important as mental agility and sheer willpower. The curse affects the mind of the werewolf even more than it does the body."

Lestrange narrowed his eyes at her, "Maybe you were listening, then. Doesn't mean anyone else was."

"Even if no one listened, it was a good presentation," Harry said.

Lestrange seemed to fight himself for a moment, then the word, "Thanks," twisted from his mouth like a live mealworm.

Harry smiled a bit, "You're welcome."

"Is that all?" Lestrange drawled.

"No," Harry said, "I'm going to grab a bite to eat—"

"Good for you."

"—and I'm inviting you." Harry finished doggedly.

"Notice you didn't claim you'd like it if I came along," Lestrange sneered once again, "Go home, Potter. Go have dinner with your precious little family, so they can all tell you how proud they are."

It was eerie how similar his words were to what she'd been thinking just a moment ago. Also unsettling was the slight pang of agreement she felt at his all-too-derisive snort.

"I could," Harry said slowly, "But I'd rather have dinner with someone who understands what I've spent all summer doing, rather than someone who's proud of the idea of what I've been doing." As soon as she said it, she realized why it was partially true. She was glad her parents had come and supported her, but at the same time…it was a little annoying, seeing their politely blank expressions as she'd tried to go over some of the finer points of her methodology with them before her presentation.

Lily was good at potions, and even she seemed a little lost when Harry started in on imbued magic vs. ingredient magic differentials. She didn't blame them for not being potions experts, of course, but she couldn't deny that their praise didn't really mean as much as it might have if they were. She would always be grateful for her family's support—and more so in the face of Lestrange's family's obvious apathy—but what did abstract, expected platitudes really amount to?

She shook her head. She was being too hard on her parents again. They gave her everything she needed to facilitate her goals, and they showed up to support her when given the chance. It was unfair to ask for more, despite the tiny part of her that craved a real connection to her parents, achievements they could share, rather than ones that went over their heads or that they could never know about.

Lestrange appeared to think about her offer for a good minute, but in the end he sniffed, "I don't date halfbloods." After a moment's pause, he wrinkled his nose, "Or children, for that matter."

Harry barely suppressed a grimace of disgust, "And I don't date bigots."

"You don't date anyone," Lestrange guessed shrewdly.

"Neither do you," Harry shot back, confident that it would take more than good looks to keep a love interest with a personality like Lestrange's. "So I guess it's a good thing it isn't a date. It's just dinner, Lestrange. Would you rather go home?"

Immediately, she knew it was the wrong thing to say. Lestrange's face shut down completely, and he said, "I don't need your pity."

"It's not pity," Harry said, lying just a tiny bit. It was pity, mostly. Lestrange apparently saw through her, and sent her a withering glare. She grimaced, and tried, "I'd like to be friends."

"I don't have friends," Lestrange scoffed.

"Maybe that's your problem," Harry said lowly. When Lestrange narrowed his eyes at her, she mentally apologized to Krait and Leo, and offered, "I don't have any friends who brew, either. Wouldn't it be…nice to talk to someone about potions after the internship is over?

"I am not being friends with a halfblood," Lestrange said bluntly.

"Pretend I'm a pureblood," Harry rolled her eyes.

Lestrange actually spluttered, "That's absurd."

"Not really," Harry started to smile, "My kind doesn't look any different than yours, you know. Actually," she was full on grinning now, "I am a pureblood. Didn't I tell you? My mother's a descendent of a very respected pureblood family that was thought to have died out a few generations ago. Turns out my great-grandmother was their long-lost squib descendent."

"You can't just make things up like that," Lestrange snapped.

"It could be true," Harry said, blinking innocently up at the pureblooded boy, "Pureblood families don't keep track of their squib children very well—if they keep track of them at all after putting them on some muggle's doorstep. I might be more pureblooded than you, Lestrange."

"Just stop," Lestrange groaned, "You're giving me a headache."

"It's probably a hunger headache," Harry said wisely, "Come on, Lestrange, we'll get you something to eat."

She started to shoo him toward the door, but the older boy drew himself up sharply, "I am not eating dinner with you."

"Yes, you are," Harry said, "If you don't, I'll tell everyone you did anyway."

"Who would you tell?" Lestrange drawled, "Even your mudblood friends wouldn't believe you."

"I'll tell my cousin Rigel," Harry said, "He'll tell all his friends at Hogwarts, who will in turn tell their parents, who will ask your parents why you're such good friends with a halfblood, and what will you say? That Lucius Malfoy was lying?"

Lestrange gaped at her, "You—you really would, wouldn't you? Crazy bitch."

Harry rolled her eyes, "The insults get boring after a while, Lestrange. Just come eat with me. You might even enjoy having someone to argue with over dinner."

"Why are you so determined to do this?" Lestrange asked, seeming genuinely confused at this point. Harry counted that as a big step up from openly hostile.

"I don't like having enemies," Harry said after a moment, "The more enemies I can turn into friends, the easier my life will be in the long-run."

"I'm not going to make your life any easier," Lestrange argued.

"You might stop making it more difficult eventually, though," Harry reasoned.

"You're just trying to assuage your ridiculously maudlin conscious somehow by pretending to be nice to me," Lestrange accused.

"So what?" Harry dismissed his objections, "Say you're right—you should still come and get free food out of it."

"I don't need charity," Lestrange said exasperatedly.

"Never hurts, though, does it?" Harry said cajolingly, "Come on, it won't take long."

She started walking toward the door, and obligingly held it open for Lestrange to follow.

He stared at her, an unpleasantly torn expression on his face.

"Tell you what," Harry said, "You come eat with me, and if you can convince me by the end of the meal that it was a bad idea, I'll never bother you again."

Lestrange bit out a harsh laugh, "It is a bad idea. You're willingly inviting me to torture you for the rest of the evening."

"I'm inviting you to try," Harry said sweetly.

To both of their surprise, Lestrange accompanied her out into the alleys without another word.

"Where are we going?" he asked eventually.

"Leaky Cauldron," Harry said, waving absently to the old lady who sold good luck charms and cinnamon twists.

Lestrange jerked to a halt, "I'm not eating in a muggle establishment."

Harry sighed, "We're not going through, I just have to floo call my house to tell my parents I'm not coming home for dinner."

Lestrange shot her a dark look, "You lied. You said you were already planning on getting food out."

"Yes, I lied to you," Harry said wryly, "I lie a lot, actually. You should get used to it if we're going to be friends."

"We're not going to be friends," he muttered, trailing after her like a disgruntled ghost who was obliged to haunt someone he hated.

Harry said a quick hello to Tom, who was too busy with the dinner shift to stop and chat. She used the outgoing floo to call home and explained quickly to her mother that one of the other interns had invited her to dinner, and she felt compelled to accept. She excused herself before her father could ask which one—she somehow didn't think he'd appreciate the potential she saw in Lestrange. In fact, she wasn't sure she could explain it even if she tried.

When she brushed the soot from her hair and looked around the pub, she half-expected Lestrange to be gone, but he was leaning broodingly against a nearby pillar, and he straightened when she approached.

"What are you hungry for?" Harry asked.

"Nothing," Lestrange said sourly.

"My choice it is, then," Harry said, smiling slightly, "This way."

She led him back through Diagon Alley, and stoically ignored the incredulous glance he shot her when they turned down Knockturn. She led him along Kyprioth Court, but they didn't take it all the way to the Dancing Phoenix. She didn't really want to introduce Lestrange to her friends, since he was certain to be insulting given half a chance.

Instead, she gestured him down a side street, which led to an alley a bit smaller than Knockturn, but much better lit. It was called Aroma Alley, and it boasted more restaurants in a square mile than any other place in London. There were restaurants stacked on top of other restaurants, squished between and behind one another, and the number of signs and arrows trying to direct people to different establishments was frankly overwhelming if you didn't know where you were going.

"What in magic's name is this place?" Lestrange asked, looking around in something like awed incredulity. Harry was pleased to note he was so distracted by their haphazard surroundings that he'd forgotten to sound sarcastic or snide.

"Aroma Alley," Harry said, "But folks around here just call it the Eating Place."

"How quaint."

Ah, there was the snideness she'd been missing.

"Over here," she said, leading Lestrange into a narrow gap between two Italian restaurants that were always in fierce competition with one another, for all that they were owned by the same family.

There was a red cloth at the end of the little alley they slipped into, and Harry held it aside grandly, sweeping her hand to allow Lestrange to walk in first.

"If this is a trap, my mother will torture you into insanity," he informed her as he passed.

"Okay," Harry said faintly, wondering just how many layers of issues the older boy was dealing with. Then she remembered what Malfoy had said the first time she led him through a secret passageway, and decided paranoia might be a pureblooded thing.

She followed Lestrange behind the curtain, and down the set of steep stairs that led down into the restaurant proper. At the end of the stairs, all they could see was a giant, semi-circle fish tank, and Lestrange turned to her with a raised eyebrow. She smiled back at him, and walked through the glass tank wall. It was a funny bit of magic that allowed them to walk through the fish tank. It wasn't as instantaneous as the barrier that protected Platform 9 ¾, so there was a confused moment when all they could see was murky blue matter before they emerged on the other side.

The restaurant was bright and cheerful on the other side of the fish tank, with red and gold decorations on the walls and more fish swimming in bowls that glowed with warm light and floated around the ceiling like watery torches.

"A seafood restaurant?" Lestrange guessed, following her over to a table.

"Actually, it's a Chinese restaurant," Harry said, "Fish are lucky in China."

Actually, fish represented a homophonic pun in the Chinese language that made them symbols of prosperity and excess wealth, but she didn't think Lestrange was the type to appreciate cultural nuances.

"So you can't eat them?" Lestrange asked, eyeing one of the swordfish in the wall-tank with interest.

"No, you can eat them," Harry said, "That's good luck, too."

Lestrange rolled his eyes, but he did order the swordfish when the waiter came over. Harry got pork dumplings. The waiter was a man of few words, and set their tea down with little ceremony.

"We didn't order tea," Lestrange said.

"It's free," Harry said, "Anyway, what do you care? I'm paying."

Lestrange sighed, "It's just poor business practice to give things away unprompted."

"Know a lot about business, do you?" Harry asked, amused.

"Of course I do," Lestrange said, "My father and uncle together own more businesses than the Zabini family."

Harry had heard that somewhere, though she'd also heard the Lestranges didn't manage their businesses half so well.

"Then you know that the principle of reciprocity compels people to feel beholden when given something for nothing, prompting them to be overly generous in return. Because he gives tea for free, he gets better tips, and the restaurant earns more in general," Harry explained.

"But as we are aware of this tactic, it fails," Lestrange said, "And he gets nothing more than he would have."

"Maybe if you were the one paying," Harry said, smiling, "I quite appreciate the free tea."

"Your Good Samaritan act is making me sick," Lestrange said, toying with his chopsticks absently.

"I'll eat your fish if you don't feel up to it," Harry offered sympathetically.

"Does it ever get tiresome, being so pointlessly nice all the time?"

"Not really," Harry said, "Why, do you get tired of being such a jerk?"

"I'm not a jerk," Lestrange said, eyebrows rising.

Harry waited a beat, just to make sure he was serious, "You…sort of are."

Lestrange actually shrugged, "Only to those who deserve it."

Harry couldn't stop an incredulous snort, "Don't try to justify it like that—like you're mean to people for their own good. You do it to satisfy something inside of yourself."

"So what?" Lestrange threw her words from earlier back in her face, "Maybe you're right, but that doesn't mean I'm not right, too. Most people do deserve it."

"Including me, I suppose?" Harry asked sarcastically.

"Yes, including you," Lestrange said, his lip curling, "Someone had to wake you up to reality. Admit it," he leaned in to pin her with a taunting gaze, "You walked into the lab that first day thinking no one would care you were a girl, and a halfblood, and years younger than all the other applicants. If you'd listened to me right off, you'd have suspected Casillas would try and blow up your cauldron."

Harry glared, "If I listened to you, I would have gone home before I started."

"That too," Lestrange smirked, "No harm in intimidating the competition while I'm doling out life lessons, is there?"

She couldn't help it—she laughed. His audacity was really too much. "I suppose you've never heard what muggles say about living in glass houses?"

"Why would anyone build a house out of something so fragile?" Lestrange shook his head, "Stupid muggles."

"I just mean, do you really think you're the one best qualified to judge others?" she asked.

"If not me, who?" Lestrange's face took on a bitter tinge, "Most people are too busy being polite to really take a hard look at the world around them, at the people around them. All the idiots and pigs continue to be so because no one wants to risk unpleasantness just to tell them what's what. I, on the other hand, am perfectly accustomed to unpleasantness. I don't care if everyone hates me, so I'm not afraid to say what I think."

"What if what you think is wrong?" Harry said.

"Then someone else better have the gumption to tell me so," Lestrange smiled mockingly, "How else will I learn?"

Harry narrowed her eyes at his childishness, "What about Rigel Black?"

Lestrange scowled immediately, "Brat. What about him?"

"I heard you were horrid to him the very first time you met," Harry said, fighting a scowl herself at the memory, "How can you have judged him so quickly?"

"Rigel Black is an idiot," Lestrange said, "No—don't interrupt. You asked, and I'm telling you. He showed up at a Dark pureblood event like he wasn't the son of a traitor. Did he really think no one was going to say anything? He didn't belong there, no matter whose kids he goes to school with. His naiveté was sickening. I just did him the courtesy of saying it to his face, while so many others would only whisper behind his back."

"You should get to know Rigel," Harry said, "He's not as naïve as you think."

"Then he's a knowing idiot—how grand," Lestrange drawled.

Harry sighed, giving up on the subject for now. The sad part was, Lestrange probably believed everything he was saying. It even made a twisted sort of sense, which Harry hated herself for understanding. As messed up as Lestrange's attitude was, there was something about his rudeness that was beginning to grow on her. In a perverse way, his demeanor was a bit like honesty. He reminded her of Ginny, sometimes, who simply didn't see the point in not saying whatever was on her mind.

She didn't think Lestrange was ready to hear that comparison made out loud, however.

Their food came quickly after that, and Harry asked if Lestrange was going to continue his research on Wolfsbane.

"What's the point?" he said, "Snape's breakthrough is going to change the whole field. My research is already outdated."

"It's not outdated until there's a cure," Harry said.

Lestrange snorted, "There's never going to be a cure. Your fag uncle is going to be a werewolf forever, so get used to it."

Harry flicked a bit of soy sauce at him, "You don't know that, just like you don't know my uncle is homosexual. This is what I mean—you're not 'telling the truth' now, you're just being ugly."

"I'm too pretty to be ugly," Lestrange smirked.

"You're really not," Harry muttered around another dumpling.

"Anyway, lots of people assume your uncles are lovers, didn't you know?" Lestrange commented.

"Remus and Sirius?" Harry shook her head, "Who thinks that?"

"People with too much time on their hands," Lestrange said, sounding disgusted, "But people whose opinions, unfortunately, mean something. Me repeating them just makes you aware of them, so you can deny them in the open if you want."

"Stop," Harry said, exasperated, "You can't justify meanness. Just admit you can't go an hour without belittling someone."

"I do admit that," Lestrange said, "Nor should I have to. There are so many people in the world to be belittled, and so little time, really. This fish isn't bad," he added thoughtfully.

"Careful, Lestrange," Harry said, "That was almost a complement."

"I'm perfectly capable of complements," Lestrange said.

"Do another one," Harry prompted.

"One's my daily limit," Lestrange rolled his eyes.

"I don't believe you," Harry said, grinning, "There's no way you give a compliment every day."

"You'll never know," Lestrange sniffed, "I don't compliment halfbloods."

"I'm secretly a pureblood, remember?" Harry reminded him.

"You're secretly annoying," Lestrange said.

"I grow on people," Harry said.

"I bet people just tell you that, so you'll go away."

Harry thought about that, "I guess I won't know until you say it—you'd never lie to me, would you, Lestrange?"

"Everybody lies," Lestrange said.

Harry shrugged. She couldn't very well argue with that.

"What? Goodie girl actually agrees with me?" Lestrange gazed speculatively at her, "Well, well, what are you lying about, then?"

"It's not really lucky to eat fish in China," she lied.

Lestrange smiled—really smiled—and shook his head, "Maybe you do grow on people. Brat."

Harry wondered if brat could be considered a step up from halfblood. It was probably about the same, she concluded, but the heat seemed to have gone out of his insults.

"So why are you really here with me, and not at home?" Lestrange asked, "As far as I can see, your parents adore you—did you see them there today, smiling like fools while you presented? Bet they're so proud of you. Bet they think you're so perfect. So why are you sitting here, perfect girl?"

"They are proud of me," Harry acknowledged, "No matter what I do. In some ways, they don't really care what I do—they'd be proud either way."

"Lucky you," Lestrange muttered, stabbing at his fish with his chopsticks, "Your parents pay for your potions indulgence, then?"

"Yeah. Yours don't?" Harry said, guessing by the way he said 'indulgence' that his parents had thrown his expenses in his face more than once.

"I get what I ask for," Lestrange shrugged, a bitter twist to his mouth.

Harry understood immediately. The feeling of always asking for things wasn't a pleasant one. She hated asking favors of people—to have to ask for every ingredient and material would be stifling. How many projects would she let fall by the wayside simply because she felt their cost to be an encumbrance once she was made constantly aware of it?

"So what do you do when you aren't brewing?" Harry asked eventually.

"None of your business," Lestrange said, "Why, what do you do?"

Harry laughed, "I don't do anything besides brew."

"Really." Lestrange looked skeptical.

"What else is there?" Harry asked.

"What else indeed."

They weren't friends when they left the alleys behind, but Harry thought they weren't quite enemies, either. That, or Lestrange really had just come along for the free food.

Harry's thirteenth birthday started very quietly, and ended…not so quietly.

Archie kept nagging her to take a PotentialisPotion, but Harry didn't see the point. All it did was reveal the magical potential in a person, and Harry already knew where her strengths lay—in potions. She didn't need her path laid out for her, or even a nudge in one direction or another, like she'd thought Draco could have used. Her future was clear, no matter what the potion indicated she ought to concentrate on. She would make it for Archie on his birthday if he wanted, of course, but Harry knew it wasn't for her.

For breakfast, Lily and James made all her favorites. It was rare that they ate breakfast together, just the three of them—four if you counted Addy, though Harry wasn't sure she was big enough to count yet.

It was nice, but curiously, Lily kept shooting her strangely wary looks when she thought Harry couldn't see her. What Lily didn't know was that Harry's vision was perfect while under the influence of the Modified Polyjuice, and so even though she still wore her 'glasses,' her peripheral vision was crystal clear, unlike James, who couldn't see anything out of the corner of his eye. She didn't know why Lily looked so concerned, but she assumed her mother would tell her when it became important.

Sirius and Remus baked her a cake, and it didn't blow up when they ate it that night, though it did keep singing the happy birthday song even as they devoured it, its voice becoming more and more frantically high-pitched as it was slowly consumed.

Her parents gave her their present after dinner, and to Harry's utter astonishment it was a Firebolt.

"I can't…" Harry just shook her head, a slow smile blooming across her face, "How—I'm not even on a house team, like Archie. Are you sure?"

"Sure?" James ruffled her hair, "You're holding it, Harry! Do you like it?"

"It's amazing," Harry breathed, "It's the broom of the world cup next year, Dad, I mean—thank you."

She hugged James, then hugged Lily too, careful not to squish Addy while she was at it, "Can I try it tonight?"

"In the dark?" Lily laughed, "Surely tomorrow will be soon enough?"

"Oh, I see," Archie grinned, "They waited until now to give it to you because they knew you'd never come in for dinner if you had it this afternoon."

"We wanted to see our girl on her birthday," Lily said, one arm around Harry, the other holding Addy to her shoulder. Her words were sweet, but there was something almost falsely chipper in her tone. Harry wasn't sure what was making Lily so on edge that day, but she hoped it resolved itself soon. Maybe there was trouble at work.

She went to bed that night thinking about what a nice day it had been, just she and her family hanging out quietly at home. She really should have known it was too good to be true.

It was darker than the darkest place she'd ever imagined. She knew she was there, but she couldn't see any part of her—not her feet or limbs or even the tip of her nose. The blackness was too complete for sight. There were other senses, though. It was cold, and quiet, and even though she couldn't see her torso, there was an aching in her gut that she couldn't explain.

Slowly, a light appeared. At first, she didn't notice the lightening landscape, so great had the pain in her stomach become. After a few moments, though, she began to blink against the growing brightness. It was coming from her middle, spilling out through the fingers she had pressed over her gut, and it was warm.

No, not warm—hot. Flames licked at her stomach, burning, scorching her insides. The light spilled out of her to illuminate the pressing blackness, but she barely saw the stars answering in the distance before a white-hot pain consumed her.

She woke to a scream, and it took several confused moments of pain and disorientation before she realized it was her own. The world seemed to be shaking itself apart around her, and as she doubled over in agony she heard books falling from their shelves all around her. Her headboard rattled against the wall, and her gut screamed at her in pain, and she screamed back until her throat closed up in protest. She'd never felt such pain before, and she barely registered her bedroom door flying open and her worried parents rushing in half-dressed.

"Harry? Baby? Harry!" her mother's voice was frantic with worry, and it drew Harry back from the world of pain she'd been inhabiting.

"Mom," she choked out, eyes blurring with the tears streaming down her face, "It hurts. I think my insides are burning up."

"Merlin," James drew her into his arms, his voice helpless as he said, "It's going to be okay, Harry, I promise it'll be okay."

"No," Harry said, "I think something is killing me." There could be no other explanation for all the pain.

"Harry, sweetie, it's your birthday," Lily said, stroking her sweaty hair back from her face, "Your magical core is expanding. I thought it might not happen, but—oh, Harry, I'm sorry. This is all my fault. It's going to hurt, baby, but it will pass, I promise."

Harry wanted to believe her, but all she could focus on was pain. She dimly heard James say, "I'm putting her out," before his wand poked her in her ribs, and she knew no more.

She dreamed of fire and pain, and when she woke up some hours later, she was drenched in sweat. Her mother was humming some mindless tune, holding her hand in her own. Harry smiled a bit in relief when she realized the pain was almost receded. Her stomach felt oddly stretched, as though she'd eaten too much for dinner, but it wasn't on fire anymore.

"You don't have to sing anymore, Mum," Harry said tiredly.

Lily immediately called for James and cupped Harry's face in her hands, "Harry, honey, I'm so sorry you had to go through that. How do you feel now?"

"Bloated," Harry said, frowning a bit, "Like I swallowed a watermelon. Does that happen to everyone on their thirteenth birthday? You'd think they'd warn us."

Lily let out a choked laugh, "Oh, sweetie, no. Most people get mild stomach cramps at the most. Many sleep right through it. I had hoped…well, I'm afraid I misjudged your magical potential, Harry."

"How so?" Harry asked.

"Your core is fully matured now," Lily said softly, not looking terribly happy about it, "The pain you felt was the influx of magic filling the expanded space. Your core was working hard to produce so much magic in a short period of time."

"Is that why I feel top-heavy?" Harry asked, trying to sit up, "Because I'm full of more magic than I'm used to?"

"Yes," Lily said, frowning, "You shouldn't be feeling that way anymore, though. Is it bad?"

"Not unmanageable," Harry said honestly, "I'll get my equilibrium back soon, I suppose. So it should have gone away by now?"

Lily bit her lip, then moved her fingers up Harry's wrist to stroke a beautiful golden bracelet that circled her forearm. It was a bracelet Harry had seen many times before, but it was not hers.

"Mom?" she asked, confused as to why she was wearing the bracelet James had given Lily the day Harry was born. If she twisted it, she could even see the name engraved on the inside of the band. It said simply, Harriet.

"Harry!" James came running in and took Harry's shoulders in his hands, staring into her eyes worriedly, "Are you all right, little fawn?"

"I'm fine, Dad," Harry said, summoning a smile, "Sorry I worried you."

"I'm sorry we didn't think this might happen," James said, looking remorseful, "You mother went through something similar, but mine wasn't so bad, so we hoped…well, we should have said something, but we didn't want to worry you."

"At least now I know why mom kept sending me anxious looks all day," Harry said bemusedly.

"Dear," Lily said softly, "I think Harry and I need to have a talk."

James looked from his wife to his daughter, and nodded slowly, "All right. I'll go make breakfast. Somehow I don't think we'll be getting any sleep after this."

He left after kissing her forehead gently, and Harry turned her gaze to her mother. She had conjured a stool by Harry's bed, but Harry scooted over to make room for her on the mattress, "What's wrong, Mom?"

Lily slid in next to her and breathed slowly in and out. Then, she began to speak.

"When I was a little girl, my parents thought I was possessed by the devil," her voice shook only slightly, but Harry clutched her mother's hand tightly between her own, shocked at what she was hearing. "They didn't know what magic was, but strange things were always happening around me—dangerous things. Some kids have three or four major accidental magic incidents when they're young. I had an incident at least once a month. They home schooled me until the letter from America came." Lily took a deep breath, and let it out on a sad little laughed, "They were so relieved when they realized there were others like me, who would deal with me. They showered me with attention when I was home, to make up for their fear and guilt, I think, neither of which ever really went away."

Harry hadn't realized why they never visited Lily's muggle relatives very often, even though she had a cousin her age. Perhaps Lily's sister was as afraid of her as her parents were?

"Did you know that muggleborn witches and wizards generally fall into one of two categories?" Lily asked. Harry shook her head silently. "The majority of muggleborns—about eighty-five percent—are magically below average. There's a stereotype that muggleborns have low stores of magic, but high control of the magic they do have. That's true for many, like your friend Hermione, I suspect. The other fifteen percent, however, are born with vastly overpowered stores of magic, and very little control. I was one of the later."

"Fifteen percent is still a lot," Harry said slowly, "Why don't we hear about more muggleborn Mage or Lord-level witches and wizards?"

"The high levels of magic aren't tempered by generations of refinement as they are in the old pureblood families," Lily said softly, "By the time I got to school, my magic was nearly beyond my control. I almost had to repeat my first year, because I couldn't get my magic to do any of the spells right. It was wild, like an animal that refused to be trained."

Harry couldn't believe how eerily familiar her mother's words were. Hadn't she felt like that? Like she had a monster inside of her at times? Except Harry could control hers sometimes—controlled it too well, sometimes.

"My temper didn't help," Lily admitted, "My emotions were all over the place during puberty, and my magic responded to the slightest ire. It was the worst right after my thirteenth birthday. I dunked my best friend in the duck pond behind our houses one day. He nearly drowned. To this day I believe Severus still hates deep bodies of water," she added regretfully.

"Master Snape?" Harry asked incredulously, "You dunked Master Snape in a duck pond?"

Lily smiled, "Oh, don't tell him I told you that, if you ever do meet the man. We were the best of friends, before…well, before James and I became the best of friends."

There was an uncomfortable silence, and Harry moved to change the subject, "So when did you get control over your magic? Will it take long for me to adjust to it?"

Lily looked miserably down at her, "I didn't, Harry. I thought I did—I was sure I had, by the time I left school, but…" she took a sharp breath, and began speaking faster, "You have to understand, Harry, one of the reasons I married your father is how in control I felt around him. The Potters have always been known for their magical precision—declared Light for as long as anyone can remember. Their family magic is just too controlled to be anything else. When I was with James, I didn't have violent outbursts. Sometimes my magic lashed out at him if I was really annoyed, but it never hurt anyone. It—it lashed out in a controlled way, if that makes sense."

It made perfect sense, to Harry. She recalled Remus' story of a young Lily sending James hurtling through a crowded train station and locking him in a compartment without a scratch. She also remembered her outburst at the SOW Party's New Year's gala, where she had so precisely moved Lestrange backwards in her anger. It sounded like a nightmare, though, living with that uncertainty for so many years. Was that her future, too?

"We married, and my magic settled down even further once it was bound to James', and I thought everything was fine," Lily said. She swallowed and stroked Harry's hair, "Then I got pregnant."

"With me," Harry prompted, when Lily paused to collect her thoughts.

"Yes, with you. Harry, Remus tells me you know the Despaco shield," Lily said tentatively.

"Yes," Harry said, grimacing, "I'm not sure where I picked it up, but my magic…likes it." She waited for Lily to dismiss her explanation of ridiculous, but instead, her mother started to cry. Big, slow tears welled up and trailed sadly down her cheeks. "Don't cry, Mum, please. What's wrong?"

Harry rubbed Lily's hands fretfully, not sure what else to do.

"I'm afraid that's my fault as well," Lily said, hiccupping through her tears, "I learned that spell in my seventh year, and my magic took to it instantly. I don't know what you know about the shield, but despite its power, it has a very simple magical pattern. It takes a lot of energy to keep it going, but it's one of the fastest defensive spells around, because the magic takes almost no time at all to assemble. When I was pregnant with you, I lost count of the number of times I used it accidentally. I was a little paranoid that something would bump my stomach and hurt you, and my magic took that worry to a dangerous level. In the last three months, it was on a hair trigger, Harry. James was wary about even touching my stomach. It was…it was not a good time, for us."

Harry tried to imagine loving someone, and not being able to get close to them for fear of their magic. She couldn't, but she could imagine being the person no one could get close to. She had never sympathized with her mother more. She wrapped her arms around Lily's waist and leaned in. It took a moment before Lily started talking again.

"The night you were born, my magic went wild," Lily's voice was almost a whisper. "It flared up as soon as I went into labor. The Mediwitch wasn't sure what would happen if I attempted magical transportation like the floo, and apparition was out of the question, so the Mediwitch came here and delivered you in our guest bedroom."

"I didn't know I was born in this house," Harry said, surprised and a little grossed out.

Lily nodded, "You wouldn't have recognized it then. We had to redo most of the bedroom after the birth. I had no control over my magic that night. It rained from the ceiling for over an hour, nearly flooding the place, and when the water cleared there were huge tangles of vines growing over everything, even the bed frame. At one point I nearly passed out from the pain, and when the blackness started creeping in the edges of my vision, I panicked. My magic flared, and a light so bright came out of me that James, who was standing closest, was blinded." Lily sobbed a bit, "I didn't mean to, but he screamed so loudly I thought I'd killed him. The Mediwitch took him away, flooed him to St. Mungo's, and she told me he'd be fine, but I didn't know if she was lying to me to keep calm or not at that point. When you were finally born, the Mediwitch didn't even stay to clean you up. She was so frightened, I think. She said she'd send someone to check on you, but no one ever came."

Harry had never realized the circumstances of her birth were so unusual, "Did Dad get his eyes fixed that night?"

"He did," Lily said, "But it took a long while. I gather the hospital was very busy that night. It was the full moon, so Remus wasn't there. Sirius took Diana and left when things started getting out of control—she was due any day as well, you know, and the Mediwitch didn't want her exposed to the magic being thrown around."

"So it was just you and me there?" Harry asked, disturbed, "What if you'd gotten sick?"

"The Mediwitch did check to make sure we were healthy before she left," Lily said, smiling slightly. "I barely noticed her poking and prodding. All I could see was you. I held you, and stroked your curly little hair. You looked like James right from the start. His hair, his chin, and…his eyes."

Harry blinked. That wasn't right.

Lily sighed, "Beautiful little blue eyes. The nurse forgot to put the eye drops in, and you just looked and looked at me, like you'd never look away. It was so hard, that labor. James was gone, and the Mediwitch was gone, and I was so tired, and I wished, just for a moment, that you had something of mine, Harry. Something that proved I had helped create you."

Harry could see where this was going, and she went very still.

"My magic—it was all around us," Lily said shakily, "As soon as I had the thought, it acted. It was a fleeting wish, Harry—you were perfect and beautiful and I didn't really want to change a thing, but…"

"The magic ran with it," Harry said.

Lily nodded, clinging to Harry hard, "Before I even realized what was happening, your eyes were green. The brightest, clearest green I'd ever seen. I tried to undo it—to change them back, but the magic wouldn't listen to me."

Harry wondered if that was the case, or if, deep down, Lily didn't really want the color to change back.

"I waited for weeks for them to turn back, for the magic to fade, but it never did," Lily said, "Haven't you ever wondered why your eyes were so unnaturally bright as a child? They've faded the last couple of years, I've noticed. I suppose the magic might finally be wearing off. Maybe they'll be back to blue in a few more years."

But it wasn't wearing off, Harry knew. She and Archie had simply been wearing green contacts the last year or so, and no contact could match the eerie brightness of her actual eyes. They'd thought they'd been so clever, avoiding eye contact with their parents while wearing them, not knowing their parents had attributed the change to something else entirely.

"When we found out you needed glasses, I was devastated," Lily said, sniffing, "I thought I'd damaged your eyes somehow. James assured me that poor eyesight runs in his family, but I've never been sure—what if you'd had my good vision, and I'd ruined it? The point is I could have damaged you. My magic changed you, on a whim. That's when I had this bracelet made." She fingered the bracelet now clasping Harry's forearm.

"I thought Dad got this for you," Harry said, "To commemorate your first child together. It has my name on it."

Lily shook her head, "It's not just a piece of jewelry. It's a magic suppressor—a powerful one. I put it on a few days after you were born, and I've never taken it off until now. I didn't want to take the chance that anything like that would ever happen again. Your name is engraved on it to remind me why it's necessary. So that I never forget what I did to you, to my baby."

Harry didn't know what to say. It wasn't as though she minded having green eyes instead of blue—it didn't matter either way to her. Lily was obviously still distraught over it, however, even after all these years. She never imagined her mother was living under this kind of guilt and pressure.

"Even with the bracelet," Lily said, "My magic is too strong. I have to use it almost constantly, just to keep it under control."

"I thought you just liked using magic," Harry said, feeling stupid. She'd honestly assumed Lily simply appreciated magic, not that she had to use it in order to control it.

"I do," Lily said earnestly, "I'm not trying to scare you, Harry, magic is wonderful. It's different for you, Harry, and for Addy. You don't have to worry about the kind of things I did. With your father's blood in you, you won't lose control like I did. You can control your magic, Harry, it's just going to take a little time."

Was that true? Harry wasn't sure. The combination of Lily's wild magical reserves and the Potters' magical control might result in the strange presence and lapse of control in Harry's magic, but she didn't think the explanation was that simple. Could her magic really have imprinted the Despaco shield from the womb? Would her eyes stay green or fade eventually back to blue? Could she cope with an even greater amount of magic in her core than she was used to? She just wasn't sure.

She wasn't sure of a lot of things, anymore.

Once she'd calmed down, Harry had to give the magic sealer back to Lily, and start re-learning to control her own magic. It was much harder than it had been the first time, and much more frustrating. Several weeks later, she was no closer to managing her swelled reserves, and she was at her wits end.

Her parents thought she was doing wonderfully—and Harry supposed by Lily's standards, she was. There were no violent outbursts after the first night, no outward manifestation of her magic. It was relatively containable, until she tried to use it. The trouble was, she couldn't let a little bit out without letting a firestorm out. She tried a levitation charm, and no matter how gently she directed the magic, whatever she was lifting slammed into the ceiling. The more powerful spells she tried were, if anything, worse. She got trapped inside her own shield charm for half a day, too afraid to try a ward-disruptor from the inside.

She was lucky she'd finished her mail-order schooling before her birthday, or she'd be way behind on the practical work. As it was, she was dreading the coming school year. What would she say when she suddenly couldn't perform any of the magic they'd learned last year?

But the worst of it, the absolute worst, was that she could no longer consciously imbue. When she tried, she overloaded the potions with so much magic the ingredients actually started spontaneously transforming into other things. It was a mess, and she melted four cauldrons before she gave up. It nearly broke her heart to have to tell Krait she was taking an indefinite leave of absence as one of his brewers, but she couldn't brew anything more complicated than a sleeping draught if she couldn't imbue. She had her summer work done, and more than enough to cover the rent on the apartment in the lower alleys for another year, but without brewing she had nothing to do except brood until school started up once more.

She went flying a lot with her new Firebolt, and her new broom was admittedly brilliant, but even that couldn't quite dim the sense of utter uselessness she felt at having wasted weeks of potential brewing time.

The final paper for her internship had gone as well as could be expected. She explained the process as clearly as possible, but as she could no longer demonstrate the process herself, she was worried experimentation in shaped imbuing would be stalled for the foreseeable future. She had been very careful to omit any references to her own gender from either the intern profile or the paper itself, both of which would be published by the Guild. There was a small chance the Potions Master at AIM would read it, and Archie had to be able to pretend it was his.

Addy had gone back to ambivalence around Harry, who couldn't perform the fun little magic tricks with her anymore, for fear of hurting her. Remus was preparing for his new teaching position, Sirius and Archie were spending as much time together as possible before he went back to school, and although Lily and James asked after her magic-controlling progress every day at dinner, Harry was left largely to her own devices for the month of August.

Since magic was beyond her capacity at the moment, Harry turned to non-magical pastimes to keep her busy, primarily self-defense training with Leo. She spent her days in the lower alleys, careful to avoid hanging around Diagon Alley while all the kids going back to Hogwarts were school-supply shopping. She didn't want another run in with someone she wasn't supposed to know.

Her lower blocks were getting stronger, as her body learned to forget that it was female and simply react appropriately to the threat coming her way. She was tanner than she'd ever been in her life, traipsing around outside all day, and she had a sneaking suspicion that the courtyard behind the phoenix was somehow lit with real sunlight, despite the open air being an illusion. She had actually gone so far as to make Archie sunbathe whenever he had free time, just so that their skin tones wouldn't be too different when they switched places.

"Higher," Leo said, catching her foot easily as it tried to connect with his shoulder. He held it there, keeping her off-balance as he lectured—he often did that, claiming the uncomfortable position would make her remember better. "See where I blocked your foot? It's at my shoulder, so my arm is across my chest, still in a good position in case you follow up with a punch or elbow. If you kick higher, aiming for my face, you force my block higher, leaving my torso open to counter attack. Also, many inexperienced fighters instinctually panic when something comes toward their face, so you have a greater chance of catching them off guard."

He released her foot, and Harry shook her leg out before getting back into the guard position. "What if I'm fighting someone much taller than me, and my foot won't reach his face without putting me off balance?"

Leo tilted his head, "You could jump, but you'd be better off going for his feet at that point. Tall people are often naturally unstable."

Harry couldn't tell if he was joking about that last bit, but before she could ask Leo's fist was coming toward her solar plexus.

At the end of their session, they ate lunch in the Phoenix, for once just the two of them. Harry supposed everyone else was out and about.

"You're headed back to America soon," Leo commented, "Excited?"

Harry shrugged, "I would be, but my magic is all wonky still."

Leo frowned, "It shouldn't take more than a couple of weeks to settle after your thirteenth. Have you seen a Healer?"

Harry shook her head, "I'm within the range of normal for my family, unfortunately."

"What are you doing to adjust? Just practicing magic all the time?" Leo asked.

"I'm not supposed to use magic over the summer," Harry said, smiling slightly.

"Funny," Leo said, "Really, though, are you working on it?"

"Every day," Harry sighed, "But it doesn't seem to help. Every spell gets overloaded and goes haywire."

Leo grimaced, "It's a shame—you were so good with your magic just a few weeks ago. Have you tried exhausting yourself and then trying a few simple spells?"

Harry nodded, "I can't spend the magic fast enough to deplete it before it replenishes itself."

"That's a problem many would kill to have," Leo said quietly, laughing a bit.

"Doesn't do me much good, since I can't actually use any of the magic without blowing myself up," Harry said, a bit disheartened by the whole situation. She had worked so hard to get comfortable with using her magic, and just when she seemed to really be getting the hang of things, she was back at square one.

"How does your family usually deal with it?" Leo asked.

"My mother wears a band that suppresses her magic to a manageable level," Harry said. She bit the inside of her cheek thoughtfully, "Do you think that would work for me?"

Leo looked hesitant, "I don't think that would be a good long-term solution, no. If you become too dependent on it, you'll never be able to handle the full capacity of your magic."

Harry thought about that, "Do I really need to? I mean, just having access to normal levels of magic would be perfect for me. I just want to be able to brew again—it's driving me mad, Leo. I can't even bring an Allergy Relief Potion up to par anymore."

"Don't you want to realize your full potential?" Leo asked, peering curiously at her.

"In some areas, yes," Harry said slowly, "But in other areas…not if they make me a danger to myself and others."

"You're only a danger if you're out of control," Leo said, "But if you really want a sealer, I know a guy who can help. Be sure, Harry. I think you're old enough to make your own decisions, but you need to decide if short-term relief is worth it, in this case."

Harry closed her eyes and imagined her life moving down two paths. On one of the paths, she got the sealer, and became for all intents and purposes a perfectly average member of the wizarding community. On the other path, she worked at controlling her magic for months, maybe years, with no guarantee that she would ever obtain full control. On the second path, she accidentally hurt people sometimes. They forgave her, probably, but they didn't get so close the next time. On that path, she became a wild card. People noticed her, expected great things from her, and people like Sirius began asking questions when everyone said Rigel had powerful magic, but Archie never exhibited any such signs.

The choice was easy, really. There was only one path that would contribute to her future goals. The other may well destroy them.

"I'd like to get the sealer, Leo," Harry said firmly. She opened her eyes and pinned her friend with her most determined look, "I'd rather be an ordinary wizard, if it means I can be an extraordinary potions brewer."

"I won't pretend to understand why you can't be both," Leo said, "But I'll respect your decision." He waggled his eyebrows a bit after saying that, as though wanting her to notice how especially considerate he was being of her choices.

Harry rolled her eyes, "Thanks, Leo. I've never had a friend like you."

"You sound more sincere when you say that in my dreams," Leo mourned.

Harry just shook her head, "Can we see that guy you know today?"

Leo thought about that, "I've got time. He should be open until three o'clock today, at least."

He led her deeper into the alleys, toward his mother's clinic, but they veered off a side street before they got that far. The doorway they stopped in front of had a simple sign hanging from a nail that said, "Custom Metalwork and Repairs."

"This chap can fix anything," Leo confided as they opened the door, "From Goblin-made armor to Fairy-forged silver, but he specializes in custom jewelry."

"Singing my praises?" came an upbeat voice from the back of the tiny shop. Every wall was lined with shelves, which were filled with the kind of containers you might use to sort beads in. Each tiny drawer was labeled with symbols that didn't make much sense to Harry, but which seemed to be meticulously organized.

The man who stepped out through a shadowed doorway behind the counter was middle-aged and very short. His red hair could barely be seen over the register when he passed behind it, but he seemed not at all perturbed that he only came up to their waists. On the contrary, he beamed happily up at them. "What can I do for you today?" he asked, "Looking for a new holster, Leo? Or maybe a nice pair of boot buckles for your young friend?"

"We need a sealer," Leo said, smiling down at the man, "Harry, this is Frein. Frein, my friend, Harry."

"A pleasure to meet you," Frein said, bowing low.

"The pleasure is mine," Harry said, bowing back.

"I like this one, Leo," Frein said, "Most of your friends aren't so polite. A sealer, you say? What level?"

Leo looked at Harry, who shrugged slightly in confusion. There were levels?

"We'll need to have you tested, then," Frein said, stepping back a bit and sort of squinting at Harry, "Just hold still, I'll read your aura in a jiff."

"My aura?" Harry said nervously.

"It won't hurt," Frein said absently. That wasn't exactly what Harry was worried about. "Oh! I'm terribly sorry for assuming you were male, Miss."

Harry waved it off, "Everyone does."

"All the same…" The little shopkeeper frowned, peering intently at her, then said, "Are you sure you need a sealer? No offense, friend of Leo's, but I can't see anything in your aura to indicate either an excess of magic or a new, uncontrolled gift."

Harry grimaced apologetically, "I'm afraid my aura may not be entirely reliable on this matter. Is there another way you can test my levels?"

"Oh-ho!" Frein smiled mischievously, "Got yours recalibrated, eh? Don't see that much these days, but a very good habit to get into, Miss."

Harry supposed by 'recalibrated' he meant she was projecting a false one, and nodded a bit embarrassedly. She'd only had her new aura for a month or so—she never expected to be called out on it so soon. Leo was giving her amused, sidelong glances, which she ignored with the ease of long practice, but she could tell he was filing away the information for a later day.

"Not to worry," Frein said, still cheerful, "We'll just do it the old-fashioned way. Over here, child."

He gestured her toward the counter and ducked behind it to retrieve a device that looked like a long, crystal tube that was fused to a metal sphere on one end. Frein held it up and said, "Put your wand hand on the end of the cylinder, and channel you magic through it—do you know how to do that?"

Harry nodded hesitantly. She imagined it was just like imbuing, but… "What if I break it?"

Frein chuckled, "Not even dragonfire could crack this beauty. The tricky part is to keep channeling your magic through the tube for as long as you can. The sphere at the end of the tube will absorb the magic, measuring the speed and strength of the flow, as well as the endurance of your reserves. I must warn you—the process can be extremely draining, as you will not get the magic you spend back until it replenishes itself naturally. You'll probably feel woozy for a few hours, and weakened for up to a week."

Harry blinked, but nodded, "I understand." It wasn't as though she had anything much to do that week, magically speaking. She didn't go back to Hogwarts for another ten days.

"Whenever you're ready, then," Frein said, handing her the strange object.

She clasped the crystal end in her right hand and held it upright, so that the metal ball was pointing toward the ceiling. It was a bit like holding a very thick, improperly balanced wand. Harry didn't need to concentrate very hard to start the flow of magic—she was good at imbuing by now—but she did need to hold on tightly. The force of the magic shooting through her fingers was like a flash flood, sudden and overwhelming. Harry held on and poured as much of her magic into the measuring device as she could, as fast as she was able.

After a minute, she began to lose the strangely bloated feeling she was still getting used to. She felt almost normal, and began to smile as she pushed more and more magic into the tube. It was relieving, she noticed with delight. Like taking the lid off of a cauldron just before it boiled over.

The crystal was beginning to vibrate in her hand, but she clenched her fist tighter, and kept pouring out her magic. There was no control to the process, no finesse. It was as simple as tipping a giant bucket upside down, and as satisfying as squeezing the jelly out of a fireslug.

She could have kept going, but Frein cleared his throat loudly and said, "I think that's quite enough, Miss."

Harry reigned in the stream with an ease that surprised her. She gaped at her own hand for a moment, then pulled out her wand excitedly. "Lumos," she said, bracing herself in case the blinding light of a thousand suns suddenly appeared. Instead, a small ball lit the end of the wand, and Harry laughed out loud, "It works! My magic works, Leo."

Leo had an odd look on his face, but he summoned a smile for her, "That's wonderful, Harry. I suppose you've so little of it left that it's easy to control, now."

Harry turned her senses inward to get a feel for her magical core. It was much smaller than it had been in months. "You're right," Harry said, "I suppose it was as simple as draining the excess off after all—I just have to do it fast enough. Do I still need the sealer?"

"Unless you'd like to be throwing that much magic around all the time, missy," Frein said, "I think you might consider one."

Harry nodded thoughtfully, "I suppose it would be hard to use that much magic all the time. It would probably alarm some people, in fact."

"That's certainly true," Frein said, looking at the measuring device with something akin to awe.

It was a brilliant purple color that she'd never seen metal turn.

"What does the color mean?" Harry asked.

"The device is charmed to portray the level at which a wizard's core registers as a color on the light spectrum," Frein explained, scratching his head as he looked at the violet orb, "Red is near-Squib level, yellow-green is about average, light blue is a solid Mage-level registry, and anything above indigo is…Lord level."

Harry blinked. She'd heard the term before, but she didn't have a good grasp of what it meant. All the most famous powerful witches and wizards were said to be Lords or Ladies of Magic, but Harry didn't know if that was based on their magical ability or their political resources combined with magical potential, or if it there were other indicators entirely. "How common is purple as a magical register?" she asked.

Frein shrugged, "I saw a light lavender color once, many years ago. It was a muggleborn boy about your age, one of the powerful ones that crops up every now and then. Other than that, you're the first I've seen. Are you muggleborn, too?"

"My mother was," Harry said, "I get it from her, as far as I can tell."

"You're lucky," Frein said seriously, "The lavender boy was emitting magic like crazy when he showed up. Rattled half the things in here off their shelves. For someone without a sealer yet, you've managed fairly well."

Harry smiled self deprecatingly, "I can clamp down on it fine, but once I've suppressed it, I can't use a little bit of it without letting all of it out in an uncontrolled stream. I'm hoping the sealer can lock enough of it away that I can work with whatever is left."

"Ah," Frein looked excited once more, "A partial-suppressant, then? And a powerful one at that. Very tricky…might need to be custom-made. Can you wait a few more days?"

"I go back to school in ten," Harry said.

"That's plenty of time," Frein said, "What specifically were you looking for? Bracelet? Necklace? If you want a pendant, you can choose the stone yourself."

Harry considered it, "Could you make it small, like a ring?"

Frein nodded slowly, "I could. You wouldn't lose it?"

"Don't you take your rings off for potion-brewing, Harry?" Leo asked, frowning.

Harry shook her head, "I never take this one off," she held up her hand with the basilisk ring on it, "It's spelled to never slip off. I'll do the same to the sealer."

"What sort of spell?" Frein asked interestedly.

Harry shrugged, "It's house elf magic, so I'm not sure. I'll ask one of the elves at school if they'll spell the sealer as well, though."

"Know many house elves?" Frein asked, amused.

"A few," Harry said honestly, "I find them nicer than most folk."

Frein scratched his red hair again, "Never thought of it like that, Miss. So what material did you have in mind? I could make it to match the ring you've already got. Is it polished jade…?"

"Basilisk scale," Harry mumbled, "Jade would be fine, though."

"Ah…" Frein peered interestedly at the ring, "Scale, you say?" He grinned a bit mischievously, "I've got just the thing."

He climbed up one of the many stools and rummaged around on a nearby shelf, pulling open drawers and shutting them with a tut here and there. Eventually he descended the stool with a triumphant expression, waving around something clutched in his little fist.

"How's this one?" he asked, holding it up for them to see, "Not the same shade of green, but not too different—just enough that they'll look like a matched set, but you'll be able to tell them apart."

It was a green scale, deeper in color than the basilisk's, but a little smaller. "Dragon?" she guessed, admiring its sheen.

"Welsh green," Frein agreed, "Will it do?"

"It's perfect," Harry said.

He took her left hand and measured the space above where the basilisk ring rested. There was room enough that a second slender ring would sit comfortably below the knuckle.

They left the shop, promising to return in three days. Harry felt light for the first time in weeks, free of the weight of extra magic swimming in her gut, free of the worry of wondering if she'd be able to learn anything at all that year, and free to resume brewing, at least until her magic replenished itself later that day.

Chapter 6

Rigel dodged yet another clump of absent-minded students gunking up the platform as they wandered aimlessly with their trunks, searching for the friends they'd left there the year before. Rigel's, or rather Archie's, trunk was safely ensconced in her robe pocket, and as she'd already said goodbye to Sirius at the platform gate, she walked with purpose through the throng toward the train. It was early yet, and most of the compartments she passed on the way to the bathroom were empty. There was no one at all in the lavatory, presumably because there were nicer bathrooms on the platform itself if anyone really couldn't hold it.

Rigel hung her satchel on the inside of the stall she ducked into and pulled out the dose of Modified Polyjuice she'd prepared. Sending up a quick prayer that she and Archie hadn't grown much over the summer, she knocked it back with a grimace. When the snakes in her stomach had settled into a more comfortable position, she abandoned the stall and sought the mirror above the sink. Comparing the face in the glass to the one Archie had worn all summer was difficult, because they were so similar, but there was definitely a sharpness around the nose and jaw that she thought had been rounder before.

She pushed her hair back off her brow into the more severe style she'd worn to Draco's birthday party. She still hated how exposed her face felt without proper bangs, but Archie assured her the style highlighted her eyes and forehead, drawing attention away from her changing lower facial features, which Archie's masculinity was beginning to noticeably re-shape with each dose of Polyjuice. She reckoned she'd only have to wear her hair pushed back for a day or two before her friends got used to her new face, at which point she'd go back to leaving it to fall over her forehead in cropped curls.

She bent to collect her bag from the floor and noticed with mixed feelings that the hem of her robes was an inch too short, now. While being taller would lend credence to her artifice, ill-fitting robes would not. If she were Harry, or even just Rigel, no one would notice too-short robes. Her friends in Slytherin would assume she simply gave her wardrobe the usual lack of attention that characterized her interaction with everything not-potion-related. Remus, however, might know that Sirius had just sent Archie's robes for re-tailoring not two weeks ago. In fact, Archie had secretly had them re-re-fitted to fit Harry's form, but in retrospect they should have anticipated some possible growth with the next dose of Polyjuice and left them.

She slouched experimentally in the mirror. It made her look a bit mopey, but it hid the shortness of her hem reasonably well. She didn't have to fake a tired expression to go with the slouch, at least—she'd started her monthlies that morning, and was already exhausted. Once she'd found a potion that let her regulate her cycles, she'd gotten in the habit of fixing them to start on the first of the month. It was a pain that she'd be dealing with the onset on the train again, but better to have them at an inopportune time than to forget when they were coming. With any luck she could get a nap in before they reached Hogwarts.

Satisfied that she looked sufficiently Rigel-like, she pointed her wand at her throat and cast the voice-altering spell, practicing a few lines until she felt reasonably sure her voice could pass as Archie's boyish tenor.

She left the lavatory and headed toward the compartment her year mates generally took for their own. It was still early, so she didn't expect to see anyone within, but Draco was sitting quietly in a window seat, elbow propped against the sill, fingers digging into the muscles of his bent neck. He looked over with a wince when the door opened, but relaxed somewhat when she stepped inside and closed it.

"Draco," she smiled a bit, looking him over subtly, "How are you?"

Her blonde friend bristled at the simple question, "What's that supposed to mean? How are you?"

Rigel shrugged, a bit taken aback, "Same as ever."

"Why shouldn't I be as well, then?" Draco said sourly.

"Are you?" Rigel asked, allowing genuine concern to leak into her voice for a moment, "Forgive me, Draco, but you seem…on edge. Has something happened?" Perhaps she was reading too much into her friend's behavior because of the vague worry that had been niggling at her mind since Mr. Malfoy had been to Krait's shop. Draco did look as tired as she felt, though, and she somehow doubted he was suffering something similar to what ailed her that day.

Draco looked incredulously at her, "I seem just fine." He sat up straighter and tilted his chin challengingly to emphasize this statement, but she could see the strain behind the façade. When she continued to peer worriedly at him, he muttered something about all-knowing, inhumanly observant friends, and sighed, "It's private."

Rigel frowned for a moment, but then nodded slowly. It wasn't like she could lecture him about keeping secrets. She took the seat next to him and pretended she wasn't worried, instead of pressing him, "How was the rest of your summer?"

Draco grimaced, "Long."

Sensing that much of his summer must have been bound up in whatever had strung out his nerves so completely, and wondering how much, if any, was related to the potion Mr. Malfoy had ordered from Krait, she dutifully changed the subject again.

"Who do you think made Head Boy and Girl this year?" Rigel asked, "Anyone in Slytherin?"

Draco considered it for a moment. "Head Boy will probably go to Weasley," he said reluctantly.

"Not Flint?" Rigel affected surprised dismay, "I thought the professors really started to warm to him last year."

Draco smiled wryly, though even that was slow coming, "Flint. I wonder if he'll even come back this year."

Rigel's eyebrows rose, "Why wouldn't he? It's NEWT year for him."

"Think he cares?" Draco shook his head, "He had to do fifth year twice, right? So he's of age now, or he will be soon. He's not stuck here anymore. He can get a job, start his life."

She considered this. There were some jobs you needed to be seventeen for, she supposed. Not everyone could work as a freelance brewer in Knockturn Alley. "He'd be better off with NEWT's, though, especially if he's looking for career-type work."

Draco snorted, "Flint's not cut out for the kind of jobs that require NEWT's."

Rigel frowned at his easy dismissal, "He's pretty smart, you know."

"It's not about smart," Draco said, rubbing his head like the conversation pained him, "It's a question of character. Stop feeling defensive over him, Rigel. Just because he was our captain doesn't mean we're obligated to overlook his flaws."

Rigel let amusement wash away her indignation, "Was? You seem pretty sure he's not coming back. Care to make a bet?"

Draco looked surprised, but no longer annoyed, at least, "Saint Rigel is going to gamble?"

"Is it gambling if you win?" Rigel asked philosophically.

Draco shook his head with amusement, "Yes. And you're not going to win. Stakes?"

Rigel tilted her head, "If Flint comes back to school this year, you come running with me every morning for two weeks."

Draco huffed, "You still do that? Fine, but when he doesn't return you have to fact check all my potions essays for two weeks."

"Deal," Rigel said, pretty sure Draco was wrong about Flint. She had a stack of summer assignments that said Flint had at least been planning to return as of a few months ago.

She reached out her hand to shake on it, and she didn't think she imagined the slight grimace in Draco's expression when he clasped it briefly.

Theo joined them shortly, looking tan and very self-assured after his summer in the south of Italy. His voice had deepened over the summer, and Rigel took that as a sign that she'd been right to start using the voice-altering spell this year.

Millicent and Pansy arrived together, and although Millicent looked about the same, Pansy's hair had grown astoundingly in just a few months. It was several inches past her collarbones, now, with highlights that spoke of too much time out of doors in the heat.

Blaise was the last to arrive, claiming the seat next to Rigel just as the whistle began to blow.

The first topic of conversation was, of course, the new Defense professor.

"Do you think they got anyone to take it after Lockhart?" Millicent shook her head, "It's not a tough act to follow by any means, but getting petrified probably doesn't appeal to many."

"The curse hasn't done anything that nasty to a someone in a while," Theo remarked, "Maybe it only reacts that badly to really incompetent professors."

Rigel smiled at that, "Then this year should be uneventful—my uncle Remus is taking the job."

"Seriously?" Theo blurted, "I mean…that's great."

"I was under the impression that your uncle was medically prevented from holding a job," Blaise commented delicately.

"He is," Rigel said easily, "But Dumbledore is a law unto himself. Apparently the Headmaster has complete hiring and firing privileges at Hogwarts, ministry sanctions notwithstanding."

"That's true," Draco said, his eyes tight despite the casualness of his tone, "Dumbledore could hire an escaped Azkaban criminal if he wanted. Father's always complaining about how consolidated his power-base is at Hogwarts."

"Well if anyone ever actually escapes from Azkaban, we'll know where to find them," Millicent said with dark humor.

"Will he be taking Professor Snape's New Wolfsbane Potion?" Pansy asked. Somehow Rigel had forgotten how shrewd Pansy could be.

"Yes," Rigel said, "The breakthrough in Wolfsbane was what prompted Dumbledore to consider Remus for the job." It also struck her privately that Dumbledore wanting Remus for the Defense position could explain why Snape had been so motivated to make that breakthrough in the first place.

"What's he like, as a professor?" Blaise asked curiously, "I don't think I've ever heard much about the man beyond rumors of his…condition."

"He's very knowledgeable on a variety of subjects," Rigel said honestly, "He's an accomplished dueler, and something of an expert in magical creatures. Personality wise, he is notoriously even-tempered, and he has a wicked sense of humor, but I'm not sure he'll show that in class."

"You're so obviously fond of him," Pansy said, her eyes soft, "I'm sure we'll quite enjoy his classes."

"Anything's better than Lockhart," Millicent shuddered, "Will it be hard to treat him like an authority figure now, though?"

Rigel smiled, "I doubt our relationship will change much. It's hard not to respect Remus."

Her uncle seemed to be working on distancing himself already, in fact. When Sirius suggested Remus escort Archie to the station, Remus was adamant that it would set an uncomfortable precedent. No doubt he anticipated accusations of favoritism, and his fair nature compelled him to nip the suspicion in the bud. Rigel wasn't going to complain—anything that would make the deception easier.

The conversation moved on to how everyone's summers had been. Theo was remarkably tight-lipped about his exploits in Italy, though he did waggle his eyebrows at Blaise when he thought Pansy and Millicent weren't looking.

He glanced at Rigel and abruptly snapped his fingers, saying, "I almost forgot, I met your cousin, Rigel."

Rigel had forgotten about that, too. "Really?" She feigned a mild interest, "Where? She was terribly busy this summer—I hardly saw her, and our families dine together most nights."

"Diagon Alley," Theo said, "She was shopping at Quality Quidditch. Does she play?"

"Beater," Rigel nodded, "She doesn't get the chance to practice much at AIM, though."

"What's she like?" Pansy asked, curious as ever about anyone she didn't know well.

"Very cool," Theo said earnestly.

"Is she pretty, your cousin?" Millicent asked slyly, eyeing the approving glint in Theo's eye.

"Not particularly," Rigel shrugged.

There was a moment of silence, after which Pansy sighed, "You're not supposed to say that about a Lady, Rigel, how many times must I tell you that?"

"Harry wouldn't mind me saying so," Rigel said, only a bit ironically, "She appreciates honesty."

"Well you've known her too long, obviously," Theo said, shaking his head at the others, "She looks a lot like Rigel, only…I don't know; not plain, though. Lovely eyes. She has a very casual air, but it's weirdly captivating, too. It's hard to explain. She looked at me like she knew things about me—but not in a creepy way. As if we were old friends, only we've never met. She's much friendlier than Rigel is. Funny, too."

Draco snorted gracelessly, "It sounds like you're in love, Theo."

Theo flushed, "Just wait until you meet her—you'll see what I mean."

"You're romanticizing her, because you don't know her very well," Rigel shook her head bemusedly, "Harry's not anything special."

"That's a perfectly awful thing to say about your cousin," Pansy said.

Rigel sighed, "I didn't mean she isn't worth knowing, just that there's nothing that unusual about her. She's just Harry."

"Like you're 'just Rigel,' you mean?" Blaise had a sardonic tilt to his mouth.

Rigel shrugged, not at all sure what to say to that.

Conversation lulled, the train rocked along, and Rigel didn't realize she'd fallen asleep until she woke to the sound of high-pitched yipping noises and several surprised curses.

She opened her eyes and rubbed at them absently as she glanced around the compartment. The door was open and Theo was standing in the middle of the compartment, balancing on one leg as he tried to avoid stepping on something jumping in circles beneath him.

It looked like a baby crup, no bigger than a small rabbit, with curly brown fur and a simple ribbon collar in black and gold.

Millicent had one hand pressed to her mouth, chortling, and Pansy was shaking her head with exasperation. Blaise and Draco just watched Theo dance around the little animal in resigned amusement.

"Found a new friend, Theo?" Rigel asked after a moment.

"It followed me in here when I went out to buy a snack," Theo said irritably, "Every time I try to shoo it out it just circles around behind me." With a sigh of annoyance, he swung his foot back slightly, as though he would give the pup a little kick in the direction of the door.

"No!" Pansy protested, but it was Blaise who reached down suddenly and scooped the crup out of harm's way.

"What?" Theo said defensively, "It's just some Hufflepuff's pet."

"It's a living creature," Pansy said staunchly, leaning over to pat the curly-haired crup apologetically on the head. "Thank you, Blaise."

Blaise shrugged unconcernedly, then frowned. He lifted the crup higher toward his face and sniffed at it. A moment later his expression stiffened and he moved from holding the animal by its scruff to cradling it in his arms.

"Aren't you going to take it to the prefect's compartment?" Millicent asked.

Blaise shook his head slowly, "His owner will come looking for him soon enough."

"All the more reason," Draco muttered, "Don't need more people in here."

Blaise didn't respond, but settled the pet rather decisively in his lap.

Theo rolled his eyes, but sat back down, "At least it's quiet now."

It was another twenty minutes before anyone came knocking on the compartment door, but it was indeed a pair of Hufflepuffs who stuck their heads in a moment later.

"Has anyone seen—oh!" Hannah Abbot rushed into the compartment and bent down in front of Blaise until she was eye-level with the crup, aiming a bright smile into its face, "He's here, Ernie. Hi there, little guy. Did you miss me?"

The crup yipped up at the yellow-haired girl cheerfully, but didn't squirm to get free of Blaise's hold.

"Thank you so much for watching…" Abbot trailed off as she looked up and caught Blaise's gaze. Their dark-skinned friend was staring very intently at the girl from under his lids. After an awkward moment in which the Hufflepuff cleared her throat, she continued, "Well, thanks. Um, I'm Hannah. I mean, we've met, but not really…well."

Abruptly she seemed to realize she was bent awkwardly over Blaise's lap, and straightened with a blush. She looked around the compartment uncertainly, smiling nervously as her gaze flitted from face to face.

"Anyway, thanks for looking after him," she said with an awkward smile, "I just got him this summer from my aunt, and he's not very well trained, and I'm really sorry if he bothered you…"

Seeing that no one else was going to say anything, Rigel put on a kind smile, "It was no trouble, right guys?"

Pansy took that as her cue to incline her head graciously, and Theo mumbled something semi-agreeable under his breath.

Abbot fingered one of her pigtails nervously, "Thanks, Rigel. I…owe you one?"

It was clear she assumed that's what one was supposed to say to Slytherins when they helped you, but also clear she had no idea what she was really offering.

"Are you kidding?" Rigel affected an embarrassed expression, "I still owe you for saving me in first year. Anyway, it's Blaise you should thank. Blaise Zabini, in case you haven't been introduced formally."

"I, ah, I've seen you around," she offered, giving Blaise a friendly head-tilt, "Hannah Abbot." She held out her hand to shake.

"He knows," Draco muttered quietly. Rigel elbowed him discretely as Blaise reached out slowly to clasp her hand.

He held it still, without shaking it, and said, "It is a pleasure and honor to make your formal acquaintance, Miss Abbot."

The girl's pigtails quivered as she glanced up at Blaise's face, down to their clasped hands, then back up in quick, nervous succession, "Likewise."

Ernie Macmillan, who was standing in the doorway with his arms crossed, cleared his throat pointedly, "Hannah. Let's go."

Abbot smiled again and tugged her hand out of Blaise's grasp gently. She reached toward the crup in his lap, and Blaise obligingly handed him over carefully. "Thanks, again," she said with a little self-deprecating chuckle, "See you all in class."

"Goodbye, Miss Abbot," Blaise said with a slow smile.

The Hufflepuff girl positively tripped her way back out into the corridor, and when the door slid closed once more Theo and Millicent both let out snorts they'd apparently been repressing.

"Smooth," Millicent laughed.

"Thank you," Blaise said, unconcernedly brushing a bit of stray fur from his robes.

"So you're going for it this year?" Theo asked suggestively. It seems Rigel wasn't the only one who'd noticed Blaise's unusual…fixation on Abbot.

"Don't be crass," Pansy said mildly.

"We'll see," Blaise said evenly. Despite Theo's needling, that was all he'd say on the subject.

The train pulled into the station just after dark. They piled out like a wave across the platform, Theo, Millicent, and Blaise splitting off in silent agreement to find their own carriage. The crowd of students was thick, but it was still a complete surprise when Draco suddenly clutched at Rigel's arm and leaned his weight on her.

She looked over to see him grasping Pansy's forearm with a slightly gentler grip as well. Pansy frowned and subtly stepped closer to support their friend without calling attention to his apparent weakness.

Rigel leaned her head in and asked lowly, "What's wrong?"

"Nothing," Draco gritted out, despite the fact that his face was paler than parchment and he was fighting full-body tremors as they moved through the crowd. Several times she saw him flinch away from the people around him.

Rigel exchanged a glance with Pansy, and in tacit agreement they propelled Draco toward the carriages as quickly as they were able to without causing a seen.

They half-hoisted their friend into the first one they came across. There was already a small girl sitting alone within, but they ignored her in favor of making sure Draco wasn't going to collapse or go into a seizure or something.

"I'm fine," Draco snapped, curling his arms around his narrow torso and turning his head out of the carriage window as it began to move forward.

Rigel and Pansy both backed off, settling back into their seats without pressing Draco further. The fourth member of their compartment didn't seem to be paying any attention to the mini-drama; in fact, she appeared to have sunk into herself psychologically. Rigel frowned as she took in the girl's drawn features and tense posture. Instead of moving with the rocking carriage, she sat so stiffly that it jarred her with every bump.

Just as Rigel was going to ask what was wrong with her, Draco sighed sharply and turned to glare at the girl. "For Salazar's sake, girl, they aren't that frightening. Stop sniveling."

Pansy frowned, "Draco—"

"What?" he turned his irritated glare on Pansy, "She's going to be taking the carriages for the next six years, so she might as well get over it now."

Pansy gaped a bit, taken aback by Draco's inexplicable vehemence.

"H-how did you know?" the petit girl gasped out.

Draco's features closed down abruptly, "It's obvious by how tense you are that you're scared. It didn't start after we got here, so you're frightened by something about the carriage. If you can get on a train, you aren't afraid of moving vehicles, which leaves the thestrals."

"Why do the horses have to be invisible?" the girl whispered, shuddering a bit, "It's like being driven by a ghost."

"Be grateful you can't see them," Draco said darkly, "They're even more hellish when visible, I hear."

"Draco," Pansy said, exasperated. She turned to the other girl with a soft expression, "There's nothing to be afraid of."

"How do you know?" the girl said, looking at Pansy very solemnly through wide, baby blue eyes. She would be incredibly beautiful, Rigel realized, when her features weren't cramped with misery.

Pansy faltered under the serious question, but Draco blew out a long sigh and said, "They let them pull the carriages—do you think the professors here would let dangerous things near the students unsupervised?"

The girl blinked slowly, her shoulders relaxing slightly, "I suppose not. What if the teachers don't know—"

"You think you know more than the professors?" Draco said pointedly.

"No," she flushed, ducking her chin so that her ringlets fell across her cheeks with little bounces.

"Then stop being afraid," Draco said. He eyed her robes with a slight sneer, "You're a Slytherin. So act like one."

Pansy suddenly seemed to place the girl in her memory, and straightened up in her seat, "You're Astoria Greengrass, aren't you? Daphne's younger sister?"

The girl, Greengrass, nodded shyly, "You're Pansy Parkinson. My sister says you look like a pug."

Pansy blinked, and Greengrass clapped a hand over her mouth in horror.

"I didn't mean—you don't!" she flushed, "You're very pretty, Miss Parkinson."

Pansy's lips tilted in a wry smile, "Thank you. Just Pansy, is fine. May I call you Astoria?"

"Of course," Greengrass junior smiled, and Rigel noted that she'd been correct—the girl was perfectly lovely.

"These are my friends, Draco Malfoy and Rigel Black," Pansy said, gesturing toward each of them in turn.

Rigel smiled and executed a parody of a gallant bow sitting down, which came out ridiculous looking and made Greengrass giggle, just as she'd intended, "Pleasure to meet you, Miss Greengrass."

The second-year girl looked vaguely familiar if she thought back to the group of firsties from the year before, who'd always seemed to move in a small herd, but Rigel was fairly sure she hadn't known Daphne Greengrass even had a sister, much less one at Hogwarts. Then again, she didn't converse with the elder Greengrass sister terribly often.

"You as well," the girl said, and only her bright eyes kept her tone from being simpering. She turned to Draco and flushed a bit, saying, "Thank you, Mr. Malfoy, for your advice. I don't feel so afraid anymore."

"Thank Merlin for that," Draco mumbled, with the barest nod of courtesy in the girl's direction.

Greengrass didn't seem offended, though. She beamed as though Draco had said something perfectly chivalrous, and settled herself more comfortably in her seat for the remainder of the trip.

They swarmed into the Great Hall like so many locusts, hungry and buzzing with impatient anticipation. The sight of the house tables all lined up and bedecked with plates and goblets brought a clenched feeling to Rigel's stomach and to her horror she felt her eyes watering in a way that had nothing to do with the thousands of floating candles shedding light down on the returning students.

I missed this place, she realized with faint surprise, not just as a place to learn and see my friends, but for the place itself. She wondered if that was part of the magic of the castle, to make it seem like home no matter how many homes a person already had.

She blinked away the strangely warm nostalgia welling up and cast her glance toward the head table. She spotted Remus immediately, sitting cheerfully beside a dour Professor Snape, and no doubt at least part of the reason the Potions Master looked even more disgruntled than usual to be presiding over the welcoming feast. She smiled when she saw Remus skimming the Slytherin table idly and gave a discrete nod in greeting when he finally picked her out of the crowd. She tried not to betray any anxiety over his presence in her mannerisms, instead affecting the relaxed, confident air that many of her fellow third years seemed to have adopted since she last saw them.

She supposed it was hard not to feel a bit superior when the second-years were looking so uncomfortably awkward at being seated during the welcoming ceremony for the first time. When McGonagall led in a line of trembling first-years the amused, smug grins on her classmates' faces only widened.

Rigel put on a friendly expression, in case any of the firsties' apprehensive glances around the hall should happen to fall in her direction, and waited in silence with the rest of the hall as the Sorting Hat was brought out and began to sing:

"It's been a merry thousand years

since this old hat was sewn.

But every moment since then

I have called this castle home.

The dungeons and the library,

the kitchens and the lawns,

The students running here and there,

their laughter and their yawns.

All of this and more I hold

close to my ragged brim.

But lately something worries me

and leaves me feeling grim.

For though I sit here every year

and sort you one and all,

And though I've said that doing so

will help you to stand tall,

I wonder if dividing you

by idealistic traits

Might overplay your differences

and chain you to four fates.

Though Gryffindor once told me

I was made to see the heart

It seems to me that naming it

thus chokes it from the start.

If one child is called clever

does that mean he couldn't dare?

Rowena used her wisdom

to defend those in her care.

Is courage so commendable

when work ethic is lacking?

Never once did Godric say

that chivalry meant slacking.

Does caring for your friends mean

wanting nothing for your own?

Sweet Helga had ambition

and the strength to see it sown.

And can the child with dreams

fulfill them only through deceit?

Salazar oft said success

comes not to those who cheat.

I see the ravens scorn the puffs

and lions fight the snakes,

And everyone thinks far too much

of ancestors' mistakes.

I can't help feel my time grows short,

my purpose all but gone.

The past must bow to present needs

or reap a future wrong.

So this time when I call a House

and send you on your way,

Listen close for all the things

I didn't get to say.

For each of you is special

in a way that can't be named.

One word cannot define you

though that's what I've always claimed.

So come up here and try me on,

I'll give you my critique

But know that fractured strength

cannot disguise that which is weak.

Your house is not your destiny,

although it is your home

The world is made of every house,

and not just one alone."

The applause came slowly, interspersed with murmurs.

"It barely mentioned the House traits—"

"I never heard that Ravenclaw knew battle magic—"

A stern throat clearing by McGonagall eventually cut the whispered speculations short, and the Sorting proceeded without major incident. Dumbledore, ever conscientious of his student's impatient bellies, did not wait long after the last student scrambled over to the Gryffindor table to let the feast begin.

"I've never heard it criticize students so openly," Rosier, who was sitting a few seats down and across from Rigel, said idly as they began to serve themselves. It took a moment for Rigel to realize he was talking about the Sorting Hat, but she observed several other older students nodding their heads in silent agreement.

"How does it know the Gryffindors are slacking, anyway?" Avery laughed, glancing over his shoulder at the red-and-gold-plated table behind him.

"They're always slacking," someone else said dismissively, "That's what happens when you have no ambition, no work ethic, and no smarts."

Several other people laughed, and the conversation moved on.

"Don't seem to have absorbed the Hat's message much, do they?" Rigel asked in quiet amusement, turning her head toward Draco as she speared a potato on her fork. The teasing grin dropped from her lips as she took in his absolutely haunted expression. He was white-faced and tight lipped, his hands clenched in his lap, not even bothering to pretend like he was eating.

Rigel immediately began surreptitiously sliding food onto his plate in between serving herself. An empty plate would attract obvious attention, once people started looking up from their food. She leaned her shoulder gently into Draco's, and he flinched violently at first, then began to sag into her side. She stiffened her muscles as much as she could to act as an unobtrusive prop, and after a few moments she felt Draco take a deep, steadying breath.

"All right?" she asked mildly, knowing that a concerned or suspicious tone would only attract the notice of those around them.

"Fine," Draco said, and somehow his voice came out with casually controlled ease, despite the slight quaking that passed from his wobbly frame to her solid one.

He began to slowly eat with his left hand while his right side leaned into her. It wasn't obvious that she was supporting him, thanks to how crowded the tables were, and she was impressed with the level of relaxation he managed to inject into his movements, despite also being painfully aware of how little strength he seemed to have. Her left shoulder and side began to ache after a while, but she said nothing, keeping as still as possible, and idly wondering if she had known Draco was ambidextrous and forgotten, or if he'd merely hidden the skill extremely well until now. His left hand didn't so much as hesitate in guiding food gracefully from plate to palate.

Even Pansy didn't seem to notice Draco's weakness, though Rigel reflected that if their blonde friend had noticed she likely would not have made any outward sign of her knowledge in deference to her friend's pride.

The feast seemed to go on much longer than usual, and it was with relief that Rigel saw Dumbledore finally stand and command the Hall's attention with a genial smile.

"Welcome all to a new term at Hogwarts," he said with a little bow in the students' general direction. The movement caused his hat to slip forward into his eyes and many laughed good-naturedly as the Headmaster straightened it with an embarrassed little grin. "So many new faces I see tonight, a few of which sit at this very table," Dumbledore gestured to his left and right. "As you may have heard, our esteemed Professor Lockhart found that teaching was not his calling after all and decided to continue his battle against the dark forces in a more active fashion. In his place, I am pleased to welcome Professor Remus Lupin, accomplished duelist and expert in the art of magical defense."

The Hall clapped politely while Remus stood and gave a brief smile and wave.

"Alas, dear Professor Lockhart was not the only one of our family to leave us this summer," Dumbledore continued, "Our good friend Professor Kettleburn has, at long last, retired. Our new Care of Magic Creatures professor is not present at the moment, but I'm sure—"

The door behind the staff table banged open loudly and a short man in a long brown coat came scurrying through, "I'm here," a small voice coughed apologetically, "Here, Headmaster. Sorry. Trouble with the thestrals…"

"Ah, your timing is most appropriate, Professor Pettigrew," Dumbledore said with a friendly wave, "Come and introduce yourself to the students."

Rigel started involuntarily at the name 'Pettigrew' and felt Draco jerk as though in echo of her surprise. "Sorry," she muttered distractedly, eyes fixed on the head table.

Pettigrew was the fourth Marauder, the one who'd broken ties with her father and uncle after declaring allegiance to the SOW party. He was to teach here, the same year that Remus happened to be teaching? That was a rather large coincidence, she thought with a tendril of suspicion.

As Pettigrew stammered through a brief, "Hello," to the Hall, Rigel looked toward Remus and surprised a look of utter bewilderment on his face. So her uncle had not known about Pettigrew's arrival at Hogwarts, either.

The start-of-term announcements continued after Pettigrew took a seat beside Hagrid, but Rigel was not really listening. She was thinking. Someone had to fill Kettleburn's place, of course, but for it to be a member of Riddle's party, even a junior member…was is really a coincidence? Riddle had promised to stop meddling at Hogwarts. Was he already going back on his word?

Rigel shook the suspicion away with difficulty. Lots of people were members of the SOW party, probably. Maybe even some of the other teachers were, too. She realized she didn't actually know all her professors' allegiances, and reassured herself that if Dumbledore had hired him, he was bound to be okay. Then she remembered that Dumbledore had hired Lockhart, too, and Quirrell before him.

He was friends with Sirius, James, and Remus, once, she told herself, he can't be as bad as all that.

He seemed familiar, too. Like a face she'd seen in a crowd once, or printed in the newspaper, perhaps. On top of all that, he was so…unassuming. He stumbled through his introduction, but not in the contrived, stuttering way that Quirrell once had. Pettigrew seemed genuinely flustered at all the attention, and his face turned a cherry red as he slinked away to his seat. She could almost feel sorry for the man—and probably would, if she hadn't know how the loss of his friendship had hurt the other three Marauders for many years after.

Dumbledore wrapped up his speech quickly and sent them off to bed. Rigel took a risk and casually slipped an arm under Draco's outer cloak and around his waist as they stood. Supporting him, she lingered at the edges of the Slytherin crowd as it headed down into the dungeons.

When they reached the common room, Rigel skirted the room with Draco and slipped unobtrusively down the hallway to their dorm room. Everyone else would be congregating for the start-of-term house meeting with Professor Snape, but Rigel thought her Head of House would forgive her for being more concerned with Draco's health, even if the meeting was supposed to be mandatory.

Maybe he won't notice we're missing, she thought, wryly optimistic.

When she nudged the door closed behind them, Draco immediately pulled away from her and slid to the floor by the foot of his bed, where his trunk was sitting. He opened it, and, thinking he meant to unpack before resting (as was the fastidious boy's usual habit), Rigel moved closer to help.

Draco snapped his head up at her with a scowl, "Going to watch me undress?" he asked snidely.

Rigel stopped and turned with a shrug toward her own bed, which was once again next to Draco's. She fished in her trunk for her pajamas and heard the rustling sound of shifting fabric that told of Draco doing the same.

Then she heard the tell tale snick-pop of a small cork being pulled from a vial. She turned her head slightly to see Draco shoving something underneath the top layer of clothing quickly, a grimace on his face, no doubt from the aftertaste of what he'd just gulped down. She politely ignored the slight smell of suppressant potion that permeated the air, but she did wonder how stupid Draco thought her to be, exactly.

She dawdled until Draco climbed into bed and closed his curtains, then let her face melt from its serene expression into a thoughtful moue. The potions were definitely meant for Draco, then, and he was taking them willingly. All clues pointed to a magical gift recently acquired, but what could Draco have unlocked that would be so draining that it required suppressant potions to—apparently unsuccessfully—subdue? Most magical abilities did not negatively affect the user, even when out of control. It had to be a gift that caused the environment to influence Draco, instead of the other way around. He could be a magic-sensor, she supposed, which would certainly explain why he was overwhelmed by Hogwarts even with the suppressant potion dampening his sensing abilities. He could also be some sort of elemental mage—the ambient magic around Hogwarts would definitely give Draco one monster of a headache before he learned to control it were that the case.

Rigel shook her head as she quietly began unpacking her things. There was no way of knowing for sure until Draco told her. Whatever his gift was, he wasn't in full control of it, and it was unlikely to pose a real threat until he was, and maybe not even then. She hadn't learned Occlumency for nothing, after all.

Severus strode quickly from the Slytherin dorms, not because he was in a particular hurry, but because only the disgustingly young thought time could ever afford to be wasted. His start of term speech had gone smoothly, though he noted the absence of two particular third-years with little surprise. Lucius had of course informed Severus of his godson's recently acquired…ailment. That Rigel Black had already noticed and responded to his friend's condition was inevitable, and a testament to the boy's suitability as an asset to the Malfoy family, besides.

He arrived at the too-familiar stone gargoyle in a timely fashion, and only after affixing an appropriately disgusted sneer to his features did he utter the phrase "Jumping Jellies" in its general direction.

Albus had already donned a dizzying nightshirt that appeared to portray a patchwork of meaningless symbols, all of which orbited the headmaster's torso exuberantly at a speed unsuited to any sort of sleepwear, much less that of a venerable wizard of Albus' age and power.

Worse than the garment he wore was the old coot's twinkling, knowing gaze.

"Has it arrived?" Severus asked tersely.

"Of course, of course," Albus smiled infuriatingly, "You'll be giving it to him tomorrow morning, I suppose?"

"That is when the students receive their schedules, is it not?" Snape bit out, resigned to the knowledge that the old wizard was not simply going to hand it over without pausing to savor the moment first.

"It is so good to see you finally taking such personal interest in a student, Severus," Albus commented with a satisfied little hum, "It's about time you took a prodigy of your own. All the other professors have had at least two—Filius has personally trained seven bright young minds, if I recall correctly."

"As you say," Severus said, holding a hand out impatiently, "If it has indeed arrived, I will take it now."

Albus chuckled as he reached into a drawer and pulled out a golden drawstring pouch, "Always in such a hurry, Severus. Let us hope your apprentice shares your…respect for time-management, eh?"

Severus took the pouch expressionlessly, mentally grumbling about wizards who took too much amusement in the sensibleness of others.

"Good evening, Albus," he said once he had secured the little bag at his belt.

"I daresay it has been," the headmaster said, twiddling his thumbs as Severus made for the door.

Rigel woke earlier than her roommates, as was her habit, and collected her running clothes before heading into the bathroom she shared with Draco, Theo and Blaise having unofficially claimed the other as their own.

Once she'd stripped down to her underwear, she quickly Evanesco-ed the evidence of her monthly bleeding and performed a bleaching spell on her underwear just to be thorough before tossing it down the laundry shoot. She wondered vaguely if Archie ever considered exactly what his clothing was going through, being lent to her, then decided that for his sake she hoped he hadn't worked out the exact logistics.

Her magic was under her complete control once more, thanks to a few days work getting used to the suppressant ring. From what she'd deduced, it worked something like a dam on her magical core, holding all but a thin trickle back when she tried to use her magic. She'd done all sorts of experimenting in the days leading up to her return to Hogwarts, and generally the results had left her quite satisfied.

Most of the spells she knew worked perfectly normally. Sometimes when she imbued a potion it took much longer than normal, because while she could direct the magic to the potion she couldn't widen the 'hole,' so to speak, so there was only so much magic she could use within a certain amount of time.

She couldn't cast the Despaco shield at all. It simply required more magic at a faster rate than she had access to with the dampener on.

She dressed quickly, making sure that the tiny bit of non-flatness that distorted the otherwise masculine line of her chest was invisible even while bouncing due to the tight elastic undershirt she wore beneath the baggier, sweat-stained outer one.

Lastly, she drew on a pair of thin, plain black gloves that nevertheless sat smoothly over the two rings on her left middle finger. There was no need for anyone to know she wore a dampener, particularly if it was one Harriet Potter might be seen wearing in the future, and there was the very slight chance that Remus had noticed Harry wearing the basilisk ring that summer.

She stopped at her trunk to pull out her trainers, and saw Draco poke his head out from behind his curtains as she shut the lid.

"Going running?" he asked, sleep thickening his voice.

Rigel nodded, "Want to come?"

Draco began to shake his head tiredly then stopped, looking thoughtful. "Yes…" he said slowly, "May I?"

"Of course," she said, a bit surprised. Draco was not a morning person, and usually grumbled about coming running with her, though he did every so often.

Draco had a determined cast to his features as he padded quickly to his trunk and rummaged for comfortable clothing. Rigel looked away as he began to change unselfconsciously into loose breeches, and didn't look back until he nudged her with the toe of his shoe and a soft chuckle.

"Still so easily flustered, Rye?"

It was the first time he'd used her nickname since coming back to Hogwarts, and Rigel couldn't help the warm feeling it gave her insides. She had begun to think her friend would be perpetually grumpy, at least until he adjusted to whatever magical gift was affecting him.

"It turns my stomach to see naked people so early in the morning," she drawled softly, a curl of disgust on her lips.

"Sure it does," Draco huffed, grabbing his wand and fitting it into the holster on his arm with casual grace. She wondered wryly how many times he'd practiced that motion since getting the wand-holder for his birthday. "Just admit you're a prude," he said as they slipped out of the room and into the hallway.

"As soon as you admit you're an exhibitionist," Rigel tossed back.

"I prefer to think of it as a form of community service," Draco said archly, "The world would be a drab little place without my beauty to brighten it."

"That's what women are for," said an amused voice by the common room door.

They looked over to see Pansy waiting for them casually at the entrance wall, dressed in loose-fitting clothing, her medium-length hair pulled back into a no-nonsense bun. At their surprised looks, Pansy laughed and shook her head mockingly, "You didn't think I'd let you boys have all the fun, did you?"

Rigel felt even warmer still as the three of them traipsed out to the castle lawn and down toward the lake where she preferred to jog. She had missed her friends over the summer. She loved her family dearly, but she never felt less alone than she did with Draco and Pansy by her side.

"I hope you kept in shape this summer," she said, a bit of cheek in her voice, "I'd hate to have to run circles around you."

"Not all of us were distracted with what was no doubt untoward amounts of potions brewing, Rigel," Pansy said slyly, "You just try to keep up."

The blonde girl took off at a brisk pace, her muscles making no unnecessary movements as her feet propelled her across the ground.

"You heard the lady," Draco said, a smile on his lips. They took off at a reasonable jog of their own and Rigel couldn't help but notice Draco noticing Pansy's admittedly trim figure as she glided just ahead of them.

When did we start getting old enough for that? She wondered idly. Not that she disapproved. It could only be a good thing if Pansy and Draco became…interested in one another. They were a good match—friendly with one another, both Heirs to prominent families…and if their attention was on one another, well, how much time could they spend wondering about their other friend Rigel's enigmatic life?

Those were thoughts for the future, though, so Rigel let her mind wander to other things as they made good time on the rest of their run.

Draco was noticeably more tired than either Pansy or Rigel by the time they reached their starting point, but it was he who, in between pants, asked, "What…next?"

Rigel led the stretching routine, then the strengthening exercises, lending her friends her hand weights when they sheepishly replied they had forgotten to bring theirs along. Rigel had long since stopped wearing weights constantly in an effort to bulk up—the amount of physical exercise she had been getting over the summer meant her arms and legs were whip-chord tight now—but she kept the hand weights in the pockets of her workout attire, since the exercises Remus prescribed her still required them.

They arrived at breakfast just in time to see Professor Snape handing out the schedules for the new term. This would be the first year they were permitted to choose extracurriculars, and their year mates were already beginning to excitedly compare their schedules.

Draco and Pansy received theirs eagerly, examining them with pleased expressions, but when the time came for Rigel to get hers, Snape fixed her with a level stare and said, "There were issues accommodating the classes you opted for, Mr. Black. Come to my office after your meal and we will discuss possible revisions."

Rigel quietly agreed, fighting a frown. Draco, who was looking much improved from the night before despite the way he continued to twitch unprovoked every so often, raised an eyebrow at Rigel's empty hands. "Tell me you didn't try to sign up for all of the optional classes."

Rigel suppressed a flush, "Of course not. Maybe one of the classes they put me in was cancelled, or something."

"What did you want to take?" Pansy asked curiously, "I've got Care of Magical Creatures, Arithmancy, and Divination."

"Divination?" Draco wrinkled his nose, "Why?"

Pansy shrugged, "I thought it would pair well with Arithmancy."

Draco didn't seem convinced, but he said, "I'm taking International Studies, Ancient Runes, and Dueling. I applied for the Healing course, but I suppose my Charms work wasn't up to snuff."

They looked expectantly at Rigel, so she shrugged uncomfortably and admitted, "I just picked whatever seemed interesting. Arithmancy, Ancient Runes, Magical Theory, Healing, Dueling, Alchemy...I knew it was too many, but I thought they'd just put me in whichever ones were convenient, providing I even got into all of them."

Draco rolled his eyes, "Did you even prioritize them on your form?"

She smiled a bit sheepishly, "I'm not too picky. Anything besides Potions is secondary, Professor Snape knows that. I didn't want to take a spot in a popular class that someone else really wanted when I'd be happy with anything."

Her friends shook their heads good-naturedly, but otherwise went back to exchanging schedules with the others.

She entered Snape's office at his beckoning and sat in the plain chair he'd provided her. She couldn't remember at what point the Potions Master began transfiguring a seat for her when they met in his office, but she felt no small amount of pride at the thought that she'd risen enough in his esteem to merit it.

Snape favored her with a long, penetrating stare before he spoke; "There are not many students in this institution who truly appreciate its purpose, Mr. Black. Many of your peers are here because our laws require a witch or wizard to earn a minimum of four OWLs in order to retain his or her wand. There are some, however, like yourself, who are here to actively pursue an education. Among those students, those who show genuine promise are even fewer. Of those with potential, fewer still demonstrate the dedication and level-headedness necessary to earn the unanimous esteem of their professors. These latter students, Mr. Black, are therefore awarded certain...opportunities."

Rigel just blinked, unsure where Snape was going with this. Would they allow her to take more than the recommended three electives after all?

"As such opportunities are not available to the majority of students, it is necessary that they be handled with a particular attention to discretion." Snape's gaze became, if possible, more serious, "What I am about to discuss with you will remain a secret. You will not tell Miss Parkinson and you will not even hint at it within Mr. Malfoy's hearing. Is that completely understood?"

"Yes, Sir," Rigel said, a bit alarmed. What in regards to her schedule could possibly warrant such secrecy?

Snape nodded in a satisfied way, reached into his desk drawer, and withdrew a thin, golden chain, at the end of which hung a sturdy-looking hourglass filled with golden sand and encased in a circular shell.

"This is a time-turner," Snape said, sliding the necklace carefully across the desk. "It allows its wearer to travel backwards in time, not to change time, but to re-live periods of it. With this model, one can travel a maximum of seven days into the past, but you will never need to use it to travel more than 12 hours back. You will never tell anyone you have access to this device. Some professors have already been informed, of course, but the other students must not know."

Rigel stared at the tiny device in patent disbelief, "You're giving me a time-turner?"

"The Ministry is loaning a time-turner to a very promising young student who has already demonstrated exceptional moral fiber in the face of adversity. It is to be used only for the purposes of academic enrichment. The moment its use is suspected to be flagrant in any manner, it will be removed from your possession forthwith."

Rigel nodded slowly, still coming to grips with the fact that Snape was giving her a time-turner. "So..." She cleared her throat and tried again, "What classes am I taking, then?"

Snape wordlessly handed her a very complicated-looking schedule. There were thirteen classes in total, she counted, seven core classes and six electives. Except... "I don't have Potions with the other third years?"

"You are beyond any material covered in third-year Potions," Snape said frankly, "It would be a waste of your time and an unfair level of competition for your classmates. You will have private lessons three times a week with me instead."

She inclined her head, not about to turn down personal lessons with Master Snape, even if it did mean one less class with her friends. "I didn't expect to be accepted into all of these," she commented faintly, scanning the extracurriculars. Arithmancy, Ancient Runes, and Magical Theory were open to all students, as none required a strong background in any particular subject, but Healing, Alchemy, and Dueling all required recommendations from the Charms, Potions, and Defense professors respectively. She supposed they must just look at a student's record for Defense, since professors were so inconsistent.

"You've already been taking Healing lessons with Madam Pomfrey once a month," Snape pointed out, "Now you will have them two hours a week. Your scores on the Defense Against the Dark Arts end of term exams have been above average both times. As for Alchemy, there is no question that you have both the Herbology and Potions experience necessary to attempt the art. The Headmaster is very busy, however, which is why you have only one double lesson a week in that subject."

Blowing out a slow breath at the idea of studying Alchemy under Professor Dumbledore himself, Rigel said, "If it's all right, professor, I would like to drop the Dueling class completely. I'm grateful to be accepted, but I believe even with the time-turner twelve classes will be more than enough."

In truth, she would have loved to take Dueling, but when she'd applied for it she hadn't known Remus would be teaching it. The less time she spent with her uncle, the better.

Snape regarded her thoughtfully, then smiled ever so slightly, "Very well. It is exactly this kind of prudence that afforded you this opportunity, Mr. Black."

Rigel swallowed the sick feeling of guilt in her stomach, and smiled back.

"If everything else is in order, I will explain how this time-turner works, and you will use it to go back one hour and arrive at your first class on time." Snape went through the mechanics of the time-turner quickly, and Rigel was surprised by how simple it was. She merely had to turn the shell 1/2 turn for every hour she wanted to go back. "I recommend you limit yourself to turning only an hour or two at any one time, then turning again later that day if you've need. Once you begin repeating whole days at once, it becomes more and more difficult to remember where and when you are supposed to be."

Rigel nodded. That made sense. "I'll be awake more than the recommended 16 hours a day with this," she commented, "Should I sleep more to compensate?"

"Yes," Snape replied, "You'll want to sleep an extra hour a night at least, depending on how many hours you turn that day. On the back of your schedule there is a recipe for a potion that will lengthen your sleep cycle an average of five hours a day. Although you shouldn't need to repeat more than two hours a day to attend all your classes, you will need the extra time to complete homework assignments for your additional workload. You are responsible for brewing the potion yourself and taking it once a week."

She nodded to show she was listening, looking over the schedule. "On Tuesdays I have Magical Theory at the same time as Alchemy and Defense. So I can redo the same hour more than twice?"

Her brain was beginning to catch up to the possibilities the time-turner represented, and she was having trouble suppressing her growing excitement.

"You can be present in the same time no more than six times at the very most, which is more than you will ever require," Snape said curtly, "Too many identical cores in close proximity can cause extremely unnerving magical resonance that has been known to disrupt or damage a wizard's magical core indefinitely."

Rigel made a mental note not to repeat any hour more than five times, just in case. "Will it age me?"

"It will," Snape allowed, "But no more than a few months unless you use it excessively." He eyed her sternly as though he knew exactly what she was thinking. "This is an enormous responsibility, Mr. Black. You will be psychologically evaluated at random intervals throughout the year and if at any point I find you are using this device unwisely, I will be unspeakably aggravated."

Rigel put on her best reassuring smile, "Academic pursuits only, Sir. I understand. Thank you. I won't make you regret giving me this chance." She was going to take twelve classes. Twelve! And she would never not have enough time for something again! Occlumency, Healing, Flint's assignments (provided he ever showed up to claim them), even brewing for Krait would be no problem now.

"There are a few more conditions," Snape cautioned, "People with registered time-turners are not allowed to participate in competitive sports, in case they use their advantage to view the game before participating in it, so you will be forced to withdraw from the Slytherin House Quidditch team if you decide to accept this."

Rigel grimaced, but nodded her understanding.

"You must never take the time-turner off. Not when you shower, not when you sleep. Change clothing in a way that will not reveal it to anyone, though it is spelled with a subtle notice-me-not that should suffice unless you call deliberate attention to it. You must remember when you are at all times; do not cross paths with yourself, do not be seen by two different people at the same time if they are likely to mention it to one another. Most of your classes are organized such that the regular third-year classes only overlap with classes you will take one-on-one, like Healing and Alchemy, but this is not always the case. Do nothing memorable in class, nothing that will be talked about. When your friends ask which classes you're taking tell them only the ones that cannot be kept private. This," he pulled out a second schedule, much simpler than the first, "Is the schedule your friends will see. You are taking Ancient Runes, Arithmancy, and Magical Theory only once a week. Your private lessons with me are during your third-year Transfiguration classes, so say only that you are self-studying Potions according to an advanced syllabus of my devising. Any questions?"

It was a lot to take in. She thought for a long moment, but the only thing she could think to say was, "Thank you."

"You are due in Charms," was all he said in reply.

She stepped into a small alcove and turned her time-turner back an hour, then checked the wrist watch she used to time potions in lieu of the pocket watch Archie gave her (being that she still couldn't open that one) and realized it still showed the time being an hour later.

Of course, she mentally sighed, her watch was moving linearly like she was; it didn't care that she'd traveled backwards in time. Its cogs just kept ticking along. She got out a small notebook and noted the date and time she'd used her time-turner discretely on a blank page toward the back. She suspected this was going to get complicated.

In a burst of curiosity, she pulled out the Marauder's Map and looked for a dot bearing her name. There were two, she realized with a small smile, one up in the Great Hall and one in the alcove in the dungeons. That was certainly going to be useful. If she ever forgot where one of her was at a given time, she could just check the Map to make sure she didn't run into…her? Herself? Shaking her head, she put the Map away and used her wand to cast a spell that showed the actual time.

She still had twenty minutes before she would even leave breakfast for Snape's office. A little unnerved by the idea that there was another, slightly younger version of herself sitting upstairs in the Great Hall in complete ignorance of her existence, Rigel pulled out her invisibility cloak and put it on. Classes wouldn't start until fifteen minutes after breakfast, so she had half an hour to do with as she liked, and she wasn't going to waste one minute of it.

She pulled out the Dark Disguise book and settled in to read. There was a fascinating section on skin-changing charms that she'd probably never use, but which she thought had a similar methodology to certain skin-related Healing charms, particularly those that vanished potentially cancerous freckles.

She arrived in Charms right on time, slipping into a seat between her friends a moment before Professor Flitwick bounced through the door.

"That didn't take long," Pansy said, her voice low, "Did you get your schedule worked out?"

"Professor Snape just had to give me my potions syllabus," she said casually, feeling the time-turner under her robes shift as she turned her head, "I'm not taking Potions with you guys this year."

Before Draco could say more than "What?" Professor Flitwick started class. When it became clear that their first lessons was to be a review of the previous year, Pansy began taking rapid notes, even though she'd barely missed a week of actual classes last term, and Draco tuned out entirely in favor of demanding to see Rigel's schedule.

She passed over the modified schedule Snape had given her and watched Draco frown as he read it over.

"You're not in any Potions class."

"Professor Snape thinks I would benefit more from self-study at this point," Rigel said, a small amount of pride leaking into her voice, "So I can move at my own pace, I suspect."

"Will it be like that from now on?" Draco asked, still frowning, "Can you take the OWL in a couple years if you aren't in the fifth-year class?"

"Yes," Pansy murmured distractedly, eyes still on the board as her quill flew across the parchment, "Marcus took the Care of Magical Creatures OWL without attending a single class."

"Oh," Draco scanned the parchment again, "Why are you taking Magical Theory? It's a dry class. No practical work, ever. Only squibs take Magical Theory."

"Anthony Goldstein is taking Magical Theory," Pansy said, still bent over her notes.

"Squibs and Ravenclaws, then," Draco drawled.

"And me," Rigel said sweetly, "I think it sounds interesting."

"Why didn't you get into Dueling?" Draco asked, "I thought you said you were applying for it last term. No way you didn't get in."

"I got in," she admitted, "But I had to choose three, and I decided I could practice dueling on my own."

"I'll practice with you," Draco said decisively, "It's an important skill to have, so I'll teach you and Pansy what I learn in the mornings after we run."

Rigel grinned in genuine thanks. Now she could get the benefits of Remus' continued instruction without actually having to spend a lot of time with him.

Her schedule was passed around to the other third-year Slytherins during class, and it seemed she would share some of her electives with her other friends.

She had Ancient Runes with Blaise, Theo, and Draco. Only Pansy would be in her Arithmancy class. Millicent shared International Studies with Draco, and was also taking Muggle Studies with Theo. Theo alone was in the Magical Languages elective, but Millicent shared Dueling with Draco. Tracy and Daphne were apparently in Divination and Care of Magical Creatures with Pansy, much to their blonde friend's unspoken annoyance.

After Charms, the third years had Transfiguration with the Ravenclaws. Rigel also had her first lesson with Professor Snape at this time, and she was nervous sitting in Transfiguration, knowing that her future self was on the way to the dungeons, presumably under the invisibility cloak. Draco must have caught on to her nervousness, because he peered at her suspiciously, then said, "What's wrong?"

Rigel shrugged, trying not to let her discomfort show, "Nothing."

Draco rubbed his forehead irritably, "You—you look guilty, Rigel. What's going on?"

Rigel flushed. She thought she'd been perfectly casual. She cast around for something to say, then settled on "I'm not trying out for the Quidditch team this year."

This, it seemed, was more than sufficient distraction.

"What? Why not?" Draco looked a bit betrayed, which only increased the guilt she felt. "Stop feeling sorry," Draco snapped, "Just tell me why."

"I think I should focus on my studies," Rigel said softly, apologetically, "With the extra classes and all, I just don't think I'll have the time."

"I have extra classes, too," Draco argued quietly as McGonagall took roll, "Just work a little harder."

"Rigel already works very hard," Pansy pointed out diplomatically, "He studies other things, in addition to classes, and he'll be self-studying Potions this semester, too, which is bound to be time-consuming."

Draco looked frustrated, but he nodded shortly and turned back to the board, rubbing his temples once more.

After Transfiguration, Rigel told her friends she had to run to the bathroom, feeling a guilty thrill as they went on without her.

She ducked into the nearest boy's bathroom and glanced around. There was no one present, so she quickly pulled her invisibility cloak from the expanded compartment in her bag and swung it on. She very carefully did not wonder if the future her was also in the bathroom, under the same cloak, waiting to take her place in real time while she turned back two hours to ten o'clock for her first lesson with Snape.

She didn't take off the cloak until she was outside of Lab One, which had been written on her schedule in lieu of a classroom number, at precisely ten o'clock.

"Right on time, Mr. Black," Snape said as the door opened and she slipped inside. She couldn't tell if he was joking, but she opted not to laugh. The time-turner was just too terrifying in its potential to be amusing.

"What are we brewing?" Rigel asked, peering into the single cauldron set out on the workspace, inwardly delighted that she wouldn't be sitting through a one-on-one lecture. There wasn't a base in the cauldron yet, but the inside had been recently treated with an oil of some kind.

"You are brewing Pensive Potion," Snape informed her, sliding a recipe (on non-flammable parchment, of course) toward her.

Rigel could hardly believe she'd heard correctly, but the recipe in front of her was one she vaguely recognized, having researched it for one of Flint's essays at some point. "It's beyond NEWT level," she said, smiling with burgeoning excitement as she read the obscenely complicated instructions, "I've heard there are some countries that require their potioneers to obtain a special license to brew this."

"There are countries that require a license for Pepper-up," Snape said derisively, "It's just as excuse to collect licensing fees. Nevertheless, the potion is indeed complex, and as such you will not attempt to brew it on your own until I deem you capable of it." Snape said firmly, "You will brew many extremely difficult potions this year. The purposes of these lessons is not to give you a grounding in the theoretical—your background in that is more than sufficient for now, and your homework assignments will help fill in the gaps. In our lessons, you will gain hands-on experience with challenging brews, becoming familiar with their rhythms and sensitive to their subtleties."

Snape eyed her sternly as he outlined the course objectives, "We will brew each potion at least twice. The first time through I will give instructions, help you keep pace with the recipe, and assist if necessary. The second time you will do it on your own. When you make errors—and you will—you will write a substantial explanation of what went wrong and how you will avoid the problem in the future. Then we will brew it again, until you get it right."

Rigel grinned widely up at the Professor, who frowned repressively at her display of enthusiasm. "When do we begin?"

"After you study the recipe," he said, a wry smirk twisting his mouth, "This is not free-brewing, Mr. Black. You will put nothing into that cauldron until you know why it is going in there and what it will do to the concoction."

"Yes, sir," Rigel tucked her smile into her cheek and bent over the Pensive Potion recipe with due attention. This year was going to be wonderful.

She snuck into the bathroom just a minute or two after her past self should have disappeared and took the cloak off, stowing it quickly. She ducked into a stall to use the facilities, just so it wouldn't be suspicious if she had to use them again too soon, and then headed off to lunch, feeling a bit smug knowing that her first real use of the time-turner had been a complete, unqualified success.

She slid into the seat Draco and Pansy had saved for her and leaned across Draco slightly to snag a roll from the serving plate.

Draco's nose wrinkled and he turned a raised eyebrow on her, "You smell like sewage, Rigel."

Rigel's brain froze for half a moment before re-starting and nudging her mouth into saying, "I think someone set off a dung bomb in the bathroom just before I got there. Is it awful? I can change before Herbology."

"It's fine," Draco said dismissively, "No worse than when you've been in your lab all evening. You'll get dirty during Herbology anyway."

Rigel hadn't realized that brewing potions made her smell so badly. It made sense—some of the ingredients were a bit noxious, objectively speaking. She'd grown used to it, over the years, but her friends, apparently, hadn't. She felt her earlier smugness recede slowly as she made a mental note not to time-turn back to her Potions lessons until after lunch. If she showed up directly to Herbology smelly, people were less likely to notice, since the greenhouses all smelled like soil in any case. It also meant she'd eat lunch at a reasonable time, instead of what felt like two o'clock.

On the bright side, if her friends were accustomed to her being smelly, they might not notice when she put on her Archie-sweat-musk-perfume before Defense lessons the next morning.

Herbology was with the Gryffindors that year, and Rigel sidled over to the red-and-gold cluster of students to say hi to Neville and Ron before Professor Sprout came and unlocked the greenhouses.

To her surprise, Ron, who had an arm around a very shaken-looking Neville, shot her a less-than-welcoming look as she approached.

"Hi," she said, "How was your summer break?"

"Fine," Ron said shortly.

"Oh," Rigel paused, unsure, "That's good."

"Yeah," Ron said, "Look, if you don't mind—"

"Stop, Ron," Neville said quietly, "It's not Rigel's fault."

"What's not Rigel's fault?" Draco had come up on her left side, presumably attracted by the unpleasant look on Ron's face.

Ron clamped his mouth shut, but Neville spoke up with a determined look on his face, "I just had a bad Defense lesson, that's all."

Rigel couldn't stop the slight frown of dismay from forming on her face, "What happened?"

"That uncle of yours is a piece of work," Ron said.

"Remus?" Rigel couldn't imagine what her uncle might have done to upset a class of third-year Gryffindors, but from the uneasy agreement on many faces, it wasn't just Neville who had been affected.

"What happened?" Draco asked with a frown of his own, "Wasn't it just review? You all look…scared."

Ron bristled, "See how you fair tomorrow. Come on, Neville."

He dragged Neville toward the doors, which Sprout was just unlocking from the inside, and the other Gryffindors followed suit.

"Melodramatic," Draco rolled his eyes.

Rigel hoped he was right. Remus' employment at the school caused all sort of problems for her plans, but she still wanted it to go well for her uncle. A lot in the werewolf community was riding on the success of his year, after all. She supposed they'd find out tomorrow morning.

After Herbology, they walked down to the dungeons and headed to their group's usual low-backed couch by one of the fires.

Pansy raised a delicate eyebrow at Rigel when she sat down amongst them. "Are you going to socialize with us, Rigel?"

"Why shouldn't I?" Rigel asked, nonplussed, "Did you want to talk about me or something?"

Pansy laughed, "No, I just assumed you'd have something you needed to be doing."

"It's the first day," Rigel said, "We don't have any homework."

"Not schoolwork," Pansy said patiently, "One of your other projects. I thought you'd want to use the time we have without assignments to make progress on other things."

"I spend time with you guys," Rigel said, a bit defensive, "…don't I?

"Yes, Rigel, but generally while we're doing homework," Pansy said, "Or when we drag you away from something else."

Rigel swallowed. Was she so negligent? Draco and Pansy demanded so little of her in their friendship. Had she been taking advantage even more than she realized?

"You're making him feel guilty," Draco said, sighing.

Pansy looked abruptly regretful, "I'm sorry, Rigel. I didn't mean to imply you were in any way at fault. I was only teasing you about being so dedicated to your pursuits."

Rigel smiled softly at the girl, "I know, Pan. How about from now on I try to make my friends one of the pursuits I'm so dedicated to?"

Pansy had a look of pleased hope in her eyes, but it was tempered by caution, "We don't want to impose on your schedule, Rigel."

"You aren't—you won't be," Rigel said, feeling that this was a promise she—for once—was going to be able to keep. "I'm going to make more time for you guys this year. I promise." With the time-turner, she'd have no trouble making that statement a reality. Her friends deserved better from her, and she was finally in a position where she could show them that.

"But not for Quidditch," Draco huffed.

Rigel started to apologize, but stopped at the understanding smirk on Draco's face.

"I get it, Rye," he said, waving off her guilty expression, "I did sort of push you into participating, last year. I shouldn't be surprised when it's not your top priority."

"Thanks for understanding, Draco," Rigel said.

"Speaking of understanding," Draco said, pulling a face, "I can't make heads or tails of the first chapter in our Ancient Runes textbook."

"We don't have that until Wednesday," Rigel said, "And I don't think the professor will expect you to know anything on the first day."

"Just because other people have low expectations doesn't mean I should comport myself to their standards," Draco plucked an imaginary piece of lint from his robes, "I refuse to step foot into any classroom without having at least some idea as to what's going on."

"You should ask Blaise," Rigel suggested, "He's really good at explaining the basics."

"Blaise has been acting weird lately," Draco complained, "He's all love-sick or something. It's driving me mad."

"Why should you care if he is?" Pansy asked, shaking her head, "He turned thirteen this summer, too. It's probably just that his inheritance hasn't settled yet."

"Inheritance?" Rigel repeated, "You mean the expansion of his magical core?"

Pansy and Draco exchanged looks that went over Rigel's head.

"No, the core growth happens overnight, and it usually only takes a day or two to get used to," Pansy said slowly, "I mean…Blaise's inheritance."

Rigel shook her head in quiet bewilderment, "I'm sorry, Pan, but I don't know what that means. Is it a—" she stopped herself before she could say 'pureblood thing' out loud. "Does a gift run in his family, or something?"

Draco scoffed, "Where in Salazar's name have you been, Rigel? Blaise is part creature. His father was a shifter of some kind, which means Blaise came into his side of the inheritance at the same time that his core developed. Why do you think he has amber eyes all of a sudden?"

"Does he?" Rigel asked, startled. She hadn't noticed that, but as Blaise's eyes had been brown to begin with…well, she didn't exactly go staring into other people's eyes all the time, did she?

"Yes, he does," Pansy laughed, "Rigel, you're hopeless. Suffice to say that everyone knows Blaise is half-creature. If the changes in his behavior are any indication, he's inherited the full set of traits from his father's side this summer. It wasn't really a surprise—he's always had incredible hearing and eyesight, not to mention his…fascination with a certain Hufflepuff who only ever wears her hair in one style. I suppose that's what has you so annoyed, Drake?"

"He positively moons, now," Draco lamented.

"It can't be that bad if Rigel hasn't even noticed," Pansy said, amused.

Draco grumbled half-heartedly, "He moons on the inside. It's annoying how he pretends he's not, but every now and then forgets he's pretending and gets this stupid wistful look on his face…he should just mate with her and have done with."

"Draco!" Pansy sounded shocked, "She's thirteen years old. I don't care how much shifter blood runs in the Abbott family—she's never shown any sign that she's inherited the abilities and even if she was a full-blooded creature it would still be much too early for them to form any sort of life-bond."

"I know, I know," Draco groaned, "It's just so annoying to watch him pine."

Rigel was quickly coming to realize that she really didn't know her friends at all. Blaise was half-shifter? His father must have been from a family of pureblooded shifters, too, or he wouldn't be able to attend Hogwarts. She wondered what animal Blaise could turn into, then remembered that shifters bonded for life, often forming instinctual attachments as young as eight years old to their intended, and subsequently realized that she was an idiot for not putting the very obvious pieces together. Certainly all of his interactions with Hannah Abbott made more sense. Rigel then wondered how much Hannah knew of Blaise's genetic traits, and if the Hufflepuff girl even guessed at what kind of regard Blaise must hold her in, whether he wanted to or not.

It was a bit scary to realize that there were people in the world with lives at least as complicated and awkward to navigate as her own.

They went to dinner when the others in the common room started trickling out in that direction, and as they claimed their seats Draco was quick to point out that Flint was still no where to be seen.

"Face it," he said archly, "You were wrong about him. He's not coming back this year."

"He's already back, actually."

They both looked up at Rosier as he slid into a place across the table, Rookwood a beat behind him and a seat beside him.

"I haven't seen him," Draco said, "Don't tell me he's too busy planning how to make Wood's life hell to come to meals."

Rosier's face didn't have its usual twist of levity to it, and he didn't smile at Draco's jibe. "He's in the hospital wing."

Pansy dropped her fork to the table with a dull clang, "What happened? Is he going to be all right?"

"He had an accident before term started," Rosier said, face studiously giving no expression away, "He couldn't make the train, so our Head of House collected him late last night. One of the twins overheard McGonagall asking the Head Boy to collect Flint's homework assignments this morning at breakfast."

To Rigel's surprise, Rosier gestured not to the Weasley twins as he said it, but to the little second-year Slytherin brothers who as far as Rigel had seen only ever talked to one another.

"Marcus had better make a swift recovery," Pansy said, looking extremely upset, "If he thinks he can get away with just—"

She broke off with a very un-Pansy-like scowl. Somehow, Rigel didn't think it was Flint that Pansy's anger was directed toward. It seemed like forever ago that Percy had intimated a less than ideal home life was partly responsible for the anger Flint often exhibited at the beginning of the school year. Could an unhappy situation have escalated?

Rigel knew it wasn't any of her business, but she couldn't help but worry. Flint may be a blackmailing jerk, but he was her friend, too, in a weird way. Then she realized that as long as Flint was in the Hospital Wing, his assignments were going to start piling up. She hoped he got better soon—for both their sakes. Maybe there was a way she could get the assignments from Percy without seeming suspicious. It would certainly be more manageable for her to work on them as they came, instead of trying to do them all at once.

As Rigel was lost in plans, Pansy was becoming more and more upset on Draco's other side.

"Marcus is the last person who deserves to have to put up with such—such an—ignorant, hateful, disgusting excuse for a—" she cut herself off with a visible effort and stood, sweeping her robes behind her as she turned from the table, "I've lost my appetite. I'm going to visit Marcus in the Hospital Wing."

She strode from the hall, angrier than Rigel had ever imagined her sweet-tempered friend could become.

As Pansy exited, Draco seemed to droop into Rigel's side. Rigel stiffened and leaned against the weight automatically, looking over in time to catch a look of unconcealed relief on Draco's face. When his eyes darted over to hers, he grimaced, "Pansy's anger is a bit…overwhelming, isn't it? I haven't seen her like that since we were very young. I think she yelled at me once for eating the last cinnamon cookie when her mother brought her to tea. I'd forgotten she had it in her, honestly."

Rigel silently accepted this explanation for his unusually acute relief at Pansy's exit, but added another tally to the 'strange things Draco does now' chalkboard in her head.

They ate in relatively subdued silence, even the usually resilient Rosier seeming content to let the meal pass without an effort at conversation. Neither she nor Draco brought up the bet again, and Rigel felt a little sick to think that she'd been making a joke out of someone else's problems.

After dinner she and Draco started toward the Hospital Wing, but halfway there Draco stopped and muttered a half-hearted curse. "We should have gotten her something to eat," he sighed.

"The kitchens are still open," Rigel shrugged, "They're bound to have leftovers."

They made a detour to the basement and pushed open the portrait entrance slowly, mindful of the house elves scurrying every which way.

A young female elf with her familiar necklace of champagne corks ran over and flung herself at Rigel with all the exuberance of a long-lost friend. Rigel caught the little elf on reflex and spun her in a circle with the momentum from her launch. She set Binny down, laughing, and said, "I missed you too, Binny. How was your summer? Did you spend it at Madame Touraine's again?"

"Oh, yes, Binny's summer is being very nice," the house elf beamed up at her, "There is being five new foals in Madame Touraine's herd this summer, and I is playing with all of them when I is being done working."

"That sounds wonderful," Rigel said, smiling, "Did you meet any attractive elves in the stables?" She wagged her eyebrows at the elf, who had confided to her last year that she was quickly reaching an age at which most elves were expected to marry."

Binny gave her a scandalized look, before dissolving into giggles, "I is not telling. And you is being very rude for asking," she added in French with a little grin.

"Is it rude to ask a friend a simple question?" Rigel grinned back, her French undeniably rusty, but comprehensible all the same.

"You speak French?"

Rigel winced inwardly and looked a bit guiltily at Draco, who she'd momentarily forgotten. He had both eyebrows raised and was looking between Binny and Rigel with amused disbelief.

She shrugged casually, deciding she could use this situation as long as she did so carefully. "Binny helps me stay in practice," she said lightly, "I'm really not that good."

"You is being very good," Binny contradicted with a waggling finger, "Saying otherwise is being insulting to your teacher."

"If you say so, Binny," Rigel said, affecting an embarrassed smile. She could see Draco glancing suspiciously at her out of the corner of his eye, which was perfect for her purposes. He wouldn't know how good at French she was, nor why she was staying in practice, but if she ever had to use the back-up cover story of being a poor pureblood from the continent he could easily interpret her speaking French with a house elf as a clue to her true identity.

"What is you needing?" Binny asked after a beat of awkward silence.

"Our friend Pansy missed dinner tonight," Draco explained, "Could we get a basket of food to take to her?"

Instantly several nearby house elves were diverted from other tasks to gather a parcel of leftovers. In no time at all they were bidding Binny and the others good night.

They strolled into the Hospital Wing to see Madam Pomfrey leaning over a bed on the far end of the room, Pansy seated quietly to one side. The mediwitch tutted a bit as she took Flint's vitals, then sighed as she jotted the results onto a clipboard and walked back to her office after a stern warning look to Draco and Rigel. She didn't have to say anything—everyone knew the only rule in the Hospital Wing was do not disturb the patients.

Draco dropped the basket of food in Pansy's lap and Rigel pulled a couple of chairs away from nearby beds for them.

Pansy picked at the food pensively, chewing and swallowing mechanically whenever her hand made its way to her mouth. Eventually she stopped pretending to eat and just stared at Marcus' sleeping face.

The Quidditch captain didn't look any worse for wear, but after a day in Madam Pomfrey's care, that didn't say much about his original injuries—she could heal surface damage in a matter of minutes. That he was still unconscious spoke volumes about the extent of his internal trauma.

"I'm sure I seem more than a little dramatic to you two," Pansy said quietly after a while, "Rigel, you've known Marcus longer than I have, and Draco, you've spent the most time with him on the Quidditch team, but…Marcus is a very dear friend to me all the same. First year, I didn't have the same network of friends that I do now."

Rigel and Draco started to protest, but Pansy held up a hand solemnly, "No, it's true. Rigel, you were always disappearing to study or brew and Draco had Quidditch practice all the time, and the other girls resented me immediately for making friends with the Malfoy and Black Heirs right off the bat—Davis and Greengrass barely deigned to talk to me, and Millicent seemed so unapproachable back then. I had upperclassmen friends, but they had their own group, and were busy with schoolwork besides. So I took to coming with Draco to Quidditch practices just to give myself something to think about besides my own insecurities."

Draco and Rigel exchanged a look. Neither could picture confident, poised Pansy as insecure.

She laughed softly at their expressions, "You don't believe me? Of course I was insecure. I worried a lot in the beginning that you two were only humoring me—that eventually you'd get tired of being friends with a girl and I'd be left with no friends at all. Who'd want to be seen with the girl the Black and Malfoy Heirs had snubbed? I went to watch your practices, Draco, because I didn't want to sit all alone in the common room waiting for you to get back."

"You never did care much for Quidditch," Draco said ruefully, "I'm sorry, Pans, I didn't realize you thought our friendship was one-sided."

"It wasn't your fault," Pansy said with a self-deprecating smile, "I certainly never advertised my uncertainty. The point of this is that I got to know Marcus at those practices. He almost always spent a good portion of practice in the stands, watching the maneuvers he'd designed from afar as you all ran through them, so one day I started sitting beside him. Sometimes I would talk to him, just prattling, really, about what I'd done that day or what classes were like. Eventually I started telling him all kinds of things. It was cathartic, I guess, just saying it all out loud like that, and I didn't think he was even listening, except then one day he talked back."

Rigel looked from Pansy to Flint and tried to imagine what her friend was telling her. She'd seen Pansy sitting by Flint in the stands plenty of times during practice last year, but she'd never have imagined they were having some sort of…heart to heart.

"Did you know Marcus' mother is a squib?" Pansy asked suddenly. She swallowed, then continued in a shaking voice, "That's why no one ever sees her out in society. She's from a good family, and they covered up her lack of magical gifts by claiming to be homeschooling her. They betrothed her to Marcus' father, and both sides considered it a good match. After they married, however, she couldn't keep up the pretense in such close quarters. Marcus' father was furious when he found out, and he's hated his wife ever since. The poor woman."

Draco nodded with an expression of rueful distaste, and Rigel realized that many people must be aware of Flint's familial problems. Why did everyone turn a blind eye? To save themselves the embarrassment of acknowledging the situation? Perhaps they were ashamed that their elitist pureblood culture produced exactly this kind of duplicity and hatred when mixed with the wrong sort of tragic circumstances.

"It caused a scandal when the Flint Family's main branch found out, of course. Marcus' father was disgraced, and his mother became a social pariah," Pansy went on, her voice thick with dissatisfaction, "Marcus was born into a home of rage and betrayal. To his parents' credit, they did attempt to keep Marcus out of their marital difficulties. Each tried to cultivate a relationship with Marcus apart from the other, but as Marcus grew older he found it more and more difficult to turn the other way when his parents fought. He started to intervene, to try and stop the violence when it escalated to spells, which of course left his mother distinctly vulnerable. He could never get them to stop, though. He spends all summer in that house, all of them shouting and bickering at one another, and more and more he finds himself standing between his mother and his father's wand. I just know that's how this happened," Pansy was openly crying now, not seeming to even notice what she was saying, "He must have gotten mixed up in another one of their fights, only this time his father didn't back down."

She wiped her tears angrily on a handkerchief she pulled from her pocket and glared at Flint's unconscious form, "If I ever get my hands on his parents I'm going to give them a piece of my mind. And then I'm going to give them a taste of their own medicine. To raise a child in that kind of environment—and one as intelligent and driven as Marcus—it's just criminal."

Pansy tucked her handkerchief away, and the fight seemed to drain out of her all of a sudden, "I told him not to go back this summer," she whispered, "He's seventeen, he didn't have to…"

"It's not easy to walk away from your family," Draco said, a troubled look on his face. He was rubbing his forehead again, Rigel noticed. When had he picked up that habit? And how had Narcissa Malfoy let him get away with it? "Even when you know they're poison."

Rigel nodded, thinking of Lestrange, who bitterly resented his parent's lack of attention yet clung to his mother's apron strings all the same. Even Rosier, who was openly dismissive of his parents' social agenda, played the model Heir for them in public.

"And for the record, Pans," Draco added a moment later, "Rigel and I will never get tired of being friends with you. Even if you are a girl."

He wrinkled his nose in such a comically uncouth way that Pansy couldn't hold back a watery laugh.

Draco winked at Rigel and Rigel smiled back gratefully. She hated to see Pansy upset. It was like seeing Archie upset—there was just something fundamentally wrong with it, like a wrinkle in the fabric of reality.

They walked back to the common room a short time later, each lost in their own thoughts. She wanted to spend time with Pansy and Draco that night, both of whom were obviously disturbed in one way or another by seeing Flint in the Hospital Wing, but she also needed to brew the potion that would adjust her sleep cycle to be proportionate to the number of hours she spent waking in a row.

She was already getting a little tired, since for her it felt like it was 10:30, not 7:30. She could take a Pepper-up Potion for an extra hour or two of energy to get the brewing done though.

Rigel debated what to do, and in the end decided that it would be easiest to ensure a seamless turn if she ducked into a bathroom now and went back a few hours, then snuck into the bathroom when time caught up and walked back out a few minutes after her friends saw her go in. Otherwise she'd be sneaking out of the common room before bed, which would be much more difficult.

It was a perfect plan, until Draco shrugged and said he'd go with her to the bathroom as long as they were waiting on her.

Rigel hid a frown as they both entered the boy's bathroom and she ducked into a stall, going about emptying her not-very-full bladder with only a modicum of self-consciousness. She was mostly over this kind of embarrassment, as it wasn't anything new, sharing a dorm as they did; she was more concerned with how she was going to make this work.

In the end, she decided staying put was her best bet, as awkward as that was. Draco was washing his hands now, and Rigel just sat there in the stall and twiddled her thumbs.

After waiting a few minutes, Draco said, "Rigel?" with a small amount of confusion.

"You go ahead," Rigel said, affecting embarrassment, "I'll just be a minute or two."

"Oh," She could practically hear her friend awkwardly grimacing, "I'll just—yeah."

The door opened and closed, and Rigel breathed a sigh of relief. She checked the time and dutifully noted it down in her notebook, which she had taken to keeping shrunk in her breast pocket, then pulled out her time-turner.

She realized just in time that turning while in a bathroom stall might not be a good idea in case someone else had been using it three hours previously. She pulled on her cloak instead and stepped out into the bathroom proper, into a corner, and twisted the hourglass three full turns. When she opened her eyes, she almost jumped when she saw a boy fiddling with his hair in the mirror.

Instead, she froze, not daring to breathe until the older boy gave his reflection a satisfied grin and sauntered out of the bathroom.

She pulled out the map and checked it. The other Harriet Potter was in the common room with her friends, and would be until she went to dinner. There were plenty of students wandering about, though, so she kept the cloak on and made her way stealthily through the school, down through the dungeon corridors, until she reached her lab. She unlocked it with the key Snape had given her after it had been broken into last year, and pulled off the cloak as she shut the door behind her.

It smelled a little dusty, and one of the torches needed replacing soon, but Rigel smiled as she looked around the small lab. It was hers. She was home again.

The sleep-adjustment potion turned out to be tricky, but not terribly time-consuming. She finished it in an hour, so with two additional hours to spare, she pulled out the list of potions she was always free to brew for Krait and tried to remember which ones she hadn't supplied in the last month.

Deciding that Krait could never have too many muscle-relaxants, she began a batch, leisurely slicing and dicing the ingredients at a slow pace. She hadn't taken the time to really enjoy brewing in too long, she thought with regret. She hadn't forgotten the beauty of the art, of course—how could she, when there were nights she dreamt of brewing potions so delicate their contents were like spun spider silk as they poured out? And yet, it was true that she had perhaps been less appreciative of her passion than usual these last busy months.

Still, she thought with a smile, she wouldn't have to worry about that any more. She finally had all the time in the word.

When seven thirty crept closer, she packed up her lab into her portable potions kit and put on her cloak once more. It was extremely surreal to watch herself and Draco enter the bathroom and go about their business, and then to watch herself disappear under the cloak in the opposite corner from where she stood under the same exact cloak.

She stowed the cloak and left the bathroom, falling into step beside Draco as they headed for the common room.

Her friend gave her an odd look as they walked, and she didn't know if he was wondering what had taken her so long, wondering why she smelled like a cauldron, or wondering if the former had to do with the latter. Whatever he was thinking, it would be best if she pretended not to notice, she decided.

By the time they reached the common room, her eyes were drooping. She couldn't take the potion until she woke up the following morning, as it was supposed to be begun at the beginning of a sleep cycle, but if this was how she would feel every day without it she could only thank Snape for thinking of it. She had been awake for nearly 21 hours, and she could feel it psychologically as well as physically. She was more than ready for her bed.

She held out for forty-five minutes, but eventually she couldn't keep her eyes open, no matter how much she wanted to stay up with her friends a little longer.

"I'm for bed," she said, rising from the couch between Pansy and Draco with a graceless yawn.

"Now?" Draco raised an eyebrow, "It's not even nine-o-clock."

"I know," Rigel said apologetically, "I'm knackered, though. I'd be poor company anyway at this point."

"Goodnight, Rigel," Pansy said, looking amused, "Sleep well, and don't worry about waking up tomorrow—Draco and I will can always go running without you."

"Do you know the way?" Rigel asked, a dubious frown on her face, "I was under the impression that Draco, at least, sleepwalked behind me unconscious most of the first lap."

"Well I'm not the one who looks like he's sleepwalking right now," Draco retorted, "Go to bed, Rigel, you're clearly dead on your feet—didn't you sleep last night?"

"Not very well," Rigel lied, "Night, guys."

Pansy cleared her throat pointedly.

"Good night, ladies," she amended with a grin.

Draco grumbled, but waved her off without further protest.

Rigel veritably collapsed into bed, and knew nothing more until early the next morning when her alarm spell poked her in the cheek.

She felt reasonably well rested, and quickly downed the sleep-adjusting potion before Draco woke up to join her for their morning run. She was both looking forward to and dreading the rest of the morning, since she would have her first Defense, Alchemy, and Magical Theory classes—all at once.

Then there was Arithmancy that afternoon. It would be nice to finally get an introduction to that course, as for the past two years she'd been copying the examples in the book to solve the problems in Flint's assignments, all without really understanding why the numbers could be manipulated that way or what the answers even meant in real terms.

With Remus' werewolf nose in mind, she showered thoroughly after their workout with strong-smelling soap, then layered on Archie's sweat-distilled perfume under her clothes as she dressed. Between that and the voice-altering spell that she'd been keeping up since she stepped on the train, any discrepancies in her appearance would likely go unnoticed. Remus would be nervous for his first week, anyway, she reassured herself. By the time he settled into Hogwarts and noticed her, he'd be used to the way she looked now.

Rigel got some reading done while Draco showered, and she pretended not to notice him slip a suppressant potion into his pocket while collecting a pair of socks from his trunk.

Breakfast passed too quickly, and soon Rigel was lined up with the other students outside the Defense classroom, trying not to sweat from nervousness and ruin the odor she'd been cultivating. When the clock struck eight, the door to the classroom creaked open, and the first few students stepped nervously inside.

It was dark in the big, empty room. There were no tables or chairs, not even a teacher's desk. The shutters were closed, but only a few of the lamps had been lit, so they made their way slowly into the room. To one side stood a large screen, the kind a person might have dressed behind a century ago, except it had been enlarged so that it reached almost to the ceiling.

Out from behind this screen, Remus stepped slowly toward them. His gait was stiff, and a bit menacing as he loomed toward them. The students watched his approach with nervous anticipation, on edge at the strange scene. When Remus moved lightning-fast toward the nearest boy, drawing his wand as he did so, several people screamed. The boy, Gregory Goyle, stumbled backwards, tripped over his pantleg and fell to the ground with a terrified expression on his face.

"You are dead," Remus commented mildly, straightening from the dueler's lunge he had sunk into and lowering his wand.

Goyle blinked, and slowly climbed to his feet once more, "You surprised me."

"Ah, yes," Remus smiled, "Surprise can be a nasty thing—but you shouldn't expect a vampire to warn you before he attacks."

"That wasn't fair, though, Professor," Tracy Davis spoke up in their year mate's defense, "We weren't expecting an attack from a teacher—we shouldn't have to be on guard at school."

"You don't think so?" Remus looked up at the ceiling as though thinking her statement over, "I heard there was a basilisk roaming the halls just a few months ago—were you on guard then?"

"Once we knew about it," Davis flushed slightly, but kept her head up defiantly.

Remus nodded gravely, "It is good to be wary of a known threat, but being wary of an unknown threat is never bad, either. Today I was the unknown threat. Tomorrow—well, you just never know, do you?"

Rigel thought he was laying on the ominousness a bit thick, but looking around at the foreboded expressions on everyone's faces, she supposed it must be working. She had a hard time taking him seriously, but only because she knew him so well, apparently.

Remus lifted his wand toward the ceiling and the rest of the lamps blared to life, brightening the room considerably. "Atmosphere is an interesting thing," Remus said, his tone as light as if he were discussing tea cakes, "The right setting can set a person at ease—or fill him with anxiety. The mind responds to certain elements instinctively—darkness, silence, surprise, uncertainty. All these things elicit fear from a person, and it is that instinctive, uncontrolled fear that will be your greatest enemy, no matter what you do in life. This class is called Defense Against the Dark Arts, but the defender who is controlled by fear is as much a danger as the thing he or she is defending against. Before I teach you how to combat the Dark Arts, then, I am going to teach you how to overcome fear. Only when you can act in the face of terror, in the midst of surprise and uncertainty, only then can you defend yourself against anything, much less the darkest of our magical arts."

There was complete silence as Remus paused to survey them all with his quietly powerful gaze. After a moment, Remus pointed at Blaise and said, "Do you know what you are most afraid of, Mr…?"

"Zabini," Blaise said, frowning, "No, professor, I…don't know for sure."

"That's all right, almost no one does," Remus said, smiling slightly, "Most people try not to think about things that scare them, and fear is often unquantifiable, so that it is hard to say objectively if you fear drowning more than being stabbed in a dark alley."

A couple of people flinched at the blunt wording, and Rigel could feel the blood drain from her face unwittingly, a flash of a man in a blue vest skittering across her memory.

"All fear is similar, however, in the way it affects the body—and in the way a person copes with it," Remus continued. "Does anyone know what a boggart is?" Pansy gasped quietly, causing Remus to glance in her direction, "Yes? You know, Miss…"

"Parkinson," Pansy said, her face grim with the knowledge of something, "A boggart is a dark creature, Professor. It is said to take the shape of whatever the person it comes across is very afraid of. It uses a kind of fear-based Legilimency magic that even Occlumency can't block out entirely to become something terrible enough to frighten its prey into a terrified stupor, so it can consume them."

"Correct, Miss Parkinson," Remus said, "Five points to Slytherin. A boggart will confront you with the thing you fear most in the entire world—usually it is a fear that you have not acknowledged even to yourself, because that's the kind of fear that will most effectively immobilize or destabilize its victims. Behind that screen," he gestured behind him, "Is a boggart I found in the staff room cloak cupboard. Today you will each face it, one at a time, and learn your greatest fear, whatever it may be."

Rigel was not the only one who looked disbelievingly at Remus as he said that. They were to face a boggart? Without any preparation or training, just to see what they were most afraid of? That sounded frankly awful. If this is what the third-year Gryffindors had to do, it was no wonder they seemed a bit leery of Remus as a professor.

Still, he was her uncle, and if he thought it was a good idea, he surely had a reason. With that in mind, Rigel raised her hand, even though she had promised she wouldn't cause attention to herself in this class.

"Yes, Mr. Black?" Remus asked politely, not a hint that he was talking to a child whose diapers he'd changed showing on his face.

"What does one do when faced with a boggart?" she asked, trying to imitate Archie's casually up-beat tone, "Once we know what our fear is, I mean. Do we just try very hard not to be afraid of that thing?"

"Interesting question," Remus said, "Apart from it being very difficult to stop being afraid of something in the first place, if you overcome your fear of one thing, the boggart can always find something else you are afraid of, and change into it instead. There is a spell that I will teach you called Riddikulus, which uses the imagination of the castor to force the boggart to take the shape of something that is utterly non-frightening. This works because the moment the boggart senses you are not afraid of it, it will retreat instinctively. We will learn that spell the next time we face the boggart, however—today the objective is not to defeat the boggart, but rather to learn a bit about ourselves."

He pinned them all with a very serious look, "I know it is unpleasant to think about facing your worst fear, but that is the point. It is important to know how your mind and body respond to fear—how it feels to be very, very afraid. Usually when we are scared, we are too surprised or distracted to analyze the feeling, so today is all about paying attention to how fear feels. Focus entirely on your own reaction to the boggart; do your hands shake? Does your skin feel clammy and cold? Do you feel like screaming, crying, or freezing in place? This is important information to have for when you are faced with a real crisis. I will worry about defending against the boggart, and I assure you that no harm will come to any of you while I am here. I know this is not how you imagined your first lesson going, but I promise you will be better off knowing fear now than being surprised by it in a life-or-death situation later."

Rigel thought Remus might be a genius. How often had she gotten into trouble and felt paralyzed by fear in a critical moment. Maybe if she'd been taught to cope with fear instead of succumbing to it, events like that night in the lower alleys might have turned out differently.

"I must ask for your patience as well, today," Remus said, smiling a bit sheepishly in the first relaxed expression he had given them thus far, "You will face the boggart one at a time, behind this sound-proof screen, which means most of the lesson will be spent waiting for your classmates to take their turns. I trust that as busy third-years you can all find something quiet to occupy your time with while you are not with me behind the screen, yes?"

There were scattered nods, but most of the class seemed to be trying to accept the idea that their teacher was going to scare them out of their wits on purpose in order to teach them a lesson.

"Any volunteers?"

Rigel hesitated. She wanted to show that she supported Remus in his first class, but she couldn't figure out what she was most afraid of. It might be something incriminating—what if she was most afraid of failing her potions mastery? Or being found out as a girl? That would be an odd fear for Archie to have.

Before she could decide if it would be better to blend into the middle of the group or not, Theo said determinedly, "I'll go first."

They all turned surprised and impressed eyes on the sandy-haired boy.

Theo shrugged at their questioning looks, "I want to know what I'm afraid of."

"But do you want him to know what you're afraid of?" Davis muttered, looking shrewdly in Remus' direction. The implication that as an ex-Gryffindor halfblood Remus was the enemy didn't go unnoticed.

"There are of course confidentiality wards in place behind the screen," Remus said to no one in particular. Rigel wondered how many of her classmates had suddenly remembered Remus's heightened hearing abilities.

Rigel wondered if those wards would apply to her, too. It reassured her that at least if the boggart revealed a very Harry-Potter-like fear, Remus would be unable to pass on his suspicions to anyone else.

"Bring it on," Theo said confidently. He strode over to the screen, Remus on his heels.

They disappeared behind the barrier and for several long minutes nothing more was heard. Just as people had begun to exchange relatively concerned looks, Theo came stumbling back around the divider, pale and sweating. He walked right past them all and to the other end of the room, where Rigel noticed a sideboard set up with big glasses of water and juice and plates of various sweets. Chocolate seemed to be a prominent theme. Rigel smiled nostalgically. Remus had always had a huge sweet tooth, especially when it came to chocolate.

After he gasped down half a glass of pumpkin juice, Theo said, "The next person can go in whenever. It's…it's not so bad."

No one seemed terribly convinced by that statement, belied as it was by Theo's shaky hands and damp brow.

"I'll go," Rigel said after a moment, "If no one else wants to."

"I'll go after you," Draco said immediately, chin up.

"Then me," Pansy added, smiling gratefully at Rigel and Draco, "Might as well get it done with, right?"

Others began to add their name to the growing list, even going so far as to arrange themselves in order, but Rigel was already walking toward the screened-off area.

She rounded the corner to see Remus leaning casually against a closed wardrobe. He straightened as she appeared and sent her a warm smile.

"I thought perhaps no one else wanted to have a go," Remus said. His tone was light, but she could tell he'd been a bit genuinely worried for a moment.

"We were just arguing over the order," Rigel said, grinning playfully, "I got first because Draco lost sprite-dragon-thestral to me."

Remus smiled back, but she could see in his eyes he knew the others had been too wary to readily volunteer. "Well, I'm going to open this door and whatever comes out is your boggart. No matter what it is, I won't let it harm you."

"I read once that boggarts can mimic the powers of the species they imitate," Rigel said, trying to get the right note of nonchalant consideration that Archie was so good at.

"That's true," Remus said, tilting his head curiously.

"If a basilisk comes out, could it petrify me?" Rigel asked. She didn't think she was most afraid of basilisks, but it was certainly a possibility.

Remus paused, "I don't believe so, no. You may feel as though you've been petrified, but it will be merely an illusion, a suggestion in your own mind. That is how boggarts mimic the effects of other creatures—they don't acquire those powers, but they can make their victim feel as though they have. It goes back to the fear-based Legilimency they are so adept at."

"So if it turns into a mandrake I would feel like its cry was killing me, but it wouldn't actually be fatal," Rigel clarified.

Remus' mouth quirked up a bit at the edges, "No to trivialize your fears, Archie, but…a mandrake? Really?"

"Just an educational example," Rigel shrugged with a boyish grin, "The sort of thing you might see on an OWL question, you know."

Remus full-out smiled, "Indeed. Well, to answer your question—exactly. There have been cases where an elderly or weak-bodied person has been so convinced of their own death that they in fact induced a heart-attack or stroke, but barring any medical anomalies you should be fine, Ar—Mr. Black."

"Okay, Professor," Rigel said gamely, "I'm ready."

She didn't feel quite as blasé as she pretended, but she wasn't entirely freaked out, either. She honestly couldn't think of anything she was absolutely, mind-numbingly terrified of. The basilisk had been scary, and so had Lee Jordan's mechanical spider back in first year, and certainly the night the Dancing Dragon went up in flames had been frightening, but she honestly thought she could handle being faced with any of those things again. She had gotten through them once, after all. A cheap imitation wouldn't be more terrifying, surely.

The door to the wardrobe sprung open, and a dark mist came pouring out. She had enough time to wonder whether the mist was some sort of initial defense mechanism to hide the boggart until it got a lock on its victim before she was face to face with…herself?

No, not exactly. It was herself as she might have been—hair long and just barely curling at the ends, eyes wide, brilliant green, spectacles resting on a pert nose dusted with freckles. This was the real Harry Potter, the girl she would never really be again.

The other Harry looked straight at her, and tilted her head in a quizzical way. "Who are you?" It asked. Rigel frowned, not sure what was going on. She snuck a quick look at Remus, but he looked equal parts puzzled and curious, while also trying—and failing—to seem respectfully disinterested.

The shape in front of her changed with an abrupt crack, and it was her mother staring down at her, Addy ducking into her skirts. "Who are you?" her mother asked in a politely puzzled tone.

Rigel's heart started to clench, and then the boggart was James, frowning suspiciously at her like he had the night she came home after curfew, "Who are you?" he asked pointedly.

Crack. It was Sirius, shaking his head bemusedly, "Sorry but, do I know you?"

Crack. It was Remus himself, a curl to his lip that she had never seen in real life, "Just who are you supposed to be?"

Crack. Draco and Pansy looked her slowly up and down, then turned their backs as one and walked away, "Who was that?" "No idea."

Crack. Professor Snape looked down his nose at her, "What are you doing here?"

"I belong here," Rigel didn't realize she'd said the words out loud until the boggart-Snape replied.

"You? Who are you?"

Crack. Riddle Sr. stepped toward her and Rigel couldn't help but take a stumbling step backwards. She could feel her breath hitch, and she tried to calm down, but there was a pit of dread, like ice, in her gut that was slowly spreading, turning her numb.

"Who are you?" Riddle asked, his voice as silky as it was mocking, "Well? Don't you know?"

"It's me, Rigel," she felt the words dragged from her, and wondered if it wasn't the boggart drawing the most pathetic possible responses from her mind.

"Who?" Riddle shook his head, "Never mind. It doesn't really matter. You don't matter. You never did. All of this was just an illusion. All your selfishness, all your ambition, and for what? No one knows you. No one cares. Even you don't care…"

Crack. The boggart was her again, the real Harry, and she stared at Rigel with the most profound disappointment, a bitter twist to her lips and lines of disgust around her eyes. "It's your fault, you know. How many lives are you going to ruin, how many people are you going to alienate, just to chase a futile dream? You'll never be anything, and the more you fight, the more people you hurt in the process of figuring that out."

"That's not true," Rigel said shakily, her fists clenching.

"You know it is," the other Harry started to smile, and the smile got wider and wider as an aura began to grow around her. It was her magic, swirling in violent patterns around her, whipping her long hair around her face in a wild tangle. "There was only one thing special about you—and you threw it away." The magic grew up around the other Harry and then surged forward in a tidal wave of power, sending Rigel to her knees at the force of it. "Do you feel special now? Do you feel anything now? Who are you? WHO ARE—" the voice was cut off without warning as Remus stepped between Rigel and the boggart.

Crack. It was the full moon, hanging peacefully among the black mist. Even as she struggled to pull her mind back from the dark place she had been, she felt a pang of sympathy for Remus—even after all these years, there was nothing he feared more than transformations?

The moon seemed to pop like a balloon, and the boggart's mist retreated into the wardrobe once more without a fuss.

It seemed terribly anticlimactic to Rigel, who was still numb and very, very disturbed. That was her greatest fear? That her ambition would take her to a place where no one, even close friends and family, recognized her anymore? Where she didn't recognize herself? That would be horrible, she realized. The more she considered the possibility, the more panicked she became. Was that her fate? Was she already headed down a road that alienated her from everyone that meant anything to her? Would she live her life alone and unrecognized, even after everything she and Archie had been through?

"Can boggarts tell the future?" she blurted out, unthinking.

Remus' warm hand landed on her shoulder, bracing her against the numbness and the fear that seemed to echo in all the empty places inside of her, even as it faded away. "Not in the slightest," Remus said softly, "They prey on the fears that sit most deeply rooted in a person's mind, but these fears are rarely a reflection of reality. In fact, often what people fear is precisely the thing they try their hardest to avoid. It is because you fear losing the esteem of those closest to you, Archie, that I know you never will. Don't take it to heart. Just remember what that feeling of fear did to you psychologically. Spend the rest of the lesson considering your response objectively—don't feel ashamed of it, and don't worry about overcoming it yet. I'll help you with that. All that matters is that you recognize the existence of that fear; that is the first step toward fighting it."

Rigel nodded slowly, just focusing on not letting the depth of her psychological upset show on her face. There was no need to alarm her classmates, not matter how disturbed she had been by the boggart's ability to breathe life into a fear she hadn't even identified herself. At least Remus had misinterpreted it.

"And eat some chocolate," Remus added, a kind smile on his face.

Rigel felt alive enough to roll her eyes, at least, "Chocolate doesn't cure everything, Professor."

"You'd be surprised," Remus said, mild as ever.

Rigel went back to the main room, giving Draco a reassuring smile that she didn't feel at all as he stepped forward to take her place. Like Theo, she bypassed her classmates in favor of taking a long drink of water and chewing on a chocolate frog. She needed a moment to herself to process what the boggart had revealed.

When she wandered back to the group, Millicent asked, nervously, "Was it bad? You look a little shaken, Rigel."

"I'm fine," Rigel said, a small smile fighting its way onto her lips, "I was just lost in thought."

"Let him be, Millie," Theo said quietly, "I told you, Professor Lupin told us to analyze our reactions to fear while it was still fresh in our minds."

Their friends accepted that, especially as Draco, then Pansy, then Greengrass all came out from the curtain withdrawn and thoughtful.

Most of those who went first seemed to be recovered by the end of the class. Rigel herself felt marginally better after consuming three chocolate frogs. She did notice that Draco, on the other hand, looked much more strung out by the end of the lesson than he had just after facing the boggart. Toward the end of the class he excused himself and stepped into the hallway for a moment. He wasn't gone long enough to have walked all the way to the bathroom and back, but he looked marginally more relaxed. Rigel assumed he'd taken a suppressant potion, then wondered if that was his first for the day or his second.

Not that she could blame him, if it helped calm him down. She could use a Calming Draught herself after that class.

Remus called them all together after the last student, a confused-looking Goyle, had helped himself to a handful of chocolate. "Excellent work today, everyone. I'm extremely proud of how well you all handled yourself even in the face of extreme psychological stress. There are many young adults your age who would not be so composed."

There was a bit of bitterness in the set looks on a few faces, and Rigel thought the others knew exactly why they were able to function better than average under pressure—they'd lived and worked under months of psychological uncertainty and fear during the sleeping sickness and in the wake of basilisk attacks. It would accustom anyone to being afraid, to a certain extent.

"Next class we will begin to dismantle the fear you felt today," Remus said, "You will learn how to function in opposition to something that frightens you, how to overcome the physical effects of fear. Once you can act despite your fear, you can do anything from defending yourself against an acromantula to giving a presentation in front of your most respected peers."

A few people laughed, but mostly the third-years just looked and felt exhausted. Remus let them go with a cheerful, "No homework this week," and they filed out into the hall.

Their next class was History of Magic, but first Rigel had Magical Theory and a block of Alchemy to get through. Lunch suddenly seemed a very long way off. She slipped away to a secluded bathroom to turn back to eight-o-clock, hoping that her new electives wouldn't be nearly as trying as Defense Against the Dark Arts had been.

In this, at least, she got her wish.

Magical Theory was just what everyone had said it would be. The textbook was dry, slow-paced, and even the introduction was written in intensely meticulous language, with the author seemingly focused on articulating every point as exactly as possible, without being either too detailed or too interesting.

Rigel sort of loved it. Sometimes the theory portions of her textbooks seemed generalized and overly simple—not so with the Magical Theory text. The professor explained that they would be giving a thorough grounding in the technical theory behind all major branches of magic, from Transfiguration to Herbology, Creature magic to Elemental magic, and everything in between before the end of the year.

She left the class feeling very optimistic about her new electives. If Alchemy, Arithmancy, and Ancient Runes went half as well, she was going to have a fascinating term.

When she turned back to eight o'clock for the second time that day (making it her third time in that time so far), she checked her schedule and wondered if it had been written correctly. Under Alchemy was Headmaster Dumbledore's name, along with 'Headmaster's Office—Floo Chews' in loopy cursive. It took her a moment to work out that Floo Chews would be the password to his office.

She kept her cloak on until she'd mounted the stairs behind the stone gargoyle, then stowed it quickly before she reached the top. Dumbledore probably knew the Marauders had had an invisibility cloak—she gathered her father had been less than discrete in its use at school—but there was no reason for him to know that she had it.

The Headmaster's office was distracting, to say the least. There were whirling and gyrating gizmos on every available surface, and Rigel wondered how she was going to be able to concentrate at all. As she closed the door behind her, however, Dumbledore stood up from his desk and gestured to the wall behind him, which was covered floor-to-ceiling in shelves of books.

"We'll have class in my workroom, if you don't mind," the wizened man said, skimming his fingers across a shelf until he settled them on a book covered in deep purple dragon-hide. He winked at her, then pulled the top of the book away from the wall, activating a set of noiseless hinges that swung an entire section of the shelving inward.

Rigel tried not to look too amused, but she did ask, "Did you install that yourself?"

Dumbledore twinkled at her proudly, "That honor was not mine, though I did recover the lever-book in purple." He waited for a beat, then added, "It's my favorite color."

"Oh," she said. He was still looking at her expectantly, so she offered, "I don't really have a favorite."

"It's always important to be open-minded," Dumbledore nodded sagely, "Especially when approaching a new field of academia."

With that, he led the way through the bookcase and into a small, circular room with no windows. It was lit by a sphere of purest white light that hovered where the ceiling peaked in the center. There were no chalkboards filled with riddling equations or laboratory stations strewn with experiments or anything that would indicate the workroom of a powerful, genius-level wizard. There was just a table with a few chairs around it and lots of spare bits of parchment lying atop it.

Rigel took a seat and pulled out her note-taking materials while Dumbledore went back into the main room. He came back with a nondescript leather journal and placed it on the desk before her. It was only the fact that she knew that diary was safely locked away at the bottom of her trunk that kept her from flinching. Instead, she frowned down at the book before turning her gaze to Dumbledore's and saying, "For taking notes in?"

"I've saved you the trouble," Dumbledore smiled, "This will be your textbook for the first semester."

Rigel curiously flipped through the first few pages and couldn't stop her eyebrows from rising as she recognized the loopy script that filled them. Dumbledore had written her a textbook? By hand? No, she realized after skimming a few paragraphs, it wasn't written like a textbook at all. It was rather stream-of-consciousness, actually—or maybe white-water-rafting-of-consciousness. There were diagrams with arrows pointing all over the place, whole pages of equations further into the notebook that looked a bit like the basic ratio-balancing equations sometimes published in potions journals, only she didn't recognize any of the denotative symbols.

"Are there chapters?" she asked, wondering how he would assign readings in such a text.

"I find there's no need for macro-level progress indicators in my one-on-one classes," Dumbledore said lightly, "As we discuss the concepts and work on practice problems together, your learning curve will become quite clear. Just read as much as interests you in the week between our lessons, and after you've summarized your understanding each week, I'll fill in the gaps and arrange an experiment to help demonstrate the ideas."

Rigel nodded to show she understood, but inwardly she was frowning. She was to set the pace of the course? Was it a test of her academic dedication? Was he going to be disappointed if she progressed too slowly, or disapproving if she pushed ahead too quickly? She wasn't worried about self-motivating—if there was one thing she could do, it was work at a good pace without prompting. She did worry what Dumbledore meant by letting her do so, however.

"For today, I'll introduce the topic briefly, assuming you know nothing about Alchemy," Dumbledore said, starting to slowly walk around the table in a circle, "Alchemy is about changing one thing into something else. It's a subject not many learn, and even fewer delve deeply into, usually because if a wizard wants to effect such a change he uses transfiguration. Alchemy is related to transfiguration, but in much the same way that potions is related to cooking. One is a science and the other more like an art. This is not to diminish the difficulty and exactness required of Transfiguration, of course, but in general transfigurations one does not usually break the first object into its constituent parts, measure them, calculate the lowest possible input of energy to effect the desired changes, and then perform the transformation. In Alchemy, however, this is precisely what is required."

Rigel was scribbling down notes as fast as she could while still trying to soak in everything Dumbledore was saying.

"In the beginning, we will focus on transmuting raw elements into compounds, working our way up to more challenging combinations throughout the year. Only very advanced students are able to transmute whole objects into other whole objects, and it requires a level of Arithmancy that I suspect you've not been exposed to yet, in any case," Dumbledore went on, "Do you know why calculations are so important in Alchemy while in Transfiguration willpower is enough to effect exact changes?"

"Because in Transfiguration the wizard is guiding the magic consciously," Rigel guessed based on what she'd heard about Alchemy and knew about shaping magic, "Alchemical transmutations are shaped by runic patterns that describe the changes desired, but the magic the wizard puts into the reaction is raw, so the equations controlling the transformation have to be exact enough to produce the right result without the wizard's will."

"Just so," Dumbledore smiled, "Because of this, Alchemy is one of the few advanced forms of magic that wizards with very little magical power can excel at. Because the calculations and runes to all the 'work' the raw magic required in an alchemical transformation is many times less than the magic necessary to perform a transfiguration of equivalent complexity."

Rigel had never heard that before—in fact, all the famous alchemists she'd ever heard of were known to be powerful wizards, not the other way around. She said as much, and Dumbledore chuckled.

"The efficiency advantages of Alchemy become apparent exponentially, I'm afraid," he explained, "In the beginning, the differences between alchemical and transfigurative energy inputs will not seem all that incredible, and Alchemy will still be far more complicated—almost unnecessarily so, it will seem in the basic reactions. It is only as one progresses through the science—not without considerable time and mental strain, I may attest—that the effort of calculation begins to pay dividends in efficiency, and even then the results of one Alchemy transmutation can take many weeks to plan and execute, while transfiguration can be done at a moment's notice."

"And if you consider that Alchemy essentially magnifies a wizard's power through extreme efficiency," Rigel said slowly, "Then the more powerful wizards will get the most out of Alchemy—like Nicholas Flamel. Alchemy is what made something as incredible as the Philosopher's Stone possible, but I'm guessing a squib couldn't do that, no matter how efficient his equations were."

Dumbledore inclined his head gravely, "You are correct. Alchemy can elevate a near-powerless wizard to feats that ordinary-leveled wizards enjoy, but efficiency does indeed only go so far."

Rigel nodded along as she took notes. It sounded like Alchemy was Arithmancy, Potions, Runes, and Transfiguration all boiled down to their most exacting and effective states. She tried not to get ahead of herself, but it was hard not to try applying the efficiency theory of reactions to potions theory in her head as she wrote. After all, so many basic potions were essentially chemical reactions in a solvent…

Dumbledore didn't keep her the whole two-period block, so she headed down the gargoyle-staircase at 11:15 with a peanut butter sandwich kindly provided by the Headmaster as she packed up her things. She doubted he'd made it himself, but it was thoughtful of him to give her a snack to tide her over through History of Magic, all the same.

In an alcove down the hallway she scarfed down the last bit of crust, slipped on her cloak, and turned back one and a half turns to nine forty-five. She snuck into the bathroom between the Defense and History classrooms and waited patiently for her past self to come inside and disappear. Draco and Pansy had saved her a seat, and she tried not to look as though she hadn't seen them in hours, since they'd seen her just a few minutes ago.

At first she wondered why everyone looked so subdued, but then she recalled that for them the overwhelming events of Defense Against the Dark Arts had only just happened. She adjusted her own expression to be suitably introspective and took out her History textbook to pass the time while Binns droned on about a goblin rebellion so miniscule that most history books from the Middle Ages didn't even mention it.

"How are you so calm?" Draco muttered a few minutes into the lecture.

Rigel glanced questioningly at her friend, raising her book up a bit so that even if the ghostly professor looked up from his podium he wouldn't see her lips moving, "What do you mean?"

"Everyone else is silently freaking out about learning their greatest fear, but you're just casually reading a book," Draco whispered, "You were upset in Defense—did you take a Calming Draught in the bathroom?"

Rigel blinked, "So what if I did?"

"Well…" Draco frowned, "Nothing, I guess. Got any more?"

Rigel frowned herself, "No, sorry." She did, of course, have Calming Draughts in her bag, but she didn't think they ought to be mixed with suppressant potions, especially if Draco was taking as many doses as she thought he was.

Draco's frowned deepened, and he looked like he would say something to contradict her claim for a moment, but then he shrugged a shoulder and turned back to his notes in silence.

The afternoon flew by, and although Rigel enjoyed Arithmancy immensely—it was so satisfying to hear the subject introduced by an experienced professor instead of reading proofs in a textbook—she was also quite looking forward to being able to relax later that evening. Nearly twelve hours of class in one day was a lot, after all, even if the day was stretched long enough to accommodate them comfortably.

She was not the only one digging into dinner with gusto—Millicent positively moaned around her beef stew, complaining, "This year is going to be so awful. It's like all the professors decided we haven't been working hard enough."

"Maybe we haven't," Blaise said, "Less free time isn't necessarily a bad thing."

"Not all of us want to use our brains every second of every day," Millicent argued, "We need some time to relax."

"It won't be as bad as you think," Pansy said reasonably, "If they took away all of our free time now, how could they take away more when we start NEWT classes?"

"That's so reassuring, Pans," Draco huffed.

Rigel blinked as the smell of suppressant potion drifted across her nose. She frowned inwardly—hadn't she seen Draco take a dose just a few hours earlier? How many had that been today? She was distracted from this concerned train of thought when Theo tentatively broached the subject of their first Defense lesson.

"So…your uncle seems…intense, Rigel," he said, not looking at her as he salted his potatoes.

"He's usually very even-keeled," Rigel shrugged, "But I suppose he'd have to put on a strong front to win over student respect."

And in immediate hindsight she wondered if perhaps she shouldn't be undermining his effort to do so by saying such a thing out loud. With a mental wince, she attempted a quick retraction.

"He's always taken learning very serious though, now that I think on it. I'm sure he's in earnest about imparting something useful," she tried not to think the silent 'while he can' that went through her head when she remembered the curse on the position. If anyone could beat such a curse, it was Remus.

"Did he tutor you when you were younger?" Pansy asked curiously.

Rigel considered the question carefully, "He did give me a lot of his old potions notes when I fist started studying the subject, and he's always there to answer any questions I have. Harry and I didn't have formal tutoring, though, unless you could the basic reading, writing, and figuring Aunt Lily taught us."

Her friends seemed surprised to hear this. She knew they'd all had specific tutors as children in history, basic spell-casting, rudimentary herbal lore, and so on. She also thought they knew she hadn't, but perhaps they'd forgotten she wasn't a 'typical' pureblood.

Not a pureblood at all, the voice that she'd had more trouble than usual keeping quiet since encountering the boggart whispered. She shook her head and clenched her jaw with renewed determination. She wasn't going to let such petty fears prey on her reality. If her friends noticed she was a bit more conversationally engaged than usual that night they didn't comment on it, and Rigel refused to admit that she was compensating for her feelings of guilt and displacement.

After dinner no one seemed to feel much like studying, so they settled into a cluster of low-backed chairs in the common room and just relaxed, conversing as they worked on a personal project or participated in a card game, as was their pleasure.

Rigel was halfway through a chapter on muscular dystrophy in one of Archie's healing textbooks when it was plucked from her hands by a very indolent-expressioned Aldon Rosier.

"Healing?" he asked, casually removing Draco's book bag from the seat beside Rigel and flopping down in its place between the two third years. The look he earned from Draco was annoyed, but also unusually edgy, even given his previously expressed dislike of Rosier. "Did you get into the OWL class, then?"

"Not especially," Rigel said with carefully doled casualness, "I have lessons with Madam Pomfrey in my free time sometimes, but mostly I'll be studying on my own, still."

"What classes are you taking, then?" the golden-eyed boy asked.

Wordlessly, Rigel swapped her 'official' schedule for the Healing book, proceeding to ignore Rosier in favor of reading while he perused it.

"You dropped potions?" the upperclassman asked, plucking the book from her fingers once more—or at least he attempted to. She'd tightened her fingers on the pages and tugged it back toward her with a miffed sort of scowl.

"I'm taking it as independent study this year," Rigel said, "Professor Snape was kind enough to create a syllabus more tailored to my interests."

"To your abilities, you mean," Rosier said, a knowing grin on his face, "Congratulations, Rigel. Professor Snape doesn't excuse just anyone from classes. Your studies must really be progressing."

"Thanks," she blinked, surprised by the honest compliment from the usually enigmatic Slytherin, "I just got a lot of studying done over the summer, so I'm a bit ahead, I suppose."

Rosier laughed, sounding more like the playful charmer she was used to, "There comes a point where modesty is simply a lie, you know."

"Does Rigel strike you as someone adverse to telling lies, Rosier?" Draco asked rather pointedly.

The upperclassman turned to look at Draco with a gleam in his eyes that could only mean trouble, "Does he strike you as someone who needs you to defend him, Malfoy?"

Rigel, flustered and a bit annoyed at her two friends, tried to change the subject, "Where's Rookwood?"

"Edmund?" Rosier turned back to Rigel almost reluctantly, "Moping, I suppose. He's ever so depressing with Alice out in the wide world."

"They have a strong bond," Rigel said neutrally, "I'm sure anyone would feel the same."

"Yes, attachments do seem to…complicate life, don't they?" Rosier said absently, "Not altogether a bad thing, of course…"

"When the attachment goes both ways, at least," Draco drawled, "One-sided obsession gets rather tiresome, though, doesn't it?"

Rosier's head turned back to Draco with an eagerness that spoke of someone looking for an argument, "With too much time, perhaps, but you must admit it's better than the milky, pathetic feeling of ambivalent attentions such as—"

"I think you boys have had enough polite conversation for one night, don't you?" Pansy rose abruptly and held out her hand to Rosier, who rose and bowed over it almost automatically. "I'd like a quick stroll before turning in, if you wouldn't mind obliging me? I feel we haven't caught up properly in ages, Aldon."

Rosier took Pansy's hand on his arm with a subservient, if ironic, tilt to his head, "I am ever at your service, Pansy. Good evening," he added with a smile to the rest of them as Pansy drew him toward the common room entrance.

Draco blew out a slow breath, then stood. "I'm tired," he said, packing up his things, "See you all in the morning."

Rigel stood as well, tucking her healing book under her arm. With a quick good night to everyone she hurried after her disgruntled friend, wondering what had prompted him to be so openly hostile with so little provocation.

Draco was at his trunk when she walked in a few seconds behind him, and from the slightly guilty expression on his face she presumed he'd been about to take another suppressant potion. She narrowed her eyes—one at dinner and one before bed? He shouldn't need that many doses a day, surely.

She considered moving into the bathroom to brush her teeth, giving him the space to take his potions discretely without any questions, but, she thought, that was what she would have done last year. She was determined to be a better friend this year, as she had ample time to be such, and she was starting to see that friends didn't politely ignore each others' problems. They confronted them, and then helped fix them.

With that thought in mind, she walked slowly around Draco to her bed and sat down on the end of it, not taking her eyes off her friend the whole way. She waited expectantly, her gaze steady, and she had the satisfaction of seeing Draco twitch visibly before he steeled himself and stood, shutting the lid of his trunk with preoccupied precision.

"Going to lecture me about being rude to Rosier?" he asked sourly.

"Have I ever lectured you about anything?" she asked, surprised.

He frowned, then slowly moved to sit across from her on his own bed, "Guess not. Well, then?"

"I was going to ask if you wanted to talk about it," Rigel said.

"About what?" Draco said, "Rosier's a jerk. He was trying to provoke me."

"You don't usually make it that easy," Rigel said, "You've been irritable since the train ride."

"So?" Draco studied one of the knobs on his four-poster rather than look at her.

"Just making an observation," Rigel said, "In case you wanted to explain."

"And if I don't?" Draco asked.

Rigel shrugged, "Then don't. But be aware that if I've noticed, everyone's noticed, so if it's not something you want to talk about, you'd better take steps to address the problem, whatever it is."

"I am," Draco pressed his lips together, "This isn't something that just goes away, Rigel."

"So you're going to be a grumpy git forever?" Rigel said, her tone devastatingly deadpan.

He threw his pillow at her. She caught it, then made a show of looking it over carefully. Smiling, she drew a short, pale strand from the underside and held it up to the light, "Oh, good. I used the last of your hair making the Potentials Potion." She didn't think it was just her imagination that he tensed when she mentioned the potion, which only cemented her idea that he'd come into a magical gift he was having difficulty managing. Ignoring his suspicious and slightly panicky look, she slid off the bed and rummaged in her bag for her potions kit with one hand, the other still dramatically holding the hair up between two fingers.

"What are you doing?" Draco said, his voice incredulous.

Rigel blinked exaggeratedly at him, "Cataloguing this for safekeeping. You never know when you might need to Polyjuice into the scion of a powerful pureblood family, after all. I bet I could get a pretty penny for it on the black market, in fact."

Draco let out a disbelieving laugh and lunged toward her from the bed, "Give that back."

"Why should I?" Rigel asked, dancing away, "You discarded it."

"Not so you could have it!"

"You threw it to me, remember?" Rigel said, grinning openly now as she circled around Blaise's trunk.

"That doesn't count," Draco was grinning reluctantly now, "Seriously, give it here—do you know how long my father lectured me when Severus asked how you'd gotten my hair to do the potion for my birthday?"

"I warned you," Rigel said archly, her snooty tone of voice completely belied as she scrambled inelegantly over Blaise's bed and onto hers. Draco followed right after her, and Rigel wondered how long Lucius Malfoy would lecture his son if he could see him clambering over his dorm mates' beds like a juvenile blonde monkey. "I told you not to leave your DNA lying about so carelessly many times."

"I shouldn't have to watch out for you, Rigel," Draco dove for the hand with his hair in it but missed as she leapt across his bed and threw the hangings shut behind her in his face. "Should I put a ward on my hairbrush, too?" he added as he dodged around the foot of his bed to block her way to the door.

She skidded to a halt and tried to change directions, but she only managed to trip on one of Theo's shoes and land with a complete lack of dignity on the floor instead.

Draco leaned down and trapped her wrist between his palms with an expression that was much more entertained—and much less defensive and crabby—than it had been a few minutes before. "Let it go," he said, smirking.

She sighed with false regret, and let the hair slip through her fingers, "You win this round—but I'll get one soon enough, Draco. You shed like a dog."

"I what?" he positively yelped in indignation, and Rigel couldn't help the laugh that escaped her. Draco rolled his eyes and turned around to flop down onto his bedcovers, "You're a complete child."

"Yes," Rigel said solemnly, reclaiming her own bed as well, "I wish I could be as mature as you, Draco, but I just don't have the aplomb to jump so coolly across mattresses like that. If only your mother could see you now."

"You will never mention this incident to anyone, or I'll find one of your hairs and Polyjuice as you for revenge," Draco warned, chuckling.

Rigel sat up straight, abruptly alarmed, "You wouldn't do that, would you, Draco?"

"What?" Draco laughed a bit before catching the serious—and, she realized belatedly, too-wary—expression on her face, "No…why would I?"

Rigel thought quickly and affected a down-turned expression of worry, "My Uncle James has told me all sorts of awful stories about people who use Polyjuice for ill ends, and they almost always meet a sticky end. It's such an unreliable brew—you can never be sure it's made correctly, and won't turn you into some kind of creature-human-hybrid for the rest of your life."

She was purely exaggerating now, but Draco didn't have to know that.

"Merlin, really?" Draco shuddered, "Who'd want to be someone else, anyway? I mean, I'm perfect the way I am—you'd be a huge step down, Rigel."

She laughed, because she knew he was making a joke, but her insides felt strangely hollow. Of course Draco would never imagine a life as someone else. After a moment she decided this was a good thing, not something to resent him for. Better that Draco never feel the ache that came from knowing that your destiny was choked by chains not of your own forging.

The rest of the week flew by, an incandescent whirl of new classes and old friends and more free time than she'd ever had in her life. The only specter casting a shadow over those days was one Marcus Flint, absentee Quidditch captain and coma-patient extraordinaire.

Friday afternoon found Rigel with Pansy and Draco in the Hospital Wing visiting Flint's inert form. Her friends didn't know that this was actually Rigel's second trip to the Wing that day, having been there earlier for her Healing class at the same time that she was in Magical Theory and Herbology. Madam Pomfrey had been a little too blasé in greeting Rigel, but she didn't think her friends were likely to notice or suspect a bit of overacting on the nurse's part.

They were about to leave when the Hospital Wing door opened and Percy Weasley strolled briskly in, his face awash in the kind of determination generally seen in one who has been entrusted with a very important mission. He paused at seeing them there, then smiled politely at Draco and Pansy while inclining his head to Rigel. The Head Boy had a thick stack of parchments in his hand, which he arranged on Flint's bedside table carefully.

"His assignments for the week," Percy explained, "If…when he wakes, he won't want to be behind."

"The professors can't make allowances for him?" Pansy asked, a troubled frown creasing her brow.

Percy shrugged helplessly, "He can plead his case when he's better, I suppose. At least he'll have the notes…"

"Did you take notes for him?" Pansy asked, "That was very kind of you, Mr. Weasley."

"Ah, just Percy," the older boy said, flushing a bit, "I didn't take all of them. The other seventh-year prefects pitched in, too. Imagine missing the first week of NEWT-prep," Percy shuddered in what was apparently horrified sympathy, "None of us envy him that."

"Thank the others as well for me, please?" Pansy said, smiling sadly, "I wish there was more I could do for him."

"I'm sure your presence is comfort enough," Percy said, a bit pompously, "Well, I'd best be off. Will I see you this weekend, Rigel? We're learning some very interesting theory on bi-part transfigurations this week."

"Most likely," Rigel nodded, "If you aren't too busy with Head Boy duties."

"Never too busy for learning, Rigel," Percy smiled as though she'd said something very silly.

He took his leave and Draco let loose a snort he must have been containing for some time, "He's quite full of himself—see how he swelled when you mentioned 'Head Boy duties?'"

"He should be proud of his achievements," Rigel shrugged. She was thinking about Flint's assignments and the most devious idea had come into her head.

"It is possible to be proud without becoming a blowhard," Draco said.

"Oh yes," Pansy agreed, her voice deceptively mild, "No one likes a showboat. Remind me again who it was showing off the wrist holster he got for his birthday at the lunch table the other day?"

The tips of Draco's ears turned a delicate shade of pink, "Theo asked to see it, and I was only wearing it because of Dueling lessons—"

"Speaking of," Rigel interrupted, hiding a smile, "Draco has promised to teach us all his illustrious new-found wisdom on the subject, has he not, Pansy?"

"Why, that's right!" Pansy's smile had points, "Perhaps we can put that holster to good use—it was looking a little, well, new. How long do you think it will take to break in? Does it irritate your skin when you wear it too long?"

Draco huffed, "It is made of the finest leather galleons can buy, so no it does not require breaking in, thank you very much, and of course it still looks new; I wear it under my sleeves, so it's not as though it gets exposed to the elements. You're just jealous my parents love me so much."

Pansy couldn't keep the laughter from escaping her mouth, "If only your father's love could buy you talent, Drake."

"I don't need to buy talent," Draco squawked.

"I'm afraid you'll have to prove that, Dray," Rigel said, grinning.

"That's it!" Draco laughed, shaking his head, "You two are coming with me right now so I can defend my much-maligned brilliance."

"Brilliance, he says," Rigel raised her eyebrows, "I sure hope he can live up to that, Pan."

"I know what you mean," Pansy sighed, "He is such a boar to live with when he's been utterly humiliated."

"Up!" Draco said, exasperated, actually going so far as to wave them to their feet impatiently, "I won't stand for this kind of treatment, especially from my so-called friends."

"As your friends, it's our solemn duty to give your enormous ego a healthy dose of reality," Pansy informed him, linking her elbow around his affectionately.

"Or at least to trick you into giving us free dueling lessons," Rigel amended.

"Should have been a Ravenclaw," Draco grumbled, "I bet their friends don't torment them for sport."

They continued on that way as they left the Hospital Wing, but only half of Rigel's mind was on the friendly banter. The other half was carefully noting the time, and noticing that the hallways outside the wing were deserted, and very carefully not noticing any glimmer of invisibility cloak material that might have tugged at the corner of her eye as they wandered off.

A few hours later, or no time later at all, depending on how you looked at it, Rigel would sneak into the Hospital Wing under her cloak, copy down all of Flint's assignments, and leave just as quietly, a ghost on a mission of her own.

On Saturday morning she was meditating in the common room while Draco poured over his dueling handbook and Pansy worked on an assignment for her Care of Magical Creatures class. Rigel was also in her potions lab brewing watered-down sleeping draughts for the new 'child-friendly' line of potions Krait wanted to try marketing, and she was also in the kitchens with Binny, chatting away in what the elf assured her was increasingly intelligible French, but that was beside the point.

Her mindscape was strange, of late. She missed the golden balls of light that represented her constructed aura floating about the summit of her mountain, lighting up the wintery atmosphere. They were stored comfortably in her potions lab, now, laying about on various shelves, but it wasn't their addition to the inner-levels of her mind that made it seem…changed. The usually warm, welcoming lab felt small and cramped, as though the walls were closing in around her consciousness. She had to force herself to move through the tunnels, which seemed narrower and more confusing than she remembered, and an absolute chill went down her spine when she reached the door to her space room. It was as though there was an ominous presence, malevolently judging her from the room beyond, and it took all of her willpower to choke out the password and open the door.

The celestial objects within, usually whirling and dancing in orbit around the sun that represented her magical core, were unnaturally still and dimly lit. She squinted through the darkness toward the center, unable to fathom why it should be so difficult to see all of a sudden.

When she caught sight of her sun, she flinched involuntarily. It was no brighter than a bundle of glowworms, and it spun sluggishly on a half-hearted axis. It looked ill, as though it had been wasting away without her noticing.

It wasn't like that last time I was here…was it? She wondered, disturbed.

She frowned deeper when she realized that the last time she'd meditated she'd been rushed for time. It was just as she and Archie were to switch places the morning they returned to school, and she'd belatedly remembered she needed to de-construct her aura before leaving for the station. She'd barely entered her mindscape before sending the orbiting spheres of energy whooshing back into the secondary layer of her mind with a powerfully worded thought. She hadn't actually entered the space room 'physically' since…

Before she started wearing the suppresser.

Well, that would explain the drastic change. She tilted her head at the diseased-looking sun. Was it a problem? It didn't look healthy, but there wasn't actually anything wrong with her magic. Quite the opposite—she had no trouble at all wielding spells appropriate to her age group, and she was even learning spells at a normal rate now, taking most of class to figure out how to cast a new spell, instead of freakishly performing them instantly the way she had before.

Uneasy, but not as wary as she had been before figuring out the reason for her mindscape's unusual atmosphere, she left her sun to its lazy rotations and returned her thoughts to the puppet-boy sitting above her in the cave-lab.

She had run into a wall with its development last year, but this year she was determined to improve upon the design until it constituted a working line of defense.

She had tried the complex command route, relying on intricately worded orders to get the puppet to behave with a semblance of awareness, and although it had worked for a while against Riddle Jr., the construct had been half-mad and completely overconfident at the time. A more careful intruder would not have been fooled.

She'd been thinking a lot about magical constructs, Riddle Jr. included, as she tried to work out a way to imitate life. What really got her thinking, however, was her little sister Addy. A child's magical core started developing in the womb, provided its physical template was expressed in its genes, with the original DNA from the parents determining the shape of its development to some extent.

The magical core didn't spontaneously create itself out of raw power—there was a design that it followed, taken from the mother and father's genetic material. She couldn't push unformed magic into something and expect it to take on a life of its own. The magic had to have a pattern to follow. In the case of sentience, this pattern was obviously very complicated, but when parents created a child they didn't design one from scratch—their bodies already had the pattern built in, they just had to…assemble the pieces.

In theory, she didn't have to design sentience from scratch; she just had to duplicate the pattern that already existed. She already had sentient magic, after all. Her magic had a will that was independent from, though still somehow related to, her own will. She imagined the trick would be getting a piece of willful magic inside the puppet, like imbuing shaped magic with a design into a potion instead of raw magic, and hadn't she already learned how to move pieces of the very essence of her magic around her mind?

When she projected her aura consciously, she broke off a piece of her original core from the heart of her mind and moved it to the edges. In theory, all she had to do now was put that piece in the puppet, and the puppet should be imbued with the will of her magic, able to follow directions efficiently and creatively, the way her magic could do things she herself didn't painstakingly supervise.

Satisfied that her theory was sound, and wondering why no one had bothered to write this kind of thing down in a book for people, she reached toward her sun and pulled coaxingly at it, asking for a handful of magic. Immediately she felt pain wash through her in a petulant backlash. Her vision went dark, and when she groggily recovered her sight she was sprawled at the foot of the couch, Pansy bending over her concernedly.

"Are you all right, Rigel?"

She shook her head to clear it, then nearly passed out again at the vertigo that produced. She sat up shakily, stifling a groan at the painful ache in her gut. Pressing a hand to her stomach, she hefted herself back onto the couch.

"I'm fine," she said slowly, trying to work out what just happened, "I tried to do something that…didn't work. Must have been knocked out of my trance improperly."

"Are you messing around with dangerous Occlumency techniques?" Draco asked, sounding annoyed, "You could make yourself brain-dead doing that."

"It was something I've tried before," Rigel said, shaking her head, "I don't know exactly what went wrong, but I won't try it again until I figure it out."

She thought she might have an idea, actually. The resistance she'd felt before the pain meant that something was preventing her from taking the magic from her core. Best guess—the suppresser ring. It must have blocked her access to such a large portion of her magic that there wasn't enough left to remove a piece without damaging the integrity of the core…maybe. She supposed next time she tried she could use the piece she'd already broken away from her magical core, the one she used to mimic her core when she projected her aura. It was sitting on a shelf in her mental lab with all the other duplicate orbs. Then again, she ought to save that piece for the next time she needed to project her aura, shouldn't she?

To distract herself from the headache that was forming, she glanced at what her friends were up to.

"How's the schoolwork going?" she asked, stretching the kink in her neck out.

"It's…" Pansy hesitated, then sighed, "It doesn't make a lot of sense, actually. Professor Pettigrew's assignments are a little vague."

"The man's a mouse," Draco said dismissively, "He cringes at everything; how could he possibly manage a class full of students and a bunch of magical creatures at once?"

"He's quite good with the creatures, actually," Pansy said, frowning, "It's uncanny how well they take to him. In that aspect he's very gifted, but as an instructor…he doesn't seem very knowledgeable. I mean, everything he's told us about the creatures we're studying has been taken directly from our textbook, and when someone asks a question he sometimes assigns it as homework instead of answering it."

"Maybe he's trying to make you learn to help yourselves?" Rigel suggested.

"Maybe," Pansy said, looking unconvinced, "Except when he grades our assignments he doesn't really correct anything, just checks it for completion. I suppose it's still just the first month, so maybe he's keeping it simple for now, but learning everything from books seems like a waste of a class."

"You get to see the creatures up close, though," Rigel said, trying to cheer Pansy up. She was pretty sure it was too late to switch classes until next year.

"That's true," Pansy said, tilting her head considering, "It is making me a better researcher."

"Even though the teacher doesn't even check your facts?" Draco shook his head, "I bet most people make up their answers. You should include something blatantly wrong next time, just to see if he's even reading them."

Pansy laughed, "Then how would I pass my OWL in a few years? I'm pretty sure those examiners do check your answers."

"The head examiner owes me a favor," Rigel said casually, "I could put in a good word."

Draco and Pansy both stared at her.

"Joke," Rigel said, blinking.

"Who are you?" Draco laughed, "Rigel Black doesn't joke about life debts."

"I'm an imposter," Rigel said, as deadpan as she could, "I've hidden the real Rigel Black in a closet and taken over his life."

"And how is that going so far?" Pansy asked wryly.

"It's not as fun as I thought it would be," Rigel said mournfully, "Rigel apparently just studies all the time, and his friends are kind of boring."

"Boring?" Draco raised an eyebrow, "Is that a challenge, Imposter Rigel?"

"I prefer Rigel the Second," she said archly, "The new and improved version."

"What new features should we expect?" Pansy asked, a smile around her eyes.

"Less reading, more relaxing," Rigel said, lounging backwards on the couch with pronounced indolence, "And this whole self-study potions thing? I'm thinking not."

They both laughed incredulously.

"I'd like to see Snape's face when you tell him that," Draco said between laughs.

"I think I could keep him off my trail until at least until Christmas," she said, grinning a bit now.

"Now you're just deluding yourself," Pansy said, "No one could pull the wool over Professor Snape's eyes for more than a month, at the absolute most."

Rigel allowed that this was probably the case, but inside she felt rather cynical. Snape wasn't nearly as infallible as her housemates thought. Adults rarely were, in her experience. They made a good show of omnipotence, but Rigel had learned at a young age that even people who were good at seeing deception when they looked for it simply didn't look for it most of the time. When they were looking for deception, their own imagination often got in the way of objectivity, so all one had to do was reveal a 'truth' that matched with what they expected the truth to be. 'Tell people what they want to hear' was the first and most important rule of getting away with things, in her experience.

She remembered a time when Lily had caught her sneaking upstairs to her room in the middle of the night. She wasn't being as quiet as she had been sneaking downstairs to her mother's potions lab, and Lily, who had apparently got up to use the bathroom, heard her soft 'ow' of surprise as she stubbed her toe on the top stair.

Her mother's forbidding expression was still mildly alarming to her, at that age, and she knew if Lily found out she'd been brewing without asking again she'd be in big trouble, so she blurted, "I only had one!" with as much childish petulance as she could muster.

"One what?" Lily had asked, managing to look every inch a stern matriarch even with her hair sleep-mussed and her bathrobe on inside out.

"Nothing," she mumbled, looking away as though she were hiding something. She clasped her hands behind her back as well, in a belated effort to hide the bandage on her little finger, the souvenir of a clumsy knife stroke.

"Harriet," Lily only used her full name when she wanted answers.

She affected the most adorably guilt-filled expression she could come up with, widening her eyes and pinching her brows together the way she'd seen Archie do when he accidently broke his mother's favorite teacup.

"I was hungry," she said sadly, sniffing a bit for effect, "But I didn't want any vegetables."

She could see the moment when her mother's imagination seized on the most likely explanation and ran with it, "Did you break into the biscuit tin again? You know you're not allowed sweets between meals, Harry."

She silently resented the 'again' comment, as it had been Archie who broke into the biscuit tin last time, but she lowered her face to the ground as if ashamed, hoping the angle would hide her annoyance. She heard Lily sigh, and when she felt arms wrap around her shoulders she relaxed into them, biting her lip on a triumphant smile.

"Next time you get hungry at night try a glass of milk, okay?" Lily said, stroking her long hair gently, "It's not good for your stomach to digest things while you sleep."

"Uncle Remus says it'll give you weird dreams," she said into Lily's hip, "If I have a nightmare, can I come sleep with you and Dad?"

"Of course you can, darling," her mother said, "But if you think of nice things before you fall asleep your dreams will all be sweet."

She remembered taking her mother's advice as she drifted off to sleep that night, thinking of the vials of hair-growth potion she'd tucked into her slippers and imagining all the places she could put it when she went over to Archie's house the next day.

Looking back, Rigel wondered if she'd been born with a natural tendency to shrug off authority or if it had come from having Sirius and James for examples of adult behavior.

She spent the rest of the morning with her friends, and after lunch she trekked up to Gryffindor tower to study advanced transfigurations with Percy.

Percy wasn't there to let her in when she reached the portrait of the pink lady, but a cheerful Oliver Wood was on his way out, broom tucked under one arm.

"Afternoon, Black," Wood said, holding the portrait for her, "Great weather today, eh?"

"I hadn't noticed," she said, blinking at the non sequitur.

"Ah, yes, the price of living in the dungeons I suppose," he looked vaguely disturbed.

"They do let us out occasionally," she said, smiling.

"It would certainly make the season duller if they didn't," he grinned.

It was only because it was Wood talking that she made the connection to the Quidditch season and realized he meant there'd be less competition for his team without the Slytherins there. Thanking him for the round-a-bout compliment, she watched bemusedly as he took off down the hallway with a whistle.

She climbed through the portrait hole and surprised a prefect who'd come over to investigate the open entrance.

It was Angelina Johnson, and she gave a friendly smile as she said, "Looking for the twins? They're about to head out to the pitch with the rest of us."

Rigel noticed she was dressed for the outdoors, and figured Gryffindor must have Quidditch practice on Saturday afternoons. "I'm meeting Percy, actually," she said, "Is he around?"

"Haven't seen him," the older girl said, shrugging, "He doesn't spend much time in his room since he's Head Boy now—likes to be seen with his badge on, we reckon," she pulled a face as she thought, "Saw him leave early from lunch with the Head Girl."

Rigel wasn't actually sure who the Head Girl was this year, but she shrugged to show she understood, "I'll wait then, if it's okay."

"Of course," Angelina said, patting her on the back, "I can go get one of the younger Weasleys to entertain you, if you like."

"That's all right," she said, embarrassed at the idea of having to be entertained like a guest, "No need to bother anyone. I'm sure they have better things to do on a Saturday than babysit their Slytherin friend."

"If you're sure," the prefect shrugged, "See you later, then. Fred! George! Get a move on!"

Rigel privately noted that no one ever shouted so loudly in the Slytherin common room.

Twin tornados of red blurred past her, both pausing just long enough to mess up her hair before continuing at their reckless pace through the portrait hole.

Rigel chose a conspicuously placed chair near the center of the common room, took a Healing textbook out of her bag, and settled in to wait for Percy.

He showed up not fifteen minutes later, his expression moving from clearly pleased with something to dismayed when he caught sight of Rigel.

"I forgot!" he blurted, walking quickly over, "Rigel, I'm terribly sorry. I know you only told me this morning what time, but I was meeting with Penelope and we—I just—it slipped my mind completely."

A rosy flush was creeping up from beneath his collar, so Rigel stopped him before he could trip over his words anymore. "It's all right, Percy," she said, putting away her book, "I haven't been here long, and it gave me a chance to catch up on some reading, anyway.

"Still…" Percy looked completely mortified, and Rigel suspected it wasn't just being late that was making him embarrassed.

"I'm sure your meeting was very interesting," Rigel said, suppressing a smile, "I couldn't very well begrudge you a bit of extra time with our Head Girl when you're spending it so industriously on we students' behalf."

There was definitely a pink tinge to the tips of his ears, now, and he muttered a quick, "I'll just go get my things," before hightailing it to his dorm to regroup.

Rigel sternly told herself not to tease the older boy any more when he got back, if only because she relied on his good graces to wade through theoretical transfigurations.

It was late Saturday night when Flint came prowling back into the common room. The whole Quidditch team jumped up from various tables and congregated around the upperclassman, who scowled forbiddingly but nevertheless seemed slightly embarrassed by all the fuss.

Pansy beamed as she set aside her notes and went to welcome the Quidditch captain back, Draco and Rigel trailing after her.

"It's so good to see you," Pansy said, clasping the burly boy's hand in earnest as the other well-wishers dispersed.

"From what I hear, you've been seeing me all week," his tone was beleaguered but his face had softened a tad at Pansy's smile.

"Someone had to check up on you," Pansy said.

"That's what mediwitches are for," Flint rolled his eyes.

"But will a mediwitch record all your fevered confessions?" Draco asked. At Flint's black look Draco widened his eyes innocently, "Didn't know you talk in your sleep?"

"Except I wasn't sleeping," Flint grunted.

They all four sobered at the reminder.

"Saw the Gryffindors practicing today," Draco said casually, "Looking in pretty good condition, considering they haven't practiced together in three months."

"Did you take notes?" Flint asked, frowning.

"Of course," Draco smirked, "Snuck into the locker rooms and copied Wood's new plays, too."

Flint barked out a laugh, "Not like Wood to leave them lying around—reckon he thought he didn't have to worry with me indisposed."

"He'll be surprised when we shove his new formations back down his throat," Draco agreed, looking unusually predatory.

Flint nodded, grinning like a shark faced with an unsuspecting meal, "You all better be in top condition. Practice tomorrow morning, eight sharp."

"I'll tell the others," Draco said.

He went off to do just that, and Pansy gave Flint a brief pat on the arm before taking her leave as well. She raised a questioning brow to Rigel, but Rigel waved her friend on. "I have to talk to him about this season," she said.

Flint cocked his head expectantly as Pansy headed back to their couch.

"I can't try out this year," Rigel said, stalling until Pansy was out of hearing range, "I'm going to focus on my academics instead."

Flint shrugged unconcernedly, "I'll replace you with somebody meaner. What do you really want?"

Rigel glanced around them casually, then said, "Expect an owl at breakfast tomorrow."

"The summer work? Good," Flint said, "I've a handful of stuff from this week already—"

"Did those too," she said, "I took the liberty while you were out."

Flint looked gratified, "I won't bother asking for an extension, then."

"You might want to," Rigel said, "To make it more believable."

"I'm not giving them an excuse to hold me back again," he said firmly.

Rigel shrugged, figuring it was his choice, and wandered back to her friends. In truth, she hadn't technically finished the assignments yet—at least, her present self hadn't. She assumed that in a few hours she would turn the day back again and get to work on them, however, so there was probably a version of herself that had finished the assignments by this time, or there would be, or…she mentally shook herself. In any case, the assignments would get to Flint by tomorrow morning.

On Tuesday morning she received a mysterious note at breakfast with 'everlasting gobstoppers' written on it, so she dutifully tucked it away until later (or earlier, depending on which version of herself she was thinking about) when she made the journey up to the Headmaster's Office for her Alchemy lesson.

She had made good headway in her 'textbook,' but instead of jumping right into the theory when she sat down, Dumbledore brought out a familiar-looking device. It was a long crystal cylinder with a metal ball attached to one end.

"Because Alchemy reactions require a very exact calculation of all input materials, including magic, it is necessary to calculate the rate of one's magical output before attempting any reactions," Dumbledore explained cheerfully, "This device will measure your average rate of magic expenditure. The results are relayed as a color on the light spectrum, then converted via conventional charts to a relative expression of energy over time that Alchemists call a person's magic constant. This constant will be used in equations to calculate the amount of time a specific witch or wizard needs to feed magic into a reaction in order to reach the required amount of power. Questions?"

"How accurate is an average rate as far as consistency?" Rigel asked, "Will the average rate fluctuate day-to-day, or change as a person ages?"

"Generally a wizard's core is stable once it fully matures," Dumbledore explained, "A stable core will have a near-constant rate of unconscious expenditure. With training, one can learn how to alter the rate at which one spends magic, either slowing it down or speeding it up, but directly affecting the speed at which your core produces and emits magic is extremely challenging, even for wizards with excellent control. At times illness or pregnancy can disrupt the flow of magic from a person's core, but the symptoms would be obvious enough to account for, in those cases."

Rigel nodded in understanding, then held her hand out to the device. Dumbledore added, "It's much like conscious imbuing," to which she smiled in thanks as though she hadn't known that already.

It was both similar to last time she'd done this, and very different. The process was the same, but instead of feeling like she was tipping over a bucket of water, it felt like she was pouring it from a bottle with a much smaller neck, or perhaps like letting water from a hose. Only so much could flow out at once, and it did so at a very constant rate, as Dumbledore had said. It didn't take long before she was tired, however, and the Headmaster told her to stop.

The metal ball was a bright green color, like grass that had only recently grown in. Dumbledore seemed to be eyeing her curiously, but he said nothing as he pulled out a chart and began comparing the shades depicted to the shade of the device.

Eventually he settled on the color green he thought the closest—Rigel was amazed to see how many slightly different shades of green alone were represented in the charts. Dumbledore asked her to copy down the figures listed next to her shade, and Rigel did so carefully.

"Your constant is 4.2," Dumbledore said, "Every time you see this symbol," he wrote down what looked like a capital 'S' with an extra curl at the end, "You plug in your constant and multiply it by whatever the equation's constant—the number that indicates how much magic is necessary for a reaction—is."

Rigel nodded, noting that the magic constants seemed to run from 1 to 8 and be inversely proportionate to the color scale, assuming Red was low and Violet was high. So less powerful shades had higher constants, presumably because it would require them to imbue for a longer amount of time in order to produce the same amount of magic as someone with a more powerful flow.

"As cores increase in power, the speed of magical output increases by a constant amount?" she asked, double-checking the relationship between colors and constants on the chart.

"Precisely," Dumbledore said, beaming at her, "This principle was first discovered by the sage Havodan, in the middle of the second century…" he went on to explain how the modern system of color-based magical evaluation had been rooted in the ancient use of crystals as channeling devices back before wand lore had developed into a powerful branch of magic in its own right.

Rigel listened with rapt attention. It seemed Dumbledore was always teaching her things she'd never heard anywhere else, and she took a moment to send a heartfelt, if silent, thanks to Professor Snape for recommending her for this class before scrambling to take notes.

By Wednesday afternoon Rigel was beginning to feel that she had settled into a strange sort of time-twisted routine. She supposed the sense of contentment should have warned her that something was about to go wrong.

She was on her way to the Library when Percy Weasley caught up with her in the hall.

"Rigel," the older boy uncharacteristically placed a hand on her arm to anchor her attention as he pulled her aside.

"Hi Percy," Rigel said. After looking up at him she frowned, "What's wrong?"

The prefect's face was drawn tight with tension and his voice had none of its usual pomp as he said, "I need to talk to you. Are you busy now?"

"No," Rigel said, but before she could ask why he was so intensely serious he began towing her gently but firmly toward an empty classroom a few doors down.

Percy shut the door behind them and took a deep, slow breath. He seemed calm when he turned around, but it was the sort of calm that Leo sometimes exhibited before a fight; it wasn't relaxed, but braced.

"Rigel, I have to ask you something and I need you to be honest with me," Percy said, his voice no louder than it needed to be.

Rigel could feel her heart beat faster, but outwardly she remained blank, "Sure, Percy. What is it?" What could he have discovered? Had Bill told his brother about an alley boy who looked suspiciously like Rigel Black? Had Percy somehow caught sight of her somewhere when she should have been somewhere else? Professor Snape would be very displeased if she had revealed the existence of her time-turner in just a few short weeks.

"On Friday you were there with Malfoy and Parkinson when I delivered Flint's assignments to the Hospital Wing," Percy began.

Rigel nodded slowly, wracking her brain to try and remember if she'd been anywhere else conspicuous at the same time that day.

"I need to know if you saw anyone—even someone who seemed like they had a good reason to—looking through the assignments I left," Percy said, voice deadly serious.

Rigel blinked, completely taken aback—this was about Flint's coursework?

Percy must have taken her surprise for reticence, because he said, "I know it goes against the Slytherin honor code to rat out a fellow snake. I understand that you don't want to say anything that might get one of your housemates in trouble, but…Rigel, it's important."

"Why?" she asked faintly, both to stall and because she was genuinely confused as to why Percy seemed so worked up over this. Even if Flint's deception had finally been uncovered by the professors, what did Percy care?

Percy clenched a fist and looked incredibly angry for a split second before his face smoothed out once more and he blew out a hard sigh, "They think I'm doing it."

"What?" Rigel couldn't stop the complete disbelief that crossed her face at that. Percy? He should be the very last person anyone suspected of anything even remotely underhanded. "They think you're—um, what, exactly? Tampering with assignments?"

"Cheating," Percy spat the work like it was filthy, "The professors think someone's been doing Flint's work for him. He turned in the assignments he missed on Monday, and considering he'd only had Sunday to complete them…well, you can see why they're suspicious. Since I was the one who was in charge of collecting them, I'm at the top of the suspect list."

"That doesn't make any sense," Rigel said, more than a bit upset at the idea that Percy might get in trouble for something she'd done, "Anyone in Flint's classes would know what his assignments were, and you don't have any reason to help someone else cheat."

"That's what I said," Percy fumed, "I would never condone such a thing. McGonagall said they couldn't ignore it any longer, though. She said Flint's assignments sometimes seem a little too similar to mine, but how can that be my fault? I'm not even in most of Flint's classes with him."

Rigel felt the burn of guilt crawling up her throat, "They can't do anything—I mean, you won't really be in trouble without some kind of proof, right?"

"I don't know," Percy said grimly, "If they take it to the school board and they decide to launch an official inquiry…well, even if I'm cleared that kind of blemish stays on a person's record. I have to clear my name, Rigel. Please, if you know anything…"

"I…" Rigel trailed off. She wished, not unironically, that she had more time to make this decision. What should she do? If she told Percy she was the one doing the assignments, she and Flint would probably both be expelled. Flint would no longer be obligated to keep her secret, as the oath would be broken on her end. Flint might go to the authorities and have her arrested for blood-impersonation in revenge. Archie could get dragged into it, too, and their parents would of course fall under suspicion as well…

"No one's going to hire a barrister they think is dishonest," Percy pressed.

She hated that his blatant guilt-trip was working so effectively. She did have a responsibility to fix this. Should she confess? Was there another way to solve the problem? She hated making decisions under pressure, but Percy would only become more suspicious the longer she waited. It was almost unbelievable that he didn't already suspect her, since she was the one he'd been sharing his understanding of Transfigurations with. Likely he had made the connection and dismissed it, she thought with yet another stab of guilt. Percy wasn't the type to think the worst of his friends.

"I didn't see anything that night," she said at last, "But…I'll put my ear to the ground in the Slytherin common room."

She could see the disappointment on his face, but he nodded wearily, "I understand. It was a long shot, but…I had to try. This is my future, Rigel."

"We'll find whoever it is," Rigel said firmly, "I promise, Percy, you won't be blamed for this if I have anything to say about it."

Percy summoned up a grateful smile, though she could see he wasn't convinced that she could do anything.

"I'll let you know as soon as I hear something," Rigel said, as earnestly as she could with guilt eating her up inside. She had to fix this, but she didn't know how…yet. "How long do you think the professors will wait before doing something?"

"Friday is the start-of-term staff meeting for the Heads of Houses," Percy said morosely, "I'm sure McGonagall will bring up her suspicions then."

"Three days is plenty of time to find the real culprit," Rigel said, more to reassure herself than Percy at this point, "We'll fix this. You'll see."

"I hope you're right," Percy said.

Me too, she thought with no small amount of panic.

That evening, Rigel was walking through the dungeons toward the Slytherin common room when someone stepped out of the shadows of an alcove and into her path. She hopped backwards defensively on instinct, putting a few feet between them, but relaxed when she recognized Flint's unhappy expression.

"We have a problem—" the seventh-year began.

"I know," Rigel said, quiet but firm, "I already have a solution."

She had spent an afternoon of time-folded hours since she ran into Percy going through plan after plan for how she was going to deal with this disaster. She was still fine-tuning the details, but she thought the course of action she'd decided on was going to work.

"Do tell," Flint drawled, one eyebrow raised in scornful disbelief. "Wait," he pulled out a wand and cast a muffling charm around them, "Damn corridors echo."

Rigel nodded in thanks, the began, "The only way to clear Percy's name is to—"

"What? Percy Weasley? What's he got…to…" Flint trailed off into dark chuckles, "Oh, that's rich."

"You didn't know the professors suspect him of doing your assignments?" Rigel asked, confused, "Then what did you think the problem was?"

Flint stopped laughing and scowled, "McGonagall cornered me after breakfast. Said she knows I haven't been doing my assignments and knows who had been, too. I honestly thought she might have figured it out." He gave another short laugh, "If they think it's

Weasley they're just grasping at straws."

"Well, either way we still have to do something about it," Rigel said, shaking her head to get back on track.

"No, we don't," Flint snorted, "Let them think it's Weasley. Because it's not, they'll never get proof, and it'll go away."

"Not before it ruins Percy's good name," Rigel protested, "I can't let someone else get in trouble for what I did."

"I can," Flint said, starting to turn away.

Rigel darted forward and caught his arm, "Flint, we are going to fix this."

Flint's expression was positively menacing as he turned his gaze slowly toward her hand on his arm. She released him, trying not to gulp, but kept her expression stubborn.

"If we confess, not only will we both be kicked out," Flint growled, "But your prettily-worded oath of silence will no longer be enforceable. Are you ready to go to prison for your precious Weasley, Rigel?"

He said her name tauntingly, but she only gritted her teeth before lifting her chin and saying, "That outcome presumes quite a bit. It assumes you would turn me in after everything—"

"I would."

"And that I'm even talking about implicating us in the first place," Rigel finished, flashing her eyes in aggravation, "Just listen for a second, will you?"

Flint adopted an incredibly insolent expression that Rigel was sure drove his professors up the wall, but he did fold his arms expectantly.

"There's a way to clear Percy's name and protect ourselves and avoid throwing anyone else into suspicion," she added when he looked ready to interject, "All we have to do is show the professors they're wrong about you cheating in the first place."

"But they're not wrong," Flint said, rolling his eyes, "They'll never believe it."

"They'll have to, when they see it for themselves," Rigel said, smiling slyly.

"First of all—they won't believe I've been doing my own assignments just because I start doing them now where they can see," Flint said, "And second—the point of this is that I don't do my own assignments."

"You won't have to," Rigel said, still smiling a bit. It really was a brilliant plan. "The professors are going to decide what to do about this situation on Friday evening, so Friday in your Transfiguration class you have to prove to McGonagall that you were the one doing all those assignments. I'll get ahold of the assignment she's going to give out that day, complete it, then give it to you before class. You pretend like you're working on it during class, then hand it in when the bell rings. When McGonagall reads it she'll have no choice but to think you are capable of working incredibly fast and accurately, thus supporting the idea that you completed a week's worth of make-up assignments on Sunday afternoon alone."

Flint mulled this over for a moment, "It'll be in the writing-style my other assignments were, too, since you'll be the one completing the assignment. It might stretch the imagination that I could finish an assignment in the last fifteen minutes of class, but that's the point, isn't it?"

Rigel nodded. She had been relying on McGonagall's practice of giving the students free time at the end of class to ask questions and work on individual projects and assignments being the same for the upper years as it was for Rigel's class. Relieved that this was the case, Rigel tilted her head, "So? Will you do it? It will get McGonagall and the other professors off your back for good, if it works."

"One problem," Flint said, "How are you going to get the assignment before my class? McGonagall gives different prompts to different sections, precisely so someone can't get the assignment from an earlier section and think it's okay to skip their own class. The Hufflepuff-Ravenclaw class on Thursday won't have the same work, even if the lesson is the same."

Rigel smiled unconcernedly, "Let me worry about that. Just meet me in the corridor parallel to the Transfiguration classroom five minutes before your class on Friday. I'll do the rest."

"If you get caught breaking into McGonagall's office…" Flint didn't seem convinced that she could pull this off.

"I just wanted to peek at her grade book and see how Draco was doing in class," Rigel said, widening her eyes innocently and biting a corner of her lip in chagrin, "He's been distant lately—I'm worried he's struggling but afraid to ask for help."

Flint grimaced, "You're gonna make me sick."

"I'm going to make you innocent," Rigel corrected, falling back into a serious expression, "If we're agreed, that is?"

"No wax off my broom," Flint shrugged one shoulder sharply, cracking his neck in the process. Rigel took that as eager agreement.

"See you Friday, then," Rigel said, moving past the older boy toward the common room. She had a lot to do in the next two days, but she wasn't as worried as she could have been. Problems didn't seem so difficult to solve, when you had a near-infinite amount of time in which to solve them.

On Thursday they faced the boggart again. Remus had been coaching them through various fear-managing strategies in the last couple of classes, and even his biggest doubters had to admit his methods were effective.

Rigel herself could see marked improvement in her mind's ability to process information and react appropriately under psychological stress. Each time she faced the boggart, she felt a little less afraid, less prone to giving credence to the insidious fears the creature reflected back at her. It was almost a form of therapy, in addition to being a good defense-related self-learning experience, and Rigel wondered where on earth Remus had come up with the idea.

The only one who didn't seem to be doing any better against the boggart was Draco. He still came out from behind the screen pale and extremely shaky after his third experience with the dark creature. While most of their classmates seemed drained but stable after the first couple times, Draco looked increasingly haggard, strained, and upset after each occurrence.

Rigel wanted to ask what was upsetting her friend so much, and she could tell Pansy, who was just as good if not better at seeing behind Draco's stoic masks, wished she could say something as well, but they both kept silent. There was an unspoken rule amongst their Defense class that no one asked what someone else's fear was, and Rigel and Pansy both knew their friend would be too proud to give voice to his weakness, in any case.

When it was Draco's turn to go behind the screen once more, they watched him go in silent concern.

When he reemerged, Rigel could only wish they hadn't stayed silent, because Draco looked very close to having a mental breakdown. There were too many curious eyes on their friend, whose trembling was easily visible despite his attempts to clench his fists against the shivers, so Rigel didn't dare do anything comforting, even though she really wanted to put an arm around her friend's shoulders and pull him along to the Hospital Wing.

Pansy pressed a bar of chocolate into Draco's hand, eventually convincing him without words to unclench it and take a bite of the sweet mechanically. As he chewed, they positioned themselves around him in such a way as to block most of their classmates' stares, patiently waiting for Draco to come back to himself.

It took too long for comfort, but eventually Draco gathered himself enough to say, "If that thing is on the final exam—" he cut himself off abruptly with a shudder that looked like it had forced its way down his spine. After a frustrated breath, he said, "Bugger this class," and stalked toward to exit without another word.

Rigel and Pansy stared after him, then looked at one another in united helplessness.

"I suppose he would prefer to be alone," Pansy said quietly.

Rigel nodded shortly, a frown pinching her brow, "I wish—"

She didn't bother finishing that thought aloud, because Pansy knew very well what Rigel wished. She could see that her kind-hearted friend wished it too. It didn't matter though. There was nothing they could do for Draco until he allowed them to help. Until then, they would do what they could from afar. Neither had to tell the other that what they could do wasn't nearly enough.

On Friday morning, the time until Flint's Transfiguration class crawled. She went through her Magical Theory and Herbology classes first, then turned back to attend her Healing lesson with Madam Pomfrey, and finally turned back a third time to slip into the Transfiguration classroom fifteen minutes before Flint's lesson was scheduled to start. She had her invisibility cloak wrapped around her, and she found a spot at the back of the classroom well away from the student desks where she could stand, unnoticed, for the entirety of the lesson.

Her plan was simple, but somewhat elegant, even if she said so herself.

She'd wait through Flint's class until McGonagall handed out the assignment, copy it down discretely, sneak into the Library to finish working on it, then time-turn back to the beginning of the class and hand the completed assignment to Flint to turn in before the class was over.

She anticipated a boring couple of hours of standing still and breathing quietly, but when McGonagall started lecturing Rigel found herself unexpectedly drawn into the lesson. It was so interesting to hear advanced transfigurations theory from a real professor like McGonagall. Percy's second-hand explanations were sometimes hard to follow, and he didn't exactly have a way with words. The actual lecture was fascinating and the examples McGonagall used to illustrate her point were incredible detailed.

She hadn't realized how much Percy was leaving out of their study-sessions. Had he been dumbing it down for her? She grumbled a bit internally, but then decided she couldn't be too offended—she had been only a first year when he started tutoring her.

Seeing the actual transfiguration performed was exciting, too, she discovered. Most of the time Percy was reluctant to practice magic outside of class, and so Rigel never got to see the magic she was researching. By the end of the lesson Rigel found she had a much better grasp of the topic than she usually did with NEWT-level transfigurations.

Maybe I should sneak into seventh-year classes more often, shethought with a small amount of humor.

That amusement vanished when she caught Percy giving Flint a cold state from across the classroom as McGonagall went around to monitor the students' attempts to duplicate the practical portion of the lesson. Rigel sobered at the reminder of why she was there in the first place, and guiltily tried not to enjoy the rest of the lesson too much.

When McGonagall wrote out the assignment on the board, Rigel hurriedly copied it down onto a small piece of parchment she'd stuffed in her pocket.

She tried not to pay too much attention to what Flint was doing in class, aware that she was skirting the line of how much people with time-turners were supposed interact with their past selves, but she couldn't help but notice when the Slytherin Quidditch captain pulled out his wand and put it to a roll of parchment on his desk. He held it there for a good ten minutes, moving it over the page as though casting a spell on the rolled-up scroll.

Near the end of class, McGonagall got around to Flint's desk and looked down at him disapprovingly as he casually tucked the rolled-up scroll into his book bag.

"And what are you working on, Mr. Flint?" she asked tersely.

Flint shrugged insolently, "The assignment, Professor."

At McGonagall's openly skeptical expression, Flint scowled as though offended and jerked his hand into his book bag once more, emerging with a scroll clenched in his fist.

"In fact, you can have it now, Professor McGonagall," Flint sneered, dropping the scroll, which Rigel would bet anything was a different scroll from the one he'd been 'spelling,' onto the desk in front of him.

With several classmates, including Percy, curiously looking on, McGonagall picked up the scroll and opened it, then scanned it quickly. She narrowed her eyes, unrolled it further, then a little more, seeming more and more confused the further the scroll unrolled.

"What is this, Mr. Flint?" she said at last, brandishing the scroll.

"The assignment, Professor," Flint repeated slowly, as though talking to someone dimwitted.

"You could not have written this so quickly," she said sharply.

"I didn't write it," Flint said dismissively, "I dictated it mentally. It's faster than writing it out by hand."

He was laying it on a bit thick, Rigel thought, but it probably suited Flint's personality to openly taunt a teacher in such a way.

"What spell did you use?" McGonagall demanded.

"The Psychic Transcription Charm," Flint said, "It's not against the rules to transcribe one's homework, is it?"

McGonagall looked fit to be tied as she managed a, "Not yet, Mr. Flint," and stalked back to her desk.

Rigel had time to see Percy's completely flummoxed expression before class was dismissed and the seventh years filed out of the classroom.

Rigel snuck out once McGonagall had left, making a beeline for the Library. She had what appeared to be a rather long essay to write before she could time-turn back and join her friends for lunch.

The essay took her three hours to research and write. It wasn't as difficult as Flint's Transfiguration essays usually were, since the lecture McGonagall had unwittingly given her had been very informative, but she spent extra time making sure it was absolutely faultless. Feeling a bit mischievous, she even quoted McGonagall's exact words from one part of the lesson for good measure.

Good luck disputing this, she thought, allowing a satisfied smile to slip onto her face, though no one could see it underneath the invisibility cloak.

She turned back to ten in the morning and waited for Flint in the corridor next to the Transfiguration classroom. At exactly five minutes till ten, Flint strolled casually around the corner. Rigel handed him the rolled-up assignment, saying, "Don't forget the handwriting charm."

Flint snorted, but took out his wand to perform the charm anyway, "This better work."

"It will," she said, and her confidence wasn't even bravado—she'd seen it work, after all.

"This is long," he frowned, unrolling it to have a look, "She's never going to believe I physically wrote this in ten minutes."

Rigel paused, then said, "Pretend to use the Psychic Transcription Charm."

Flint raised an eyebrow, "How do you even know about that spell?"

"I looked it up in the Library this morning," she said. She firmly told herself that she would be time-turning back to earlier that morning yet again and looking up the charm technically before she told Flint about it temporally. That way it wouldn't be a lie, and she could stop feeling like she'd caused a time-paradox accidently. The whole situation was really starting to freak her out, and she was trying not to think about what would have happened if she didn't tell Flint to use the charm that she'd witnessed him pretending to use later…she barely suppressed a shudder.

Flint narrowed his eyes at her, "And you're sure this is the topic she'll assign?"

"Absolutely," Rigel said. She realized that sounded a bit too sure, so she added, "If not, I'll think of something else."

The older boy looked skeptical, but put the scroll in his bag nonetheless, "All this for a Weasley."

Rigel allowed herself a cynical smile, "Don't kid yourself, Flint. I'm doing this for myself. If all I wanted to do was protect Percy, I'd turn the both of us in. Lucky for you, I'm completely selfish."

She wondered silently whether she'd always been such a ruthless person, or if the more she sacrificed for her ambition the harder she'd become. She was afraid that the further she took this charade, the less willing she would be to throw it all away, even if someone else got hurt along the way. How would she know when to cut her losses? At what point would it be too late to turn back?

"You're not completely selfish," Flint said gruffly, "Or you'd let Weasley take the fall to protect yourself. Just because you don't recklessly sacrifice yourself for another doesn't mean you're evil; it means you're smart. You found a way for everyone to win."

Rigel thought that sounded like an excuse to do the wrong thing, but all she said was, "You should be getting to class."

Flint gave her a long look, but eventually turned and did just that.

When Rigel was sure he'd gone, she took out her cloak and grasped her time-turner once more. She mentally checked to make sure she wasn't pushing the limits, but if she went back one last time to look up the Psychic Transcription Charm there would still only be four versions of her at one time. Her last thought before the whirl of time whisked her away was that if things like this kept coming up she'd be aging a lot faster than Snape had anticipated. Luckily, the Modified Polyjuice meant that no one would notice a thing.

It had been a very satisfying week for Severus Snape. One of his more talented sixth years had caught the eye of a notable Australian Potions Master over the summer and Severus had taken great pleasure in drafting a suitable letter of recommendation for his apprenticeship. Not a single Slytherin had been given detention, and several miscreant Gryffindors had unwittingly volunteered to clean all of his cauldrons on Thursday evening, leaving him free to complete all of the week's marking ahead of schedule.

He was looking forward to a guilt-free evening of quiet solitude before a weekend of lesson preparation and inventory stocking, and the only thing standing in the way of that was the dreaded Heads of House meeting on this third Friday in September.

As he made his way to the staff room, he wondered what drivel his colleagues would bring to the table this year. No doubt Flint's mysteriously efficient method of assignment completion would be brought to the fore yet again. Minerva had been hinting all week that she was rearing to finally do something about the situation, but Severus was skeptical that she would establish the proof necessary to see it so. Severus was of the opinion that the situation didn't warrant interference—Flint was graduating this spring, so the problem would resolve itself before long. Whoever was doing Flint's assignments probably benefitted from the extra studying more than Flint would, in any case.

Pomona greeted him cheerfully as he claimed his preferred chair; Severus summoned an appropriately disinterested response, wary of tempting his loquacious coworker into attempting to start a conversation. He knew from long experience that the Head of Hufflepuff would take any politeness as friendly encouragement.

Dumbledore arrived before long, and the meeting commenced with a discussion of the newest additions to the staff.

"I had a few distraught reports the first week of classes," Pomona said hesitantly, "But recently favor for the new Defense professor has been on the rise."

"The boggart was an inspired idea," Filius said, smiling approvingly, "I've already seen an increase in confidence among a few of my more timid Ravenclaws."

Severus sneered, "Traumatize the students to make them stronger—why ever hadn't we thought of such methods sooner?"

"They haven't been traumatized, Severus," Minerva shook her head, "Overcoming one's fears is an excellent lesson for any child to learn."

Any child that could overcome one's fears, Severus thought darkly. And for those who couldn't, those children whose fears were too dark or upsetting for them to handle? Their psychological upset was worth the boost of confidence in their peers, apparently. The number of Calming Draughts the Hospital Wing had gone through in the first week alone…Severus scowled. How like a Gryffindor to encourage the strong and forget the unable.

"Mr. Pettigrew seems to be fairing well with his classes as well," Pomona said tentatively, "I wouldn't have guessed his interest in educating, but I peeked over at one of his lessons while I was tending the outdoor gardens, and I have to say he certainly had good control over the lyrebirds he was showing them."

Severus had no interest in the ex-Marauder's teaching ability. He kept one ear half-trained on the conversation while the rest of his attention went to listing the ingredients his personal lab was running low on. Eventually, the meeting moved back to a topic he had vested interest in. To his surprise, it wasn't Minerva who brought up Marcus Flint, but Filius.

"No idea how he did it, but he turned in the assignment first thing Monday morning!" the diminutive professor exclaimed, "I saw him myself on the Quidditch pitch Sunday morning, and Pomona says he turned in her assignments on Monday as well. Even if he is having another student do his work, they'd have to have been in the Library all day. I asked Madam Pince if she saw anyone, but—"

"Don't bother," Minerva said wearily.

Even Severus couldn't help but raise an eyebrow at her.

"I know how he's been doing it," the Gryffindor Head said, her mouth twisting bitterly, "He all but flaunted his method during class this morning."

"It was not another student, then?" Dumbledore asked, looking intrigued.

"No, assuredly not," McGonagall said, sounding more than a little bitter.

Severus felt suspicion stir in his mind. Flint would not be ostentatious with his methods unless it gained him something. "Unusually accommodating of Flint to show you his method, Minerva. Did you accuse my student of something without proof?"

Minerva flinched, but said stoutly, "I thought I had proof. Percy Weasley was charged with collecting Flint's homework assignments while he was in the Hospital Wing, and then the assignments were turned in complete Monday morning—no one else had access to those assignments. I even changed the Transfiguration prompt so that it differed from the one his section received."

"You set him up?" Severus could not believe what he was hearing. She'd arranged for Weasley to pick up Flint's assignments as a test.

"Gryffindor or not, the rules are very clear," McGonagall said, "It was the only way to know Mr. Weasley's guilt or innocence for certain and resolve this problem once and for all."

"Except it failed," Severus said, smirking just to provoke her, "You somehow interpreted the results as a false positive and implicated your own student just to get at mine."

"I was not trying to 'get at' Mr. Flint," Minerva protested, "I was merely—"

"Did you tell Mr. Weasley you suspected him?" Severus was being cruel, now, but Minerva deserved to be reprimanded in this case, "Did you give him a chance to defend himself?"

The Gryffindor Head of House pressed her lips together, which was all the answer Severus needed.

"Was he terribly shocked and hurt that his Head of House would accuse him of such a thing?" he asked silkily, "I do hope you apologized—to both our students."

"Of course I did," Minerva said stiffly, "I can admit when I'm wrong." The unspoken unlike some people did not go unnoticed.

"How is he doing it, then?" Filius asked, bursting with curiosity as usual.

"The Psychic Transcription Charm," Minerva said.

"That's very advanced," Pomona frowned, "It takes incredible mental agility to dictate a coherent stream of thought at a fast enough pace for the charm to be useful."

"It explains everything, though!" Filius beamed, "The style would obviously be different from Flint's actual writing style, as most people formulate their thoughts differently from how they'd speak or write. It would be phenomenally quicker than writing an assignment by hand, as well. His assignments are so well-informed, though…I knew he was hiding a brilliant mind, but this is far beyond my expectations."

Severus quite agreed. If Flint were really using that transcription spell to complete his assignments, he'd happily eat bat wings. The very fact that Flint had 'proven' his innocence so conveniently on the eve of his indictment meant he'd merely found a way to cover his tracks.

Minerva spotted the amusement on his face, for she said, "I know what you're thinking, Severus, but it wasn't a trick. I saw him do it, not ten minutes after I'd given the assignment. It wasn't the same assignment as the earlier section, and it wasn't vaguely-worded as though he'd guessed at the topic ahead of time. He quoted something I'd said in class an hour earlier, for Merlin's sake."

Severus could not help the curl of amusement he felt at the older woman's disgruntled expression. He didn't know how Flint had managed that, but for the boy's sake Severus was pleased it had his colleagues convinced to let the problem go at last.

"All's well that ends well," Dumbledore said, smiling benignly, "And speaking of students who surpass expectations, what has become of young Mr. Black?"

Severus wondered if there would be a staff meeting in the next four years that did not bring up the enigmatic Rigel Black.

"He seems distracted," Filius commented, "While the practical work used to come seemingly effortlessly, now he struggles as the other students do to learn a new spell, casting many times without success before succeeding."

"Coursework is significantly more difficult for third years as they start OWL preparation," Minerva said, "I'm sure Mr. Black is simply falling into the normal learning curve at last."

Severus frowned. Nothing about Rigel should be considered 'normal.' The boy had more magic than he knew what to do with, a problem that should only have exacerbated after his core fully matured. He'd expected to hear reports of uncontrolled spellwork, violent accidental magic, and more in response to the boy's awakened core. To hear that he'd somehow managed to become average over the summer disturbed him far more than hearing that the boy had accidently blown something up ever could have.

The Headmaster, too, seemed concerned, "I tested his output coefficient during our lessons this week and found him at a 4.2, much higher than I expected, considering how powerful I assumed him to be. Is it possible we misjudged his potential two years ago?"

Severus shook his head sharply, "At the end of last term the boy was capable of imbuing four Aconite Alleviations in a row. That was several months before his core would have fully matured. He has the magic. That it is neither uncontrolled nor manifesting under scrutiny is…surprising."

"Are you suggesting he fooled the calibrating device?" Pomona asked carefully.

"If he has, it will be obvious when we begin Alchemy in earnest—it would take an incredible amount of control to be able to maintain the same average rate of expenditure artificially," Albus said, characteristically reasonable, "Mr. Black has above average control, as we have seen, but it takes more than natural skill to be able to measure one's own power consistently."

"Perhaps we are jumping at shadows," Filius suggested, "It may be the child's core simply settled later than most. If his core was unstable, its maturation could have stabilized his magic, rather than upsetting it. There have been cases of such happening before."

Severus resisted the impulse to roll his eyes. In magically incompetent children, the maturation of the core sometimes had an equalizing effect, but Rigel's core was not unstable—it was powerful. The boy's unconscious suppression of his core was what made it unstable. There was something else going on, and the next time he saw his most troublesome student he would figure out what it was. Then he would put a stop to it.

Chapter 7

Archie had never really considered blue to be his color. He'd been told many-a-time that he looked dashing in shades of red and positively shone in golden hues, but as Sirius had been the one telling him this it was no wonder that he'd never realized how blue brought out the silver in his eyes until he'd begun donning the career tract robes at AIM. They swished around him as he walked, as though teased by an invisible breeze.

Hermione often said the cut of their school robes was ridiculous, usually while huffily stumbling over the extra fabric at the bottom, and Archie hummed agreeably, not sure his friend would appreciate a lecture on traditional wizarding fashion, nor lessons in how to make the fabric flair appropriately while walking. It was a shame, though, for Archie suspected Hermione would be utterly intimidating with the right kind of strut.

He was contemplatively comparing their respective strides as they walked through the halls toward the cafeteria for an afternoon snack, but before he could decide if Hermione was more of a lilting gait or a careless stroll, an oily hand came down on his shoulder from behind.

"Mr. Potter, a word, if you aren't currently engaged?"

Archie stifled a groan at the too-familiar voice. The last person he wanted to give a word to was Master Tallum, head potioneer at AIM. His expression when he turned to face the venerable man was, however, entirely expectant, "Yes, sir? Is it about my last homework assignment? Cause I know it was a little off topic, but you have to admit the question of whether hummingflies are sentient is more important than how their wings can be used in cough syrups. I mean, imagine the implications—"

"Er, no," Tallum cleared his throat in a clumsy ad hoc conversational maneuver that Archie had been trained out of before he was five, "Actually I was hoping you'd come by my office this week to answer a few questions about your internship this summer. I just received the newsletter with the summer's research reports in it, and I must say I was surprised to see 'Harry Potter' in the by-line! The English Guild is notoriously picky in its interns, you know."

"Oh, are they?" Archie struggled to keep a relaxed expression on his face. Harry had gone over her work with him, but he wasn't sure he could answer detailed questions from a Potions Master about it.

"Yes, indeed! To think such talent lay under my very nose—why aren't you in the Potions Mastery tract, young man?" Tallum demanded.

"I want to be a Healer," Archie shrugged apologetically, "I love potions, but I want to use my talent in the field to come up with cures to rare illnesses. I took the internship in part because it was such a rare opportunity and in part to compensate for not being able to join the Potions tract here at AIM."

"Your research at the English Guild doesn't seem to be closely related to Healing Potions," Tallum frowned.

"I knew I wasn't ready to pursue anything so complex, especially in the short time-frame," Archie said, definitely reaching now, "So I chose a topic that I thought the Guild would be interested in, since they were funding my research."

"I see," Tallum still looked mildly confused.

"I'm a little busy this week," Archie invented suddenly, "But what if I give you my notes from this summer? I'll have to find them, but they should be able to explain things in much better detail than we could go over in a conversation. I'm really terrible at oral explanations, anyway." He rubbed his neck sheepishly, and was pleased to see Tallum looking giving him an appeased nod.

"See that you do," the older man said, "The possibilities are certainly intriguing…"

He strode off down the hallway, and when Archie made to take up walking again Hermione stayed him with a firm hand on his arm.

"What's going on, Harry?" she asked, her hair bouncing a bit as she tilted her head expectantly.

"What ever could you mean?" Archie smiled, attempting to diffuse the tense atmosphere.

"You are exceptionally good at oral explanations," Hermione said, her voice more accusing than complementary, "And we certainly aren't all that busy this week."

"I could have other stuff to…" he trailed off with a sigh at her disbelieving expression. He wondered what Hermione would say if she did know just how many side-projects he worked on when he was 'goofing off in his room all weekend.' There was one project in particular that was taking a huge amount of his time and energy to work through, but he knew his friend wouldn't believe that—he'd cultivated his care-free personality so effectively, after all. Instead, he said, "I just didn't want to talk about my internship with Master Tallum."

"You've been avoiding the subject with me, too," Hermione said, frowning, "You were so excited about the internship last term, and I even ordered that edition of the English Guild's periodical so I could read your work, but whenever I ask you to explain what you meant by most of it you brush me off. Are you getting it copyrighted first, or something?"

Archie shook his head, a bit taken aback by Hermione's persistence. "I just…" he affected a pouty expression, "I don't like all the attention. It was just a bit of fun! I thought I could do some off-beat experimenting over the summer, just to keep me busy; I had no idea everyone would take it so seriously!"

"It seemed like important work, though," Hermione said, brow still furrowed, "How can you not be proud of something you spent so much energy on? I'd be glad if people were paying attention to something I'd done—how many thirteen-year-olds can say they've made an academic breakthrough in any field?"

Archie shuffled uncomfortably, "I don't like people having such high expectations of me, especially since if I decide to get a Potions Mastery I'll use it for Healing, not this kind of methodology research."

Hermione hesitated, but eventually said, "I understand that you want to have control of your career, but at some point you might have to weigh your right to follow your dreams against the responsibility you have to natural talent. If a musical genius decided he'd rather become a mediocre anthropologist than a peerless composer, it's his right, but…is it really for the best?"

Archie could not stand one more second of Hermione's melancholy expression, so he clapped a hand over his heart in a heavy swoon, "Are you calling me a mediocre Healer?! I'll have you recall we tied in the last Craniofacial Alterations exam."

"Of course not!" Hermione looked absolutely appalled—for half a second. Then her sharp brown eyes caught his playful grin and she blew out the incensed breath she'd sucked in with an exasperated eye-roll, "You know I respect your Healing ability," she said, "Why can't you take anything seriously, Harry?"

"Because I have you to do that for me," Archie smiled, taking Hermione's hand and leading her toward the mess hall once more. He was a little disappointed to notice that Hermione hardly blushed at all—it was becoming much more difficult to tease her as their friendship progressed. Clearly he'd have to become even more charming somehow.

The afternoon found Archie and Hermione underneath their favorite tree, both enjoying the silence of the other's company while they each read whichever textbook they were currently engrossed in. For Archie, it was actually a medical periodical from the late eighties. He'd finished his schoolwork for the week and while he should probably be catching up on the syllabi Harry had sent over for the new semester, he was dreading the thought of it. Harry was taking Magical Theory, Arithmancy, and Ancient Runes this year, on top of the usual subjects, and her potions work was getting even more advanced, apparently. He didn't know how he was going to keep up, seeing as he had extra electives starting this term as well. Harry didn't seem worried about the extra work, but she never worried about anything, as far as he could tell.

So he was putting off the overwhelmed feeling he just knew was creeping up on him by relaxing. At least, he was until a page dressed in the school colors came jogging over to them. He wondered if he'd forgotten to return a library book, until he caught sight of the patch on the front of the boy's robes that signified the wearer worked in the owlrey. The boy produced a letter from a messenger bag over his shoulder and said, "Potter, right?"

Archie nodded, standing up to take the letter with a smile and a quick, "Thanks."

Harriett Potter was written in fancy script on the outside of the envelope. When Archie had first arrived, the poor professors had all been terribly confused as to why he had shown up when they were expecting a girl called Harriett Potter. He set them straight quick enough, and now the majority of the staff and students were laboring under the impression that his parents had a very poor sense of humor.

"Is your father still addressing your letters as if you're a girl?" Hermione said, her eyes narrowed in indignation on his behalf as he sat back down beside her.

"It's still pretty funny," Archie said, shrugging, "And he's not one to let go of a joke until it's breathed its last."

"It's a wonder you didn't turn out worse," Hermione sniffed. After a moment, she sent him an apologetic glance, "I mean, I'm sure your relatives mean well. Not that I've ever met them. Am I ever going to meet them?"

Archie pretended to think about that for all of three seconds, "Sure. Someday."

Hermione sighed, "I don't know why you're so reluctant. I'm perfectly nice."

"It's not you, 'Mione," Archie laughed, "I don't want to expose your ethereal self to the plebeians that make up my beloved family, that's all."

"They can't be that bad," Hermione said, a smile tugging at her mouth, "You said your father was an Auror, for goodness sake. And your mother's a researcher for a very private company, right?"

"And yet they still address my letters to 'Harriett,'" Archie said.

"Yes, well," Hermione frowned down at her book, deflated. "You've met my parents," she tried.

"And now I know from whence your loveliness springs," Archie said automatically, distracted by the letter he was unfolding. As he glanced down at the signature he couldn't help but blanche in surprise. Quickly, he tucked the letter back into it envelope and stowed it in the pages of his periodical with a movement he knew was less than casual, but couldn't help.

"What is it?" Hermione, observant as ever, asked, "Bad news?"

"Sort of," Archie shrugged uncomfortably, "Nothing too important, though."

Seeing that he would say no more, Hermione went back to her book, but not before saying, "You've been holding a lot of things back, lately."

Archie wasn't sure how to respond to that. He had been, after all. He just wished Hermione could understand that it was for her own good that he did.

The letter burned at the back of his mind. Why would the British Ministry of Magic send Harry a letter? Did they know? Were they coming for them? Was he going to be detained and Harry shipped off to Azkaban? He calmed himself with deep, slow breaths, only the knowledge that surely James would have sent a warning if Harry was in trouble with the government keeping him from tearing the letter open right there, Hermione's curiosity be damned.

When he got a moment to himself later that afternoon he ripped into it with shaking hands. His heartbeat slowed nominally when he saw that it was from the Department of Mysteries, not the Department of Magical Law Enforcement, but only enough that he could hear his own frantic thoughts over its pounding.

Harry, what have you done?

In the aftermath of clearing Percy's name and settling the question of Flint's assignments in the professors' minds once and for all, Rigel couldn't help but let her guard down the tiniest bit, thinking that surely she'd solved all foreseeable problems for the time being.

That was when the letter, addressed in screaming red ink, came from AIM. She froze only an instant before collecting herself enough to detach it from the owl and stow it in her book bag.

"News from home?" Pansy asked, face slightly eager. Ever since Lily had sent Rigel a picture of little Addy gurgling happily in her pram, Pansy had kept a curious eye on Rigel's post, clearly hoping for another picture. Rigel would have to write to her parents requesting additional prints.

For the moment, she shook her head, trying to conceal the feeling of dread the sight of the letter had given her. Archie had only been back a month—what could have gone wrong? "It's just from Harry," she said, faking a disinterested shrug.

"What's wrong?" Draco asked from the seat beside her.

She silently cursed whatever was giving her friend his newfound perceptiveness, "I'm sure it's nothing. I just wasn't expecting to hear from her so soon. It's odd."

"So you think something's happened?" Draco frowned, "You should check—better than walking around with it hanging over your head."

Rigel shook her head, "I'll read it later. I don't want to be distracted during classes today."

"If you don't trust us not to look over your shoulder, just say so," Draco snorted, turning back to his food.

Pansy offered Rigel a sympathetic smile, "Rigel is entitled to protect his cousin's privacy—or were you not going to read over his shoulder?"

Draco glanced at Rigel sidelong, "Of course I was. If Rigel wants me not to, he should just say so, instead of making up an excuse."

"Rigel's too polite for that," Pansy said, seeming a bit exasperated, "And just when, exactly, did you become the rude one in our group, Draco? What is going on with you lately?"

"None of your business," Draco said, smiling slightly to soften the words, "See, Rigel? It's that easy."

Rigel and Pansy shared a long-suffering look, but Pansy dropped the subject in any case.

For Rigel's part, she was still going to wait to read Archie's letter. Even if Draco didn't read the letter itself, there was no telling what her suddenly observant friend would be able to tell from her face as she read it.

It was a Wednesday, which meant the only class she was doubled up on was Transfigurations, at which time she also had a Potions lesson with Snape. She figured she could read the letter after lunch. Whatever trouble Archie was having, it would keep until that afternoon.

The morning passed quickly, and after stopping by the kitchens for a quick snack to tide her over, Rigel turned back to ten o'clock and ghosted through the dungeons under her invisibility cloak.

Snape seemed to be perusing a publication of some kind when she arrived in their usual lab, and Rigel was surprised to note that no cauldron had been prepared for their lesson that day.

"Good morning, Professor," she said politely as she shut the door behind her, "Are we having a theoretical lesson today?"

"In a manner of speaking," Snape looked up and gestured for her to take the periodical he'd been reading.

Upon glancing at the cover, Rigel immediately recognized it as the issue of the Guild's newsletter containing her summer research. "The Guild's internship reports?" she asked, curious as to why Snape would bring them to her attention.

"What do you know about this 'shaped imbuing' your…cousin claims to have come up with?" Snape asked, eyeing her shrewdly.

"Just what she's told me," Rigel shrugged, "It's a bit difficult to explain, I gather, though she said she did her best in the word limit the Guild allowed her."

"It is intriguing," Snape said, not seeming terribly pleased at the words leaving his mouth, "Such an expansion of the field bears looking into." Rigel looked up, hardly daring to believe her ears. "If I were to undertake such research, however, I would need much more detailed information on the subject."

Rigel tried very hard not to let the giddy feeling of flattered disbelief show on her face. Master Snape wanted to expand on her research for his next project? "I could ask my cousin for more extended notes on her project," Rigel said after a moment of inwardly beaming to herself, "I'm sure she'd be delighted to send you any information you need—she's an avid follower of your work, Professor."

"So you've said," he didn't seem to be able to quell his slight sneer of disbelief, "Can you recreate her methodology?"

Rigel grimaced, "No, I don't think so. It requires a level of magic manipulation I don't have the control for. I'm sure you'd be able to do it, Professor. It's based on wandless magic to hear Harry describe it."

"You have wandless capabilities as well," Snape pointed out sharply, "And unless I miss my guess the method is not unlike the potion you created for Draco's birthday last year."

Rigel carefully affected a look of slight guilt, "I, ah, may have had Harry's help with my gift that year," she tried to look sheepish, "I didn't want Draco to think I hadn't put effort into his gift, but in truth Harry helped me come up with the idea and imbue it. That's where she started developing the theory for her eventual research project, actually."

Snape's face only darkened, "If I find that you have been involved in helping your cousin plagiarize your own research, I will—"

"I haven't!" Rigel burst out, offended and appalled that Snape had jumped to that conclusion. Surely Rigel having access to some of Harry's methods hadn't been that suspicious…had it? "Sorry, Professor," she added quickly, "I just meant we haven't done anything like that. Harry's research is completely her own—she would never take that kind of help. Her integrity means a lot to her."

Snape did not look entirely convinced. After a moment of consideration, he said, "You are still passing along much of what I teach you, are you not?"

Rigel nodded carefully, hoping Snape hadn't changed his mind about being okay with that arrangement. "She'd be happy to give you credit if—"

This time Snape interrupted her, "Don't be ridiculous. It is time I met this girl, however. I want to be certain my teachings are not enabling an imbecile." At Rigel's offended look, the Potions Master smirked, "I'm afraid I cannot take your word in this case, Mr. Black. I know how biased your opinions of your own family often are."

She frowned, but inclined her head in understanding, "I could arrange a meeting next summer, then."

"What is wrong with the winter holiday?" Snape asked, brows arching, "Does your cousin not return home for Yule?"

Rigel blinked. That was a bit soon, but…she supposed she could make it work. As long as Snape didn't suggest she be there as well. There was simply no way Archie could play either Harry or Rigel convincingly around Professor Snape. His potions knowledge was good, but not that good.

"All right," Rigel said, "I'll write her about it. I'm sure she'd be honored to meet you, sir."

Snape inclined his head, only the mocking glint in his eye betraying his thoughts on her statement, "Be sure to request those notes, as well, Mr. Black. In the meantime, why don't we start on today's lesson?"

To her mild confusion, he led her across the lab to a sideboard, on which stood a cauldron full of what appeared to be an already-completed potion.

"I brewed this earlier," Snape said, so casually that Rigel immediately felt wary, "It's under a stasis charm. I want to see how your instincts are developing. When I lift the stasis charm, you will imbue whatever amount of magic you deem sufficient for its cohesion, and while you imbue you will apply your senses to the potion and determine its purpose."

Rigel grinned a bit—she did enjoy a challenge, and Snape never failed to deliver in that regard.

Linking her core to the potion was second nature by now, so the imbuing process began swiftly. It continued a little too swiftly, however, and it wasn't long before Rigel felt her brow break out in a light sweat. Whatever this potion was, it would be powerful—she could feel her core expending magic at a worrying rate. She tried to ignore the drained feeling that was beginning to set in, but it sapped her focus even as she tried to concentrate on the potion itself.

She could feel the familiar, satisfied feeling that meant all the ingredients were balanced according to their properties, but the mental 'taste' of the potion was unlike anything she'd experienced before. It definitely wasn't a love potion, as those had a distinct sense of headiness about them. It lacked the aggressiveness of a transformative potion, and she didn't think it could be any sort of externally applied potion simply because it was the wrong consistency. It looked as though it was definitely made to be drunk. As much magic as she was putting in it, the potion would have to effect some extraordinary change, as well. But what? It felt closest to some kind of healing potion, but at the same time it felt completely wrong. Dangerous.

When the potion finally felt 'full' to her extended senses, Rigel wearily withdrew the connection and caught herself on the lab bench before her knees gave out.

"What…was that?" she panted, wiping a hand across her forehead to push back her sweaty bangs.

"You tell me," Snape said, a displeased frown in his voice.

"A…healing draught?" she guessed, "For someone extremely close to death, given how much magic is involved."

"I doubt it's ever been considered a medical potion before," Snape said with dark amusement, "This brew is one of the components in raising inferi from the grave."

Rigel couldn't help but recoil from the cauldron reflexively, "Isn't it illegal?"

"I have a research brewing license," he said, "Only selling it would violate my oath. It is not my intention to instruct you in its preparation, in any case. I chose it for this exercise because I was fairly certain you would not have come across its kind before now. It is important for a brewer to be able to recognize the darker concoctions, even if he never attempts them himself."

She nodded her understanding. No wonder it had seemed so alien and wrong to her senses—it was a potion that would enact the most challenging of magic, to force re-animation where true life had already fled. It reminded her enough of Riddle Jr.'s possession of the basilisk to make her glad she wouldn't be studying the draught, no matter how interesting the theory itself would likely prove.

"I wonder that you had so much trouble with the imbuing," Snape said, voice casual once again.

"It is a powerful potion," Rigel said slowly.

"Not so much more so than Aconite Alleviation," her professor said, brows descending, "Have you been using magic excessively this morning?"

"No," Rigel said, mentally grimacing as she realized where this conversation was heading, "I…don't have as much magic as I used to."

"Explain," his tone was positively forbidding.

"I had my thirteenth birthday over the summer," she began, unsure how to explain, "So my core changed significantly."

"It doesn't work that way," Snape said, "Magic only increases with age, unless you were in a severe magical accident over the summer, and simply didn't see fit to inform your Head of House."

"Ah—no, I wasn't," Rigel said. She debated for a moment, then realized there wasn't any way to hide her lack of stamina if indeed her power levels had changed so much. "Will you keep what I tell you in confidence?" she asked, knowing it was an insulting question, but needing to make sure the knowledge that Rigel Black was magically powerful wouldn't reach anyone who knew that Archie was only moderately above average.

As expected, Snape favored her with an especially annoyed expression as he said, "You are a Slytherin." Apparently that was reassurance enough.

"My magic got out of hand after my birthday," she said, "It was completely unusable that way, so I fixed it. But now I have less magic than before."

She'd never seen someone as pale as Snape blanche before, but she didn't have time to wonder at the impossibility of such a thing before Snape was shaking her by the shoulders urgently. "What did you do?" he snarled, "You foolish boy, what kind of ritual did you attempt—"

"I didn't!" Rigel said, wondering why she was always having to protest her own innocence, but sure that she didn't want Snape thinking she'd tried to sacrifice part of her magic permanently in a dark ritual—she knew better what sorts of evil a wizard's magic could wreak once freed of his will. "I didn't get rid of it, I just…repressed it to manageable levels."

Snape's eyes narrowed to angry slits, "How?"

Rigel held back a sigh as she fingered the black gloves she wore to hide her rings from casual appraisal. If she would be keeping them as Harry, she didn't want too many people knowing what they looked like. "I found a jeweler who could make suppressors and commissioned a ring that reduces my usable magic to reasonable levels."

"Take it off," Snape said.

She frowned, "It's the only thing keeping my magic in check. I don't want to endanger either of us."

"Remove. The. Ring." Snape seemed very insistent, but Rigel had asked Binny to spell her rings irremovable for a reason.

"I won't," Rigel said, quiet but firm. "I'm sorry I won't be able to imbue as many high-level potions in a row, Professor, but this is for the best."

"You are too young to know what is best for anyone, especially yourself," Snape snapped, "You cannot become dependent on a dampener, or you will never be capable of wielding the full power of your magic."

"I know," she said, shrugging slightly, "I don't mind. I don't need that much magic." No one needs that much magic, she added silently.

"Never could I have imagined such laziness and waste would take residence in your person, Rigel Black," Snape's stare was heavy with disbelief and disgust, "You are dismissing potential that every other wizard in Britain would—and have—killed for."

"Exactly," Rigel muttered. For the first time she thought maybe it was better that she had such magic, if the alternative was that someone like Lucius Malfoy might have actually tried to use it to its fullest, most dangerous potential.

Snape turned away to pace quickly across the lab and back, and she thought she actually heard a growl in his voice as he said, "You cannot possibly expect that ignoring this problem will in any way work. Magic does not fade away when it is repressed—it grows stronger. You of all people should know that."

Rigel winced, realizing that he had a point. One of the reasons her magic had been so unwieldy first year was because of how successfully she'd repressed it as a child. Still… "It isn't the same situation," Rigel said, "I'm not relying on myself, but on an external stabilizer."

"Stabilizer?" Snape let out a vicious sneer, "It is crippling you, boy."

"It's protecting me, and everyone around me," she bristled, tired of being reprimanded for making the responsible decision regarding her magic, "You would have me selfishly grasp at the power I could wield, wrestling with it for years and years, apologizing every time it lashes out at those around me, praying it doesn't maim anyone when I get upset, just so—what? So I can say I'm the most magically powerful Potions Master to ever live? I don't care about the power. It's useless to me. I just want to brew potions, and do you know what happens when I take off my ring and try to imbue anything? It explodes in my face!"

"That's because you cannot control it yet—"

"No one can control it, Professor," Rigel said, her voice rising, "Don't you think I thought about that possibility before I decided to permanently affix a piece of powerful magic to my finger?"

"Where did you even get such a ridiculous idea?" Snape growled.

Rigel blinked, taken aback at the slightly tangential question, "My aunt Lily."

Her Professor froze, "What?"

"Aunt Lily has a bracelet that she wears for the same reason," Rigel said.

"She certainly does not," Snape sounded very sure of that.

"She does," Rigel disagreed, "She started wearing it after Harry was born, when it became clear that no matter how many years she tried to control it, her magic would always be too powerful to be safe." She hoped her mother didn't mind her telling Snape about her bracelet, but from how awkward their meeting at the hospital was last year, she didn't think she had to worry about them talking to one another ever again.

Snape was very quiet for a moment. He still looked furious, but she had the feeling some of his anger had been redirected for some reason. When he spoke again, it was quieter, if just as severe, "Your aunt is muggleborn. She does not have generations of control bred into her family line—as a pureblood you have no such disadvantage. There is no excuse for your refusal to control your magic."

Rigel could feel herself growing angrier the longer Snape dismissed her concerns and belittled her efforts to control her own life. She was tempted for a moment to give into the anger, to shout at him that he didn't understand the fear and anxiety that came with carrying a loaded weapon everywhere she went. She didn't, though. Just because she wore a suppressor didn't mean she was suddenly free to give reign to her emotions whenever she pleased. Even without the danger of a magical accident, letting her frustrations crowd her mind was a terrible habit to indulge.

So she took a deep breath, then said, "Respectfully, it is my decision to make, Professor."

"And I am to accommodate your new handicap in determining our lessons, I suppose?" he sneered. She winced, but said nothing. If Snape refused to teach her because she was less powerful, well, it would be awful, and probably mean the end of her purpose in coming to Hogwarts, but not the end of everything. The last two years hadn't been a waste, after all. Some things were still more important than her own ambitions.

At her impassive expression, Snape seemed to deflate. His face looked positively aged as he shook his head slowly, a bitter twist to his mouth. "Far be it from me to prevent you wallowing in mediocrity, Mr. Black."

"Thank you for respecting my choice, Professor," she said softly.

A snide look was the only response as Snape swept off to the cabinets and began pulling out ingredients and piling them on the counter in a brisk manner. When she cautiously joined him at one of the lab stations, he said flatly, "If you are determined to languish magically, at the least I will force your potions ability to its maximum extent."

After that, Professor Snape proceeded with the morning's lesson as though the entire incident had not occurred, aside from being slightly more demanding than usual in his instruction.

Rigel was relieved that they'd worked through the matter, though she wasn't so optimistic as to think the issue settled entirely. Likely Snape was merely waiting for an opportunity to change her mind.

Sure enough, as she packed up her things at the end of the lesson, Snape said, "I would not have expected a braggart like Sirius Black to so easily acquiesce to his son's magic being effectively sealed."

There was something in his voice that made her think he was fishing for information—did he hope to use her sense of familial duty to sway her opinion? Or was he looking for someone other than Rigel to blame for her decision? Either way, there was a chance she could use this to forestall the possible complication that was Snape's knowledge.

She looked up at Snape through her bangs, a plea that Rispah would have been proud of in her eyes, "You won't tell him, will you?"

Snape's lip curled, but something almost satisfied flashed in his eyes before he sneered, "How can he not already be aware of your foolishness?"

"My core matured in the night," Rigel said, biting a lip. "After the initial stage, the increased power didn't manifest outwardly. It only acted up when I tried using it, and since we aren't allowed to do magic over the summer I didn't try around my family, so Father didn't see any change."

"You did not go to him when you realized your magic was beyond your control?" Snape was definitely deriving some sort of pleasure from this, she thought, but she had committed to the story and would stick with it. She doubted Sirius cared either way about Snape's option of him, in any case.

"I don't need other people to solve my problems for me," she said, tilting her chin stubbornly so that she appeared as a prideful child.

"Clearly," Snape's sarcasm could not possibly bite any deeper.

"I don't," she insisted, "My family doesn't need to be bothered with things I can take care of myself." At the last bit, she allowed her lower lip to tremble ever so slightly.

It was enough to make Snape pause. A suspicious look overcame his face once more, and he asked, "Do you fear their reaction?"

Rigel swallowed, "I…no." She didn't even try to sound convincing.

"You foolish child, they would only be proud of your gifts," Snape hissed fiercely, "And enraged to see you squandering them."

"Pride only flows to a certain point before it turns to fear," Rigel said, allowing her eyes to flash, "A child who gets straight O's is something you brag about, but a child whose magic can kill with a thought? Being dangerous is not something to be proud of, Professor."

"You are wrong about that, boy, though you are too naïve to realize it yet," Snape said, "Even so, your father is many ignoble things, but afraid of powerful magic he is not. Your argument holds no water."

"Many people are not afraid of the idea of something until they are confronted with the thing itself," Rigel said darkly, "My aunt's family had no idea what magic was, but when it showed up in their daughter they learned to fear it fast enough."

"Your aunt's family are muggles," Snape said, clearly exasperated, "Ignorant about magic in every way. Of course they fear what they do not understand."

"They were people confronted with something they were supposed to love, did love, but couldn't control," Rigel returned, not realizing until she said it out loud that she believed it. Blowing out a half-hearted sigh, she added, "Wizards aren't so different from muggles when it comes to how they react to fear. My uncle Remus never talks about his father, and I don't think it's because he's dead."

In fact, she was pretty sure Remus had once said that he'd been bitten as a child in an act of revenge against his father, who had said some inflammatory things about werewolves in the presence of one Fenrir Greyback. She wasn't sure gaining a son as a werewolf had changed his opinion overmuch.

Snape did not, apparently, have anything to say to that.

Just to sink the point home, she added in a small voice, "I just don't want them to be afraid of me all the time. And I don't want to hurt any of them. My father and the other adults could protect themselves, but what about Harry? What about Addy? I have to know I'm not a danger to anyone, Professor. Being pretty sure isn't good enough, and that's all my control would amount to."

"You don't know that," Snape said after a moment, "You could benefit the world in so many ways, Rigel."

At the use of her first name, she had to blink back an awkward surge of moisture in her eyes. She hated disappointing this man, her mentor in so many ways, but pleasing him had become less important than protecting her secret. No one could know that Rigel Black had powerful magic. Snape had to agree to keep it to himself, and the best way to do that was to make him see that it didn't matter as long as she refused to use it.

"I've weighed the risks and made my decision," she said, the words coming out rushed as she hiked her bag over her shoulder and backed toward the door, "I'll see you next class, Professor. I've got—I'm late for lunch."

She left before he could point out that with the time-turner under her shirt she couldn't be late for anything.

She stopped her half-run a few corridors away, ducking into an alcove to regain a bit of her composure. Of all the people she lied to, Snape was one of the most difficult, second only to Draco in terms of the wracking amount of guilt that assaulted her gut afterwards.

To distract herself, she took out the letter from her cousin and began to read it by the meager torchlight. By the end, she felt so sick she had to sit down on the floor and pull her knees to her chest. She knew it wasn't going to be good, but a letter from the Ministry?

Archie had included the letter in his missive, and after scanning it once Rigel saw it for the politely worded demand that it was. The Department of Mysteries was intrigued by her proposed new brewing technique, and 'requested' several samples be sent to their offices by owl at her earliest convenience. She didn't know how long they would wait before reiterating their request, but considering the amount of time it took to get a letter from AIM to Hogwarts, she should probably start working on them yesterday.

In fact…a smile slowly started to spread across her face. That's exactly what she would do.

She flipped to a blank page in her notebook and wrote down the exact time and date. After a moment of thought, she scratched out the time and wrote 11:45am, so she would be sure to make it back to lunch before her friends missed her.

Then she took out her time-turner and steeled herself. She'd never turned more than a few hours at a time, but this time she wouldn't have to worry about making it to certain places at certain times. With her invisibility cloak, she would just disappear. Ignoring the little voice in her head that told her she was running from her problems, she began to turn the hourglass, spinning it and spinning it, past the twenty-four-hour mark and on and on until the world bled and she closed her eyes and fell back into reality with an odd whirring motion.

She cast the tempus charm, and was pleased to see that she had traveled exactly two days into the past. She figured she could brew the samples for the Ministry, write up all her notes on shaped imbuing for Snape, Tallum, and anyone else who requested information in the future, and still send them off to Archie before the Ministry found a reason to harass her for noncompliance.

In theory she could just mail the potions directly to the Ministry herself, but who knew what sort of tracing charms the Department of Mysteries might employ on any packages sent there. Better to have it all come from Archie, just in case.

She started toward her lab, then stopped as her stomach growled. Right, she thought, food would evidently have to come before brewing.

She turned toward the kitchens instead and slipped her cloak off just before ducking inside. It was a little past lunch time, so most of the elves were washing dishes, but Binny didn't hesitate to toss the goblet she was drying to a friend and skip over to the pantries at the sight of Rigel's embarrassed grin.

"You is being hungry already?" Binny asked in French with a little laugh, "Lunch is being not long ago."

"I'm a growing boy," Rigel said in the same language after a pause to get her tense straight.

"You is growing in the wrong direction if you isn't exercising," Binny said, and Rigel marveled at how much more natural the accented language sounded when the house elf spoke.

"I'll run all the way to class," she promised.

"You is still being late," Binny pointed out, a mock-stern expression crossing her small face briefly.

"You won't tell on me, will you?" Rigel asked, accepting the plate of chicken with only a small grimace. She was getting used to eating meat, though she doubted she'd ever enjoy the taste.

"Binny is only telling if Dumbledore is asking," there was a twinkle in the elf's big eyes that made Rigel think that was rather unlikely to happen.

She was learning words related to travel that month, so she and Binny chatted for a bit about an imaginary trip to Lithuania they would one day take, and when she'd cleared her plate, she got up to go. As she told the house elf she'd see her that night for dinner as well, Rigel stopped, realizing suddenly that she had no where to sleep that night, since her bed would be occupied by herself already.

"Binny," she said slowly, "Is there…anywhere besides the dorms I could find a bed lying around?" As far as she knew there weren't any unoccupied rooms in the dorms themselves, at least not in the Slytherin dorms, where students always spread out to fill any vacancies.

Binny blinked before saying, almost automatically, "Students isn't allowed out of the dorms after curfew."

"But if I wanted to take a nap during the day," Rigel said innocently, "In between classes, you know."

Binny fixed her with a rather suspicious look for a house elf, "You isn't getting up to any hanky-panky is you?"

Rigel could not stop the laugh that sprung from her lips, "Definitely not!" She leaned closer to Binny and said, conspiratorially, "Girls have cooties, you know."

"I isn't knowing anything about it," Binny sniffed, "And neither is you, apparently."

Rigel laughed again, "So, barring hanky-panky, is there a place students can nap?"

"There is being the Hospital Wing…" Binny said slowly, "But if you is not being sick…there is being one other place that is having beds. It isn't a place students is going."

The house elf was frowning, but it sounded like a promising place to Rigel if other people wouldn't be going there. "Are students not allowed there?" She hoped it wasn't something like the staff room.

Binny thought for a long moment before saying, "There is being no rule against it. I is showing you?"

Rigel smiled wide in relieved thanks, "If you're not too busy, I'd really appreciate it, Binny."

"Binny is never being too busy for her friends," Binny said brightly.

"I'm honored to be counted among them," Rigel said, quite sincerely.

Binny held out her hand, and Rigel took it with care. She wasn't sure, but she suspected her human muscles were much stronger proportionately to a house elf, as they used magic to augment almost everything they did.

With a noticeable crack, they teleported, and when Rigel looked around she saw an unfamiliar corridor with a painting of…dancing trolls on a nearby wall.

"Where are we?" she asked, wondering why she'd never been down this hallway before.

"Seventh floor," Binny said, "This is being the entrance to the come and go room."

"The what?" she had never heard of such a room; she was sure she'd have remembered such an odd name.

"The room where things is coming and going," Binny said earnestly, "The Room of Lost Things."

A memory sparked, and Rigel struggled to capture it, "You…told me about this room once, didn't you?"

"You is remembering!" Binny clapped her hands happily, "Yes, I is telling you the first time we is meeting. I is telling you about the place lost things go."

"So it's around here?" Rigel grinned, "Do people lose beds very often at Hogwarts?"

At the least she could curl up on a pile of old robes, she figured.

"People is losing everything at Hogwarts," Binny giggled, "You is seeing. Come."

She started walking down the corridor, but when she reached the other side of the troll tapestry she turned about and went back the way they'd came. Rigel followed her, thinking she'd gotten confused, until Binny turned around again and paced back the way they'd been going originally.

Before she could even ask what was going on, a door appeared on the opposite wall.

Aware that her mouth was slightly open, Rigel wordlessly followed Binny inside. Her first thought was that she'd never seen so much clutter before, even in the attic at Grimmauld Place. There were stacks of things everywhere, all sorts of things that Rigel could not for the life of her imagine anyone losing. Books, sure, and the occasional sock, but chandeliers? Coat racks taller than her and broomsticks that didn't even look broken and—was that a garden gnome?

"This is all stuff people have lost at Hogwarts?" she asked, slightly awed. She knew Hogwarts had been around a while, but it was one thing to know it and another to see something like this just laying about.

"Or is not wanting to be finding," Binny said, nodding so fast her ears flapped. "This room is having everything; you is only needing to ask."

"Ask the room?" she said, a bit confused, "Can it hear us?" The idea of a sentient room was a tad alarming, but not outside the realm of possibilities, given that it was Hogwarts.

"It is not hearing, but it is knowing," Binny said, frowning as she tired to explain, "You is thinking very hard, thinking thrice, and the room is finding."

"I think what I need three times?" at Binny's nod, Rigel sucked in a deep breath and 'shouted' I need a bed in her head. I need a bed I need a bed I need a—

She nearly fell over as the room transformed itself around her. The stacks of things were gone, and the room looked considerably smaller. It was completely bare, in fact, save for a single twin-sized bed that looked a lot like the one in her dorm. In fact… "Is this my pillowcase?" she touched the material carefully, "But I didn't lose it…will it be in here from now on?"

If the room worked by pulling things from elsewhere in the castle, she'd have to be careful what she asked for.

"It is not taking," Binny shook her head with a smile, "It is providing. Only things in the Room of Lost Things is staying in the come and go room forever."

It was confusing to think that there were multiple different rooms inside the same room, but Rigel told herself not to be surprised. Magic was like that, after all.

"Can it provide anything?" Rigel asked, stunned that this kind of resource was available and no one even used it.

"It isn't providing food," Binny said, looking a bit defiant, as though Rigel were considering replacing her services in the kitchen with the come and go room.

"I'll definitely see you for dinner then," Rigel said, smiling reassuringly at the elf.

Binny nodded seriously, then said, a bit sadly, "I is needed in the kitchens. I is seeing you!" She waved, curtseyed, and popped out of the room with a crack.

For one worried moment Rigel looked around in search of an exit—it would be just her luck to get trapped in a room that half the time didn't even exist. As she thought about needing to get out, however, a door appeared on the far wall.

She smiled, and it was not innocent. The door disappeared, and a few moments later the pewter cauldron she'd been imagining materialized on the floor beside her.

"This is going to be fun," she said, setting her school bag on the bed. She doubted the room could produce ingredients, as perishables likely counted as food as far as the laws of conjuring were concerned, but she had more than enough supplies for a couple days of intense brewing. She hadn't brewed straight through the night in a long time, not since coming to Hogwarts and finding so many other things to spend time learning and doing besides potions. She found herself quite looking forward to it.

Her enthusiasm lasted approximately twenty minutes, at which point she attempted to imbue the base of her Portable Protection Potion and discovered, to her utter dismay, that she couldn't shape the magic into the correct shield charm. She tried several times, and in each instance the magic slipped away from her grasp and dissipated as unshaped raw power that did nothing but give the potion an iridescent shimmer after a while.

She vanished the potion and sat down on the bed, thinking hard. With trepidation, she tried several everyday spells and found nothing overtly wrong with their execution. Puzzled, she tried more advanced charms, but they worked just fine, too. Why couldn't she imbue shaped magic? She hadn't had a problem imbuing since she started wearing the—

Oh, no. Rigel scowled down at the glove protecting the forest green suppressant ring from her glare. It had locked a good portion of her magic away, and while what was left was more than enough for everyday magic and imbuing, what if it had compromised her wandless magic capabilities as well? It wasn't something she would have anticipated, as the point of the suppressant was to increase the control she had over her power, but if wandless magic depended in part on the user's strength of magic…she had definitely shot herself in the foot.

She ran a hand through her short hair and scowled at the air. Nothing could ever be simple, could it? In donning the suppressor she regained her regular imbuing ability, but apparently sacrificed her shaped imbuing. She couldn't just remove the suppressor, because then she'd lose all control and not be able to imbue anything. And she only had a few days before the Ministry would start expecting samples and possibly investigating the delay. Imagining Archie trying to explain to British Ministry personnel why, exactly, Harriett Potter was a boy made her shudder. It would be the undoing of everything they had worked for.

What are the odds that the Ministry will accept a polite refusal? she thought morosely. Maybe she could sneak into the Library and look for books on wandless magic. Wizards without a lot of magic could learn to use it wandlessly, couldn't they? Maybe she could learn the old-fashioned way instead of relying on the power behind her core to control the magic without a wand.

As she was thinking it, a book appeared quite suddenly on the bed next to her. Unbelieving she could be so lucky, Rigel picked up the thin tome and read the faded lettering on the spine. A Treatise on the Wielding of Wandless Power, it said. She smiled grimly and whispered a "thanks" to the room at large before settling into the bed cushions and flipping to the first page.

The book was rather old, and the language antiquated, but it introduced the theory behind wandless magic in a way Rigel had never come across. The author, whose name was too faded to make out on the spine, argued that without a wand to give form and structure to magic, a wizard had to condense his magic so compactly that its shape would hold up de facto once it was released. This, the author noted, required two major factors. The first was an immensely focused will on the wizard's behalf, as his mental directions became the pressure necessary to compress the free-flowing magic of a wizard's core into a stable form. The second factor was magical power. According to the book, it took much more magic to perform a spell wandlessly than it did with a wand because the magic had to be densely packed into the shape of a spell, rather than merely flowing through the pattern created by a wand.

It was the difference, the writer explained, between making ice with a mold and making a snowball by hand. If you have a mold, you can fill it half with water and the water will naturally expand to fill the rest of the mold when it freezes. If you start with snow, however, and attempt to make the same sized ball of ice, you have to pack the snow very tightly together to get it to hold its shape, and you end up with a denser, heavier ball than the ice made with a mold. For wand magic, the wand movements provided a mold for your magic to fill and spread out in naturally. Wandless magic meant packing magic so closely that it would hold a shape without the 'walls' of a mold to keep it in place while the magic 'set.'

Rigel no longer had enough magic to pack a high-level shield charm densely enough to hold its shape without a wand to manifest through. On the other hand, if she took off her suppressant it would be akin to trying to make a snowball in the midst of an avalanche, she thought wryly.

The solution seemed to be recalibrating the suppressant band. She needed it to leave her with the same amount of magic she'd had before her thirteenth birthday. She could talk to Frein when she got back to the Lower Allies over the winter break, but what to do until then? How could she adjust the amount of magic she had access to by herself?

Unbidden, a memory of that day in Frein's shop came back to her. After expending most of her energy in measuring the strength of her core, she'd been able to brew normally for the rest of the day. She wasn't sure, but she thought she remembered making one more shaped-imbued prank-potion that afternoon for curiosity's sake. If she could expend energy fast enough, then, she would have a temporary window in which she could shaped-imbue…in theory. The trick would be in not expending too much. She wasn't sure if she even remembered how her magic felt before her birthday, but she had to try.

An idea struck her, and though she was half-afraid it was too good to work, she thought at the come and go room, I need a…magic measuring device. That was as specific as she could get, she realized, as she didn't know what it was actually called, but she pictured the device as clearly as she could, hoping that if the room could provide a copy of an actual book it would be able to provide an actual magical device despite its complex nature.

It wasn't instantaneous, but when a long crystal tube attached to a metal sphere appeared in her lap, a grin threatened to tickle her ears it was so wide.

"Yes," she breathed, clutching the tube like a lifeline. She would be in Binny's debt forever, she decided, and would have to make it one of her life's projects to make sure the elf never wanted for anything.

Trepidatiously, she slipped off her gloves and removed the suppressant ring very carefully. It was difficult to get off, despite her sweaty fingers, because Binny had helped her spell it so that it could never fall off on accident or be removed by anyone but herself back in early September when she'd reached the castle. She had to bend her will to removing it, but once off it lay cool in her palm like any other ring. She set it aside carefully, and took a few steps away from the bed before focusing on the measuring device.

It was harder than she remembered to get her magic to start flowing through the tube. She had to coax it a bit, as though it had fallen asleep or become dormant. Once the flow began, however, it was like a dam bursting. She struggled to keep the device from shaking around as power coursed through her hand and bathed the crystal tube with light. The sphere on the end went through rapid color changes from red through orange, yellow, and green, only beginning to slow slightly when it reached blue. She poured more and more magic into the device, trying to feel her core at the same time and decide when it was back to barely-manageable levels. The sphere continued to darken from indigo to violet, and by the time she was able to get a hold on the flow and reign it back, the device was a brilliant purple.

She eyed it with some trepidation—was it a shade darker than it had been in August? Ignoring the worrying implications of that possibility for the moment, she placed the device back on the bed and stretched out her magical senses, prodding her core experimentally.

It arched like a cat under her examination, and Rigel was sure that if it were able, her magic would have purred. A little bit disturbed, she focused her intent and asked her magic to bring one of the pillows on the bed to her. With barely a breath of pause, the pillow flew neatly into her arms, despite her wand still being in her pocket. Smiling, Rigel tossed it back to the bed. She sent a politely worded request to the come and go room, and tossed up a "thank you" when two more standard cauldrons appeared beside the first.

Now she could start brewing.

It was a little over two days later that Rigel felt ready to rejoin the time stream. She lost count of how many batches of Portable Protection Potion she'd brewed, all she knew was that she'd completely filled the remaining spaces in her undetectably-extended brewer's bag, and that was quite a feat if she did say so herself. After the brewing was finished (well, after her magic had regenerated to the point that she felt uncomfortable working without the suppressant ring on), she'd turned her attention to writing up official notes on her process.

She tried to make them as detailed as possible, and with the help from the book on wandless magic she thought she was able to explain the theory much more clearly than she had in the Guild's report. She finally had terminology to express a lot of the magic manipulation that went on in shaped brewing, and since she wasn't limited to a couple pages like in her research report, she felt free to explain every aspect of the brewing process to the point of near-redundancy.

She made three copies of the notes—two to send to Archie along with two dozen bottles of protection potion, and one to give to Professor Snape after enough time had passed that having had her cousin mail the notes to her would be a plausible story. All three copies had been written with dicto-quills, as she was taking no chances with handwriting charms where the Department of Mysteries and Professor Snape were concerned.

The original notes she would keep for herself, as well as all the extra vials of protection potion. The next time someone requested information or samples from she or Archie, Rigel wouldn't be caught flat-footed.

It was late afternoon and she was quite hungry, but even though she'd been taking all of her meals with Binny in the kitchens (sometimes at very odd hours of the day in order to avoid other versions of herself who were also eating in the kitchens), she decided to wait to eat until rejoining the time she thought of as 'present,' which was actually several hours earlier than the time she was in currently.

When she turned back to 11:45 that Wednesday, she'd be just in time to join Pansy and Draco for lunch.

It was a bit surreal stepping out of the first floor bathroom without the invisibility cloak on and catching up to her friends in the Great Hall. She hadn't talked to anyone but Binny for the last few days, and most of that was in French.

As soon as she sat down, Draco turned to her and said, "Rigel, what did McGonagall say about the alternative method for animate to inanimate transfigurations again?"

Rigel blinked. "I…don't remember," she said honestly. That lesson seemed like a lifetime ago.

"It was ten minutes ago," Draco raised an eyebrow.

"You don't remember either," she attempted weakly.

"I wasn't paying attention," Draco waved a hand dismissively, "I'm sure you were taking notes, though."

Rigel shrugged, poking at her potatoes, "Well, you're welcome to take a look at them."

Her friend seemed to drop the subject, but later that night when she was catching up on homework in the common room with the others she caught him staring at her from his seat next to her on the couch.

"What?" she asked, covering her mouth to hide a yawn a moment later. It was only seven in the evening, but as the last few days caught up to her it felt like midnight.

"Why are you tired?" Draco demanded, looking her over closely.

"Didn't sleep well," she said automatically.

Draco huffed, "You slept ten hours last night, just like you've done every other night since the beginning of term. Are you ill, Rigel?" A concerned look passed over his face, and he lowered his voice to keep the others from overhearing, "Is your…condition getting worse?"

The worried expression in his eyes kept Rigel from dismissing his questions. She felt guilt try and climb up from her stomach but she swallowed against it and gave what she hoped was a reassuring smile, "I've been taking a new medication," she said quietly, "It makes me sleep longer." She told herself she wasn't lying, if you counted the sleep-cycle-extending potion as a form of medication.

Draco looked both relieved and sympathetic, so Rigel smiled and nudged him in the ribs, "What's your excuse, hmm? Why weren't you paying attention in Transfiguration today?"

Draco abruptly scowled, "Blaise was distracting me."

"I didn't see him doing anything," Rigel said slowly, trying to remember if anything about that particular Transfiguration lesson stuck out in her mind. It was ordinary in every way as far as she could recall.

"He doesn't have to do anything," Draco said petulantly, "He annoys me just being these days."

"Okay," Rigel said, accepting that Draco was in another of the weird moods he was prone to this semester, "Have you asked him to stop…being however it is that annoys you?"

Draco sighed, twirling his quill between his fingers morosely, "It's not his fault. But that doesn't mean it's not aggravating."

"Whatever you say, Draco," Rigel said, smiling a bit. Her friend would explain himself eventually, she was sure. Until then, she had more than enough on her own plate to deal with.

September bled into October, and one crisp autumn morning Draco said he had something new to show them in their unofficial Dueling lessons on the lawn. Up until then they'd been learning footwork-drills and spending a lot of time on aim-and-dodge exercises.

"It's a new exercise Professor Lupin has been teaching us all," Draco said, still panting a bit from their warm-up run. "First you have to learn the color charm."

"The one that turns its victim a bright color where it hits?" Rigel smiled, "My dad and uncles use it all the time. The incantation is colouris, right?"

Draco nodded, "The wand movement is two quick flourishes, but it's pretty easy to cut the wand movement short once you get the hang of the spell. You have to focus on the color you want very carefully, though."

"Let's see it," Pansy said, pulling out her wand in anticipation of imitating Draco's movements.

When Draco playfully aimed his wand at Rigel's leg, she gave it a taunting wiggle. "Colouris!" he said, brandishing his wand in an exaggerated double flourish for their sake. A jet a neon yellow light shot from his wand in a straight line to Rigel's shin. Her lower leg turned completely yellow, like someone had colored it in with a highlighter.

"The color erasing charm is just a broad swiping motion, with the incantation eradere," Draco said, jogging over to Rigel to demonstrate that one as well. Her leg resumed normal coloring, and Rigel shook it out reflexively, despite feeling no effects whatsoever from the spell.

"So what's the exercise?" Pansy asked while trying out the wand motions a few times.

"It's like battle simulation," Draco said, "The attacker gets three colors of light to work with—red, orange, and yellow. The defender has to alter his response depending on what type of light comes at him."

Rigel nodded to show she was listening, all the while thinking it sounded a lot like some of Flint's practice drills from last year.

"Red light means a spell you either don't know the counter for or can't counter, like an Unforgivable," Draco shivered a bit, "Orange is a spell with effects you have to counter, like Jelly-legs. You either dodge or, if it hits you, cast the color erasing charm before you're allowed to move or cast anything else. Yellow is a spell you can shield against, so you can dodge or cast a Protego if you see a yellow light coming. If you get hit with either a red or yellow light, you lose."

"Interesting," Pansy said. Her face closed into a mask of concentration, and she said, "Colouris!" fiercely while brandishing her wand in Draco's direction.

It caught him in the arm, and while the color was weak, it was recognizably orange. Grinning, Draco cancelled the color with his erasing charm and said, "Good one. Picture the color more intently in your mind. It's supposed to simulate the amount of concentration you'd have to use to cast a spell on the fly."

Rigel tried the spell herself on a patch of ground not far from the trio, smiling in satisfaction when the blades seemed to have been painted red a moment later. "This sounds fun. Does one person attack at a time, or is it like a real duel?"

"We started with one attacking and the other defending in class," Draco smirked, "But I think a free-for-all sounds much more entertaining."

With matching grins of anticipation, the three Slytherins spread out by mutual accord.

"Anyone who gets more than fifty feet from the others forfeits," Rigel suggested.

"And the last one standing gets the other two's notes in History," Pansy added, flashing a positively wicked smile.

Rigel privately reflected that perhaps the radical increase in competitive activity had brought out a previously-dormant side of their usually-prim friend, but Draco was calling, "Let the duel begin!" before she could dwell on the matter. She certainly didn't mind this new side of Pansy. Even if she does cheat, she thought with surprise as Pansy fired her first red-colored spell before Draco had even finished speaking.

Rigel had never faced two opponents at once before, so even though her summer lessons with Leo and Remus had given her plenty of practice dodging, she realized immediately that knowing what to dodge wasn't as easy as seeing the spells coming, though keeping track of both her friends long enough to do even that was hard enough.

It took a lot of split-second decision making to be able to decide immediately how to respond to the red, orange, or yellow lights. They weren't moving at the actual speed light moved at, obviously, but spells still cut through the air pretty quickly. You couldn't just dodge everything indiscriminately, because you risked tiring yourself out, and constant dodging meant no chance for offensive maneuvers.

Their first round didn't last long. Rigel ganged up with Pansy on Draco, one of them tricking him into countering a yellow spell while the other used his distraction with the shield to come at him from the side and stick him with a red light to the leg. After that, Pansy got Rigel by firing three orange spells in a row—one to her chest and one on either side of her—to force her into taking one of them. Unfortunately for Rigel, she got caught in her wand arm while trying to dodge, and wasn't fast enough figuring out how to un-color herself with her left hand before Pansy shot a yellow spell neatly into her shoulder.

Pansy patted down an imaginary stray hair as she struck a carefree pose, "Up for another one, boys?"

Draco and Rigel shared an evil grin. Pansy's confident smile faltered only for a moment before she grinned back, "Bring it on, gentleman."

Needless to say, they were all three disheveled and flush-cheeked by the time they hurried back to their common room to shower and change. Rigel had won the second round rather cunningly, but Draco had beaten them both soundly in rounds three and four. Apparently the blonde boy had been holding back some of his skills to give them a chance. It was only fair, Draco had said, since they were new to the exercise and he'd been practicing in class. Rigel and Pansy both vowed to seek revenge in the name of their pride the next morning.

As they entered the common room, Blaise was stepping out into the hallway. He eyed the three of them with raised eyebrows.

"What are you doing out so early?" Draco asked the dark-skinned boy.

Blaise smirked, "I would ask you the same, but by your stench and appearance it's obvious that you've just lost a fight against a mountain troll."

"We might have won," Rigel said reasonably.

"Yeah, maybe we're as good at dodging clubs as you are at dodging questions," Draco added.

"So blunt lately, Draco," Blaise said admonishingly, "You'll catch more flies with honey than vinegar—and more with traps than obvious bait."

With that, their friend slipped off into the dungeons, leaving the three of them to hurry back to their rooms before the rest of the House started waking up as well.

The first time Rigel caught Draco struggling with his transfigurations, she didn't realize what was wrong. Their course material was steadily growing more difficult, and it made sense that even Draco, who was rather talented at transfigurations, would have a bit of trouble with them.

It wasn't until she saw him wrestle with the engorgement charm, a spell they'd learned in their second year, that she realized what the problem was. The engorgement charm wasn't technically challenging, but the power behind the charm had to be proportionate to the thing you were trying to engorge. Draco was attempting to enlarge one of the bushes near the lake to use as mock cover for their dueling practice that morning, but the bush barely quivered under his annoyed gaze.

Rigel took over wordlessly, but at that point she decided she'd waited long enough. It was one thing not to pry into her friend's private business, but watching him harm himself was a different matter.

She waited until they were alone in their dorm room later that day, Draco sprawled face down on his bedspread, writing a letter to his mother. Rigel pretended to be looking over the recipe for a potion Snape had her learning while she worked up her nerve. It felt wrong to confront Draco so bluntly about his problems, but…well, he'd do the same for her, she supposed.

"You've been taking too much suppressant potion," she said finally.

It took Draco a second to register what she'd said, and when he did, a frown crossed over his face, "What are you talking about?"

"The suppressant potion you take," Rigel said patiently, "You've been miscalculating the dosage."

"And if I said I don't know what you're talking about?" Draco said slowly, setting down his quill.

"I'd have to ask if you think I'm stupid, Draco. The suppressant potion has a distinctive smell, first of all, and even if I hadn't seen you take it when you think no one's looking, I can see the effect it's having on your magic," Rigel said, "It's starting to mess with your conscious magic as well as your unconscious magic because you are taking it too often."

Draco let out a slow breath, propping his head up in his hands and looking at Rigel sidelong, "I know. I have to keep taking it, though."

"Take less," Rigel said, trying to be firm without sounding like she was mothering him, "The teachers are going to notice soon."

"I can't," Draco said, grimacing, "It's not working as well as it used to, so I have to take more."

"You've been taking it since this summer," Rigel said, trying to make it sound like a guess, though she already knew the answer.

He nodded, looking downcast, "Yeah. I hoped it would get better with time, but…it's getting worse. I—Rigel—"

Her friend looked so torn. She could see there was a part of him that wanted to confide in her, but there was also a nervous reluctance that Rigel had seen often enough in the mirror to recognize as fear of acceptance. "You can tell me," she said, as supportive as she could, "You don't have to, but you can. It won't change how I see you."

Draco laughed a little, the sound bitter, "Do you know what I see when I face the boggart?"

Rigel blinked at the non sequitur, but shook her head mutely, turning so that she was facing Draco's bed more fully, giving him her undivided attention.

"It's me," Draco said. His voice shook just a tiny bit before he cleared his throat and firmed it, "The boggart is myself, only…I'm mad."

By the look on his face, she could tell he didn't mean angry.

Draco went on in a kind of daze, as though once he'd begun the words just slipped out of their own accord, "It just screams and laughs and screams and laughs. Sometimes I can get it to change, to sound more like a little kid laughing, but more often it stops laughing, and then it starts whispering…awful, mad things." Draco rolled over so that he was looking up at the ceiling, and Rigel felt absurdly like a muggle therapist as he went on, "I'm half Black, you know. You understand better than anyone about the madness that runs in the family, especially through the branch lines. Aunt Bella is a bit unhinged already."

Rigel nodded, though Draco didn't see it. The Black's were near-infamous for the madness that plagued their family tree. The sane members were incredibly talented, highly functional witches and wizards, the insane ones, however…well, it wasn't only their wealth and power that had kept the Black name feared throughout the ages.

"I suppose you've figured out I came into a gift over the summer," Draco said, resignation colored with relief in his voice, "I think I'm losing my mind, sometimes."

"You aren't," Rigel said fiercely.

"Not yet, maybe," Draco's face was screwed up in an expression of despair, "It's only a matter of time. I'm going to lose my mind, and with it everything I've ever wanted. The Malfoy Heir can't be insane, Rigel. My father will be forced to sire another son, and if my mother can't bear any more children he'll have to—to—divorce her, and we'll both be sent to the French countryside to live out the rest of our lives in shame and it'll be all my fault."

She couldn't believe her ears. She'd known Draco was struggling with whatever his new gift was, but she had no idea he was working under such a dire estimation of his predicament. She slid off her bed and climbed onto Draco's, waiting while he sighed and sat up to make room.

"You are not going to go insane, Draco Malfoy," she said, trying to project as much confidence as she could in her voice, "For one thing, I won't stand for it."

He snorted, "Because you have so much say in it."

"I do," she said, sniffing haughtily, "I saved your mind from the sleeping sickness, remember? In doing so I claimed it as conquered territory. If any madness tried to trespass, I'll break back in and show it what's what."

Draco laughed softly, "I'm not sure my father would appreciate an heir controlled by the Black family any more than a mad one."

"Both better than a magicless one, though," Rigel said, affecting a stern expression, "You are going to be more careful with those potions, aren't you, Dray?"

"My father is the one who bought these potions for me," Draco said, frowning.

She barely restrained herself from saying 'I know' and instead said, "They aren't meant to be a long-term solution." She couldn't help the slightly guilty thought that she was being a complete hypocrite by cautioning Draco against suppressors, but ignored it. Their situations weren't the same.

Draco looked sharply at her, "You don't even mean that."

Rigel blinked, "Yes I do. You need to wean yourself off of them or you won't reach your full potential." Now she definitely felt like a hypocrite.

"Why do you look so unconvinced of your own words, then?" Draco demanded, an angry scowl in place.

Rigel was surprised—she didn't think she'd shown anything but earnestness on her face just then.

"Oh, don't act so surprised," Draco said, rolling his eyes, "You aren't nearly as mysterious as you think."

She narrowed her eyes and considered everything she had been ignoring about Draco's behavior since September.

"What?" he asked defensively, "I'm not the one acting suspiciously."

Rigel's frown deepened, and a sinking fear began to creep over her, "Draco…does your gift tell you things about other people? You've been quite good at guessing what I'm thinking, lately, and forgive me, but usually Pansy is the observant one."

Draco flinched minutely, but it was enough to fill Rigel with dread.

"Are you some kind of natural telepath?" she asked, trying not to panic. How much might he have already learned from her if that were the case? She thought her Occlumency shields were good enough that she would at least detect an attempt at reading her mind, but a natural gift for Legilimency might be able to bypass such defenses without effort.

"I wish," Draco said darkly, "Voices I could handle. It's…feelings," he said the word with utter distain.

"Empathy?" she tried to disguise the gratitude she felt for the universe in that moment by sounding nonchalant.

"Don't bother," Draco said, "Even with the suppressant muting everything I can feel your relief. Don't worry, I won't be reading your mind any time soon—not that I don't want to. Your emotions never make any sense."

Choosing to ignore that can of worms, Rigel said, "That's a very rare gift. I didn't realize it ran in the Malfoy family."

"It doesn't," Draco glared half-heartedly at her, "It's your fault I have it."

Rigel raised an incredulous eyebrow, "What do you mean?"

"Your potion," Draco said, "The one you gave me this summer. That's what brought this on."

"That's not how it works," Rigel disagreed, "The Potentialis Potion only reveals gifts that are already there. You came into it naturally as your core matured."

"No," Draco said, shaking his head, "I was thirteen weeks before the party, remember? The empathy started after I took your potion."

"Maybe it just helped you notice it," Rigel said weakly. Inwardly she was panicking. It couldn't be true, could it? The Potentialis Potion wasn't described as doing what Draco claimed it had—unlocking a latent or unexpressed gift that would otherwise have stayed part of the wizard's recessive traits, but then again…it wouldn't be the first time her magic had done something unusual.

Draco looked more weary than angry at her, "I would have noticed debilitating headaches and mental breakdowns without help, I think. It was hell, Rigel. I didn't even know what was going on at first. Every time one of my parents became even the slightest bit upset or concerned I'd fly off the handle, screaming and wailing uncontrollably. I thought I'd been possessed."

Rigel could feel her face losing color, but she didn't interrupt. If what Draco said was true, she deserved to hear this.

"I was bedridden by the third day, couldn't eat, couldn't sleep, just lay there slowly losing my mind. They had to force nutrient potions down my throat. I'm lucky my parents are as levelheaded as they are. We had to dismiss one of the house elves, even. He'd always been a bit odd, but his line has been with the Malfoy family for hundreds of years. In letting him go we separated him from his mother and brothers for the rest of his life, but we had to because every time he got near me his mental illness made me feel like I was crazy, too. It took me weeks to even sort out what was me and what was other people, and even then if someone's emotions were strong enough they changed mine, making me sad or angry or scared or—or—" Draco let out a shaky breath, running his hand through his hair agitatedly, "At least with the potion I just get headaches when the emotions around me are too strong."

Rigel swallowed, feeling wretched for many things, but mostly for not noticing that Draco's problem was so serious. "Don't you get the good emotions, too, though?" she asked, tentative.

"Good feelings aren't as powerful as negative ones, and they don't last as long," Draco said matter-of-factly, "But even so they can overwhelm me if it's concentrated enough. You saw me at the welcoming feast, Rigel, and that was with the potion still in my system. That much excitement in one place felt like a hammer pounding away at me. Most of the time I don't get any good emotions, though. Proportionately there are apparently many more unhappy people than happy in the world. And teenagers are the worst," he added, burying his head in his hands with a groan, "I see what Uncle Sev meant now, nothing but angst and jealousy and pettiness and—and—I hate it."

"I'm so sorry, Draco," Rigel said, wondering if she should pat his shoulder comfortingly.

"I know," Draco laughed hollowly, "Your guilt is one emotion I've got an excellent handle on, you feel it so often."

"What?" she asked, taken aback.

"The other day you felt guilty about leaving to go to the bathroom," Draco said, rolling his eyes a bit, "It's a little ridiculous how often you fall back on that emotion."

Rigel hid a wince, realizing Draco must have been picking up on her guilt about using the time-turner without telling him and Pansy for weeks.

"And now you're feeling guilty about feeling guilty," Draco said, exasperated, "Just stop."

Rigel calmed herself with a force of will, and felt satisfied with the knowledge that at least Draco would not be able to tell the reason for her emotions without serious guesswork on his part. She felt secure enough in her ability to misdirect him in regards to her secrets.

How was she going to help Draco, though? She could offer to make a weaker dose of the potion to start weaning him off of it, but if the gift was as overwhelming as he said, Hogwarts would be a terrible place to try and learn to control it.

"Have you thought about learning Occlumency?" she asked after a moment of thought, "Perhaps Snape could teach you."

"He's been trying, but he doesn't have a lot of free time now that school's started again, and he was busy with important research this summer so father didn't want to demand too much of him," Draco said dispiritedly.

That explained why Mr. Malfoy had commissioned the potions instead of having Snape make them, at least. That, and it was probably easier for Malfoy to pay for the work of an anonymous stranger than to ask a close friend for a delicate favor.

"We'll just have to figure it out ourselves, then," Rigel said, smiling grimly.

"We?" Draco looked so hopeful she couldn't help but give him a quick hug.

"Of course, Dray. We're in this together now. I'll lend you the books that were the most helpful when I started Occlumency. We'll have meditation time before bed every night, and once you can access your mindscape on your own, I'll come in and help you design something to help control your gift, okay?" Rigel wasn't entirely sure that would work, but it was the most logical first step, "Meanwhile you should practice letting the potion wear off in a controlled environment when you can. Just focus on one or two other people, try to differentiate their emotions from yours, pay attention to when you can feel their emotions trying to interact with your own."

Draco nodded slowly, "Yes…I can do that." He looked more than a little relieved, and Rigel thought perhaps shouldering the problem by himself had contributed greatly to the despair he had shown earlier.

"You might talk to Remus—Professor Lupin, I mean—about sitting out the rest of the boggart unit, too," Rigel said, "I'm sure he'd allow you to complete some sort of alternative assignment if you asked."

"Everyone will think I'm a coward," Draco shook his head, "I'm not going to refuse to face the boggart when Greengrass can handle it."

"No one would have to know," Rigel tried to reason, "Professor Lupin would help you keep up appearances, I think."

"I would know," Draco said shortly, "I'll figure it out eventually."

"All right," Rigel shrugged. Then she asked, "Are you going to tell Pansy?"

To her surprise, Draco didn't look hesitant so much as uneasy at the mention of Pansy's name, "I'm…not sure. Does Pansy seem different this year to you?"

Rigel blinked, "Not particularly. She's a bit taller, I suppose."

Draco shook his head, "It's just…sometimes I get these emotions from her that don't make any sense. They aren't the kind of emotions I'd ever expect from Pansy, of all people. Then again," he sighed, "It's probably just me. I don't fully understand everything my gift tells me, especially when I use the suppressant potion. I suppose I should tell her. I think I'll wait until we know if Occlumency is going to get me anywhere, though. I want to have a plan when I tell her, so she doesn't worry too much."

Rigel nodded her agreement. She went to slip off the bed, but Draco's hand on her shoulder stopped her.

"Thanks, Rigel," he said, a sober look of sincerity on his face, "I know I've been a prat about this whole thing. I'm going to try and get this under control, like you said, and I want you to know that I'm grateful to have a friend who tells me what I need to hear. I don't blame you for the Potentialis Potion, either," he added.

Rigel thanked him for his understanding, but there was a specter of dread lurking in the back of her mind all the same. Draco wasn't the only one she'd made that potion for. Her cousin had begged her and pestered her about making him one once he turned thirteen, and Rigel, once she had her brewing abilities back under control, had done so.

Archie would have told me if something weird had happened though…wouldn't he?

As the weeks went on, Rigel found that time-turned life strangely suited her. It hadn't taken her long, she ruefully reflected, to begin spending mind-boggling amounts of folded time each day studying anything and everything that she could justify as 'academic,' which was, she silently argued to herself at times, the purpose of the time-turner in the first place. She rationalized that the hours of time she spent with her friends each day were hours that other students who didn't have so many classes and academic pursuits would have anyway, so even when she used the time-turner to live those hours, she wasn't using the time-turner non-academically. It was making up for the hours from each actual day that she spent in learning. If some of the things she learned were technically extra-curricular…well, it was still academic to study Occlumency and practice brewing potions, wasn't it?

She half-expected to burn out after a couple months, figuring that the stress of living so many days each week would eventually catch up to her and cause some sort of mental fatigue that required her to take a break from such enthusiastic use of the device. As the end of October neared, however, her mind and body showed no signs of slowing down. With the time-turner, in fact, she felt better than she ever had. She had time to eat, sleep, and exercise as much as she wanted, and the time she spent with her friends more than offset the extra study time crammed into each day.

It was even becoming easier to hide its use from her friends as she got the hang of her schedule. She was never either too consistent or too irregular in the times and places she slipped away and rejoined them. Even Draco, with his slowly improving grip on the emotions of those around him, hadn't seemed to notice.

Speaking of Draco's gift, Rigel almost wished she hadn't offered to help him harness it. It wasn't that she liked the idea of her friend in constant discomfort—quite the opposite, she'd do almost anything to keep Draco from pain—but for some reason when she'd pictured teaching Draco to control his gift, she'd imagined finding a more effective way of preventing the effect it had on his everyday life.

Draco, it turned out, had a different interpretation on what controlling his ability meant. After giving Rigel a very strange look the first time she'd wondered aloud if they might construct a containment field of some sort in Draco's mind once his Occlumency was good enough, her friend had explained very patiently that he didn't want make his empathy go away—he wanted to make it useful.

In retrospect Rigel supposed that of course Draco would want to harness the natural advantage his empathy could afford him socially and politically, considering who his father was and what kind of work the young scion would eventually go into. She just hadn't anticipated that Draco would take to the idea of practicing his gift so…enthusiastically.

"Stop worrying, Pans," Draco said. He was ensconced in a low-backed armchair with a book on meditation and focusing techniques, but he lowered it for a moment to look at Pansy over its top, "You're going to do fine on that test."

He had become positively imperious about the emotions of others, Rigel noticed. Once he identified what someone was feeling, Draco had developed a tendency of telling them quite bluntly not to feel it, particularly if the emotion was one he himself didn't want to be feeling. Rigel hoped quietly that this habit would go away once Draco learned to ignore the emotions around him, but in light of her friend's sometimes domineering personality, her hopes weren't particularly high.

Pansy, who was pouring over her Care of Magical Creatures notes on the couch next to Rigel, looked up distractedly. "What an unhelpful prediction, Draco," she sighed, "No one is going to do fine on this test, because we haven't been taught anything comprehensive. The study guides Professor Pettigrew handed out are just gibberish."

"You should ask Rookwood what the tests were like in his third year," Rigel said, "Since Pettigrew is new this year, he'll probably rely on the last teacher's notes and exams, at least to help him determine appropriate content."

"Brilliant," Pansy snapped her book shut, ignoring the roll of parchment that got smashed between the pages, "Thanks, Rye."

She got up and wove her way across the common room, presumably looking for the upperclassman in question.

"I'm telling you there's something different about Pansy lately," Draco muttered.

Rigel ignored him, mostly because he'd said the same thing so many times in the past few weeks that she no longer had any novel reply to give. Instead, she focused on trying to understand the emergent patterns of late-stage lung diseases as related to age and vitality of the victim. Patient, she mentally corrected herself, not victim. Archie had some rather pointed things to say about her callous discussion of sick people in their last letter exchange. In her defense, she didn't actually treat any real people the way Archie did whenever his class had volunteer duty at the local hospital. All Rigel did was learn the theory, which sometimes made it difficult to humanize the subjects.

Before Draco could espouse his latest theory as to what, exactly, was different about Pansy this year, the girl in question returned, Rookwood in tow. Rigel obligingly moved to a different couch so that the two creature specialists could spread out Pansy's notes between them, and wasn't terribly surprised when Rosier wandered over a few minutes later and dropped gracefully into the cushion beside her.

"Evening, Rosier," she said, quickly finishing the paragraph she was reading. The odds of Rosier not starting a conversation were slim, after all.

"And what are you reading tonight, Rigel?" the golden-eyed boy asked through half-mast eyelids, "Another anatomy textbook?"

"Treatise on airborne pathogens," Rigel said, lifting the cover in case for some reason he was interested in noting the title.

"Got into the Healing class this year, then?" he guessed.

"Not really," Rigel said vaguely, "I still have the occasional lesson in my free time, but I didn't have room in my schedule to be in the regular class."

"What did you take in its place?" Rosier asked, visibly surprised, "Besides Potions, Healing is all you seem to study in your free time."

"I opted to take Arithmancy and Ancient Runes," Rigel said, not bothering to mention Magical Theory, for which she only officially attended the lab section. "Since my cousin Harry takes Healing classes in America, I can learn enough through correspondence with her that making room for a whole class here seemed unnecessary. Arithmancy and Runes would be much harder for me to self-study."

"Interesting criteria," Rosier said slowly, "Most people take the classes they're good at or interested in pursuing a career in, if only so that they might take the OWL's and NEWT's that will qualify them for future employment in the field. Why study Healing if you'll have no credentials to apply for an internship when you finish Hogwarts?"

Rigel shrugged, "I haven't decided what I want to do for sure yet. I'd prefer to concentrate on maximizing my learning now, and worrying about the future later. I can always take the Healing NEWT if I want to, even without taking more lessons with Madam Pomfrey. It's so rare for students from Hogwarts to have a Healing NEWT in any case, because the program here is so small, so even major hospitals like St. Mungo's will interview candidates without credentials if they show an aptitude."

All of which was technically true. She disliked spouting such long-winded lies, but when she and Archie switched back one day, she didn't want someone she'd gone to school with to think it odd if they happened to hear that Rigel Black had become a Mediwizard. She felt a momentary pang at the thought that she would have to cut ties with all of the friends she had here when she graduated. She shied away from the implications with the ease of practice, however. She didn't have to worry about that, at least, for a while yet.

"For entry-level positions," Rosier said, "Do you plan on cleaning bed-pans for six months when you turn seventeen?"

"If they need cleaning," Rigel shrugged, unconcerned with so unlikely a future.

Rosier laughed. "Big words. Are you really so unconcerned with your own future?" he asked, unconsciously mimicking her thoughts.

Rigel considered this; "I find that making too many plans for the future can undermine one's ability to appreciate the present."

"Or maybe you're just confident in your ability to secure a worthy position regardless of academic credentials," Rosier mused, "I wonder, is it a faith in your own abilities, or the ability to trade on your family connections?"

Rigel felt herself still for a moment before slowly closing her book and setting it deliberately aside. "I don't understand," she said.

The upperclassman considered her with sharp interest, "Your father is very well-liked at St. Mungo's. Aside from volunteering, he heads a committee for organizing fundraising events and personally donates an embarrassing amount of galleons every Yule. That kind of clout is very useful for someone seeking employment in a competitive field."

She couldn't quite believe he had actually insinuated what she thought he had. After peering into his expression for a moment and receiving nothing but impassive amusement, she took a breath and let it out slowly, deciding what to say. Eventually she said, "My father invests so much time and money into St. Mungo's for the same reason I want to learn about Healing for its own sake, not for a mark or job prospects."

"And what reason is—"

She could see the exact moment the realization hit him, regret flashing across his face and trepidation replacing smooth aloofness in his eyes. Before he could talk his way backwards she added, quiet enough to be chiding, "She passed in the winter, close to Yule."

"Rigel, I didn't mean—"

"Yes he did."

They both turned to see that Draco had been following their entire conversation, his face set in an angry glare.

"I'm certain Rosier spoke in ignorance, not malice," Rigel said, not feeling particularly sympathetic as Rosier winced. She would be generous because Rosier was a friend, but she wished she knew what he'd hoped to accomplish with such tactless inquiry. "My mother passed a long time ago, and there's no reason he would remember the details of her illness when he was so young at the time."

"And I'm certain he did that on purpose," Draco said, shooting Rigel a meaningful look that told her he'd been using his rudimentary grasp of empathy to read Rosier's emotions during the conversation. "He was positively pleased as he said it."

Rosier frowned, looking indignant, but also unsure whether he was allowed to defend himself after his thoughtless blunder.

"He didn't realize his mistake until the words were out," Rigel said, sighing. That much was obvious, even without a gift in empathy. "He's perfectly sorry now."

"Now that you called him on it," Draco growled, "Rigel, when are you going to see that he enjoys tormenting people?"

"I don't," Rosier bit out. His face was pale and he seemed, for the first time since Rigel had met him, at a loss for what to say. "I don't torment people," he said again, clenching one fist ineffectually.

"You do," Draco argued, "What else do you call purposely making people uncomfortable and asking inappropriate questions just to see them squirm? It's impermissible, and yet no one says anything because your Father has bought up half the businesses in Diagon Alley. You're just like him, bullying people into doing what you want for a bit of amusement—"

"Do not compare me to that man," Rosier spat so venomously that Draco actually leaned back a few inches, a shocked expression on his face. If Rigel had to guess, she'd say he just got a huge backlash of emotion he'd been unprepared for. Personally she thought it served him right for using his gift to try and outmaneuver someone he didn't get along with.

Rigel glanced around the common room and noticed they were drawing attention from nearby groups. "Maybe we should talk about something else," she suggested.

"No, I think Draco and I need to settle whatever this is now, before it festers any longer," Rosier said, uncommonly stiff.

"Agreed," Draco sniffed, standing with exaggerated ceremony, "After you, Rosier."

Before Rigel could say that this had all been a misunderstanding, both boys had left their group of couches and made their way into a private study room, closing the door resolutely behind themselves.

She looked over at Pansy helplessly, wondering how she'd managed to make such a mess of a quiet evening, but Pansy had nothing to say besides "boys."

After a moment of private consideration, Rigel decided that pretty much summed up the situation.

Draco considered himself very contained, in most situations. He did not stomp his feet or shout when things failed to go his way, but that didn't mean he sat idly by and watched while something he found personally reprehensible was going on before his eyes, either. Rosier's little mind game had been going on long enough, and it was past time that somebody put a stop to it. That somebody was clearly not going to be Rigel Black,

Rosier shut the door to the study room behind them, and they each claimed a seat on opposite sides of the small wooden table. The older scion seemed to have some of his usual equilibrium back as he lounged indolently and favored Draco with a displeased expression, but Draco could tell, if he concentrated for a moment, that Rosier was actually feeling off-balance and uneasy.

"What is it that you thought you were doing just now?" Draco asked bluntly. In a ballroom with the eyes of ones peers all around, a man had to be circumspect. In a private conversation from one pureblood to another, however, directness was always preferred.

"I was holding a conversation," Rosier said smoothly.

"Usually you're much better at not swallowing your foot while you talk," Draco pointed out.

He had the pleasure of seeing the older Slytherin grimace, "I misspoke, yes, and I'll apologize to Rigel for my lapse in memory, but I fail to see why you need to take me to task for a question I already regret asking. Rather, I'd like to know why it is that every time I have a conversation with Rigel you become personally offended, Draco."

Draco scowled openly—the use of his personal name was an obvious ploy, but it didn't stop it from rankling. "Perhaps it is because every time you have a conversation with Rigel you upset him, and he's too polite to be offended on his own behalf."

Rosier visibly checked himself from scowling back, and Draco took the moment to lay a mental brush over the part of his magic he was coming to recognize as his empathic senses. It told him in vague impressions that Rosier felt defensive but not overtly guilty. Draco supposed that meant Rosier thought his actions justified in some way; he withheld a snort, but couldn't crush the spark of curiosity that had him wondering what the older boy's motives in antagonizing Rigel could possibly be.

"As difficult as I know it is for you to believe, you are not the only one with Rigel's best interests at heart," Rosier said quietly, "Yes, I provoke the boy sometimes, but Rigel is exactly the type of person who needs to be provoked. You've known him as long as I have; don't pretend you don't know his character. He avoids everything that makes him uncomfortable, including other people more often than not. Do you think that's a habit his friends should encourage?"

"Rigel doesn't avoid us," Draco said, "He's been around all the time, lately."

"Around, yes, but engaged?" Rosier asked, his voice pointed, "He sits among you all and reads, but how often does he volunteer information about how his life is going? Or initiate casual contact?"

"That's none of your business," Draco said, more sharply than he'd intended. Really, though, where did Rosier get off thinking he could decide what was and wasn't good for Rigel? He didn't know what he was talking about.

Rosier's eyes narrowed and his emotions became suspicious. Draco groaned internally as he realized he'd given something away with his vehement protest. "You know something," the older boy said.

"Just leave Rigel alone," Draco said.

"You really want Rigel to end up alone?" Rosier asked, a mocking note back in his voice, "Because that's where he's headed. He'll never seek out friendship or companionship of his own volition."

"He's not required to," Draco tried.

"But he wants to, can't you see that?" Rosier argued, leaning forward and giving off an earnest vibe Draco had a hard time disregarding, "Rigel soaks up friendship and affection like a sponge when he lets his guard down, but left to his own devices he pulls away. He needs people to pull him back in again."

Draco wasn't convinced, "Rigel has secrets. There are things you don't understand—and things I don't understand, too—and making him too uncomfortable is only going to push him away."

"Is it?" Rosier asked, "It hasn't yet."

Draco opened his mouth to argue and then stopped, thinking. Rosier, the sick bastard, was right. Every time Draco had urged Rigel to get angry and say something in response to Rosier's prodding, his friend had effectively shrugged it off and decided it wasn't worth getting upset over.

"Rigel says he has strict boundaries, maybe even believes it, but every time someone crosses one he forgives them," Rosier said knowingly, "Rigel wants to be close to people; deep down, he wants to drop his mask, which is all I want him to do. I want him to relax around his friends, to tell us uncomfortable truths he keeps to himself, to realize that no matter what he says or does we've already got his back, and to understand that getting close to someone doesn't have to be scary or confusing. Right now he pretends to trust us, to believe that we care, but in reality he shoulders everything himself and doesn't trust us to want to help him, or to forgive him any imperfections. That's unhealthy, and it isn't fair to us, either."

Draco couldn't believe he was even considering Rosier's arguments, but…some of it made sense. Rosier didn't know about Rigel's medical condition that made it uncomfortable for him to touch people too much—come to that he didn't know much about it, either—but before Rigel had confessed to it he remembered wondering if Rigel had been mistreated or traumatized somehow. He was just so unnaturally cautious and spatially aware of his surroundings.

Still… "It's not our place to confront Rigel about his issues," Draco had to point out, "We're his peers, not his parents."

"If not his friends, then who?" Rosier countered, "His father, who doesn't seem to see Rigel even when he's looking right at him? Professor Snape, who couldn't nourish emotional bonds in a child if it was his own, much less the son of his hated rival? Perhaps we should leave it to his cousin, off living in America most of the year and by all accounts more antisocial than Rigel is?"

Draco had nothing to say to that.

"Or maybe you think Rigel will work it out for himself, given time?" Rosier's expression was positively sardonic now, "Do you think Rigel will leave his self-imposed comfort zone on his own? No. He'll nurture what he sees as one-sided friendships, always willing to help others but never accepting any help in return, smiling and making small talk while whatever secrets he's keeping slowly eat away at him from the inside out. You've seen the contradictions embedded in the life he leads, Draco. You know it can't last. Isn't it better to show him now that getting closer to people doesn't mean facing rejection when something less than perfect shows through that veneer of his?"

Draco held up a hand so that Rosier would stop talking for a moment. He needed to think. Everything Rosier was saying sounded so overbearing and presumptuous, but…is he wrong?

Hadn't Draco thought similar things, at different times in the past? Rigel was his best friend, who he'd do anything for, but…did Rigel understand that? He knew Rigel took his side of the friendship very seriously, but he never expected anything of Draco, even after Draco had repeatedly asked Rigel to let him help with anything he could. Was Rosier right in suggesting that a more demonstrative show of trust and affection was necessary to get through to Rigel? Draco grimaced. Rosier still didn't know about Rigel's condition, and it really wasn't his place to tell the older boy, no matter how genuine his concern felt to Draco's rudimentary empathic understanding.

"I understand where you're coming from," Draco said slowly, "But I have to strongly advise you that even though things like sitting closer to Rigel or touching his hair seem casual to you, they aren't to Rigel. He takes physical contact extremely seriously, and that part really does make him uncomfortable and confused, and I don't think you can acclimate him to it, not matter how often you try."

Rosier considered Draco's words carefully. "He hasn't had a strong adverse reaction yet," he said after a moment, "It can't be that strong of a psychological barrier. It seems to me that he keeps a distance on purpose, but not out of fear or extreme paranoia. It's more like he thinks he ought to."

Draco could feel Rosier's confusion as he tried to figure it out, and felt a deep sympathy that he was pretty sure came from himself—he certainly knew how it felt to be utterly perplexed by Rigel Black. "Just trust me on this one thing," Draco said eventually, "Don't try to use physical contact to break through Rigel's social barriers—he'll be too polite to tell you so, but there are reasons you don't understand for why it upsets him."

"All right," Rosier shrugged, "I'll try a different approach." He winced, "Although, I was trying that tonight and rather botched it, I fear. I thought if I caught him off-guard with a pointed question he might reveal something more than his usual vague answers to queries about his goals and ambitions."

Draco sat back, satisfied with that concession. He could have left then, but something compelled him to ask, "How do you really feel about Rigel, Rosier?"

He didn't listen to Rosier's answer—the words weren't important. He listened to his empathy instead. When Rosier talked about Rigel he didn't give off any of the strange, sadistic excitement Draco had been expecting. Rosier felt fond of Rigel; he felt concerned, intrigued, and something warm that felt a little like kinship but more active, for lack of a better descriptive. There was a pleased sort of curiosity underlying it all, and just a tiny bit of possessiveness that Draco really wasn't surprised by at all.

Draco wasn't entirely pleased with this vague assessment, but he felt much better than he had going into the conversation. Maybe Rosier wasn't as obnoxious as Draco had originally assumed. Scarily enough, he found himself agreeing with the upperclassman more than not. He still thought Rosier was an overbearing ponce, but maybe—just maybe—the other Slytherin had a point when it came to Rigel Black.

When they rejoined the common room, Rigel looked each of them over warily, as though searching for signs that they'd been brawling like muggles. Honestly.

Rosier reclaimed his seat next to Rigel and very earnestly said, "I'm sorry for the insinuations I made earlier, Rigel. I went too far with my speech, and I can only hope you'll forgive me. I was only trying to gauge your reaction, but that's no excuse for my rudeness."

Rigel, to no one's surprise, only tilted his head and said, "It is already forgotten. Only—why were you trying to get a reaction?"

"Just wondering what's under that mask you always wear," Rosier said, actually winking his ridiculously orange eye at the other boy.

Predictably, Rigel frowned at that, "People are entitled to their masks, Rosier."

"Are they?" Draco said mildly. He knew it was cruel, but he just couldn't resist seeing the look on Rigel's face when he realized that Draco was agreeing with Rosier, "Sometimes provoking people is the only way to get an honest reaction out of them, isn't it, Aldon?"

The brief but acute horror on Rigel's face as the boy glanced between the two of them proved that point quite nicely, Draco thought. He tried not to smirk too obviously as he retook his own seat and settled back in to read. Things would be more interesting from now on. He'd been a passive friend to Rigel for a while, now. Perhaps it was time to change that.

Chapter 8

Remus Lupin had wanted to teach since he was a lonely eleven-year-old watching prefects tutor the younger students in the Gryffindor common room. At the time, he'd been too nervous to ask for help himself, even though his potions marks could probably have used the boost, but although he didn't partake of the upperclassmen's services, he still admired their patience and generosity from his seat in a dimly-lit corner.

Even after he'd—somehow, miraculously—made friends with the kind of kids who sat in oversized armchairs in the center of the bright firelight, Remus often found his gaze drawn to the prefects and their charges. He'd known it was a foolish wish at the time—what were the odds that the Ministry would allow him to open a school for werewolves, after all?—but he found himself jotting down ideas in a small notebook whenever he heard a particularly well-phrased explanation, or whenever one of his professors gave them an especially creative project or activity.

A couple decades later, and that little green book sat proudly on the shelf behind a desk he'd never, even in his most fanciful imaginings, imagined he'd one day lay claim to.

The desk itself was piled high with parchment and notebooks of varying sizes and colors. The stacks were arranged somewhat haphazardly, though Remus knew about where everything was. None of the papers were homework assignments, in which Remus put rather little stock, having witnessed the half-baked and entirely dishonest way in which most of his own housemates had completed their assignments in school. Rather, the notes were his own, compiled on each student he taught, in all seven years, and all four houses. He kept tabs on which students answered questions correctly, which students helped their year mates by whispering answers to them in a tone they (mistakenly) assumed Remus couldn't hear, which students could rapidly cast shields, which students were reluctant to use offensive spells, and so on. He liked to think a good teacher would know his students well, from their strengths and weaknesses to their character traits and ambitions.

He tried to take time before and after classes to talk to students, ask them questions, solicit their opinions on how his classes and assignments were received, and address any concerns they had about their own performance in his class. He also made sure to keep a friendly expression on his face throughout mealtimes and in the hallways. Remus knew better than anyone how scary the dark arts could be, and he didn't want any of his students to be too scared of him to get the education they needed to protect themselves.

This was easier said, of course, with his furry little problem being common knowledge these days, but Remus could only do so much to mitigate others' prejudice. He had some reservations about being the poster-boy for werewolf integration in the workforce, but on the other hand, if not him, then who? It wasn't as though everyone he knew didn't already know about his condition—he'd long since stopped being too ashamed to tell people he met about it. And his face, while not as handsome as someone like Sirius' might be, was certainly a good deal more unassuming than that of Fenrir Greyback's, for example.

Imagining Greyback's face on a motivational poster for equal rights, perhaps with the man's abundance of hair neatly combed and braided, gave him quite a laugh, and Remus paused in outlining his lesson for the next day to savor the image.

Opening his eyes once more, he focused on the columns of names before him. Tomorrow he had the third-year Slytherins, in their last class of boggart-training until the final. He'd separated their names into groups of those students who no longer had any trouble with the boggart, those who needed a brief mental-psyching to get a handle on it, and those exceptionally brave students who, despite having enormous difficulties in grappling with their fears, returned each period to try again anyway.

It was somewhat difficult for him to commit even this basic information onto parchment, due to the confidentiality wards. The magic in the wards bonded to memories as they were created within them. Since they were keyed to Remus, they affected the way he remembered events he'd witnessed, but only when he attempted to use the information in some way. If he were just recalling a memory, it was perfectly clear. As soon as he attempted to convey information about the event in any way, even to himself, the recollection became vague. It was clear enough to sort the students into three simple categories, though.

He told himself not to feel surprised that Draco Malfoy's name, which had recently been moved to the middle group of students, had for a long time resided firmly in the latter column. If Archie likes him, he can't be much like his father, he told himself. He ignored the voice that suggested Archie's judgment of character might have been heavily influenced by his sorting. If I assume all Slytherins are pompous gits without the right to fears and uncertainties, I'm no better than Sirius.

He hadn't seen Archie very often since coming to Hogwarts, which he supposed was for the best, at least until the end of term. He had, however, seen him often in the company of his two best friends, Miss Parkinson and Mr. Malfoy. Miss Parkinson was a thoroughly brilliant witch, in Remus' estimation, and as charming as any pureblood heiress ought to be. Remus could easily see why her soothing temperament and playful wit had endeared her to Archie. Sirius' son had grown up around smart, even-tempered females, after all. His friendship with the Malfoy scion was…more puzzling.

It wasn't that the younger Malfoy wasn't perfectly polite. There were no hidden flinches or sneers when Remus called on him in class, which was more than Remus could say about many of his students. He was also quite intelligent, from what Remus could tell. He didn't run his mouth as young boys his age were want to do, and, when pressed, always had something insightful to say on a given subject.

Remus sighed, tapping his quill absently against the inkwell as he turned the problem of Draco Malfoy over in his mind. The boy was arrogant, of course, and not afraid to dismiss and scorn those around him when he felt their behavior warranted correction. He didn't know how Archie could stand such a high-handed friend, but he couldn't deny that Draco was a friend to Archie. He'd seen the proof himself, after all.

His mind took him back to the week before, the last time his third year Slytherins had faced the boggart, and the first time Draco Malfoy had beaten the creature on his own.

Remus couldn't help the slight grimace he gave when young Mr. Malfoy walked behind the screen. While boggarts were meant to be terrifying and upsetting to the victim, Malfoy's boggart was one of the few that disturbed Remus when he saw it. Most children feared the sort of monsters they'd heard about in bedtime stories, though a few of the more worldly students sometimes had a vague fear of violent criminals or losing loved ones or even simply failing important examinations. Mr. Malfoy's greatest fear, however, from what Remus could tell, appeared to be madness.

Remus was all too familiar with true madness: the utter loss of mental facilities so debilitating that one cannot even appreciate the horror except in retrospect, or, in the case of Draco's boggart, from an outside perspective. Why the otherwise confident and poised young man should fear such a thing, it was not his place to guess. His only concern was the difficulty Malfoy had in attempting to overcome his fear psychologically.

As the boggart assumed its now-usual image of Draco's doppelganger laughing and crying with hysteria, Remus readied himself to interfere if it, once again, proved too much for the young pureblood.

This time, something was different, however. Mr. Malfoy didn't flinch at the sight of his afflicted counterpart. He stood straight, his wand brandished with a sense of confidence that had been missing in his previous session. Remus began to relax, sensing, somehow, that he would not be needed this time.

"Riddikulus!" Malfoy snapped, silver eyes intent with concentration.

For a moment, Remus wasn't sure it had worked. The blonde boy on the floor didn't stop laughing or rocking himself insanely. Then something else stepped out of the shadows behind the boy and Remus tensed, surprised.

It was Archie. The image of his nephew wasn't perfect, but it was at least as solid as the boggart, and as Remus watched, the image of Archie came around next to the madly muttering Malfoy and sat down beside him. Archie put both arms around the other boy, and the rocking abruptly stopped. Slowly, the look of madness faded from the boggart-boy's eyes, and he looked over at the image of Archie that the real Malfoy had apparently conjured. Both boys on the ground smiled at one another, and the real Mr. Malfoy smiled down at them with a mixture of fondness and relief.

Remus snapped himself out of his surprise quickly. By the time the young scion looked over, Remus was smiling genially, as though nothing interesting had occurred. "Well done, Mr. Malfoy," he said, "Ten points to Slytherin for creative thinking. Get yourself some chocolate, and send the next student in, please."

The boy bowed his head in polite acknowledgment and turned on his heel without a word.

Remus banished the boggart back into its temporary home, wondering at what he'd seen. He had studied boggarts extensively before he decided to use them in his classes, and he'd never once heard of someone using the idea of another sentient being to affect their own fear. People always changed something about the boggart itself in order to make it less frightening. Changing the environment sometimes worked, too, but he'd never thought to introduce a new variable entirely to interact with a boggart. Remus was very impressed that Malfoy had come up with such a solution, and more than a little intrigued by the meaning of his choice.

Archie had a more devoted friend than he realized, Remus suspected. What sort of devotion that friendship would turn into, given enough time…well, he supposed that wasn't really any of his business.

If anyone had told Rigel at the beginning of the school year that she'd find one of her electives as interesting as Potions, she might have given an indulgent smile to hide her dismay that someone could ever be so fundamentally misguided about the universe.

That was before she started Alchemy lessons with Albus Dumbledore. She wouldn't say it was more interesting than Potions—such a thing would be sacrilegious, at the least—but it had quickly become a very close second.

Alchemy was fascinating. Much like Potions, it was an exacting science that required an extensive range of knowledge about myriad, interlocking fields of magic. Alchemy at its most basic level involved small amounts of actual magic and raw ingredients, very precise Runic arrays to shape that magic, and Arithmancy equations to calculate and describe the amount and direction of the magic and ingredients involved. It drew on her understanding of Herbology and Magical Creature parts, which she had a vast repertoire of knowledge about from her Potions studies, as well as a comprehension of Runes, Arithmancy, Transfiguration, and even Astronomy in those alchemical reactions that were intensified or nullified according to the positions of celestial bodies at the time.

She found herself constantly surprised at the way one subject could be at once frustratingly complicated and yet beautifully simple. Input always equaled output in Alchemy, and with enough understanding of the values different ingredients and magical processes equated to, one could design a runic array that would enable almost any alchemical transformation one could imagine. Dumbledore never tried to make her memorize tried and true arrays, either; rather, he encouraged her to design her own rune circles and equations without a biased idea of what types of magic or ingredients should go into it. Often times her ideas were wildly inefficient or off the mark, but Dumbledore's Socratic style of inquiry-based learning, while slow, always made the eventual answer seem rooted in her mind like a truth that she'd always known, but hadn't noticed before.

The efficacy of his teaching methods more than made up for the Headmaster's other…oddities.

As she carefully copied down the rune sequence Dumbledore was etching with chalk onto the table, Rigel wondered what her friends would say if they knew she was taking private lessons from a Master of Alchemy in the same subject. Her friends, while often vocally disapproving of the Headmaster's muggle-loving ways, were still rather unsubtly in awe of the great wizard.

She also wondered wryly what they'd say if they knew he had an incredibly cliché secret passage in his office. Or that he sometimes curled his beard with his wand when he lectured.

She studied the carefully separated piles of ingredients lying in the center of the circle. Someday, Dumbledore assured her, she would know instinctively how much of this or that was necessary to effect a certain reaction, but for beginners it was better to clearly separate and triple-check the quantities of ingredients before attempting to 'jump-start' an array with the appropriate amount of raw input magic.

The reaction Dumbledore was demonstrating was relatively simple, in that it involved only raw materials that would be transformed into a compound material, with no left over raw ingredients at the end. Specifically, it was an array that would transform proportional amounts of wood and metal into a cubic wooden box. It was similar to an array they'd studied last week, but with pine instead of cypress.

"The magic coefficient on the pine is higher than the cypress coefficient was," she commented after a moment.

Every substance used in alchemical equations, from elements to organic compounds, had been given by wizards a magic coefficient that described the amount of magic needed to transform one unit of a given ingredient in an array with an order of complexity of one. Wood was fairly easy to transform, given its high level of innate magic to assist and its susceptibility to what Dumbledore called 'the idea of change' and which Rigel had renamed an ingredient's flexibility factor. Arrays were categorized according to levels of complexity, with each increase in complexity corresponding to an increase in factor of the magic involved in the change.

If you wanted to change one unit of wood into a wooden flute, for instance, you calculated the magic needed by multiplying the magic coefficient of the type of wood you used by the magical constant unique to the wizard powering the reaction, then multiplied that number by the factor of complexity, in the case of a flute a 2.5. The result was the number of seconds the wizard should imbue the array with magic in order to initiate the reaction. The actual transformation was all described in the runes that made up the array, and of course when you had varying amounts of varying ingredients the equations got more complicated, and that was without even touching on second- and third-order arrays that enacted multiple reactions simultaneously. Still, Rigel was new enough to the subject that even something as basic as the differences between magical coefficients was interesting to her.

"What about it?" Dumbledore prompted, reminding her of her question as she recalled herself from her musings.

"Does a higher coefficient mean that pine as an ingredient has less innate magic per unit than cypress? Or does it mean that pine is more resistant to transformation?"

"In this case, it is the latter," the Headmaster said, smiling vaguely, "But the answer is not important as long as you have the proportions correct. Why is that, Mr. Black?"

Rigel thought. "Whether it is more resistant to magic or simply containing less magic, the extra amount of magic on the input side will be distributed in the same way, acting on the material that requires the magic," Rigel said slowly, "So all you need to know is how much magic to add, regardless of why."

"Precisely," Dumbledore said, "It is a sad truth of our times in fact that many burgeoning alchemists do not bother learning the exact whys of various ingredients' magic constants, because that particularly tedious endeavor has already been undertaken by the unlucky wizards who invented the field."

Rigel thought that made a certain amount of sense, even if it seemed an incredibly lazy way to learn a discipline.

"Aren't the coefficients just averages?" Rigel asked, approaching a theory she'd been mulling over for some time, "When I make a potion that calls for eight ounces of beetle wings, I can tell by smelling the fluid they're preserved in how potent they are, and if I should add slightly more or less of any given jar. If you took pine wood that grew near an incredibly potent natural reservoir of magic, wouldn't its magic coefficient be slightly lower than the average for pine?"

"It certainly would," Dumbledore twinkled happily at her, "It will be many years before you are expected to be able to compensate for your ingredients in such a manner, however. Indeed, most students do not even think to ask such a question until well into their second or third year of study."

Rigel felt her neck grow hot at the indirect praise, and mumbled, "It's just how I would see a potion, so…"

"So there we see why Professor Snape's recommendation, as stingy as he is with them, is a necessary prerequisite for this subject," Dumbledore said agreeably, "At times I think that I wouldn't mind a few more students, but I cannot deny that no student Professor Snape has recommended to me has even fallen short of exceeding my expectations."

"There are other students, though," Rigel hazarded, setting down her quill for a moment, "In other levels, I mean."

Dumbledore smiled, "Just the one, at this moment. Mr. Albright, a sixth year Gryffindor. Are you acquainted?"

Rigel shook her head, "Not that I'm aware."

"Well, he is an exceptionally bright boy, and very keen on pursuing a Mastery in Alchemy when he graduates," Dumbledore said, a bit of pride seeping into his voice, "You might introduce yourself, if your paths cross. Although your place in this class is of course a secret, I am sure Mr. Albright would be happy to indulge a fellow…enthusiast, were you to seek his help on some of the more complicated concepts."

"I'll be sure to keep my eyes open for him," Rigel said, wondering if she could ask Percy to introduce her. As Head Boy, he had to know most of the upperclassmen in his House.

The lesson continued with her practicing calculations for different types of woods and metals in varying amounts. Dumbledore waved her off to History of Magic with a sandwich in hand and many interesting things to think about.

Rigel and the other third-year Slytherins were on their way to the Great Hall for lunch later that day when they heard it.

Thump, stamp, thump, stamp! Boom! Boom! Boom!

"What on earth?" Tracy Davis gasped, echoing Rigel's thoughts exactly.

They all looked upwards reflexively, despite knowing the racket was at least two stories above them.

"Come on!" Theo said, picking up the pace, "Let's check it out."

They sped up to just under what might qualify as a run, and soon reached the staircase leading to the Great Hall, at which point the commotion became exponentially louder. Upon reaching the top of the stairs, they ran into a roadblock in the form of a large crowd of students pressed to either side of the entrance hall. Not tall enough to crane her neck over the tops of the other students, Rigel peered between heads and subtly shifted through the throng until she had a clear view of what was happening.

The Hogwarts suits of armor appeared to be on parade.

Blinking to make sure she hadn't stumbled upon a mass hallucination, Rigel let her eyes sweep the scene. A long line of suits of armor, some of which Rigel realized in retrospect had indeed been missing from their usual stations along the dungeon hallways, stretched along the Entrance Hall from the doors of the Great Hall to the grand staircase. She could see the cue extending up the stairs, winding about the landings and several more staircases before becoming lost somewhere in the upper levels.

The suits of armor were marching to a slow but steady beat of thump, stamp, thump, stamp! Boom! Boom! Boom! Every other step was accentuated with the thump of a pike or spear against the floor, and every fourth step was followed by resounding booms as the suits carrying swords crashed them against their shields as though banging on metal gongs. It made for an unholy racket, but most of the watching students were grinning even as they clutched their hands to their ears.

Rigel began to smile when it became clear, from the cheering students and disgruntled but resigned expressions on the staff members' faces, that this was not supposed to be happening. A prank, then—but how on earth had Fred and George pulled this off?

As the procession fed into the Great Hall, students began filtering in alongside them, eager to see what all the suits of armor were going to do next. Rigel followed along, catching sight of Pansy gesturing amusedly to a grimacing but nevertheless impressed-looking Draco just ahead of her. She caught up to them in time to hear Pansy say, "—and look, they've all got the house colors on!"

Rigel looked, and saw that the suits of armor, once through the doors, broke regiment one by one and sat down as though just coming in to eat lunch. As they sat, Rigel could see that each had a colored neckerchief tied to the bottom on their helmets that corresponded to the table he or she sat down at. More and more suits of armor marched in, more and more students pouring in along with them, and by the time the last suit of armor sat down at the Ravenclaw table, nearly every student in the school seemed to be crowded along the edges of the Great Hall, watching.

"Don't suppose they're going to eat our lunch?" Draco drawled into the momentary silence.

Before Rigel had finished smiling at the joke, there was movement once more. A suit of armor from the Hufflepuff table suddenly stood up and waved across the hall. A suit of armor from the Slytherin table, to everyone's surprise, stood and waved back, then gestured in an exaggerated 'come over' motion. The suit of armor from the Hufflepuff table got up, crossed the hall, and the other suits of armor at the Slytherin table scooted over and made room for it, patting it on the back in a welcoming way.

"What is that supposed to mean?" she heard one student mutter behind her.

Soon it was clear, however, as more suits of armor began abandoning the tables that corresponded to their neck cloths and sitting with 'friends' from other tables instead. Eventually, all the tables were completely mixed, and then the suits of armor began stomping their feet and pounding their hands on the tables in front of them all at once.

At first it sounded like noise, but slowly Rigel began to hear a pattern emerging. "It's the Hogwarts anthem," she said, smiling in appreciation.

"What?" Draco snorted, "No it isn't."

"He's right, Drake," Pansy said, cocking her head, "Listen… whether we be old and bold…"

"Or young with scabby knees!" several nearby people sang out excitedly.

Before long, everyone was singing along to the beat of the armored band. With a round of hearty laughter and cheers to finish off the final verse, the suits of armor stood as one, bowed, and then began an orderly evacuation of the hall, presumably back to their posts throughout the school.

As the clamor died down and students finally started to take their seats for lunch, a young voice cried out loudly, "I'm sitting with the Ravenclaws today!"

"Well I'm eating with the Hufflepuffs!" another voice answered.

Two small boys in Slytherin ties, who Rigel recognized as the second-year twins with the perpetually-sly expressions, darted from the crowd and raced to the tables they'd claimed without further consideration or ado.

"Oh, no," Draco muttered sourly. Rigel supposed it was rather obvious where this was going to go next.

A second later the Weasley twins separated themselves from the other side of the hall with matching grins and sat down firmly at the Ravenclaw table with innocent expressions. After that it was organized chaos as students from all Houses plopped down at whichever table suited their fancy, giggling and waving to friends across the hall all the while.

Draco headed determinedly toward the Slytherin table, but Rigel said lightly, "I think I'll go visit with some of my Gryffindor friends today."

"Not you, too!" Draco groaned, rubbing his head agitatedly, "What a mockery."

"It's supposed to be fun, Draco," Rigel said, shaking her head with amusement. "I suppose it's a good idea for some of us to sit at the Slytherin table, though—have to make the new additions feel welcome, right?"

Draco rolled his eyes and turned his back on her without another word. She did notice him smiling tightly at a nervous-looking Ravenclaw who'd taken his usual seat, though, so she guessed he wasn't as annoyed as he let on. In fact, she mused, weaving through the swarm of students, it was probably a lot of work for him to feel anything but excitement and enjoyment at the moment, with so many happy people about. She supposed she ought to be impressed at his tenacity, if nothing else. The headache probably helps, though, she allowed mentally.

When she passed the Weasley twins on her way to the Gryffindor table, she slowed down to give them a congratulatory grin. To her surprise, however, they both shook their heads at her in bemused defeat. Raising her eyebrows, she wondered who was responsible for this enormous prank if not the Weasley twins. Her mind went back to the incident at last year's going away feast. Fred and George had denied that one, too.

If there was a new group of pranksters in the school, they certainly knew how to put on a show.

On Thursday evening, Rigel found herself with free time before her Astronomy lesson, and, since the weather permitted a walk, packed up her Healing notes and stopped by the kitchens to beg a mouse from Binny before heading out to the edge of the Forbidden Forest.

She had been devoting more time than usual to her Healing studies, and Rigel thought her extra attention was paying off nicely. It was much harder for her to Heal while she wore her suppressant ring, but she found the challenge engaging rather than frustrating, and the end result more satisfying when she had to work for it magically as well as mentally.

Archie was getting regular practice on humans at AIM, and while she couldn't match that kind of experience without turning all of her friends into guinea pigs, she could and did put her growing skills to use out in the forest. If Madam Pomfrey wondered how she practiced when she only had one class on theory a week with the Healer, she hadn't yet asked. Rigel didn't think practicing on animals was unethical—there were all kinds of injured animals in the forest, and if she didn't at least attempt to heal them, they'd likely be preyed upon by stronger creatures in the wood. In any case, one of the perks of magical Healing, unlike muggle medicine, was that as long as it was actual Healing, not potions, the magic worked just as well on animals as on humans.

When she reached the tree line, she began to walk along it. She preferred not to go far into the forest proper, seeing as it was technically forbidden, and usually there was no need to. Sure as clockwork, within ten minutes of her traversing the fringes of the forest a soft hissing voice caught her ear.

"Ssspeaker! Come thisss way!"

Following the familiar croon, Rigel soon came upon her frequent companion of the forest, Treeslider. He was getting quicker at scenting her out, she noted, or perhaps he had recently moved his nest closer to the forest's edge. The boomslang snake was a bit difficult to see in the setting light of the approaching sunset, but he wiggled in place until her eyes caught sight of his thin, green form. His eyes were disproportionately big on his head, and they seemed to gleam excitedly when she knelt down next to him.

"You have come again, ssspeaker," the snake swung his head back and forth approvingly, "You come with giftsss?"

"Of courssse," Rigel said softly, fishing in her bag for the mouse she carried. She set the cloth-covered bundle gently on the ground and uncovered the rodent with a little flourish.

"It isss ssso sssmall," Treeslider complained, poking the mouse morosely with his tail.

"You alwaysss sssay that," Rigel smiled with amusement, "Thisss wasss the biggessst one they had in the kitchensss."

"That isss becaussse your cassstle hasss too many moussse-killersss inssside," the snake bemoaned. Rigel had discovered that Treeslider had a generally poor opinion of any animal he might have to compete against in mice-catching, cats and owls included.

"If the moussse is ssso sssub-par perhapsss I ssshouldn't bother sssuplying them," Rigel said wistfully.

"That lacksss sssenssse, Ssspeaker," Treeslider assured her quickly, "You sssimply need more practiccce at sssupplying."

"Practiccce?" Rigel asked, "What am I to be practicccing for?"

"For your future nessstlingsss," the snake hissed out a laugh. "But of courssse you mussst firssst tempt a mate, yesss?"

"Definitely no," Rigel rolled her eyes, "To matesss and nessstlingsss both."

Treeslider hissed disapprovingly, "Life isss nothing without thossse thingsss, sssilly Ssspeaker."

"I have other thingsss in my life," Rigel said, "Sssuch as my reassson for coming. Have you any newsss?"

"Of sssick and dying creaturesss?" Treeslider curled and uncurled unhappily, "I sssupossse I know of one. But I do not think you ssshould be helping thisss one, Ssspeaker. It ssswiped at me asss I ssslid by earlier."

"I'm sssure it was merely jealousss of your ssstunning ssscales," Rigel cajoled, "Have you been sssunning yourssself recccently?"

"You noticcced!" the boomslang snake positively preened, stretching his body and turning his scales until they appeared to the best advantage, "A pity all creaturesss do not possssessss ssscales."

"I'm sssure the other creaturessss agree," Rigel said, ever-amazed by the vanity of snakes. "Can you take me to thisss poor, ssscalelesss, injured creature?"

"I ssshall," Treeslider poked his nose against the mouse once more, "You will hold thisss sssnack while we ssslither. I will eat it onccce you have sssettled."

Rigel gamely picked up the dead mouse once more and followed the snake through the undergrowth. Treeslider led her somewhat deeper into the forest than she was comfortable with, but Rigel knew from experience that her friend would be willing to show her the way out once he was finished eating, so she wasn't afraid of losing her way.

A few minutes later, she could hear a pitiful whining noise coming through the trees. As they rounded a particularly large trunk, Rigel caught sight of a huddled lump of fur shivering in the leaves. Suppressing the urge to coo at the wretched thing, Rigel approached the animal slowly, saying, "Hey there, little one." Its head snapped up and Rigel had to smile at the mournful look it gave her from its big puppy eyes. It was a baby crup, and when Rigel squinted at its neck, her suspicion was confirmed; a tattered yellow ribbon marked the crup as Hannah Abbott's.

"How'd you get all the way out here?" she murmured, reaching out her fingers for it to sniff sadly at. She sat down beside the little pup, and when it tried to stand and move toward her, she saw its left forepaw collapse beneath it. Before it could finish yelping, Rigel scooped it up gently and deposited it on its back in her lap.

"How long hasss it been sssitting here, Treessslider?" Rigel asked, wondering if Hannah was looking for it.

"Not ssso long, asss it hasssn't been sssnacked on yet," the snake said, a bit unkindly. "It isss ssstupid for wandering thisss way. Ssso many ssstupid animalsss in your cassstle, more and more wandering thisss way of late."

Ignoring the grumbling snake, Rigel got her wand out of her pocket and whispered a 'Lumos' to give herself some more light. The dying sun didn't penetrate the thick leaves very well in this part of the forest. She carefully extracted the crup's injured paw and examined it. There was sticky red blood covering the soft pad, and Rigel suspected the pup had simply stepped on something sharp. Still, she examined the joint and bones of its leg just for the sake of professionalism.

Once assured that the only injury was a flesh wound, Rigel began softly cleaning the blood away to look for the source. The crup whined as she revealed a fairly large gash between two of its toes. Shushing it absently, Rigel bent her mind to the task of Healing. As she ran her wand along the cut, she imbued her magic into the area around it. The flesh knit together under her watchful gaze, first into a bloody scab, then fading to light pink scar tissue before smoothing out into soft, unblemished skin. She debated trying her hand at re-growing the fur there, but decided she wasn't confident enough with that spell just yet. She might overdo it and end up making the poor pup look like a miniature wolf.

The crup attempted to lick her face happily as she stood up with it in her arms, but Rigel avoided its slobber while turning to see if Treeslider had finished his meal. The boomslang snake was nearly comatose with happiness, it seemed, curled around the awkward bulge in its stomach.

"I sssuppossse you want to ssset off onccce more?" he hissed, stirring blearily.

"Thanksss, friend," she said, following the sluggish snake toward the edge of the forest.

Before long, she could see the end of the forest up ahead. Night was setting in, with just a deep orange glow to break up the shadows.

"Sssee you nexxxt time, Ssspeaker," Treeslider said, swaying his way back into the forest contentedly. Rigel smiled after him. He was an amiable snake, despite how prickly he pretended to be.

As she emerged from the forest, a cracking sound further along the tree line cause her to freeze, listening intently. Anything big enough to make a sizable branch snap was something she should definitely try to avoid. Why would something that big be so close to the castle, though? As far as she knew, the greater denizens of the Forbidden Forest preferred to lurk in the deeper, darker expanses.

After a moment of intense listening, however, she heard a soft whistling noise coming from the same direction. Relaxing, she wondered who was taking a walk so close to dusk. Then she realized the person wasn't whistling a tune, but making the high-pitched noise to call something.

"I guess your owner is looking for you," she told the crup, scratching it behind its ears to keep it from leaping down. It would be better if it stayed off its foot for a day or so. "Over here!" she called out softly, starting toward the whistler.

There came the sound of rustling, and then the whistler rounded a tree just ahead of Rigel. It wasn't Abbott, to her surprise.

"Blaise?" she said, slowing to a stop, "What are you doing out here?"

"Rigel?" her friend sounded completely nonplussed, "I thought you were in your lab tonight."

Rigel shook her head, "I'm not always in there, you know."

"Apparently," Blaise said, a smirk on his dark face, "Searching for potions ingredients?"

"Just taking a walk," she huffed out a laugh, "I heard this one yelping, though, and got a little side-tracked. Were you whistling for it?"

Blaise's teeth flashed white in the growing dark, "Yes, I was. I didn't think I'd actually find it, but…" he trailed off, shrugging sheepishly. "I overheard Hannah crying at dinner. She's worried sick over this thing. Said this is the third time it's run off in the last month, but this time she couldn't find it anywhere in the castle."

"So you thought you'd find it for her?" Rigel asked, smiling slightly, "I guess you two are friends, now?"

"Something like that," Blaise said, frowning, "Is it injured? You said it was yelping."

"Ah, it was," Rigel said, now giving her own sheepish shrug, "I think it stepped on something sharp and tore its paw open. I healed the gash, but the fur will take a little while to grow back in, so you'll have to explain that to Hannah. Tell her to make sure it doesn't run around too much for the next twelve hours, as well."

Blaise accepted the crup gently, inspecting the paw for himself with serious eyes, "I will tell her. Thank you, Rigel. It was very kind of you to care for a lost animal so thoroughly."

"It wasn't any trouble," Rigel said, honestly, "I appreciate the practice for my Healing skills, and I think it would take a real monster to just leave an injured animal—especially someone's pet—alone in the dark."

"Such a thing takes less than you think," Blaise said, voice low. "Let us get back to the castle. It will be night, soon."

They made their way across the lawn toward the castle steps.

"You know," Rigel said tentatively, "You don't have to mention me. To Abbott, I mean. It might sound more impressive if you tell her you found it all on your own."

Blaise chuckled softly, "Do you take me for a liar, Rigel? And how would I explain the healed cut? I am no Mediwizard."

"It's an easy enough spell for anyone to learn," Rigel said, "So you could stretch the truth a little tonight and then learn the spell tomorrow. Don't you want to be her hero?" she added, nudging her friend playfully.

"If I told anyone I was getting love advice from Rigel Black, they'd laugh themselves into a coma," Blaise drawled, "I suppose I would owe you one for supporting the altered story?"

"Of course not, Blaise, we're friends," Rigel said, grinning, "I owe Abbott a debt, too, so it's in my interest to make her happy. Aren't you going to make her happy?"

"I'll try to," Blaise said, looking subdued once more, "It's complicated, though. Our families have been aligned for centuries, but because of something my mother did, there was a falling out between the members of the previous generation. Hannah and I ought to have been close, should have been raised together, really, but we hardly know one another. It is…difficult to vie with my instincts; they get closer to the surface every passing day."

"Is there anything I can do to help?" Rigel asked, worried because Blaise, cool, unflappable Blaise, seemed worried.

"No," he smiled, stopping on the top step in front of the Entrance Hall, "I thank you, but this age is notoriously difficult among my kind. I will come to terms with these things in time. I think…a closer relationship with Hannah will help."

"I'll teach you how to Heal a cut like this tomorrow," Rigel said firmly, "Just imply you learned it in order to have basic first-aid knowledge. It's a good idea, in any case, and a girl likes a guy who thinks ahead."

"What do you know about girls, Rigel?" Blaise raised an eyebrow.

"Well, Pansy once told me that ladies appreciate it when gentlemen think through their actions before taking them," Rigel said lightly, "I believe she was rebuking Draco for eating so many strawberry tarts that he got sick, but I think the sentiment is sound.

Blaise laughed, "If Pansy thinks something, it must be a golden truth. Her mind is razor sharp."

"It is," Rigel agreed, stepping into the castle and holding the door for Blaise, who somehow managed to look extremely suave cradling the crup, "Most people don't notice how smart she is, for some reason."

"The reason is Pansy is very good at what she does," Blaise snorted. At Rigel's quizzical look, he shook his head wryly, "Never mind, my friend. Thank you again for this. I'll see you back in the dorms later."

At the stairs heading down, they split ways, Rigel continuing down into the dungeons and Blaise making his way toward the Hufflepuff common room. She silently wished him the best of luck, and wondered vaguely if crup hair would be of any use in a potion. She had a goodly amount of the stuff stuck to her robes, now, and there was really no sense letting it go to waste.

As Fall made headway toward Winter's embrace and the days grew shorter, Rigel found her days, quite contrarily, becoming longer. She tried to resist the temptation to use the time-turner more than she needed to, but there always seemed to be a need. Sometimes it was a supplementary book that she felt she really ought to read before the next Arithmancy class, other times it was an extra hour or two spent meditating in the quiet of the library, but whatever the reason it was always educational. At least, that's what she told herself when the guilt became noticeably insistent.

The less academic activities were necessary, too, she argued, to keep her healthy and mentally sound so that she could do well in her many classes—which was exactly the purpose of the time-turner in the first place, so she wasn't doing anything wrong. For instance, when she realized that she was only exercising once every real-time day, she made a point to add at least an hour of physical activity to every additional twenty-four hours of turned-time she lived. It wouldn't do to grow lethargic and weak, after all—that sort of unhealthiness lead to stress. In any case, Dueling was one of the subjects she considered an important part of her education, and staying in shape was critical to her learning in that field.

Sleep was also very important to healthy functioning, she told herself. If she were going to live a day twice, she might as well live the night twice as well, and use the extra turned hours to sleep. In this way, she could, for instance, live all of Thursday normally, sleep the night in her room, then turn back a full 24-hours to Thursday morning, work on brewing or studying in the room of requirement, sleep there overnight, then sneak back into her room in time to 'wake' with Draco for morning exercise on Friday.

All told, it was a very satisfying system. She felt healthy, mentally and physically, she was ahead in many of her classes, her extracurricular pursuits were progressing at a reasonable speed, Flint's assignments were completed in record time (from his point of view, at least), Krait had no complaints about the amount of product she supplied him, and she was closer to her classmates than ever.

There was no reason to feel nervous, she told herself as she approached Professor Snape's office door on Friday night. Snape was only going to assess her mental competency and emotional state. He would have no reason to take the time-turner away. She refused to give him one.

She knocked and waited to be granted entry. This was the first actual psychological evaluation Snape had gotten around to arranging, so she wasn't sure what to expect.

When the sharp bid to come in sounded from inside the office, Rigel entered with her most placid expression, a relaxed poise to her walk that Rispah herself had deemed 'serene.'

"Sit," Snape said, moving a stack of essays to the side of his desk. As Rigel did so, Snape pulled a folder from a drawer and opened it. Inside was a form that he drew out and placed before her.

At the head was a crest the she was familiar with, having seen it on a politely-worded letter addressed to Harriet Potter not long ago. The parchment was from the Department of Mysteries, and it appeared to be an evaluation form specific to those who had access to time-turners. There were places at the top for the subject's name, age before using the time-turner, reasons for use, frequency of use, noticeable side-effects if any (including signs of obvious aging, which was a check-box of its own), and so on.

Rigel filled in the top portion herself, then passed it back to Professor Snape, who she supposed was the 'evaluator' responsible for conducting the psychological interview and reporting in the blanks that made up the latter half of the form.

"To clarify, you have noticed no obvious side effects from your usage of the time-turner, including but not limited to disorientation, dizziness, nausea, loss of memory, or a sense of the surreal?" Snape asked, sounding very much like he was reading from a particularly dull essay on frogsporn.

"None," Rigel said, "It works just as you said it would, Professor."

"Good," Snape scanned the form for a moment, then looked at her piercingly, "You noted that you use the time-turner five hours each day? Including weekends?"

"Approximately," Rigel said, lying through her teeth, "On days like Tuesday, it's closer to nine or ten once I include time spent doing homework and preparing for lessons, but other days, like weekends, I don't need to turn as much to keep up with work."

"Are you adjusting your sleep cycle appropriately to account for the differences in awake hours?" Snape asked, frowning.

"I am," Rigel said, "The sleep-cycle adjusting potion turned out to be very easy to tweak, so I can lengthen or shorten my sleep cycle day-to-day." Not that she needed to on those days she decided to repeat the nights as well.

"Do you find you have difficulty staying awake in classes that you've doubled-up on, or at the end of a very long day of turned-time?" Snape asked.

"Not at all," Rigel said, "Unless you count History of Magic."

At Snape's sharp look, she dropped her small smile and coughed apologetically. It had been a mistake to make a joke, apparently.

"Can you remember what you were doing on Wednesday at eleven in the morning?" Snape asked after ticking another box on the form.

"I was in Transfigurations, taking a quiz on the different methods of animate to inanimate transfiguration," Rigel said, "I was also with you in Lab One, re-brewing a Memory-Restoration Draught for the third time."

"Very good," Snape said, moving his quill down the form, "Is there anyone who might have noticed your use of the time-turner thus far? Anyone asking suspicious questions or making accusations pertaining to your workload or schedule?"

"Not that I know of," Rigel said, "The only class someone might notice a discrepancy in is Magical Theory on Tuesdays. There's only Hannah Abbott and Anthony Goldstein in that section with me, however, and they have no reason to mention me to anyone, much less my housemates."

"Your friends don't notice your disproportionate amount of schoolwork?" Snape asked, one eyebrow raised.

"I'm known amongst my peers for having academic interests beyond classwork," Rigel said carefully, "No one thinks it odd anymore that I study all the time. It helps that they're all busy with elective work, too."

Snape inclined his head and moved on, "Do you feel at all disconnected with reality or tempted to abandon your present life to one of quiet solitude in the folds of time?"

"Excuse me?" Rigel blinked. They couldn't be serious.

"Just answer the question," Snape said, sounding aggrieved, "And in the future expect that anything pertaining to the Department of Mysteries will be cryptic and likely eccentric in nature. Many believe they are intentionally anomalous."

"Ah, no," Rigel said, her lips quirking, "I don't feel at all tempted to retire from reality."

"As you appear to be in good health and of sound mind, I am concluding this interview unless you have anything relevant to add," Snape said, poising his quill above the signature line expectantly.

"Go ahead, sir, I just have one question—purely for curiosity's sake," Rigel said.

Snape finished off the form with an impatient scratch and jerked his head in invitation for her to speak.

"What would happen if I did show signs of obvious aging?" Rigel asked, "Would I take a de-aging potion to compensate?"

Snape tilted his head considering, "Possibly. I'm not sure what the standard procedure is, but you are unlikely to necessitate it. At this point you should be no more than nine or ten days older than your classmates. Unless you greatly speed up your usage, you are unlikely to experience an acceleration in aging significant enough to cause notice."

Rigel nodded, knowing that with the Modified Polyjuice in effect no one would notice even if she aged twice as quickly. She would notice, of course, as her monthly courses came more often than 30 days now, but she had decided that was actually to her advantage. Now the symptoms that came along with her period, like fatigue and stomach aches, wouldn't be noticeably regular. If anyone thought to count the days she was tired or, in the case of someone like Remus, smelled slightly off, it would seem largely random.

It was interesting nevertheless to consider the possibilities; she wondered how common time-turner usage was, that there were procedures in place for all possible contingencies. If she did find out how the Ministry handled accelerated aging, maybe she could make use of their method when the summer came and her Polyjuice needed to be reworked.

Snape dismissed her after asking a few questions about her new electives, and Rigel bade him goodnight as she stepped into the hallway.

A few minutes later for Rigel, she passed through hallways lit by the mid-day sun. She wasn't worried about anyone seeing her on the way to the room of requirement—all her classmates were down in Herbology at the moment. If she hurried, she might finish the rest of the Blood Replenishers for Burke's order before dinner.

Saturday morning there was a great deal of ruckus in the Great Hall. It was always noisier on the weekends, with everyone more relaxed and optimistic about the day, but Rigel thought she could detect an extra level of exuberance in the air as she stirred raisins into her oatmeal.

"What's all the fuss about?" she asked, addressing the table with a gesture that encompassed all the laughing, shouting kids around them.

"You're kidding, right?" Theo asked, a smile tugging at his cheek.

"You know he isn't," Millicent said, rolling her eyes.

"I appear to have missed something obvious," Rigel said to no one in particular.

"It's the first Hogsmeade weekend!" Theo said, a full grin now stretching his features, "And we're third years, in case you've forgotten. We get to go!"

Rigel had known that third-years had Hogsmeade privileges, but she'd somehow never applied that knowledge to herself. She'd been to Hogsmeade before, of course, but she supposed it would be a nice break from the Hogwarts grounds. She could restock at the apothecary, too, which would save her from needing to owl-order supplies before the winter break.

"You did get your permission slip signed, right?" Blaise asked, gazing shrewdly at her.

Rigel felt her heart thud as she realized she had no idea whether Sirius had signed it or not. She vaguely remembered Archie commenting on it as they went through one another's school papers on one of the long summer afternoons. She recalled that he'd set it to the side, but… "I think so," she said slowly, "I guess I should look for it."

"Your father probably mailed it in. That was part of the directions," Draco said, chuckling a little. He didn't seem to be feeling the strain of so much excitement around him, though Rigel thought he was merely getting better at hiding the effects his gift had on him at the same rate he was getting better at controlling it.

"Maybe," Rigel said, hoping that was the case. It would be a shame to miss spending the day with her friends because she'd been too absent-minded to ask Archie about a simple form.

"Just ask Professor Snape if he received it," Pansy suggested.

"Right," she said. Catching sight of Snape getting up to leave the hall, Rigel wiped her mouth with a napkin and hurried to stand. "Be right back," she said.

Snape, noticing her approach with his usual inability to miss anything in his sphere of perception, stopped just outside the doors. "Yes, Mr. Black?" he said, "Are you not eager to be away with your friends to Zonko's and its ilk?"

"I am," Rigel smiled, knowing that most of his sardonic tone was affected in this instance, "I came to double-check that you'd received my permission form. Can I infer from your question that I am allowed to go?"

"You may," Snape said, one eyebrow raised aloofly. "Your father didn't tell you he'd sent it in?"

"He probably did," Rigel said, affecting a sheepish shrug, "I must have forgotten. Thanks, Professor Snape."

She left at his nod, returning to her friends. She didn't notice her Professor's puzzled frown following her back to the Slytherin table.

"So you're coming?" Draco asked as she sat back down.

"Apparently," Rigel said, "Where should we go first?"

"Shopping first," Millicent said, looking excited, "Then the Three Broomsticks for lunch. Then more shopping."

"Why are we going again?" Draco asked, nudging Rigel conspiratorially.

"To hold things, apparently," she said, playing along.

"That's what you get for going stag," Theo said, radiating smugness.

"What's that supposed to mean—you've got a date?" Draco demanded. "Is that why you've been acting like a peacock all morning?"

"I haven't!" Theo protested. Seeing Draco's smirk and Rigel's own admittedly curious look, he added, "Blaise has a date, too."

Theo's bid, while clumsy, was certainly effective.

"Blaise?" Draco nearly choked in his surprise. Rigel privately thought he ought to stop relying on his gift to tell him things about the people around him—clearly he was missing more concrete observations if he was caught that flat-footed. Even Rigel could tell Blaise was dressed especially nice that morning. She hadn't put much thought into the information, but Draco would have, if he'd noticed.

"I asked Hannah to meet me at Wizards' Waifs," Blaise said, smiling slightly, "I thought her crup's ribbon looked a little frayed, and offered to replace it with a yellow collar from the shop. It's hardly a date."

Rigel ignored the small puddle that had just formed in her gut, suspecting that if she dwelled on it her face would look something like Millicent's, which was currently doing a silent impression of the word 'awww.'

"That's very sweet, Blaise," Pansy said, seeming impressed.

"Thank you, Pansy," Blaise said, "It's not nearly as sweet at Theo's date, though. Where were you taking Padma Patil, again? Madam Puddlefluff?"

"Puddifoot's," Theo muttered, looking distinctly less smug. Rigel thought it served him right for trying to throw Blaise to the thestrals like that.

"I'm sure you'll have a lovely time," Pansy said, not quite stifling a smile.

They finished breakfast and set out toward the carriages with grins all around. Rigel couldn't remember the last time she and her friends had done something novel. She could see why the weekends at Hogsmeade had become such a successful tradition.

Millicent, Draco, Pansy, and Rigel took a carriage together. Millicent and Pansy set about planning which order they should visit shops in, taking into consideration such things as likelihood of crowds at various times, leaving heavier purchases for after lunch, and so on.

Draco insisted they visit Spintwitches Sporting Supply. "Where do you want to go, Rigel?"

"Oh, didn't I tell you?" Rigel said airily, "I actually have a date—"

"Very funny," Draco deadpanned, not looking the least bit impressed.

"It isn't entirely outside the realm of possibility, Draco," Pansy said, a sly smile on her face, "Rigel is quite good looking, and very smart."

Draco snorted, "Like that's the issue."

"I think I'm insulted," Rigel said lightly.

"You aren't either," Draco said. Damn empathy. "Tell me you're interested in someone romantically and I'll eat my tie."

Rigel had to concede that point to her blonde friend. She certainly had no interest in romance of any kind.

When Draco continued to stare at her, she raised a questioning eyebrow at him. He shook his head as though dispelling a ridiculous thought, and said, "You don't care where we go, then?"

"Apothecary," she said quickly.

"We might have guessed," Pansy said, not unkindly.

"Zonko's," she added, knowing Remus might ask what she'd picked up in town when he saw her next. They didn't interact much outside of class, just friendly waves in the hall and the occasional quick exchange between classes. It helped that Remus and Archie had never been as close as Harry and Remus were. It also helped that Remus seemed to be keeping a professional distance in deference to his new position.

"Okay," Millicent said, looking a bit taken aback but jotting it down dutifully, "Let's go there first, then, before the crowd."

Rigel wasn't sure they were entirely successful in beating the crowd, considering how many people were inside of the joke shop when they approached, but there was room enough for the four of them to squeeze through the door, at least.

She didn't really need anything from Zonko's, since the twins supplied their own pranking materials, so she browsed the shelves with an eye toward sending Archie a care package. Her cousin really ought to be rewarded for all his hard work this semester. He didn't have a time-turner, after all. Even if he was only learning the classes she was 'officially' taking, he still had a full plate.

She picked up a few tins of colored sneezing powder that turned invisible upon contact with skin—at least until that skin came into contact with water, at which point the powder condensed into a colored goo that was nearly impossibly to scrape off. She also snagged a couple of barrier buttons, remembering how effectively Patil had used one against her last year. After a moment's consideration, she picked up a packet of teacher-trackers as well, recalling that Archie and she had used the packet they'd picked up for her birthday trying to track the neighbor's collection of cats. Archie was convinced they were the ones who ate the miniature pies he and Lily had set on the window ledge to cool. Rigel personally thought James the more likely culprit, but it had been fun attempting to prove otherwise.

"Rigel, look at this," Millicent said, holding up a bag of sleeping dust with the familiar Marauder logo on it. "Does this stuff work? I have trouble sleeping before big exams, sometimes."

She peered at the dust inside the see-through bag, then smiled ruefully, "It works—a bit too well to use for a good night's sleep, though. Sirius tested that one on m—ah, on my cousin Harry. She slept for two days straight."

"They drugged her?" Pansy asked, looking slightly aghast.

"Not really," Rigel said, shaking her head. "It's not ingestible. You just blow it in someone's face and they fall asleep standing up. It's actually a very complicated stasis spell that my uncles tweaked to look like sleep, though. It doesn't dehydrate you or make you hungry, even. You wake up feeling like no time has passed."

"That's…a bit intense," Millicent said, slowly putting the pouch back on the shelf.

"They probably toned it down before selling it," Rigel said, distractedly. "Most of the things my cousin and I see at home get much tamer before they hit the stores. The two-day version of sleeping powder probably got submitted to the DOML developments division, now that I think about it."

"Your prankster uncles develop weaponizeable wizardtech for the Aurors?" Draco asked quietly.

"Well…" Rigel looked away from the display of trick wands and caught the mildly astonished look on Draco's face. "Is that not a common thing for inventors to do?"

"All wizards who work in experimental magic need a special permit to even attempt projects that might have dangerous uses," Draco said seriously, "It's extremely difficult to obtain one, though. The hoops the Ministry makes people jump through are ridiculously involved."

"Really?" Rigel hadn't known that. As long as she could remember, experimental magic had been a normal part of her family's everyday life. Her mother tested experimental products and spells that her company was contracted to certify as safe, and her uncles all had a hand in designing and reworking Marauder products. When James and Sirius casually discussed which versions of what products would be safe to mass distribute and which would have potential for Auror development, it seemed natural to her. Was experimentation truly so uncommon in the wider Wizarding world?

"How can you not know that?" Draco asked, frowning. "I suppose it's easy for the Head Auror to get permits for his joke products. Never mind all the witches and wizards whose applications get turned away by the screening board every year simply because of the nature of their magical heritage."

Dark wizards, she realized he meant. She didn't bother pointing out that James, Sirius, and Remus must have obtained permits long before James and Sirius became distinguished Aurors. The Marauder line was well over a decade old, after all. Instead she asked herself: was it true that ancestrally dark witches and wizards would have a more difficult time obtaining permits to experiment with potentially dangerous spells and potions? Probably, she acknowledged mentally. Was that unjustified, though? She didn't know.

I don't know a lot of things, she thought tiredly.

"I'm sorry for speaking so casually about it," Rigel said after a moment of reflection. "It was such a prominent part of my upbringing that I didn't think to question it before now."

"That makes perfect sense, Rigel," Pansy said smoothly, placing a hand on both Draco and Rigel's arms, as though she could physically diffuse the tension between them. "I had noticed that you never thought it extraordinary that you and your cousin both began experimenting with potions at such a young age."

Rigel blinked, not having thought of that, either. Experimentation always seemed the natural aim of any study of magic, potions included. Why explore a field without the eventual intention to improve it? If you weren't going to contribute anything, why join the dialogue of progress in the first place?

"I suppose," she said, speaking slowly as she tried to work out where the disconnect was, "I must have been too close to the idea to see how unusual it was. As far back as I remember, my cousin and I have read Potions journals and Medical periodicals, and the important articles are always about improvements to the field and newly developing methodologies. All of the adults I grew up with worked in spell development. Even mom, before she passed." Seeing the regretful expressions on her friends' faces, she hurriedly summoned a smile, "So, I really never imagined doing anything else with my life. The more I learn about magic, the more sure I am that everything is connected, that all branches of magic bleed into one another and can be used to advance other fields in surprising ways. I—" she broke off, realizing that she had been speaking a bit too forcefully, saying things she hadn't even known she believed until they spilled out.

"Now I get why you took Magical Theory, at least," Millicent said, smiling bracingly, "Though how you noticed being the only one in there is beyond me."

"There are three people in my class," Rigel said, feeling stupid as she finally woke up to the implication that only three out of about fifty students were even interested in spell-development and the theory of how magic worked across disciplines. And she knew Anthony Goldstein, at least, was only taking the class as a required pre-requisite for the NEWT-level curse-breaking elective.

Draco seemed to thaw a bit at her obviously abashed expression. "Only you could be so entirely oblivious, Rigel."

"Thanks," she said wryly, "I guess that's what I have you guys for."

They left Rigel to pay for her goods with a promise to meet up in Scrivenshaft's in a few minutes. She wasn't yet up to the front of the line when a whirlwind of freckles blew in from behind a large display of fake crystal balls that showed a person's wildest dreams coming true.

"Rigel Black—"

"—as we live and sneeze!"

"The Weasley Twins—in the flesh!" she gasped, affecting a dramatic lurch, "I see the rumors of your early demise were wildly exaggerated."

She was surprised to see a serious grimace exchanged between the two before Fred said, "Not so exaggerated, if you ask some."

"What do you mean?" Rigel asked, shuffling over to make room for them in line, after smiling apologetically to the trio of young Gryffindors in line behind her.

"We're old news," George sighed, leaning his elbow against Rigel's shoulder despondently, "Dried up. Forced into early retirement and replaced by a brighter, younger model."

"But not prettier," Fred said solemnly.

"Right," George sighed, "Probably not prettier."

"You mean the Animators?" Rigel asked, not having to feign a sympathetic grimace. The suit of armor prank had been the talk of the school for at least a week. Somehow a rumor had been started that the group responsible for the prank was called Animators Anonymous, characterized by the trademark of animated objects used in pranks. No one knew whom Animators Anonymous consisted of exactly, but the current running theory supposed them to be a group of highly talented upperclassmen with some kind of agenda. Their two displays so far did seem a bit grandiose for mere pranks, Rigel had to admit.

"It's not that we can't appreciate talent when we see it," George said, rubbing an ear agitatedly, "But we aren't ready to hang up our hats just yet either, you see?"

"You've got something in the works, then?" Rigel asked, leaning in to keep her voice from being overheard.

"Might have," Fred smiled, eyes twinkling in a way Rigel knew from experience meant trouble. "You interested?"

"If you need the help," Rigel said, smiling back. "I know how difficult it can be to… execute in your advanced age."

"Just for that, you can be surprised," George said, laughing.

Rigel chuckled uncomfortably, "I was just joking, George. I'd love to help out."

"No, no, we wouldn't want your smart little motor-mouth to rust, hanging out with the geriatric folk like us," Fred cut in, smirking deviously, "In fact, we'll include something extra special just to keep you on your toes, Rigel."

"Oh, there's really no need," Rigel said, falsely ingratiating.

"Anything for our puppy, right Gred?" George simpered, a proprietary hand guiding her forward a step as the line moved.

"Anything but mercy, Forge," Fred said, his arm looping around George's on her other side.

Rigel just sighed, knowing she had walked right into whatever they had cooked up. Once she'd paid for her armful of gags, the twins waved her off with matching maniacal grins. She set out for Scrivenshaft's with a slight specter hanging over her head, resigned to spending the rest of the week looking over her shoulder. At least she could rest assured they hadn't planned anything for today…probably.

Although Rigel had been to Hogsmeade many times in her youth, she'd never actually eaten at the Three Broomsticks. It was the most commonly used flooing destination in the village, but she didn't know anyone who frequented the pub for its fare. Her dad and his Auror buddies met up at the Leaky Cauldron every now and then, and she knew from overhearing him talk about his work that seedy folk were known to congress at the Hog's Head. There were also a few music bars that she'd heard of (and been forbidden from setting foot in before she turned seventeen), but as far as she knew the Three Broomsticks wasn't an overly popular destination as far as pubs went. She supposed the largest bulk of the Three Broomsticks' business must come from Hogwarts students.

Not that such a business model was unsustainable, Rigel thought wryly as her friends tried to scout a table around lunchtime. It was a large establishment, and it was barely noon, but the main dining room was already brimming with students—even a few Hogwarts staff members.

Through the sea of black robes came a friendly voice.

"Oi! Silver snakes! Over here!" Adrian Pucey called out from a large table by one of the windows.

"He can't possibly be talking to us," Draco said, looking away in embarrassment.

"Oh he's definitely talking to you three," Millicent said, "Don't you know what people call you behind your backs?"

She started toward the table confidently, leaving Pansy, Draco, and Rigel to exchange looks of mild discomfort in her wake.

"I really thought such an uninspired moniker would have died off by now," Pansy said, her mouth in a moue.

"People are much too impressed with their own incredible lameness," Draco grumbled, "Silver snakes indeed."

Rigel shrugged, "At least it's alliterative."

Apparently her comment wasn't deemed worthy of dignifying, for her companions abandoned her on twin sighs without a backwards glance, leaving Rigel the last to arrive at the round, wooden table. Apart from Pucey and Millicent there were several upperclassmen Rigel recognized, including Rosier and Rookwood, as well as the sixth-years Lucian Bole and Peregrine Derrick. She claimed a seat between Pansy and a dark-haired girl she assumed was Pucey's date, judging by the way his arm was slung around the back of her chair.

Rigel thought the girl looked familiar, once she got a good look at her profile. It was Asian in set, and very pretty. She couldn't put her finger on it, however, until the girl turned to her and said, "It's been a while, Rigel—or is it Reggie?"

"Miss Chang," Rigel said, smiling to hide her embarrassment, "You look exceptionally well, today. It seems this past year has agreed with you."

"Careful, Rigel, that's my date," Pucey said, "I'll feel intimidated if you don't explain how you know each other now."

Dismissing the idea that a fifth year like Pucey could ever be intimidated by someone as unassuming as herself, Rigel simply shook her head. "We met in the Library in my first year. It's a credit to Miss Chang's memory that she was generous enough to remember me."

"How could I forget the boy who appeared in my mind to save me from the sleeping sickness?" Chang said, shaking her long hair back with the sort of effortless grace that Rigel had never managed when her own hair had been long.

"I'd forgotten," Pucey said, though his interested glance told Rigel he probably hadn't. "Rigel must know a great many people for similar reasons."

"Not so many," Rigel said sweetly, "Those two weeks blend together after so much time; I almost didn't recognize Miss Chang, even though we'd met outside of a mindscape as well."

"Under circumstances I am forbidden from explicating, if my memory is as good as you say," Chang's voice was even sweeter, and Rigel suppressed a wince as Pucey looked even more curious.

"That was so long ago," Rigel deflected, "How have you been lately, Miss Chang?"

"Just Cho is fine," the fourth-year Ravenclaw smiled, "We are old friends, after all. I've been well, though, as you noted earlier."

"Good," Rigel said, smiling lamely as she glanced around the table for a distraction. The last thing she needed was for someone to press for details surrounding her and Chang's acquaintance. It was embarrassing enough that the Raven knew Rigel had resorted to dressing up as a redheaded Gryffindor in order to gain Library privileges in her first year.

Her eyes met the golden irises of Aldon Rosier across the tabletop and Rigel wasn't sure if she should be relieved or more apprehensive. He smiled slowly at her and Rigel groaned internally. Much more apprehensive, then.

"Speaking of the sickness, you never did tell us how you cured it, Rigel," Rosier said, bringing the attention of the rest of the table to rest on her as well.

"Not much to tell," Rigel muttered into her butterbeer, "It wasn't even a real sickness."

"It was real enough to me," Chang said, shuddering, "I still get nightmares about that sludge invading my mind. You shouldn't downplay it, Rigel."

Rigel grimaced apologetically, but it was Rookwood who said, "Rigel is ever reluctant to tout his own accomplishments. Perhaps you would be so kind as to relieve our curiosity, Miss Chang? If the ordeal brings you no pain to speak of, of course."

"Rigel really never explained his methodology to any of you?" Chang seemed quite taken aback, "It was all we talked about in the Ravenclaw common room for weeks. By pooling together information from all the first and second years afflicted we were able to come to a fairly good understanding of the sickness and its cure." She smiled sheepishly, saying, "I suppose that's a Raven for you, though."

"Our first years were reluctant to recount their experiences," Bole said, looking said first-years over with veiled speculation. Derrick placed a hand on Bole's forearm in a subtle admonishment, and, to Rigel's surprise, after glancing at his fellow sixth-year, Bole reduced his gaze to a gentler curiosity.

"It's not anyone's business," Millicent said, crossing her arms and tilting her head in open challenge, "And Rigel obviously didn't want the attention he was getting. Encouraging gossip and speculation would have been beneath us, as his friends."

Draco nodded at Millicent's words and Pansy raised her chin proudly in agreement.

Rigel felt something warm blossom in her stomach at such a staunch defense. Theo and Blaise must have gone along with it as well, if none of the upperclassmen were any more well-informed about the sickness than they had been two years ago. She truly didn't deserve her friends' loyalty. When Draco glanced at her with a knowing smile tugging at his lips Rigel belatedly tamped down on the feeling as best she could. Having amazing friends was all well and good, of course, but there was no need for them to become smug about it.

"I didn't realize you wanted the cure kept quiet, Rigel," Chang said, apology in every syllable, "None of us would have talked about it if you'd asked—it's the least we owe you."

Now she felt like a churlish villain. "It's all right, Miss—Cho, I mean. I don't talk about it simply because it seems uninteresting to me. I wouldn't deprive the Ravens of satisfying their curiosity—I have learned my lesson on that count, at least."

As she'd intended, the reference to what Chang had told her about the enduring tenacity of a curious Ravenclaw drew a relieved laugh from the older girl.

"Then you no longer intend to deprive the rest of us, either?" Rosier asked smoothly.

Noting that the older Slytherin was rather like a dog with a bone on this subject, Rigel decided to give in as gracefully as she could while backed into a corner. There shouldn't be any harm in telling people now, anyway, over a year after the clamor about the sickness had died down. "What exactly do you wish to know, Rosier?"

He raised a reproving brow at her use of his last name, but still smiled crookedly. "Everything, of course," he said, "But let's start with the ability apparently unique to you that allowed you to, as Miss Chang put it, appear in her mind."

"I can enter people's magical cores," Rigel said bluntly, thinking a simple answer would be less interesting, "That gave me the access needed to bypass the sickness' primary defense. After that, the Mind Healers did the actual curing."

Rosier blinked slowly, "I'm not sure I've ever heard of such a thing. Edmund?"

Rookwood shook his head, "Nothing comes to mind. I'm no expert in the mental arts, however."

"It shouldn't be possible," Bole said, drumming fingers on the table in thought.

Chang leaned forward earnestly, "It's true. Rigel came into my mind through my magical core, and exited the same way. It's the same for all the afflicted students we interviewed. The Mind Healer used the mists to gain entry, we think, but Rigel did something different."

"It isn't possible to enter someone's mind at any point except the mists," Bole argued, sounding certain, "Such a thing would redefine Legilimency completely, undermining the defenses that every Occlumens uses almost without exception.

"I don't know what any of you are talking about," Millicent said flatly, "But Rigel wasn't using Legilimency. That's the point."

"That's incredible," Rosier said, "Is it a natural gift, like your Parseltongue?"

Rigel shook her head, "I don't think so. Maybe. It's not something everyone can do, but I can't just do it without thinking about it, like Parseltongue. It's not that kind of ability."

"It's still very dangerous," Rookwood said, his deep voice rumbling as he lowered it, "It makes sense that you wouldn't casually admit to such a thing."

"Why not?" Chang asked, tilting her head, "It saved us. It could be used in other ways, too, to help people. Rigel's gift should be celebrated, and explored, surely."

Pucey grimaced slightly, "No offense, Cho, but this is why you aren't a Slytherin. The good Rigel did with this ability isn't the point—the problem is the harm he could do."

Chang reared back, looking stung, "Rigel…wouldn't do anything bad with it. Would you?"

"Of course not," Pansy answered for her, sighing, "But the potential for harm will be more important than Rigel's assurances, to some. It's fine if it's just Hogwarts students who talk about it—most have seen the good things Rigel can do with his talents. If it became common knowledge that a dangerous, poorly understood new ability had manifested in a traditionally Dark family tree, though…can you understand why discretion is the wiser choice for Rigel?"

The dark-haired girl nodded slowly, "I didn't think…well, I suppose even though knowledge is inherently innocent, it can sometimes be used for less savory purposes than academic understanding. I won't speak of it so freely in the future, Rigel."

"It's really all right," Rigel said, concerned that her friends were making too much of this, "It's not as dangerous as it sounds. I can't enter a person's core without leaving myself completely vulnerable, mentally and physically. It requires deep meditation, and the transference of my conscious away from my mental defenses. So it's not as though I can just enter someone else's mind on a whim. Learning Legilimency would be more useful, honestly. I think its only purpose would be in Healing, as a matter of fact."

She told herself that its use in bypassing the magical binding Riddle jr. had placed on her was incidental, with circumstances unlikely to reoccur.

"If you think others will see it that way, you are an optimistic fool," Bole said, frowning.

Rigel shrugged, "It's been so long since the sickness, I didn't think others were even thinking about the incident, still."

"Unanswered questions have a way of hanging about," Rosier said, "But this conversation has been ever so demystifying. I find myself less interested in you already, Rigel."

He could not have sounded more insincere, but Rigel smiled gamely at the upperclassman in any case. "Thank you, Aldon."

"Why don't we speak of more entertaining things?" Pansy suggested, drawing the attention away from Rigel, finally. "Does anyone have plans for Samhain?"

"I plan to eat my weight in pumpkin pasties," Millicent said. Everyone chuckled, and the atmosphere around the table relaxed.

"We're having a pumpkin-carving contest in the Ravenclaw tower," Chang said, perking up, "My friend Marietta and I are going to enter our jack-o-lantern. We've been trying to charm it to cackle like a hag, but so far it only chuckles heartily like St. Nickolas."

"You know, I happen to be an expert in Charms," Pucey said, leaning into the girl's space and speaking directly beside her ear, "Maybe I could help you out sometime before Saturday."

"That would be cheating," Chang protested, though Rigel noticed she still smiled shyly at the table.

"Edmund and I have a wager on whether we'll see a prank that night," Rosier said, eyes alight with mischief, "I think the Animators won't miss a chance to give us another show, but Edmund believes the Weasley twins have been biding their time for an answering prank, and will seize on the holiday as an opportune moment."

"Any insider knowledge, Rigel?" Pansy asked, a playful smile in her cheeks, "You're an accessory to many of their pranks, if I'm not mistaken."

"I'm not at liberty to say," Rigel pretended to sniff, "A prank's real value lies in the element of surprise."

"In that case, I'm going to spend Saturday evening making sure Rigel doesn't get into trouble," Draco said, smirking, "He has abominable luck with Halloween for some reason, and there are certain kinds of surprises I've had quite enough of."

"Last year had nothing to do with me," she argued, feeling cold at the memory of that debris-scattered hallway and Neville's stiff, motionless form.

"Not for lack of your trying," Draco scowled, "This year if something happens I expect you to run away from the trouble, not toward it."

"I wish you hadn't said that," Rigel sighed, "Now Fate is going to make things difficult."

"Poor, star-crossed Rigel Black," Rosier drawled.

That would make a very accurate caption for her life, at times, Rigel thought sourly.

That afternoon, their group left the pub and ambled their way through the rest of the shops on their list. Her friends seemed to have forgotten the serious conversation they had over lunch, but Rigel was having trouble letting the implications fall to the back of her mind. She had thought speculation all but died out concerning the events of her first and even second year. The incidents that had faded to only background importance to Rigel's mind still seemed to merit concentrated interest in others', however. Should she be worried that she was still the object of many people's curiosity? It was natural to wonder, she supposed, and things probably seemed more fascinating to people who didn't understand all the underlying facts, but should she work harder at seeming inconspicuous? It couldn't hurt to try, surely. She didn't know what more she could do, though. Her day-to-day routine was about as boring as she could make it—for someone with a complicated double-life and a time-turner, that is.

On Wednesday morning, Rigel received a packet from Archie with several letters enclosed. She tucked it into her bag to go through later, guessing at least one of them was an order list from Krait. He was due to start transitioning some of his stock to winter-appropriate potions like Cold Cures and Warming Solutions.

When she took a moment after lunch to sift through the packet before time-turning back for her morning potions lesson with Snape, Rigel noticed that in addition to the letter from Krait, there was one from Leo as well, and a very thick envelope with Archie's handwriting on the outside. Inside that envelope was a letter from Archie himself, and a letter that seemed to have come from the Department of Mysteries. Suppressing a groan, Rigel ripped open Archie's letter quickly, wondering what the Ministry could possibly want from her now.

Hiya Cuz!

How's Hogwarts? I bet it's cold already. Just know that while you're bracing yourself for winter's worst up there, Hermione and I will be basking in Fall's gentle embrace for a few more months.

Thanks so much for the notes you sent me—with things so clearly explained, I understand a lot more about that potion I mentioned now. It's really gotten my Potions teacher off my back. Some people are just easily pleased I guess—not everyone, though. Remember that annoying request I got a little while ago? It seems my reply wasn't quite enough to appease them. What do you think I should do now? You know I value your input in these sorts of things—I just hate disappointing people.

I know Halloween is coming up, and all I'll say is be careful! Your luck is rotten this time of year, so try to do as many boring, harmless things as possible. No broomstick-riding or dragon-baiting for at least two weeks.

Everything is going swell, here. The amount of classwork we have this year is a little amazing. I'm afraid some of my extracurricular studies may not get my full attention until the winter holidays. I've still found time for a little side project though. You can't see it, but I'm winking at you very smugly. Just wait until you see what I've been working on—it's gonna completely change the way you see me. As in, I'll be so awesome you don't even recognize me.

Stay warm! And try to send more letters to your dad, will you? My parents mentioned he seemed kind of distracted, since we left for school.

With love,

Harry

Rigel tucked Archie's letter away with a frown and opened the letter from the Ministry next. To her relief, it wasn't anything threatening. The Department of Mysteries thanked her for the notes and samples she'd sent, and politely requested notes and samples on any similar potions she had been experimenting with. She wondered if they'd gotten wind of the Modified Weightless Draught Harry had given to Thompson during her internship. It was possible the Guild's Safety Division colluded with the Ministry at times. Or perhaps they wanted the counter-potion, she thought wryly.

To be on the safe side, she decided to send samples of the Modified Weightless Draught, the Shield-Disrupting Potion, the Hair-Changing potion she'd been working on with Archie, and the few other shaped-imbuing projects she'd started working on peripherally in between the internship's conclusion and her thirteenth birthday. She thought it was a bit rude to ask for a potioneer's notes and findings on projects that hadn't been vetted and published by the Guild, but for all she knew this sort of thing was common when dealing with experimental fields.

Judging from what Draco had said in Zonko's, Rigel was probably lucky no one had demanded she get licensed for the potions she experimented with over the summer. It probably helped that the only potions she'd been working on so far weren't dangerous. The Department of Mysteries could have the Modified Weightless Draught and the pranking potions if they really wanted them. Maybe when they saw how juvenile the rest of her work was, they'd stop pestering her and research the subject themselves.

Putting that letter aside as well, all the while mentally setting aside time-turned hours in the Come and Go room to compile her notes yet again and see about re-draining her magic so she could shape-imbue once more. It was going to be a longer week than usual, she thought with only a small amount of irony.

Leo's letter wasn't very long, but the tone was more restless than she was accustomed to receiving from the laidback alleyrat persona he generally adopted.

Harry,

How's school? I hope you're enjoying the warmer weather over there, because it's already turning bitter here in the alleys. Everyone at the Phoenix sends their regards, and my cousin in particular wishes me to tell you how dull she finds the crowd these days. I daresay your good manners have spoiled Rispah for our court's somewhat lackluster refinement. Marek challenged me again this week—I made him regret it this time, though, so he ought to lay low for a while if only to avoid the embarrassment of explaining why his eyebrows have been singed off. I know if you were here you'd have grown them back for him or some such soft-hearted nonsense, so it's probably best for my reputation that you remain so far away.

That's not the only reason I'm glad you're gone, though. We had a real scare the other night, and it wasn't some roughed-up alley dogs looking for trouble like last summer, either. The Ministry conducted a night raid all through the lower alleys—biggest raid we've seen in years, easily. My ears tipped us off ahead of time, naturally, so our people were all well prepared, but the Aurors hit Borgin and Burkes pretty bad. Krait won't tell you this, but his place almost got burned down in a bout of very sloppy crossfire when one of the local covens didn't take too kindly to an unscheduled Ministry intrusion. He's just fine, and his stock was barely singed, but the fact that the Ministry is desperate enough to provoke the Nightwalkers worries me. Whatever they were looking for must have been ugly, and something tells me they haven't found it yet. Wish I knew what it was, Harry. I'd hand it over just to save the alleys all the hassle.

Everybody's on edge, here, and even the folks over on Diagon and down Craftsman Alley are all riled up like a nest of hornets. With this cold weather coming in, it'll quiet down quick, but the winter brings all kind of other problems, of course.

Look at me, whining about my day to you like some tired old man. I just wrote to say I hope things are going well for you, whatever you're up to now.

Stay safe,

-Leo

Harry folded the letter ponderously, wondering at the serious nature of her friend's correspondence. Harry knew Leo's work in the alleys was complicated and often dangerous, but the older boy didn't usually talk about his troubles with her. He must be more overwhelmed than usual, she supposed. It certainly sounded as though things were getting out of hand. A raid on the entire Lower Alleys? The scope of such a thing would be incredible.

She wondered if her father had been involved. He was the Head of the Auror department, so it would make sense. She privately hoped he hadn't been responsible for the damage to Krait's shop, but she knew that her hopes were irrelevant. Part of having friends in the alleys meant that the people she cared about wouldn't always all be on the same side of certain situations. She consoled herself with the knowledge that at least it wasn't any different than what she was doing at Hogwarts, making friends both with prominent Dark scions and children of Light families, too. And she wasn't the only one straddling a dangerous line. Archie and Leo led double lives, too, and Bill Weasley come to that. At least she was in good company.

Speaking of good company, she thought sourly, I've stalled long enough.

She definitely hadn't been avoiding Professor Snape. Their interactions outside of classes were entirely civil, and the psych evaluation had gone nicely, she thought. There was just something about their interactions in class that had…changed in the weeks since his discovery and subsequent disapproval of her suppressor ring. It had taken several days for him to give up attempting to dissuade her from its use. Eventually he'd settled for tossing out sarcastic, biting comments whenever a particularly difficult potion gave her dampened magical core a strenuous workout, and even though she thought he would come to accept her right to make the decision she had in the end, she was getting tired of wondering when they'd settle back into the more casual mentorship relationship they'd had before things had gotten so out of sorts.

Steeling herself against the passive vitriol she knew would be coming her way momentarily, Rigel reached into her robes and pulled out the pretty golden chain. She wondered why all the adults she knew were so inclined to assume they knew best for everyone. Maybe if she used the time-turner often enough, that ever-vaulted maturity that supposedly came with age would help her understand. Judging by examples like James and Sirius, however, Rigel suspected that the problem with her lack of comprehension wasn't a difference in age but rather a completely antithetical system of beliefs and experiences.

Resigned to simply viewing the world differently than most people, Rigel turned the hourglass over in her hands, and blurred through space once more.

Halloween morning dawned quietly, but Rigel knew it wouldn't stay that way. Everyone was ecstatic about the upcoming feast, and since it was Saturday they had the whole day to enjoy the festivities. The castle was decorated lavishly, with cobwebs strung up artistically in nearly every available corner, suits of armor charmed to moan eerily if someone got too close, and even transfigured bats that swooped in droves out of nowhere every now and then to scare a group of students silly.

The Great Hall was only modestly decked out at breakfast, but everyone knew it would be a treat to see later that night when the elves got through with it. They ate lightly, anticipating a very heavy meal that evening, and absolutely no one felt like discussing schoolwork, so they laughed and joked and forgot about being students for a while. The mail came and went with little festivity, but long after the owls had left, just as the meal was winding down, a large origami flower fluttered in through the doors on a gentle breeze.

The flower twirled and danced above students' heads, and one by one people tapped their friends curiously on the shoulder, craning their necks to see where it was headed. It looped around the hall twice before making its lazy way toward the Slytherin table. When it began to spin in place above Rigel's head, she tried not to groan aloud. Whatever it was, it was sure to be troublesome.

The paper flower stopped spinning after a moment and softly floated down to land in her lap. Rigel glanced up to see the eyes of the entire Great Hall upon her, several hundred curious students and staff members, and she knew that she couldn't just pretend it had disappeared. She picked the origami construction up gingerly and opened it as the hall held its collective breath.

Inside, in standard dicto-quill writing, were just three words: Sorry In Advance. The words were followed by a pair of smiley faces, and Rigel didn't even have time to curse the Weasley twins' good names before people all over the hall were gasping and pointing in flurried commotion. She looked up and saw several dozen paper flowers fly in through the doors from the Entrance Hall, swirling through the air in a dizzying spectacle. More and more origami flowers floated into the room, filling up the space above their heads.

One by one the other flowers, too, seemed to find a certain recipient and come to a slow spin before stopping and gently falling into the chosen person's lap. Rigel looked around, and couldn't help but be amused at the excitement and confusion on the students' faces as everyone—actually every single person that Rigel could see—eventually received a paper flower.

Murmurs and bits of laughter broke out as students began unfolding their flowers and reading the inside. Rigel leaned over the table and asked, "What do they say?"

"What did yours say?" Millicent asked, looking bewilderedly down at her flower.

"Something ominous," Rigel grimaced, a little worried now.

"Well mine says, 'Your history of magic essays speak eloquently to the problems facing our society, even though everyone knows Binns doesn't even read them. For going beyond expectations, you deserve a…sticker.'" Millicent shook her head, "It's signed 'all the dead famous people' and there actually is a sticker taped in here that says 'excellent effort.'"

"What?" Rigel let out a little laugh in sheer disbelief, "I don't get it."

"Mine says, 'Thank you for re-alphabetizing the biographies section in the library when you noticed they were mixed up, love, Madam Pince,'" Blaise said, looking torn between confusion and unease.

"I don't think she wrote it," Theo said, his cheeks a little pink, "Mine says, ah, 'It takes a true gentleman to sit in Madam Puddifoot's for three hours and not stare at your date's cleavage even once. Our hats off to you—the gentleman's club. P.S. she's not the one.'"

"It can't possibly say that," Pansy said, her lips twitching, "A gentleman? You, Theo?"

"I can be," Theo muttered, looking very embarrassed, but also a bit pleased.

"What does yours say, Pans?" Draco asked, an odd expression on his face as he looked down at his flower.

Pansy glanced at Rigel with a quizzical expression, "Mine is from Rigel, supposedly." Rigel blinked at her friend in surprise. "Here, it says, 'your charm and generosity cast a light on all who meet you' and it's signed 'Rigel Black.' Did you write these, Rigel?"

Rigel shook her head slowly as her friends turned to look at her, "No, I didn't. I mean, I agree, Pan, but I'm afraid I didn't write these."

"So you didn't write mine, either, I take it?" Draco asked, still looking at his.

"No," Rigel said, "I had nothing to do with this prank."

"Why, what does yours say, Draco?" Blaise asked, a sly expression on his face.

Draco haughtily folded it up and placed it in his breast pocket, "Wouldn't you like to know."

"Did everyone get one of these?" Millicent asked, awe in her voice, "I mean, there's hundreds of students in Hogwarts, and the staff have got them, too."

"And how do they know these things?" Theo asked, coughing, "I mean, they're right about Padma, but I didn't talk to anyone about that date."

They were not the only ones who seemed perplexed. All around them students seemed to be debating the issue.

"It thanks me for telling off that third year for not washing his hands before leaving the bathroom, and it's signed 'the hygiene police,'" one prefect from the table next to them was saying, "But how could anyone possibly know that? And why would they thank me for something so ridiculous?"

"Mine says 'you're a ray of sunshine in the mornings even on double potions days—"

"Don't know how they heard about my extra credit assignment for McGonagall—"

"—must have been watching me practice if whoever wrote this saw the improvement in my barrel rolls—"

"—signed the 'kindness elves'—"

And on it went. Rigel couldn't help but be amazed at how much time and detail had gone into the scope of this prank. It had to have been the big one the Weasley Twins had been working on, especially as they made good on their promise to embarrass her by sending her flower in all alone ahead of the rest. She wondered why her flower had said 'sorry in advance' instead of just 'sorry,' though. She'd gotten it after being embarrassed, after all.

She might have continued to wonder, if a Ravenclaw girl with long, scraggly blonde hair and enormous eyes hadn't walked up beside their table and said, "You're Rigel Black, right?"

Rigel turned away from the table to say, "Yes, that's me. Have we met?"

"Not yet," the girl said, smiling vaguely, "I'm Luna. I just came to thank you for the flower."

"The…" Rigel looked down at the paper flower in the girl's hands. Surely they didn't.

"I'm not sure who told you about my search for the Crumple-Horned Snorkack, but your words of encouragement are very touching," the Ravenclaw girl smiled serenely once more, and left.

Rigel turned back to her friends with a sense of dread, "I didn't write that one, either."

"Do you think whoever did this signed your name to any more?" Pansy asked, tentatively.

Rigel didn't have to answer, as not a moment later a group of Hufflepuffs all came giggling to their table and thanked Rigel profusely for "such kind, insightful words" and asked her where she'd come up with "an idea so thoughtful and creative." No amount of protestations convinced them that Rigel wasn't the one responsible, and they left with lilting laughter at her helpless expression.

Nor were they the last. It seemed a very large number of flowers had come with her name attached to them, and for some reason, likely because Fred and George thought it would embarrass her more, it wasn't any of the funny or casual praise that her name appeared after. It was inevitably the most sincere, softhearted messages that were attributed to her, and all throughout the day random people she didn't know smiled at her in the hallways or gave her puzzled but friendly expressions from across a room.

It did not help that her friends were openly amused at her expense as the morning went on.

"It isn't funny," Rigel groaned after she once again failed to convince a pair of sixth-year Gryffindors that she knew nothing about their love lives, despite the apparently touching messages of encouragement they'd received in her name.

"It's pretty funny," Millicent said, leaning back on the blanket they were all sharing. It was chilly out on the grounds, but they all agreed they'd be missing the sun when winter really set in, so the six of them were bundled in scarves, watching some first-year Hufflepuffs trying to rake up a pile of leaves without getting too close to the Whomping Willow.

"The whole school thinks I'm some kind of misty-eyed do-gooder now," Rigel sighed, burying her face in her knees as yet another group of curious students stared at her while crossing the lawn.

"Just think of it this way," Theo grinned, "You could pull any guy or girl in the whole school right now. I heard they're calling you 'Romantic Rigel' already."

"Please tell me you made that up," Rigel closed her eyes against the mortified heat in her face.

"Do I strike you as the creative type, Rigel?" Theo asked.

"Everyone is going to think I'm a crazy stalker, too," she realized, already picturing the suspicious looks. How on earth had the Weasley twins managed to get information on the whole school, anyway? Didn't they have better things to do?

"No one thinks you're a stalker," Pansy said bracingly, "Most of the people smart enough to be wary of whoever knows so much about them are also smart enough to realize that you would be too smart to sign your name to the information if you were smart enough to obtain it in the first place."

"Oh yeah, that much is obvious," Theo said, laughing at Pansy as the blonde girl wriggled her nose in response to his teasing.

"It is," Pansy insisted, "So Rigel really only has to worry about all the people who aren't smart enough to figure that out. Those are the ones who think you're a great big pile of goo."

"Thanks, Pan," Rigel said, "I feel much better."

"It's not that bad," Draco said, smiling, "Remember when everyone thought you were setting Slytherin's monster on unsuspecting Hufflepuffs? That was worse."

"All attention is bad attention," Rigel grumbled, "Just when people were starting to forget about that mess, too."

"I really hate to break this news to you, Rigel," Blaise said, affecting a mournful expression, "But no one is even close to forgetting about that mess. You should embrace your celebrity status with grace. Use your fame and—well, just fame so far, as you haven't got a fortune yet—to raise awareness for good causes."

"And whatever you do, don't sleep with your manager," Theo drawled.

They all laughed, and Rigel supposed she could see the humor in it—but that didn't meant she was going to take this lying down. The Weasley twins were absolutely going to pay. The only questions were when, where, and how much they would squirm before Rigel was satisfied. It seemed she would be writing to Archie about more than shaped-imbuing this week. She needed his expertise to pull off something truly…appropriate. The punishment should fit the crime, after all.

Despite the eyes that followed her and the burning need to strangle a couple of redheads, Rigel was relatively relaxed as she entered the Great Hall later that night for the Halloween feast. She'd spent most of the day mortified and exasperated, it's true, but on the other hand, the worst was now over. Her annual Halloween bad luck had to have been used up on the prank and its aftermath, which meant for once she could enjoy the rest of the holiday in peace.

All right, maybe peace wasn't quite the word to describe the orgy of sugar consumption going on against a backdrop of cheesy horror that was the Halloween Feast, but she was determined to have fun, at least.

She was a little late getting there, as she'd stopped by to check on Remus beforehand, so her friends were probably already seated. She didn't think they'd begrudge her tardiness this year, though. It was the first night of the full moon, and even as Rigel, she couldn't quite quell Harry's need to make sure everything was in order with the Wolfsbane potion. She could tell he was bemused by 'Archie's' newfound interest in the subject, but she credited working with Professor Snape on the modifications last spring to explain it. All thoughts of her uncle faded from her mind, however, as she gazed at the revelry around her.

Thousands of candles hovered above their heads, and yet each was no brighter than a flickering will-o-the-wisp. The semi-darkness added to the excitement and mystery of the event, and everywhere along the house tables various dishes and goblets glowed orange, green, and yellow. The ghosts were enjoying themselves this year, as well; the laughter and chatter were interspersed with the occasional shout of fright as one of those silvery forms suddenly burst up through a table or swooped down from above.

Before sitting down with her friends, however, she made a beeline for the Gryffindor table.

"So there I was, between a river and a very scratchy place, when—Rigel!" Fred laughed nervously as she oh-so-casually dropped into a seat beside him, "What brings you to our humble table tonight? Finally figured out the pumpkin pasties are sweeter over here?"

"They can't be as sweet as that lovely flower I received this morning," Rigel said, "If only I knew who to thank."

"All right, nothing to see here, people," George said loudly, jumping up from his own place next to Fred and taking Rigel's elbow with an insistent flourish. "Let's have a chat, then, eh?"

He and Fred together towed her toward one of the many arched windows that stood in a long row along one side of the hall. When they were sufficiently away from prying ears, Rigel took back her arms and folded them in open displeasure. "Do you know how many people think I'm a sappy, naïve twit right now?" she asked.

"No one thinks that," Fred waved her words aside with an air of supreme unconcern.

"Everyone loved the flowers, Rigel," George added, smiling winningly.

"That's not the point," Rigel said, eyes narrow, "They're associating the flowers with me, which means every time they talk about the prank, they're talking about me. You know I hate attention—"

"We did apologize for it," George cut in.

"In advance, even," Fred nodded sagely.

Rigel huffed out a laugh against her will, "Some advanced notice. Wasn't sending me the first flower bad enough? Why link me to all those notes?"

"Not all of them," George rolled his eyes, "Only the really nice ones. It's a good thing if people think you're nice, Rigel."

"We are your PR team, after all," Fred added, grinning, "You've already won them over with your mysterious healing abilities and your daring monster-slaying nerve. That's Ravenclaw and Gryffindor taken care of already! This is about getting Hufflepuff to your side. Now, you've got the whole school in your corner!"

"Except all the Slytherins wondering how I got so much personal information on them," Rigel groaned.

"Which was not easy, by the way," George sighed.

"Besides…um…" Fred scratched his head, "House loyalty?"

"Slytherins," Rigel said.

"Right. Well, we'll win them back with our next prank, then," Fred said brightly, "It'll have to be something really sneaky."

"No more tying me to pranks!" Rigel tried to sound firm, "I'm not running for president of the school."

"Although you would certainly bring a lot of charisma to the job," George said, voice thoughtful.

"Why not take credit for it yourselves?" Rigel sighed, "You put all that effort into it, even getting all the flowers to somehow go to the right people—"

"Modified the spell Ministry officials use to send inter-departmental memos," Fred said.

"Dad was ever so nervous about teaching it to us," George recalled.

"Can't imagine why," Fred shrugged.

"—and all that time spent digging up dirt on people—"

"Not dirt!"

"More like daisies, really."

"—so why put my name on it?" Rigel finished, exasperated.

Fred and George exchanged a long look.

"You're right, it was a lot of work," George said, inspecting his fingernails, "We had to eavesdrop on all the biggest gossipmongers, break into a few teachers' student files, go undercover in various common rooms, follow, ask about, and basically investigate every single person in this entire school. But it was worth it! Did you see people's faces today? No one can believe the amount of work that must have gone into this—everyone is impressed, whether they appreciate pranks or not. Even Percy looked vaguely approving today."

"It's so much better than animating a bunch of fruit, anyway," Fred said, sniffing.

"But it's not us, Rigel," George said, his voice softer now, "No one takes the Weasley twins seriously. If we'd signed our names, the messages would have been treated as a joke—as something insincere, when they weren't. Somewhere in the midst of this prank we actually got to know the entire school, and the notes were supposed to be heartfelt."

"Which no one would believe, coming from us, but which people might believe coming from the notoriously serious and soft-spoken Rigel Black," Fred said.

"People are going to figure out I didn't do it pretty soon," Rigel said, frowning.

"But the prank will still be associated with you, like you said," George pointed out. "The name Rigel Black in turn will be associated with kind words, thoughtful notes, etc, don't you see how it's a win-win?"

"It's a lie," Rigel said, still troubled. She didn't want to be known for anything, as Rigel Black.

"Lies aren't always bad," Fred said.

She found that she couldn't argue with that without being a complete hypocrite, so she simply shook her head, "Well, I guess you win this time. You really got me good," she added with a wry smile.

"No less than you deserve," George said, smiling once more, "Calling us old men like that—the nerve."

At Rigel's disbelieving look, Fred said, "Well, okay, we were going to use your name all along, but after Zonko's we didn't feel as bad about it."

Rigel chuckled softly, "Fair enough. I'll let you get back to the feast, now. Sorry for getting my back up about all this. I ought to know better how to be a good sport, with my family."

"All's forgiven," George said, slinging an arm around her shoulders.

"So this means we've got the green light on the next one, too?" Fred asked, adding his arm on top of George's.

Rigel ducked out and turned to favor them with a droll look, "Sometimes our friendship worries me."

She left to the sound of twin laughs and wove her way back to the Slytherin table to join her friends. From the flickering of the lanterns on the tables, it looked like she'd get a seat just in time to hear Dumbledore's Halloween speech.

"So was it the Weasley twins who wrote those things, Rigel?" Millicent asked as she sat down, apparently having seen her talking to them.

"I asked them, but they denied it," Rigel sighed for good measure, "Who knows?"

"I heard Professor McGonagall's said 'you look hot with your hair down' and was signed 'the bedroom fairy,'" Theo said, waggling his eyebrows.

"That can't possibly be true," Draco scoffed, "McGonagall would still be livid if someone sent her a note like that this morning."

They all turned to look up at the Head Table, noting that Professor McGonagall was looking much too fond of the children beneath her gaze to have been the recipient of such a message. Rigel found her eyes drifting over to Professor Snape, who was seated in between Flitwick and an empty chair that was probably meant for Pettigrew, since he appeared to be the only Professor not yet present. She wondered if Snape had gotten a flower that morning, too, or if the Weasley twins had simply been too sane to attempt to give him one. Rigel closed her eyes for a moment to pray to any gods who might be listening that Samhain that if Snape had received a flower it wasn't one of the ones with her name on it.

When she opened her eyes once more, the Headmaster was standing before them, smiling genially.

"Welcome, everyone, to this year's Halloween Feast!" he said, gesturing to the hall with both hands, "Let's have a cheer for our magnificent house elves, who have put their hearts into the decorations once again."

There was a loud round of approval from the students, although Rigel noticed that most seemed to be applauding the house elves ironically, rather than in any true spirit of gratitude. She made a mental note to visit the kitchens tomorrow and tell Binny what a nice job they'd done.

Dumbledore waved his hands, and said, "Yes, yes, marvelous. This month's jack-o-lantern carving competition was judged this afternoon by our Head Girl, Miss Clearwater, and I hope everyone finds the time to stop by the Library before the weekend is out to see the first prize and runners up on display. Thank you to all who participated, and congratulations to Mr. Oliver Wood, whose Quidditch-inspired design has won him twenty galleons, and ten points extra credit towards his Transfiguration mark."

There was another short round of applause, but before it had a chance to die down, the air was split with a horrible, deafening screech. Students everywhere hunched over in pain as what sounded like a thousand screaming banshees rent the hall, echoing and filling their heads with white-hot vibrations.

The sound cut off all of a sudden, and Rigel looked up, still slightly stunned, to see Dumbledore brandishing his wand as something like a silvery bubble expanded to encompass the entire hall.

"Students, remain where you are," the Headmaster called over the confused and frightened yelling, "Filius, Severus, with me."

The old wizard, flanked by his Masters of Potions and Charms, strode quickly out of the Great Hall. As the three of them exited the periphery of the silver bubble of magic Dumbledore had cast, they all three cast what Rigel assumed was muffling charms on their ears.

"What could make such a noise?" someone wondered allowed.

"Merfolk," Pansy said quietly. Rigel turned and caught her friend's worried expression, "There would have to be hundreds of them above water-level to make such a sound, though. What could they possibly want?"

"Something desperately," Blaise said, frowning, "It hurts their voices to speak above ground, so if they're clamoring for something so loudly, it's got to be important."

"THE GIANT SQUID'S GONE MAD!"

Everyone spun to look at the small boy who was standing at one of the windows and waving his arms wildly, "IT'S ATTACKING!"

"What in Merlin's name—" Draco got no further as students all around them erupted into panicked screams. The prefects attempted to restore order and McGonagall was shouting something from the Head Table, but everywhere Rigel turned there was mass confusion. Students got up and ran to the windows to see what was happening, Theo and Millicent among them, and before Rigel could figure out what was going on, Draco collapsed sideways into her, his head in his hands.

"Shit," was all Rigel could think to say as her friend shook uncontrollably against her side. She wrapped one stabilizing arm around Draco and used the other to dig her ever-present bag from under the table and thrust it into Pansy's lap, as hers was currently half-occupied with an armful of slumping Draco.

"What's wrong with him?" Pansy demanded, her fear etching grooves of worry beneath her cheekbones

"Later," Rigel said, already rummaging for her potions kit, "Hold the bag open for me."

Pansy did so without further questions, angling it toward the light of the nearest glow-lamp so Rigel could find what she was looking for. A few moments later, a Calming Draught and a Suppressant Potion she'd taken to carrying around just in case found their way to her fingers and she thrust them at Pansy wordlessly. The blonde girl mechanically uncorked them and, with Rigel's help, they forced the potions down Draco's throat in quick succession.

It took almost half a minute, but soon Draco's eyes were fluttering back open and he was gasping for breath against Rigel's shoulder.

"Can you hear me?" Rigel asked, feeling a bit useless as she rubbed his back the way Lily used to rub hers when she had a stomachache.

Draco nodded, then winced, rubbing his forehead, "Thanks."

"Draco, are you all right?" Pansy asked, her soft tone belied by the sharp concern in her eyes.

"I'll be fine, as soon as we get out of here," Draco said, grimacing as he pulled away from Rigel and sat up, "What's going on?"

"We aren't sure yet," Rigel said, trying to make sense of what everyone was shouting around them.

Blaise appeared out of the mass of hysterical students just then, sliding onto the bench next to Pansy and speaking quickly, "Dumbledore's gone down to the lake with Snape and Flitwick. The Giant Squid looks like it's trying to climb out of the water for some reason, and the merfolk seem to be arguing with the Headmaster over something. No one really knows what's going on, but the Professors look like they've got the squid under control, for now."

"That's good," Pansy said, visibly regaining her composure, "I'm certain this will be resolved in short order. When Professor Dumbledore makes his way back here to release us, we can—"

She was cut off by a cry of, "THE CENTAURS HAVE REVOLTED TOO!"

"That's it!" Draco growled amidst renewed shrieks and shouts, "We're going to get over there and see what's going on."

"Good luck," Blaise scoffed, "I barely got back here."

"Rigel, Pansy, V-formation shields on my count," Draco snapped, pushing someone aside so he had room to stand and snapping his wrist to deposit his wand into his hand.

Rigel and Pansy nodded, standing as well with minor difficulty. Rigel shouldered her book bag, just so it wouldn't get lost in the confusion, and palmed her wand as well. With Draco in the point position, they all three cast simultaneous physical shields, with Rigel's and Pansy's angled 45 degrees to either side of Draco's, creating the 'V' the formation was named for. Draco had taught it to them in their dueling lessons the previous week, and Rigel supposed they'd see if it was useful in a crowd.

The three of them, standing tightly together, began slowly pushing their way through the crowd. They had to be careful not to walk too quickly, as the shields would be doing all of the 'pushing' and they didn't want to hurt anyone, so it took a couple of minutes to displace enough people to carve a path for themselves to the windows, but eventually they reached their goal.

Looking out the window over the moonlit lawn, Rigel almost wished they hadn't.

The Black Lake was in turmoil. Water churned and frothed as a myriad of tentacles swarmed out of the depths and attempted to climb the shore. She could see Professor Snape and Professor Flitwick clearly by the light of their wands as they worked in tandem, sending spell after spell at the giant squid in an effort to contain it. Rigel couldn't imagine why the squid would be trying to get out of the lake, unless there was some sort of danger within. Was that why the merfolk had abandoned their submerged city and come to congregate on the surface as well? She could see Dumbledore shouting at a merman whose pearlescent crown glinted in the moonlight. The merman appeared to be shouting back, along with dozens of other merpeople, who were brandishing their tridents and pointing long, webbed fingers toward the castle.

"Maybe something dangerous has gotten into the lake," Pansy said, squinting through the window between Draco and Rigel.

"That doesn't explain what the centaurs are doing," Draco said, shaking his head.

Rigel turned toward the forest, where a massive heard of the proud four-legged beings swarmed along the edges, clearly agitated. They didn't seem nearly as distressed as the merfolk, but there was something certainly sinister in the way they moved, slowly but steadily, along the tree line toward the castle.

"Where is Peter?" she could hear McGonagall's voice cutting through the panic and looked over to see the older witch standing not far from Rigel and her friends, "Where is our Magical Creatures expert?"

Rigel thought that was a very good question, and sighed at the dramatic irony of Fate when she heard Professor Trelawney's distinctive voice say breathlessly, "He has not emerged from his chambers all day, Minerva. I shall go and seek him out!" She scurried away toward the Entrance Hall, looking quite pleased for an excuse to get away from the commotion.

Professor Sprout squeezed by Draco to reach McGonagall, panting, "Poppy is working in the dungeons tonight, Minerva. She'll need to be notified in case Severus or Filius require medical attention when this is through."

"Go help her ready the infirmary," McGonagall said briskly, "First find Professor Binns and request that he inform the Fat Lady of the trouble and tell her to stay in her frame in case we need to evacuate the students."

The Hufflepuff Head of House bustled off with a curt nod, and Rigel couldn't help but wonder at the Deputy Headmistress' forethought. How many such emergencies had she dealt with, exactly? Thinking back over the last two years, Rigel allowed that it had probably been quite a few.

Rigel turned back to watch the merpeople, some of whom were now struggling to get closer to shore, but seemed to be having trouble moving past the writhing tentacles that had once again escaped the professors' control.

"Dumbledore seems confused about what the merfolk want," Pansy noted, "It's not as though they can all actually get out of the lake, after all, so you'd think the Headmaster would be doing something about whatever's bothering them."

"Maybe they don't know what the problem is, either," Draco said, "The odds of the centaurs and the merpeople both becoming agitated at the same time…what are they doing now?"

He was referring to the centaurs, who, without any apparent reason, suddenly split their ranks into two, those in the center galloping toward the edges while those on the fringes of the herd dove quickly out of the way. Then, through the wide path that had emerged in less than a few seconds, came a swarm of stampeding giant spiders headed straight up the lawn toward the castle.

"What the—" Draco broke off with a quiet grunt as the boy next to him panicked, pushing his way backwards from the window violently.

The spiders were advancing quickly—faster than Rigel had seen anything that big ever move. She supposed eight legs gave quite an advantage in speed.

"They're coming this way!" People were screaming all around them.

"Barricade the front doors!" she heard McGonagall shout, her voice magnified over several times. Rigel saw Professor Sinistra, Professor Burbage, and Madam Hooch rushing out of the Great Hall to help bar the Entrance Hall doors, but as she turned back toward the rushing spiders, she had a sinking feeling they weren't going to head for the traditional entryway. They looked too mindless, too rabid.

"The windows," Rigel muttered, seeing those multi-jointed legs and easily picturing them scaling stone walls. She looked around the hall frantically, but to her dismay she could not see a single staff member nearby. McGonagall must have run to assist the others with the entrance doors.

"What?" Draco asked, distracted.

"The windows," Rigel said, more forcefully this time, realizing someone needed to take over command inside the hall, "They're going to climb the walls."

The students around her who'd heard all surged backwards away from the glass with varying degrees of horror. Only Pansy and Draco stayed composed.

"What do we do?" Pansy asked, gripping her wand tightly.

"Barricade them, same as the doors," Rigel said quickly, "Let's use the tables."

"EVERBODY AWAY FROM THE WINDOWS!" Draco bellowed in a way Rigel had never imagined him doing, but it was certainly effective. All along the wall students scurried backwards. "EVERYONE PUSH THIS TABLE UP AGAINST THE WINDOWS! NOW!" he shouted, motioning for those around the closest table running parallel to the windows to help him push it.

"It's too heavy," Rigel said, seeing the way even a dozen students' straining muscles barely convinced the heavy tables to slide a few feet toward the windows. "Clear everyone out of the way."

Draco and Pansy cast shield charms and carefully expanded them to press all the students packed between the table and the wall toward the ends of the hall and out of the way, even pushing some over the top of the table to the other side, shouting, "MOVE IT! NOW!"

While they worked, Rigel closed her eyes and tapped into her core with urgency. It stirred willingly enough, or at least the part of it she had access to with the suppressor on did. She briefly considered taking the ring off, but then realized any spell she tried with her magic beyond her control would probably blow up in her face.

"Rigel!" Pansy called, drawing her back from her moment of doubt. The space between the long house table and the wall of windows was vacated. It was now or never.

She let the flow of magic consume her, sweeping out from her wand to encompass the entirety of the enormous table in an overpowered levitating charm, and asked, called for her magic's help with this task. As she wove the magic, a window on the left side of the hall burst inwards, glass tinkling to the ground as a long, hairy leg hooked itself through the frame. Amid the screams, Rigel let her magic pulse forward, catapulting the table in one swift movement forward over her own head, turning it mid-leap so that its sturdy wooden top flattened itself against the windows with a deafening crash. Food flew everywhere, covering the floor and her head. She ignored it, pinning the table in place with sheer willpower, checking to see that it was long enough to cover all the windows along the hall. It was, but it wasn't quite wide enough, she realized with a grimace. About a foot of space was left between the upright edge of the table and the top of the arching windowpanes.

Window after window cracked and rained glass inwards as a multitude of legs grasped for purchase on the outer wall of the castle. Rigel was starting to sweat with the strain of the magic she wielded, but in the background of her concentration she could hear prefects attempting some form of order now that students were more concerned for their own personal safety than for satisfying their curiosity.

"Younger students toward the back of the hall!" she could hear Percy Weasley shouting. "Those who know 'Evanesco,' get rid of this glass!"

A stunner flew over Rigel's head and impacted one of the furry legs feeling its way around the small opening above the table. The leg curled back immediately, but as other students began similarly stunning the legs they could get a good shot at, Rigel heard a bellowing cry shout, "No! Don't hurt 'em!" from behind her.

Hagrid, she realized, and hoped for his sake that the spiders weren't being seriously injured as they dropped off the castle walls to the lawn. She doubted the stunners would keep the spiders down for long, in any case—Acromantula were notoriously spell-resistant. Rigel had other things to worry about, however, as her arm was beginning to shake with the amount of magic running through it to keep the table in place. She could feel her core's available magic beginning to dip below comfortable levels.

"I need help," she called over her shoulder, "Can anyone do a really strong levitating spell? Or a sticking charm?"

Twin voices called out from the crowd loud and clear, "We can do it!"

Rigel glanced behind her, careful not to disrupt the magic keeping the table up, and was more than a little shocked to see two small Slytherin boys break away from the chaos. They rolled up their sleeves and came to either side of her. "We'll make the table take some of the weight," one of them said. His twin nodded seriously, and they both held their bare hands out toward the table.

Rigel wondered what on earth they were going to do without wands. A few moments later, however, she could feel the toll that the table had been taking on her magic lesson, then lighten to an easily sustainable level. She looked over to see the young twins rigid with focus. One of them spared her a grin, though, and said, "What, like it's hard?"

"You're the Animators," Rigel said quietly, her lips tilting up in a smile as it clicked, "And you're both actual animators, aren't you?" Animation was quite a rare gift, as she understood it, and unusual to have manifested before their cores had finished developing. They must be either incredibly talented or naturally powerful. Rigel was lucky to have such effective help with the barricade, though she wondered if animation became more difficult the larger the object to be animated or if it took more skill than endurance. She would have to ask when this was all over.

"Mums the word," the one on her left said cheekily, as though he knew what she was thinking, "Literally, though—we get it from our mum's side."

They both laughed before focusing completely on the table once more.

Rigel was beginning to wonder what had happened to all of the professors when McGonagall came tearing up beside them with her wand out, "Can you hold it, Mr. Black? The Entrance Hall is being pummeled, and we can't spare the staff until it's completely warded. Just our luck the warding expert is outside with Albus," she added in a growl Rigel didn't think she was meant to hear.

"We've got it for now, Professor," Rigel said, panting just a little.

She nodded sharply, then turned to survey the crowd, "Argus! Argus where are—oh!"

Filch appeared a moment later, a shaking kitten in his arms that Rigel had heard he'd taken to calling 'Miss Norrie' in remembrance of his old familiar. "Yes, ma'am," he said, standing at attention.

"All prefects are to prepare their houses for evacuation. The upper levels may not be secure if these spiders climb any higher, so Gryffindor will go with Hufflepuff to the basement common room—no, don't argue! This is no time for house secrecy. The Ravenclaws will bunker in the Slytherin dungeon, as well. Send the Gryffindors and Hufflepuffs first, with the Head Boy, then the other two houses with the Head Girl."

"What about the noise?" Filch scowled, "Not enough staff to stick 'em all with deafening charms quick enough, unless you can do what the Headmaster done in here."

Another window pane crashed inward and McGonagall swore colorfully, "You're right, there isn't time. Too much exposure to the sound will damage their eardrums. And Poppy is still in the Hospital Wing…" More cursing. Rigel saw the twin to her right fighting a grin as he, like her, eavesdropped shamelessly. "All right. Here's what we do," McGonagall decided, "When the barricade is finished in the Entrance Hall, we'll—"

She broke off as a hysterical Professor Trelawney rocketed out of the crowd and collapsed in the Deputy Headmistress' arms.

"Sybill, what on earth are you doing?" McGonagall demanded, "Where is Professor Pettigrew?"

"Couldn't—not—trapped—" Trelawney broke off with a huge gasp of air and then slumped dramatically, "It's the werewolf, Minerva—he's loose."

"What!?" McGonagall lowered her voice to a near-hiss.

"The beast has trapped Pettigrew in his rooms, pacing outside the door and howling, Minerva. I barely escaped with my life. If only I'd had time to do a second tea reading this morning, I might have been able to prevent—"

"Yes, yes," McGonagall thrust the woman away from her impatiently. "That's all we need. If Remus has lost his mind to the wolf, then moving students in the hallways is out of the question, even in the lower levels. There's no way to track him quickly enough if he moves."

"Can't you send Hagrid to put him down or—"

At Trelawney's words, Rigel's focus slipped completely in blind panic. Put Remus down? They couldn't—

The table slipped two inches toward the floor as both boys beside her gave out surprised grunts. She struggled to get the magic back under control, but she was too numb with fear and helplessness at the mere thought of what might happen to Remus. A rogue werewolf was completely fair game, as far as the Ministry was concerned. He could be murdered, and it wouldn't even be considered a crime. And if he hurt someone defending himself, then his life would be forfeit anyway by default.

The table was vibrating now. "Hey," one of the twins glared at her, "Settle it down, Black!"

"Mr. Black!" McGonagall brandished her wand at the table and it stopped shaking immediately, pinned by fresher, stronger magic than what Rigel had been working. The two younger Slytherins slumped and stretched their arms out with relief.

"I'll take it from here, boys," McGonagall said, her mouth thin, "Thirty points to Slytherin. Now move toward the back of the hall, where it's safer."

The other two scurried off toward where the rest of the students were congregating, as far from the windows as possible, but Rigel stayed put. "You can't hurt Remus, Professor. I know he took his potion tonight—I watched him!"

"In case you haven't noticed, Mr. Black, the creatures of this school have gone feral tonight, regardless of their previous sanity, apparently," McGonagall snapped, stress in every line of her face. At Rigel's despairing look, she softened minutely, "I'll do my best to see he isn't harmed, Mr. Black."

Rigel nodded slowly, but in her mind she wondered how McGonagall could see to Remus' safety, when she was worried over the safety of all the students at the same time.

"Argus, when the barricade is finished I will send a patronus to Poppy telling them to ward off the Hospital Wing and remain there until further notice. They'll be safe enough," she said, half to herself, "If the students are to remain in here, however, we need to take more proactive measures. When the others are done at the front doors, we will set up a protective barrier around one half of the Great Hall. Keep the students behind it, then create a small opening and send Hooch and Sinistra out on brooms to attack from the air. By then Albus should have been able to do something about those thrice-cursed seamen…"

Rigel didn't think she needed to hear whatever McGonagall had planned after that. She had her own plan to execute.

Filch and Trelawney began herding all the remaining students into close quarters toward the back of the hall, opposite the doors to the Entrance Hall, clustered around the Head Table. Rigel saw a pair of pale-headed students bobbing toward her through the crowd, and slipped as casually as she could out of their line of sight. Draco and Pansy were not going to approve of what she did next.

She hunkered down behind the staff table, pulling out the Marauder's Map and searching frantically for Remus. Her uncle's dot was moving erratically back and forth outside of a door in the staff quarters, beyond which sat a dot labeled Peter Pettigrew. Rigel traced a shortcut with her finger that could take her from the first floor to that part of the castle in just a few minutes. All she had to do was slip through the door behind the Head Table and into the trophy room it connected to without anyone seeing her.

She worked her way surreptitiously through the crowd, and had just reached the small enclave containing the door when a large hand grasped her elbow and spun her around.

It was Rookwood, and he had a very forbidding expression on his face. "Your friends are looking for you," he said, voice tinged with disapproval, "Now would be a bad time to run off."

"I have to go, Rookwood," Rigel said, tugging on her elbow, "Remus is in trouble. He needs help."

"How can you help a werewolf?" Rookwood said lowly, "It's not safe."

"I have to protect him from himself," Rigel said fiercely, "If anyone else comes across him, they'll kill him, or he'll kill them, but I can help him. Let me go."

Rookwood looked torn, but his hand didn't release her.

"He's family, Rookwood," Rigel said, as imploring as she could, "What if it was Rosier? Or Selwyn? You'd do the same."

"At least let me accompany you," Rookwood bit out, obviously displeased with his capitulation.

"No, you need to stay here," Rigel said. At the upperclassman's warning growl she held up her other hand, "Pansy and Draco will try to follow me if they find out I'm gone. You have to be here to keep them from coming after me."

"You once again take risks that you yourself forbid others from taking," Rookwood said, shaking his head.

"Yes. I do," Rigel said. It was the truth, after all. She didn't have time to analyze it, however, "Keep Pansy safe, Rookwood."

He let her go with a sigh, "Keep yourself safe, Rigel."

Rigel nodded her thanks, then slipped through the door quickly, and left the older Slytherin behind.

Horrid, awful wailing greeted her ears as she left the protective barrier of Dumbledore's magic. Swearing silently to herself, she palmed her wand and called on her magic to deafen her ears as she ran through the gold-bedecked room. She rummaged in her bag as she ran, pulling out her ever-present invisibility cloak from its undetectably expanded pocket, then paused to carefully retrieve two bottles from her potions kit. One she uncorked and winced at before pouring all over the outside of her cloak. It was peppermint oil, undiluted, and while it was one of the strongest-smelling things in her kit, she also thought it would be one of the most disinteresting, at least as far as a werewolf's nose was concerned.

The other bottle she shoved in her pocket, along with a packet sealed tight with preservation charms that had an apothecary's logo stamped across the front. Barely remembering to vanish the food that had settled in her hair, she threw the cloak over herself, took out the Map once more, and followed it toward Remus' restless dot with steely determination.

When she reached the parallel corridor, she slowed, then crept forward, keeping to the shadows as she rounded the corner and caught sight of the wolf at the other end. It prowled back and forth before the door, snapping its jaws and scratching at the wood with a desperate fervor. This behavior was coupled with frequent flinches and shakes of the head. If Rigel weren't deaf, she suspected she'd hear the werewolf whining and yelping, so obvious was its pain.

Rigel pulled the bottle from her pocket and uncorked it quietly, silently praying that her research lived up to her expectations. Otherwise she would likely be wolf food before the hour was out.

Shying away from that mental image, she began to carefully pour the protection potion in as wide a circle as she could manage within the walls of the corridor. She held the bottle as close to the ground as possible so as to minimize the sound the liquid created as it hit the floor. She cast the circle clockwise, holding her breath as she walked closer to Remus and only relaxing minutely when she made it back to where she'd begun. She left a small opening between the start of the circle and the end, just big enough to keep the magic from connecting.

Her hand shaking slightly, she balanced what was left of the protection potion in her pocket while taking out the packet quietly. As she ripped the seal, she could see the werewolf's ears twitch in her direction, but after a brief glance, the creature turned back to the doorway it was stalking. She pulled one perfectly preserved bullfrog from its wrappings and set it down in the center of the circle before backing away swiftly.

The wolf bared its teeth in a challenge as it whirled, obviously having heard something that time, though how with all the merpeople's racket going on she didn't know. It hunched its forelegs menacingly. Rigel, from within the relative safety of the cloak, jerked her wand at the frog, making it flop wildly into the air and back down to the floor with a wet smack. The werewolf charged. She grabbed for the rest of the potion and waited breathlessly until its loping run carried the werewolf soaring past the potion line. She completed the circle just as the beast closed its jaw on the now-limp bullfrog, watching with acute relief as the barrier shone into place around the werewolf with seamless grace.

The wolf flung itself at the barrier, only to be pushed backwards into the center with gentle finality. Grinning, she removed her cloak and stuffed it out of sight as she quickly skirted around the protected circle and stopped, breathing deeply, in front of Pettigrew's door. There was a moment in which she could not tear herself away from the glowing eyes of the wolf, which shone with such hate and hunger as she had never imagined coming from a living thing. Then it passed, and she remembered her purpose, and threw her fists against the door violently.

"Professor! It's safe to come out! Hurry, Professor, they need you in the Great Hall!" she hollered and banged and scrabbled at the knob, but to her frustration received no response. She checked the map frantically, but he was definitely still inside. Perhaps the door was soundproofed? Or maybe the professor had been rendered unconscious by prolonged exposure to the merpeople's screaming.

In either case, she would have to open it herself. She could feel her magic running dangerously low, but all she needed was enough to overpower whatever locking charm Pettigrew used. She prodded at her core once again, feeling it stretch in a way that had become familiar to her after exhausting her magic so often in Professor Snape's lessons. With whatever juice she had left, she willed the door in front of her to open.

The wooden door flung itself inwards and slammed into the stone wall of the room beyond with a crash she could feel vibrating in the floor as she rushed inside. Whatever she was expecting, it wasn't for Professor Pettigrew to be sitting in a meditative pose on the floor, eyes closed in concentration and hands clenched tightly in his lap. She didn't have to say anything—the moment the door opened he jerked into awareness, grabbing his ears in a cowering flinch and causing whatever he had been holding to drop onto the floor and roll away under a chair.

He gazed around wildly, his beady eyes bulging as he took in her standing there. He began fumbling to stand, gesturing wildly and shouting something angrily.

"I can't hear you!" Rigel shouted, realized that even with that the professor likely wouldn't hear her over the merfolk. She gestured to her ears with a confused expression for emphasis, but received and even more confused look in response. "I deafened myself because of the…shrieking…" She stopped shouting and faltered at the impatient and uncomprehending look in his eyes. He wasn't holding his ears any longer, she realized, and he didn't appear to be in any pain, despite not having cast any muffling spell that she had seen.

Cautiously, she allowed the magic around her ears to dissolve away and smiled when she heard nothing but a bit of static that was probably a residual effect of the temporary deafness. "It's gone," she breathed out a relieved sigh.

"What is?" Pettigrew demanded, "What in Merlin's name are you doing, young man, barging into my rooms like—"

"There's an emergency, Professor!" Rigel cut him off, remembering the urgency of the situation once more. "The creatures on the grounds have gone mad. There are spiders attacking and the centaurs are amassing and—well, they need you in the Great Hall right away."

Pettigrew paled dramatically, staggering backwards a step and patting himself down frantically.

"Your wand is on the floor," Rigel said, gesturing to where he must have laid it while meditating.

"Wand…yes…" Pettigrew seemed incredibly out of sorts, but Rigel didn't think they had time for him to collect himself properly.

"Come on, Professor, you need to get to the Great Hall," she said insistently, picking up his wand, shoving it into his hand, and leading him as politely as she could out the door.

When he caught sight of the werewolf lying just up the hall, Pettigrew squeaked and dug his heels in with a lurch. "What is—Remus isn't suppose to be—"

"He's not going to hurt you," Rigel said, steering the plump professor around the protected circle firmly, "I'm taking him to the Hospital Wing so don't worry about Remus, just get going."

"I—you—it's not safe…" Pettigrew trailed off.

Rigel wasn't sure if he was talking about Remus or the walk back to the Great Hall, but she smiled reassuringly and prodded the professor gently in any case. "I'll be fine, just go."

Pettigrew whimpered a bit pitifully, but then bit his lip and nodded, "Yes, I'll…I'd better go." He hurried off at a shaky run, and Rigel turned back to the werewolf.

She circled the creature slowly, looking for any sign of sanity. It already looked calmer, and she wondered if it had been the merpeople's screeching that drove it so insane. If the pain was awful to a human, she couldn't imagine what it would be like for a werewolf's sensitive ears. It was the reason she thought he ought to go to the Hospital Wing, instead of staying in the corridor all night. She knew from Archie's books that eardrums were extremely delicate, and an injury there could easily become permanent and debilitating if not treated in a timely manner.

"Remus, are you in there?" Rigel asked, kneeling down outside of the barrier to look the werewolf in the eyes, "Can you understand me, now?"

The wolf looked at her, calm and steady, but made no motion of understanding or even acknowledgement. After a moment of doubt, Rigel rolled her eyes. If his eardrums had been damaged by prolonged exposure to mermish wailing he probably couldn't hear anything she said.

Rigel got down on all fours and looked at the wolf very seriously. She then tucked her body to the side and executed a clumsy roll along the floor. She got back up and looked at the wolf expectantly. It cocked its head at her. She rolled again, then gestured at the werewolf insistently. The creature lolled its tongue at her, then rolled gracefully inside the circle.

Either Remus had his mind back, or Rigel was the first person in history to teach a werewolf to do a trick. Weighing the odds in her head, she smiled and dug in her satchel for the bottle of ward-disrupter potion that would render the protection potion inert. Pouring it across one of the lines, she broke through the ward to wrap Remus in a tight hug. He was shaking and clearly exhausted, but he licked her cheek affectionately in response.

Rigel stood and, with Remus at her side, set out at a light jog for the Hospital Wing. She didn't know whether the rest of the castle was safe or not yet, so she figured she'd just take shelter behind the wards there as well until things died down.

The doors were sealed tight, so Rigel kicked on the wards in a parody of a knock until a voice on the other side called, "Minerva? Is that you?"

"It's Rigel Black, Professor!" she called back, "I've got a patient for you!"

"Mr. Black!" that voice was definitely Madam Pomfrey, "What on earth did they send you up here for?"

The wards parted and the nurse's stern visage poked through the open door. As the sight of Remus, however, she reared back with a gasp, "Mr. Black, get away from—"

"He's fine, Madam Pomfrey!" Rigel assured her quickly, "He's in his right mind, just hurt from all that noise before."

Concern for Remus quickly replaced any worry the woman harbored for Rigel's safety, and she waved them both in with a brisk arm before closing up the wards once more and shutting the door behind them.

Remus trotted rather calmly over to one of the beds and leapt up on it before anyone could direct him. Clucking to her self, Madam Pomfrey began running a scan over his head. Professor Sprout pulled Rigel aside while this was going on and said, "What's happening out there, Mr. Black?"

"The merfolk have stopped screeching," Rigel said, assuming that the Hospital Wing would be warded against noises as a matter of patient comfort and guessing they wouldn't have noticed the change. "The spiders from the forest were scaling the walls when I was last in the Great Hall, but Professor Pettigrew is on his way there now, so perhaps he can help them deal with that. I think the Headmaster and Professors Snape and Flitwick were still outside at the lake last I saw them. They've boarded up the Great Hall and the entryway, though, so I'm not sure anyone knows what's happening outside the castle yet."

"The students?" Sprout pressed, her faced lined with anxiety.

"All safe last I knew," Rigel said, "McGonagall seemed to have their protection well in hand."

"Thank you, Mr. Black," Sprout sighed, flexing her fingers agitatedly, "I just hate waiting here while my house is in trouble."

"Remus isn't a danger anymore," Rigel said, "You could make your way to the Great Hall, if you were careful."

The stout woman smiled, but shook her head, "Minerva has posted me here, so I'll remain until the all clear. Running about on my own without anyone knowing where I'd gone would just making the situation more chaotic."

Rigel tried not to wince, but had to wonder if Sprout had guessed she wasn't supposed to be 'escorting' Remus to the Hospital Wing, as it were. "At least send a patronus so Professor McGonagall knows Remus is here, and safe," she suggested, "I think his presence in the hallways was deterring her from evacuating the students underground."

Professor Sprout stepped away to do just that, and Rigel went back to Remus's bedside to watch as Pomfrey finished healing his ears.

"I'll have to do another diagnostic when he's transformed back," she said as Rigel took a seat beside her uncle, "But he should recover full use of his hearing once I'm finished."

"Good," Rigel said, finally allowing her body to relax. She ached everywhere from the strain she'd put on her magic, and as the adrenaline drained away she felt empty and stretched, like a sponge that had been wrung out too many times.

"You did well, Rigel," Pomfrey said, looking away from Remus briefly to give her an approving smile, "Other times I would scold you for what I suspect is another of your impulsive inclinations toward irresponsibility, but in this case…it's a good thing you got him here when you did. I don't like to think how debilitating this kind of injury might have been if it had gone unchecked even another few hours. The eardrums are troublesome enough, but the nerves that pass information to his auditory cortex are even more fragile than a human's. The overload put such a strain on his temporal lobe. Much longer and it might have resulted in permanent damage to that section of the brain. So, good job, Mr. Black." She fixed Rigel with a stern look, "But don't do it again."

Rigel ducked her head in a nod that was part acknowledgement, part avoidance. If she had to do it again, she absolutely would, in this case.

Some time later, Rigel was dozing, curled up in a chair by Remus' bed, where the werewolf was sleeping peacefully in the semi-darkness created by the curtain drawn around them. Rigel lifted her head when she heard a knocking against the Hospital Wing wards. McGonagall's voice came clearly through the curtain a moment later.

"All's well, Pomona," the Deputy Headmistress sounded tired, but satisfied, "Albus is repairing the damage done to the outside of the castle as we speak."

"What happened?" Madam Pomfrey asked, "What caused all this?"

"We don't yet know," McGonagall said, "The official story is that the ambient magic around the castle interacted with the wild magic of Samhain tonight and created a dark energy that upset the creatures around the castle, causing them to react strongly against the castle itself."

"That sounds a bit far-fetched," Pomona sighed, "Think the Daily Prophet will swallow it?"

"I do, as a matter of fact," McGonagall sounded as though she wished to roll her eyes, "I'm more concerned about some of the more perceptive students. They witnessed the ferocity of this incident, and aren't like to believe it was a simple accidental intermingling of strong magics that upset the creatures. The spiders, perhaps, even the merfolk, but the centaurs? They are intelligent beings, not prone to panic, and yet their chief claims there is a dark force within the castle that is agitating Fate itself. What are we to make of such a statement? There could be any number of old artifacts hidden around the school, but none of them have caused this sort of upset in the past. Why now?"

"There, there, Minerva," Pomona said consolingly, "Albus will sort it out. In the meantime we ought to focus on moving the school past this. I'm sure we'll have our hands full with night terrors and panicky parents before the weekend is out. How long do you think it'll be before Lucius Malfoy pays us a little visit?" This last was added with a distinctive bite.

"Not long enough," McGonagall sighed. "Well, I just came to inform you of the resolution and check on Remus. How is he? Did he regain his mind with the rest of the creatures?"

"We don't know," Pomona said, "What happened at the end? How did Albus get them to regain control?"

"It wasn't Albus," McGonagall said, "One moment the squid was thrashing, the spiders were climbing, and all hell was reigning, and then…they stopped."

"Just like that?" Pomfrey sounded skeptical.

"Yes," McGonagall said, "I've never seen the like. The spiders seemed to shake themselves, then they retreated into the forest, calm as anything. The squid settled right down, and the merfolk stopped screeching all at once, disappearing back into the depths. Albus tried to talk to the Mer-King, but he was no clearer than the centaurs, apparently."

"Well, what of Peter?" Pomona asked, "Does our resident expert have any explanation for this phenomenon?"

McGonagall scoffed quietly, "He came running in a few minutes after it was all over, mumbling something about Samhain and the full moon and tumultuous energies. I'd accuse him of hiding out the storm in his chambers, but I gather he was detained by Remus' presence in the hallway outside his room. Thank the gods no one was hurt in this mess."

"All students are accounted for, then?" Pomona asked, sounding relieved.

"All but one," McGonagall said, now with an annoyed edge to her voice, "In your patronus you intimated Rigel Black was here. For his sake I sincerely hope he has remained so."

Rigel figured that was her cue. She stood from the chair and stepped out from behind the curtain. "I'm here, Professor."

"Would you like to explain yourself, Mr. Black, or shall I guess?" McGonagall's eyes were tired, but very sharp.

"I saw that you had your hands full in the Great Hall, so I thought I'd better take care of Remus myself," Rigel said. At McGonagall's darkening look, she said quickly, "It's not that I don't think you could handle him. Just that…he's family, and other people might not be as gentle with a rogue werewolf. I couldn't let anything happen to him or anyone else because of whatever was making the creatures go crazy."

"It is not your responsibility to go running after werewolves, Mr. Black, even if they are your uncles," McGonagall snapped.

"In times of difficulty, anyone with the ability to effect positive change also has the responsibility to do so," Rigel said, tilting her head, "Godric Gryffindor said that. I had the ability to help Remus, and the opportunity, so I did. I didn't hurt myself or anyone else. And Madam Pomfrey said it was a good thing that I did. Remus was injured when I found him, and might not have gone to the Hospital Wing without prompting. With all due respect, Professor, I'd do it again."

McGonagall pursed her lips, but Professor Sprout burst into chuckles. "Ever thought you'd hear a Slytherin quoting Godric Gryffindor at you to get out of trouble, Minerva?"

The older matron suddenly smiled, making Rigel extremely nervous. "You're right, Mr. Black. It would be an affront to my house to do anything but give you twenty points to Slytherin for bravery and selfless nerve." Rigel smiled hesitantly, then gulped when McGonagall continued, "While I may not punish students for having courage in a crisis, however, you can bet that Severus Snape will see your little adventure in an entirely different light."

Rigel grimaced, realizing she would be lucky to break even on house points by the time Snape got through with her. He had a very poor opinion of her 'reckless stupidity' and all actions and inclinations thusly associated. "I should get back to my common room, then," she said, moving back to Remus' bedside to collect her bag, "Is it safe to return?"

"The students should all be heading to bed now, yes," McGonagall said, "And Mr. Black?"

Rigel turned at the door with a polite expression, "Yes, Professor?"

"Good luck."

Wondering how a woman of her age had time for a sense of humor after such an exhausting evening, Rigel pasted on her fakest smile and left the Wing. She passed a multitude of students heading toward their common rooms on her way back to hers. None of them took much notice of her, and Rigel though wryly that if one good thing came from all this, at least no one was talking about the prank anymore. And she had thought her bad luck used up that morning. Ha.

She reached the common room just as the last Slytherins were filing in, and she barely made it three steps toward the dorms when a now-familiar hand gripped her elbow and re-directed her. "This is becoming a habit," she told Rookwood as he led her across the room.

"The habit is yours," Rookwood said, "They aren't happy with you."

"I know," Rigel sighed.

"I advise you to sound contrite," Rookwood said.

"I'm not," Rigel frowned, though some part of her wondered if she should be.

"Pretend," Rookwood suggested, "Or it's going to be a long night."

Rigel nodded, "Fair enough. They're okay though, right?"

"See for yourself," the upperclassman said, releasing her when they reached the group of chairs and couches by their usual fire.

Pansy was the first to react, rising from the couch and bringing Rigel into a gentle hug.

"Hi, Pansy," Rigel said, "I'll glad you're all right."

Pansy released Rigel and gave her a steady look, then turned and reclaimed her seat without speaking. Rigel turned awkwardly to Draco, who took Pansy's hand when she sat back down, and didn't acknowledge Rigel's presence at all.

"Draco," Rigel said. No reaction. She turned to Theo and Millicent, who were frowning, but didn't seem quite as angry. Blaise showed no signs of upset, even smiling at her when she met his gaze, but Rosier leveled her with a glare. For some reason, this response surprised her more than the others. What did Rosier have to be so angry at her about?

"You seem to be in one piece," Rosier said, raking her with his eyes, "Wasn't the werewolf hungry tonight?"

"Don't talk about him like that," Rigel snapped, forgetting that she was supposed to be contrite. It was exactly the sort of careless thing people said all the time about werewolves, and it enraged her to hear it, bringing back the fear and anger she'd felt when Trelawney had casually suggested killing Remus to protect everyone else.

"Like what? Like a rampaging beast?" Rosier stood from his seat and towered over her. He kept his voice low, in minute deference to her sensibilities, she supposed, but his words belied the kindness, "That's what he was tonight, Rigel. Not your uncle, not your friend. Dangerous. If you can't tell the difference between man and wolf then you need a serious reality check. When Edmund told me where he'd let you run off to I wanted to strangle him, but after thinking about it I realized it's not Edmunds fault. It's yours, Rigel. You chose to place yourself in danger, knowingly abandoning your friends and allies to run off after an incredibly deadly magical creature without so much as a thought about how the rest of us would feel if you got eaten by a bloodthirsty beast—"

"Are you finished yet?" Rigel said, more coldly than she'd meant to. She just couldn't stomach Rosier's words at the moment.

"I am not—"

"I think you must be, because you're starting to repeat yourself," Rigel said, her face as blank as a wall, "Or didn't you notice you'd called my uncle, your Defense professor and one of the nicest, most intelligent men I've ever known, a beast, Rosier?"

"He may be all of those things most of the time, but tonight he was dangerous," Rosier said, gritting his teeth, "Edmund, what class is a werewolf?"

"It's a 5-X creature by classification," Rookwood said promptly.

"Why is that, Edmund?" Rosier asked.

"It rivals the Nundu for speed, the Manticore for strength, and the Lethifold in its appetite for human flesh," Rookwood said, unflinching.

"I know that," Rigel said, glaring at the two of them, "You think I'm some excitable first-year who's read about werewolves in books and thought, gee, wouldn't it be swell to get a real good look at one up close? I know what werewolves are. Better than you two, I daresay. I've also known Remus my whole life, so I know that if he isn't in his right mind it's because something is wrong, and he's in trouble, and when my family is in trouble I help them."

"You can't run off every time someone you know is in trouble," Rosier said, running a hand through his hair in frustration, "All it does is put you in trouble along with them."

"Better than doing nothing," Rigel argued, "And besides, I had a plan to help Remus; I didn't go tearing off in a panic without any way to actually help. I don't fling myself into situations I can't handle, contrary to popular belief. I'm careful. I wasn't in any danger tonight, Rosier. I took every precaution."

"Like what?" Rosier bit out, eyes narrow.

"I turned myself invisible. I doused myself with peppermint oil, too," she said, "He couldn't see or smell me."

"Is that why you smell like a candy-cane?" Blaise asked, chin propped against the armrest of his chair in casual indolence.

"Yes," Rigel sighed, realizing that some of the oil must have seeped through the cloak, "And Remus couldn't hear me, either, because the merfolk's screaming had already ruptured his eardrums. He had also taken the New Wolfsbane potion tonight, which means he was significantly weaker than a true rogue werewolf would have been. When I found him, he was hurt and confused and not dangerous to anyone." That was a bit of a stretch, but Rigel wasn't above lying to protect her loved ones.

She could see the hesitation in Rosier's gaze, so she pressed forward, her eyes imploring him to understand, "My cousin invented a potion this summer that can safely contain a werewolf. I have several vials of it. I didn't rush off without a plan, Rosier."

"I don't like it when you do dangerous things, Rigel," he finally said, blowing out a defeated breath, "None of us do."

"I don't like it when people I care about are in danger, either," Rigel said, smiling a bit, "If you could have stopped me going, or had some way of contributing something to help, you would have come after me, wouldn't you?"

"Yes," Rosier said, grimacing.

"Then you already know why I couldn't have stayed in that hall and done nothing," Rigel said. Rosier gave her one long-suffering look, then shook his head despairingly. He wrapped her in an unceremonious hug, which Rigel returned after only a moment's confusion. "Thanks, Aldon," she said, "I'm sorry I worried you."

"You aren't either," he sighed, stepping back.

Rigel stepped forward, standing in front of the couch that Pansy and Draco sat on. "Do either of you have anything to say to me?"

Draco glanced at her. "Would you listen, if we did?"

Her gaze softened without her impetus, "Of course. You're my best friends."

"You use that word, Rigel, but you don't live up to the equal relationship it implies," Pansy said, still not looking directly at Rigel.

"You mean when I do things on my own without consulting you?" Rigel clarified.

"It's not your independence that's the issue," Draco shook his head. "The fact that you told Rookwood, in advance of your leaving, to stop us from coming after you, implies something important. Do you know what?"

"Tell me," Rigel said, frowning.

"It means you didn't just not tell us what you were doing," Pansy said, "You knew us well enough that you anticipated what our actions would be when we found out, and then took that choice away from us by telling Rookwood to stun us to keep us from coming to your aid."

"I didn't tell him to—"

"You know that's how he deals with people he doesn't know how to deal with, though," Rosier pointed out, smiling now, "Remember the New Years Gala?"

She did, at that, though she didn't appreciate him bringing that up in front of so many curious ears.

"The point is this: If you have the right to protect Remus from danger, then we have the right to protect you from danger, Rigel. You telling us we can't help you is just the same as us telling you that you can't help other people." Pansy was looking directly at her now, "Don't you see that?"

Rigel thought for a moment. "Except you would have stopped me from helping Remus," Rigel said, "You would prioritize my protection over his, whereas I prioritize his over mine. We can't agree on a course of action when we want different things. In such a case, aren't I justified in seeking my own goals by circumventing yours? Why should I prioritize your ends over my own?"

"Because we're friends?" Draco suggested, more than a bit sarcastically.

"Because," Pansy said, giving Draco a disapproving look, "We exist outside of models in your mind, Rigel. You assumed that we would be a detriment to your goals, instead of entertaining the possibility that we could be an asset to you. By treating us as an automatic hindrance, you insult us as well as our friendship with you."

"I don't think you're hindrances," Rigel said, knowing she was explaining it wrong but unable to make the right words come out, "I only wanted to protect you and Remus."

"You only get to protect people who consent to be protected," Draco said, rolling his eyes, "If you try to force someone into a position of weakness, it's just demeaning. Insulting. Patronizing. Take your pick."

Rigel rather thought some people might just see it as someone caring about them, but she also had to admit she saw her friends' point. "I hear you, and I understand where you're coming from, but can't you also understand how completely wretched I would feel if anything happened to either of you because of something I felt I had to do? Risking a certain amount of danger to myself is my choice, but bringing you guys into danger by default because of an obligation of friendship—I couldn't justify that. It would be the height of selfishness and carelessness if I did. What would I say to your parents if anything happened? I promised to be a good friend to you. That means not making your association with me hazardous to your lives. If I did what you asked, invited you into trouble with me…how can I live with that kind of guilt? What kind of person would that make me?"

"A normal one," Theo said bluntly, "No offense, Rigel, but Draco and Pansy are right on this one. Yeah, it feels awful when your friends get hurt or into trouble because of something you did, but that feeling is part of what is supposed to deter you from being reckless. You're the kind of person who doesn't see consequences to yourself as a bad thing, so it's exactly right of Draco and Pansy to try and make you see the weight of your actions by involving themselves. If it's something you wouldn't want Draco and Pansy doing, it's something you shouldn't be doing, right? Unless you think you're better than or different from them."

There was a beat of complete silence as the group stared at Theo with varying levels of surprise.

"What?" the sandy-haired boy scowled, "I can be deep."

Rigel had to laugh at that, a low chuckle that brought her back from desperate hypotheticals and to a more even-keeled focus. "Okay, I guess I'm wrong about at least some of this," she said, rubbing her hair a bit sheepishly, then grimacing at the oil that stuck to her hands, "If I say the situation wasn't dangerous, I should have been willing to at least give you the chance of offering your help."

"Yes, you should," Pansy said.

"I'm sorry I took your choice away like an imperious prat," she added, willing to let the matter rest, at that point.

"And you're sorry you forgot the conversation we've already had about how our friendship means that your problems are our problems and your responsibilities are our responsibilities and vice versa," Draco said, folding his arms as he looked up at her.

Rigel winced, "And I'm sorry for that, too." She really would have to remember these things before she got herself into messes like this in the future. "When I'm in crisis mode, I react to things very quickly and coldly. I forget about people's feelings. I'll work on that, all right?"

"And we will work on not losing you in crowds right as crises are occurring," Pansy sighed.

"You should put a teacher-tracker in one of his shoes," Millicent said helpfully.

"Go ahead," Rigel sighed, "But can we be done fighting? I'm exhausted and I smell like a breath mint. I just want to shower and sleep."

"Rest up," Rosier said, smirking, "You'll need your strength in the morning when Professor Snape has his words with you. The only reason he's not here waiting for you is because he has, and I quote, 'more important things to do than waste my breath lecturing a deaf imbecile…for now' end quote."

She feared Rosier was, if anything, understating the good professor's ire. Their relationship knew only the veneer of amiability of late. Her acting in a way he would undoubtedly categorize as reckless and foolhardy would only worsen his disappointment. It saddened her that recently she had somehow become used to upsetting and disappointing people, when for so many years she had worked hard to please them. She wanted to repair the rift in her relationship with Professor Snape, but at the same time…harsh words would still be nothing in comparison with Remus' safety.

She couldn't call herself a hero in her own mind, though. Rigel hadn't been completely honest with her friends. She'd made it sound like the only reason she was worried about Remus was because he was family, and that did indeed play the major role in inspiring her to act. She couldn't deny that there was a cold, ruthless part of her that saw Remus' importance in terms of the greater whole, however. An incident in which Remus was injured or injured anther could prove disastrous for werewolves everywhere. All eyes were on Hogwarts right now in the arena of creature rights.

A werewolf incident at Hogwarts meant other things, too. A blow to Dumbledore's credibility, for instance, and therefore to the platforms he put forth and all the causes he championed in their world, muggleborn and halfblood rights included. Innocent people everywhere would have their lives impacted by such a thing. She couldn't deny that all of these things and more had also been going through her mind as she raced to stop Remus from breaking down Pettigrew's door. She thanked magic for Professor Snape's New Wolfsbane potion. It was probably the only reason the werewolf hadn't been able to shred through that barrier like tissue paper.

One of her last thoughts before going to bed that night, once she washed herself thoroughly and made a mental note to ask Binny if she knew a good way to get oil out of invisibility cloaks, was that she'd really have to do a trial with a full-strength werewolf before she marketed her potion for such protective uses. Still, she thought with a yawn, it had certainly been a preliminary success, all things considered.

The whole day had been a tentative success, in fact. She'd have to phrase it that way, at least, when she wrote to tell Archie what had happened. She certainly did have a lot of people worrying about her, for someone who had started out at eleven with the intention to remain completely unnoticed. Perhaps it was time to accept, as so many people kept saying, that anonymity was simply beyond her grasp.

For now, anyway.